<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-15T01:22:18.711Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dragon and Knight]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:627fedf0a121b024e468bca9</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/dragon-knight-intro"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T17:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For better or worse, however, not everyone processes conflict and 
competition the same way. This is where things get interesting (and 
potentially dangerous).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.67]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9102</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/05/14/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-67/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T10:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of oledump.py brings support for user defined properties and an update to plugin plugin_msg_summary.py Office documents with VSTO applications have user defined properties. These properties can be extracted with my plugin plugin_medata.py, but not with the current version of olefile.However, the development version of olefile can be used to extract these properties. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting RBCD Using a Normal User Account*]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2022/05/exploiting-rbcd-using-normal-user.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2022/05/exploiting-rbcd-using-normal-user.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T02:29:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Caveats apply.
Resource Based Constrained Delegate (RBCD) privilege escalation, described by Elad Shamir in the "Wagging the Dog" blog post is a devious way of exploiting Kerberos to elevate privileged on a local  Windows machine. All it requires is write access to local computer's domain account to modify the msDS-AllowedToActOnBehalfOfOtherIdentity LDAP attribute to add another account's SID. You can then use that account with the Services For User (S4U) protocols to get a Kerberos service ticket for the local machine as any user on the domain including local administrators. From there you can create a new service or whatever else you need to do.
The key is how you write to the LDAP server under the local computer's domain account. There's been various approaches usually abusing authen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyranid's Lair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IIS Failed Request Tracing]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565592</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/iis-failed-request-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Failed Request Tracing is the most important IIS feature for diagnosing and troubleshooting any problem. It helps you determine what is exactly going on with your requests and why, provided you could reproduce the problem after enabling the failed request tracing feature.
IIS Failed Request Tracing first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunting evasive vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>hunting-evasive-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/hunting-evasive-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you ever wonder about the vulnerabilities you've missed? Why didn't they show themselves - and will they be discovered by somebody else later? Certain vulnerabilities have a knack for evading audit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO approved as APT Response Service Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=11293</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/05/13/nviso-approved-as-apt-response-service-provider/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T10:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO is proud to announce that it has successfully qualified as an APT Response service provider and is now recommended on the website of the German Federal Office for Information Security (BSI).   Advanced Persistent Threats (APT) are typically described as attack campaigns in which highly skilled, often state-sponsored, intruders orchestrate targeted, long-term attacks. Due to their … Continue reading NVISO approved as APT Response Service Provider →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Tischer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.22]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9111</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/05/13/update-zipdump-py-version-0-0-22/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T06:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is just a bugfix version. zipdump_v0_0_22.zip (http)MD5: 68F9F3809E4E1F9ADE4A4C3835CDF475SHA256: 92ED372579001C826D5AF31615B8334CC798FF2DA4AF8B7C46267BF7D995C757]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove or block Chrome extensions with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565679</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/remove-or-block-chrome-extensions-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comment on the previous post about deploying Chrome extensions posed the question of whether PowerShell could be used to remove Chrome extensions.
Remove or block Chrome extensions with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SecureAuth Welcomes Apple, Google, and Microsoft’s Commitment to Passwordless by FIDO Alliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=42783</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/secureauth-welcomes-apple-google-and-microsofts-commitment-to-passwordless-by-fido-alliance/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, Apple, Google, and Microsoft announced plans to expand support for a common passwordless sign-in standard created by the FIDO Alliance and the World Wide Web Consortium. We are excited about this announcement and applaud the players involved. It will accelerate momentum towards eliminating passwords entirely in the future. And to be a […]
The post SecureAuth Welcomes Apple, Google, and Microsoft’s Commitment to Passwordless by FIDO Alliance   appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Neurodiversity Summit 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-neurodiversity-summit-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-neurodiversity-summit-2022?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Neurodiversity in Cybersecurity Summit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D-Link DIR-1260 GetDeviceSettings Pre-Auth Command Injection Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=1984</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2022/05/11/d-link-dir-1260-getdevicesettings-pre-auth-command-injection-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=d-link-dir-1260-getdevicesettings-pre-auth-command-injection-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-3b20d7b3 A command injection vulnerability exists within the web management interface of the D-Link DIR-1260 Wi-Fi router that allows for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the device with root privileges. The flaw specifically exists within the SetDest/Dest/Target arguments to the GetDeviceSettings form. The management interface is accessible over HTTP and HTTPS on the local ... Read more D-Link DIR-1260 GetDeviceSettings Pre-Auth Command Injection Vulnerability
The post D-Link DIR-1260 GetDeviceSettings Pre-Auth Command Injection Vulnerability appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting Things in Context | Timelining Threat Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=66799</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/putting-things-in-context-timelining-threat-campaigns/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visualizing data is integral to threat research. See how we used this timeline analysis tool to track activity in the Ukrainian cyber conflict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure AD certificate-based user authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565708</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/azure-ad-certificate-based-user-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T13:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certificate-based authentication is an extremely robust and secure mechanism for validating a user's identity. However, until recently, you had to deploy Active Directory Federation Services (AD FS) to make it available for Azure AD. Microsoft has recently introduced an Azure AD certificate-based authentication service (Azure CBA), which significantly simplifies implementing certificate-based authentication.
Azure AD certificate-based user authentication first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earn $200K by fuzzing for a weekend: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://secret.club/2022/05/11/fuzzing-solana-2.html</id>
        <link href="https://secret.club/2022/05/11/fuzzing-solana-2.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Below are the writeups for two vulnerabilities I discovered in Solana rBPF, a self-described “Rust virtual machine and JIT compiler for eBPF programs”. These vulnerabilities were responsibly disclosed according to Solana’s Security Policy and I have permission from the engineers and from the Solana Head of Business Development to publish these vulnerabilities as shown below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>secret club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earn $200K by fuzzing for a weekend: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://secret.club/2022/05/11/fuzzing-solana.html</id>
        <link href="https://secret.club/2022/05/11/fuzzing-solana.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By applying well-known fuzzing techniques to a popular target, I found several bugs that in total yielded over $200K in bounties. In this article I will demonstrate how powerful fuzzing can be when applied to software which has not yet faced sufficient testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>secret club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Instance Metadata Services (IMDS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-instance-metadata-services-imds-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-instance-metadata-services-imds-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A misunderstood but deeply important feature to lock down when deploying workloads in cloud. Learn about Cloud Instance Metadata Services (IMDS) in this blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release of Technical Report into the AMD Security Processor]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/05/release-of-technical-report-into-amd.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/05/release-of-technical-report-into-amd.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ol{margin:0;padding:0}table td,table th{padding:0}.RmvCPDuePa-c3{padding-top:0pt;padding-bottom:0pt;line-height:1.5;orphans:2;widows:2;text-align:left;height:11pt}.RmvCPDuePa-c0{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:11pt;font-family:"Arial";font-style:normal}.RmvCPDuePa-c7{padding-top:0pt;padding-bottom:0pt;line-height:1.5;orphans:2;widows:2;text-align:left}.RmvCPDuePa-c2{padding-top:0pt;padding-bottom:0pt;line-height:1.0;text-align:left}.RmvCPDuePa-c6{text-decoration-skip-ink:none;-webkit-text-decoration-skip:none;color:#1155cc;text-decoration:underline}.RmvCPDuePa-c4{background-color:#ffffff;max-width:468pt;padding:72pt 72pt 72pt 72pt}.RmvCPDuePa-c1{color:inherit;text-decoration:inherit}.RmvCPDuePa-c5{border:1px solid black;margin:5px}.title…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The May 2022 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:62758c658c0fa352ba465e24</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/5/10/the-may-2022-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T17:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the fifth second Tuesday of 2022, which also means it’s the also the fifth Patch Tuesday of the year, and it brings with it the latest security updates from Adobe and Microsoft. This is also the last release before Pwn2Own Vancouver, which means multiple participants will be holding their breath to see if their exploits still work or were patched out. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security offerings.
Adobe Patches for May 2022
For May, Adobe released five bulletins addressing 18 CVEs in Adobe CloudFusion, InCopy, Framemaker, InDesign, and Adobe Character Animator. A total of 17 of these CVEs were reported by ZDI vulnerability researcher Mat Powell. The largest of these patches is the fix for Framemaker with 1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Attack Resistance Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/company-news/what-attack-resistance-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/company-news/what-attack-resistance-management"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Security Survey on How to Close Your Organization's Attack Resistance Gap]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Matthews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to check the PowerShell version]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565689</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/wiki/how-to-check-the-powershell-version/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T09:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is important for an administrator to know what Windows PowerShell and PowerShell edition and version are installed on a system, especially due to script compatibility. This article covers all the ways to check the PowerShell version on Windows, Linux, and MacOS and offers tips and tricks. I will also discuss the changes in PowerShell 7 and PowerShell 7.2.
How to check the PowerShell version first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on World Password Day: Are You Going Passwordless Yet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=42560</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/reflections-on-world-password-day-are-you-going-passwordless-yet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With all the talk about the growing obsolescence of passwords, it may seem strange that there exists such a thing as World Password Day. Aren’t we trying to move away from, rather than center on, passwords? This is, in fact, the real purpose of World Password Day: to draw attention to the increasing vulnerability of […]
The post Reflections on World Password Day: Are You Going Passwordless Yet? appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing pyCobaltHound – Let Cobalt Strike unleash the Hound]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=10399</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/05/09/introducing-pycobalthound/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction During our engagements, red team operators often find themselves operating within complex Active Directory environments. The question then becomes finding the needle in the haystack that allows the red team to further escalate and/or reach their objectives. Luckily, the security community has already come up with ways to assist operators in answering these questions, … Continue reading Introducing pyCobaltHound – Let Cobalt Strike unleash the Hound →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adriaan Neijzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable detailed IIS errors]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565584</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-detailed-iis-errors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, the IIS server is set to show detailed errors for local requests only, whereas it displays a custom error page for remote requests. This is done for security reasons, since detailed errors could reveal potentially detailed technical information about the web server and website.
Enable detailed IIS errors first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constrained environment breakout. .NET Assembly exfiltration via Internet Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=24811</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/constrained-environment-breakout-net-assembly-exfiltration-via-internet-options/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T05:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not uncommon for developers to find that they need to help their end users. For starter, the business requirements for software can be highly convoluted and technical. Working with […]
Constrained environment breakout. .NET Assembly exfiltration via Internet Options first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guy Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: cs-parse-traffic.py Version 0.0.5]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9094</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/05/08/update-cs-parse-traffic-py-version-0-0-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T08:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this update for cs-parse-traffic.py, my tool to decrypt & parse Cobalt Strike traffic, I added some error handling. cs-parse-traffic_V0_0_5.zip (http)MD5: CFF6D97E816B23065F051D91B0F101A6SHA256: 69763EB4D3A163824B417A0E23131B318F5E97198F255ECE449A65D4360C6302]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautiful Basics: Lesson 2]]></title>
        <id>https://malicious.link/post/2022/beautiful-basics-lesson-02/</id>
        <link href="https://malicious.link/post/2022/beautiful-basics-lesson-02/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons Learned
Slides
Lesson 1
Lesson 2
Lesson 3
Lesson 4
Lesson 5
Lesson 6
Lesson 7
Lesson 8
Lesson 9
Lesson 10
Lesson 11
Lesson 2 - Least Privilege
No one should have administrative access. All elevated access should be checked out when you need it and checked back in (automatically if possible). Just like UAC. MFA should be required, proximity or push based. And every use of a break glass account should be highly monitored

I think “Least Privilege” has been harped on at least … you know what, let me wager that you can’t find a single infosec or hacking conference from 2000 until now (2022) that doesn’t have 4 talks with the words “least privilege” in the talk. But maybe a handful out of all of those talks tell you how to accomplish such a feat.
The Goal
Lets talk about the goal first …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Posts on malicious.link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautiful Basics: Lesson 1]]></title>
        <id>https://malicious.link/post/2022/beautiful-basics-lesson-01/</id>
        <link href="https://malicious.link/post/2022/beautiful-basics-lesson-01/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-07T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons Learned
Slides
Lesson 1
Lesson 2
Lesson 3
Lesson 4
Lesson 5
Lesson 6
Lesson 7
Lesson 8
Lesson 9
Lesson 10
Lesson 11
Lesson 1 - YOU could be “Legacy”
Stop thinking that just because it did or didn’t work X way when you learned it, it still does or doesn’t. That could be 20 years ago. Technology changes faster than you do.

I guess that’s a bit mean for a title but here’s the thing:
One of the greatest yet most challenging things about doing any job in technology is staying current. Everyone struggles to stay up to date with as much of what is going on around you. Many people specialize, which makes it easier to stay up to date with a specific thing. Yet that can lead to tunnel vision as well.
All I’m trying to say here is that sometimes, the person with the least amount of “experience” in a given technology field is going to have the most open mind to what is possible. No matter how long you have been in cyber security or technology in general, you should consider your knowledge on a specific topic a point in time piece of information. At that exact moment in your life, that fact was true. This doesn’t mean that it stays that way.
Take passwords for example. Everyone said “8 character passwords are secure” for decades. I’m still hearing that. Or “never write your passwords down”. This is just one example. “Never use X software, it’s insecure”, is it still?. One of the ways I stay “current” is by always challenging my knowledge of how I think things should work vs how they do.
This is why during my keynote I noted when and where I leaned these lessons, there is every possibility I am complete off base with all of them. This is also why it’s my beautiful basics lesson #1. Something to always keep top of mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Posts on malicious.link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attacking Systemic Security Risk, Part 1]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62754bb5027928567d854223</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/attacking-systemic-security-risk-1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T20:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our intent with FRAME is to bind the functions of model-based red teaming 
to security risk awareness across the extended enterprise. Among other 
things, we’re intentionally expanding the field of vision to include 
strategic and operational functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home-Grown Red Team: Creating A Red Team Development Workstation]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/31092d94169b</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-creating-a-red-development-workstation-31092d94169b?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T18:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having a good red team development workstation is essential for creating payloads, testing out new tools and keeping your work organized…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory: Ruby on Rails – Possible XSS Vulnerability in ActionView tag helpers (CVE-2022-27777)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15648</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/05/06/technical-advisory-ruby-on-rails-possible-xss-vulnerability-in-actionview-tag-helpers-cve-2022-27777/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Ruby on Rails is a web application framework that follows the Model-view-controller (MVC) pattern. It offers some protections against Cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks in its helpers for the views. Several tag helpers in ActionView::Helpers::FormTagHelper and ActionView::Helpers::TagHelper are vulnerable against XSS because their current protection does not restrict properly the set of characters allowed in … Continue reading Technical Advisory: Ruby on Rails – Possible XSS Vulnerability in ActionView tag helpers (CVE-2022-27777) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Álvaro Martín Fraguas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disable Windows 11 widgets using Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565647</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/disable-windows-11-widgets-using-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The widgets in Windows 11 are essentially the successors of News and interests, known from Windows 10. Like these, the widgets are often annoying in professional environments and therefore not desired. You can only completely disable Windows 11 widgets with Group Policy.
Disable Windows 11 widgets using Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signing and Encrypting with JSON Web Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3885</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/signing-and-encrypting-with-json-web-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptographic weaknesses often arise in applications when the core security concepts are misunderstood or misused by developers. For this reason, a thorough review of all cryptographic implementations can be a juicy target when designing an application or starting a security assessment. Often, cryptography is used in the context of communication (e.g. a key exchange or […]
The post Signing and Encrypting with JSON Web Tokens appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sportsman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.66]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9086</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/05/05/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-66/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of oledump.py brings some fixes and an update to plugin plugin_vbaproject to decode and display the password for plaintext passwords: oledump_V0_0_66.zip (http)MD5: 20D89F0477ED7B533C2B0C6D27EC4255SHA256: F67051EF2FA3FD42206C5ADFAC807C94ECD5F7F0F6427433B366217F675D3195]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Account Relaying Vulnerabilities Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3878</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/computer-account-relaying-vulnerabilities-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T13:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Recently I’ve been working on writing a custom SMB client that implements the initial handshake and NTLM authentication functionality to perform port fingerprinting within Chariot Identify, our attack surface management product. While reading through the SMB specification, I got to thinking about Computer AdminTo Computer vulnerabilities we have exploited over the last few years […]
The post Computer Account Relaying Vulnerabilities Part 2 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sportsman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerabilities in Avast And AVG Put Millions At Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=66104</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/vulnerabilities-in-avast-and-avg-put-millions-at-risk/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two high-severity flaws in popular end user security tools allow attackers to elevate privileges and compromise devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasif Dekel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install the PowerShell Active Directory module]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/wiki/</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/wiki/how-to-install-the-powershell-active-directory-module/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T09:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide has been updated for the latest Windows versions Windows 11 and Windows Server 2022. You'll learn how to install the Active Directory (AD) module for PowerShell Core 6.0, PowerShell 7 and Windows PowerShell. For Windows PowerShell, the tutorial describes how to install the AD module for Windows 7, Windows 8, Windows 8.1, Windows 10, Windows 11 Windows Server 2008 R2, Windows Server 2012 R2, and Windows Server 2016, Windows Server 2010 and Windows Server 2022. You'll also learn how to work with the AD module on other systems such as macOS or Linux with the help of PowerShell remoting.
How to install the PowerShell Active Directory module first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea’s Lazarus: their initial access trade-craft using social media and social engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15727</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/05/05/north-koreas-lazarus-and-their-initial-access-trade-craft-using-social-media-and-social-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T08:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post documents some of the actions taken during the initial access phase for an attack attributed to Lazarus, along with analysis of the malware that was utilised during this phase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RIFT: Research and Intelligence Fusion Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Reasons You Don’t Want to Miss SANS ICS Security Summit & Training 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/8-reasons-you-don-t-want-to-miss-sans-ics-security-summit-training-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/8-reasons-you-don-t-want-to-miss-sans-ics-security-summit-training-2022?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICS Security Summit & Training kicks off June 1. Register today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Password Day – Readying Your Workforce for MFA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/world-password-day-readying-your-workforce-for-mfa</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/world-password-day-readying-your-workforce-for-mfa?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is the perfect opportunity to talk about strong passwords.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Machine Learning Part 3: Attacking Black Box Models]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3efffc256909</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/learning-machine-learning-part-3-attacking-black-box-models-3efffc256909?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first post in this series we covered a brief background on machine learning, the Revoke-Obfuscation approach for detecting…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Expect when Exploiting: A Guide to Pwn2Own Participation]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:627181d82d4b771042c0c533</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/5/3/what-to-expect-when-exploiting-a-guide-to-pwn2own-participation"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you’ve heard of Pwn2Own and think you are up to the challenge of competing in the world’s most prestigious hacking competition. Great! We would love to have you! However, there are a few things you should know before we get started. With Pwn2Own Vancouver just around the corner, here are 10 things you need to know before participating in Pwn2Own.
1.     You need to register before the contest. 
We try to make this as apparent as possible in the rules, but we still have people walk into the room on the first day of the contest hoping to participate. There are a lot of logistics around Pwn2Own, so we need everyone to complete their registration before the contest starts. We can’t support anyone who wants to join on the first day of the competition.
2.     You need to answer the vetting em…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sending email anonymously through Exchange Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565563</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sending-email-anonymously-through-exchange-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T09:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purpose of this article is to raise awareness of the possibility of sending mail anonymously through Microsoft Exchange Servers and to show mitigations for the resulting risks. After setting up Exchange Server 2019, you might be unaware that it's possible to send mail anonymously to internal recipients by default. This means that, using PowerShell, for example, anyone in your LAN may send messages to internal accounts without revealing their identity.
Sending email anonymously through Exchange Servers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Welf Alberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impacket v0.10.0 Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=42304</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/impacket-v0-10-0-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T08:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are pleased to announce the release of the latest version of Impacket, our collection of Python classes for working with network protocols, and much more. Impacket release 0.10.0 is available now and brings several new features and enhancements including a refreshed NTLMrelayx, the Kerberos Key List attack implementation, a refactored Credential Cache, the sunsetting […]
The post Impacket v0.10.0 Now Available appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why HackerOne Acquired Pull Request and What It Means to Our Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/company-news/why-hackerone-acquired-pull-request-and-what-it-means-our-customers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/company-news/why-hackerone-acquired-pull-request-and-what-it-means-our-customers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add a language pack in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565557</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/add-a-language-pack-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft started to provide language packs as Language Experience Packs (LXP) in Windows 10 1903. At the same time, LPs have still been shipped as CAB files. The duplicate formats have led to inconsistent administration of language settings. Windows 11 now removes some of these issues.
Add a language pack in Windows 11 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Themes from Real World Crypto 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102141</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/05/03/themes-from-real-world-crypto-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William Woodruff Last week, over 500 cryptographers from around the world gathered in Amsterdam for Real World Crypto 2022, meeting in person for the first time in over two years. As in previous years, we dispatched a handful of our researchers and engineers to attend the conference, listen to talks, and schmooze observe the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Woodruff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS CloudSecNext Summit 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2022?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cloud Security Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS CloudSecNext Summit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Reasons SANS 2022 Security Awareness Summit is a Must-Attend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/6-reasons-sans-2022-security-awareness-summit-is-a-must-attend</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/6-reasons-sans-2022-security-awareness-summit-is-a-must-attend?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agenda for the SANS 2022 Security Awareness Summit, Aug. 3-4, is live and the event is epic!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Linux on RISC-V 64-Bit]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5157</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2022/05/02/shellcode-risc-v-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T20:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RISC-V (pronounced “risk-five” ) is an open standard instruction set architecture (ISA) based on established reduced instruction set computer (RISC) principles. Unlike most other ISA designs, RISC-V is provided under open source licenses that do not require fees to use. … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amplify Your Existing Risk Efforts]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62700ef5c96ab17ab2902928</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/amplify-existing-efforts"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red team input can break prevailing “business as usual” perspectives, 
processes, priorities, and planning. Then again, an unexpected adversarial 
event can do the same, only worse (pay a little now or pay a lot later).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Results of the 12-month DIB-VDP Pilot]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-disclosure/announcing-results-12-month-dib-vdp-pilot</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-disclosure/announcing-results-12-month-dib-vdp-pilot"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moshen Dragon’s Triad-and-Error Approach | Abusing Security Software to Sideload PlugX and ShadowPad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=66097</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/moshen-dragons-triad-and-error-approach-abusing-security-software-to-sideload-plugx-and-shadowpad/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-aligned APT group Moshen Dragon caught sideloading malware through multiple AV products to infect telecoms sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring SSO between Active Directory and Azure using pass-through authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565543</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configuring-sso-between-active-directory-and-azure-using-pass-through-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T12:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pass-through authentication is an alternative to AD FS and password hash synchronization in Azure AD. This technology allows users to access cloud apps after authenticating against the local Active Directory. The configuration of pass-through authentication is less complex than that of AD FS, for example.
Configuring SSO between Active Directory and Azure using pass-through authentication first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel Küppers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Girls Day at NVISO Encourages Young Guests To Find Their Dream Job]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=11170</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/05/02/girls-day-at-nviso-encourages-young-guests-to-find-their-dream-job/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T09:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO employees in Frankfurt and Munich showcased their work in Cybersecurity to the girls with live hacking demos, a view behind the scenes of NVISO and hands-on tips for their personal online security. Participating in the Germany- Wide “Girls Day”, we further widened the field of future career choices for the young visitors and brought … Continue reading Girls Day at NVISO Encourages Young Guests To Find Their Dream Job →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carola Wondrak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautiful Basics - Series]]></title>
        <id>https://malicious.link/post/2022/beautiful-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://malicious.link/post/2022/beautiful-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I keynoted @BSidesVancouver. It was an honor to be asked and I had a great time.
Conference Link: https://hopin.com/events/bsides-vancouver-2022/
I talked about 11 lessons learned over my career that contradict some of the edicts that are well known in the Cyber Security space.
Before we get into the lessons though, let me attack the things I know many of you reading this already have queued up in your head.

Counter Point 1
“All of that is well and good, but it’ll never work where I work.”
Why not? Every single one of these lessons learned are things that I was told wasn’t possible. For the most part they were things I didn’t even do, they were things either already in place when I joined the company or put into place while I worked there.
I saw first hand that something I was told was “impossible” was not only possible but accomplished much more than I could have imagined. Until you see something for yourself, it’s hard to go against what you are taught, but as Security Professionals isn’t that what we are supposed to do? Look beyond the scope of what is seen as “possible”?
Counter Point 2
“It’s not as easy as you are making it sound.”
You are right, none of this is easy. Good work hardly ever is. If you are looking for the easy solution, something that can be done in a day or a week this is not the blog series for you.
Counter Point 3
“We already known all of this”
Awesome! I wish I would have known these things earlier in my career.
Lessons Learned
Lesson 1
Lesson 2
Lesson 3
Lesson 4
Lesson 5
Lesson 6
Lesson 7
Lesson 8
Lesson 9
Lesson 10
Lesson 11]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Posts on malicious.link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Management Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/vulnerability-management-resources</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/vulnerability-management-resources?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Vulnerability Management Resources for Cloud and Enterprise collected in one place for easy access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in April]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9082</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/05/01/overview-of-content-published-in-april-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-01T10:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in April: Blog posts: Power Consumption Of A Philips Hue lamp In Off State .ISO Files With Office Maldocs & Protected View in Office 2019 and 2021 New Tool: myjson-filter.py Update: cut-bytes.py Version 0.0.14 Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.13 New Tool: pngdump.py (Beta) Update: re-search.py Version 0.0.19 Update: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Machine Code Infinite Loop]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9064</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/04/30/quickpost-machine-code-infinite-loop/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-30T08:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone asked me what the byte sequence is for an infinite loop in x86 machine code (it’s something you could use while debugging, for example). That byte sequence is just 2 bytes long: EB FE. It’s something you can check with nasm, for example. File jump-infinite-loop.asm: nasm jump-infinite-loop.asm -l jump-infinite-loop.lst File jump-infinite-loop.lst: Quickpost info]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Year to I/O Ring: What Changed?]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=452766</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/one-year-to-i-o-ring-what-changed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-year-to-i-o-ring-what-changed"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T22:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[…]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventures in the land of BumbleBee – a new malicious loader]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15699</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/04/29/adventures-in-the-land-of-bumblebee-a-new-malicious-loader/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T10:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BUMBLEBEE is a new malicious loader that is being used by several threat actors and has been observed to download different malicious samples. This post provides our initial analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RIFT: Research and Intelligence Fusion Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing VSTO Office Files]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=11089</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/04/29/analyzing-vsto-office-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T09:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VSTO Office files are Office document files linked to a Visual Studio Office File application. When opened, they launch a custom .NET application. There are various ways to achieve this, including methods to serve the VSTO files via an external web server. An article was recently published on the creation of these document files for … Continue reading Analyzing VSTO Office Files →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>didiernviso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.65]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9074</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/04/29/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-65/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T09:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of oledump.py brings a new plugin (plugin_metadata) and Python 3 fixes for 2 plugins (plugin_msi and plugin_ppt). The new plugin is actually an old unpublished plugin, that I updated recently. This plugin parses Office document metadata as defined in document [MS-OLEPS]. I started to write this in 2015 to parse the metadata […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Hyper-V virtual switch with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565485</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/wiki/create-a-hyper-v-virtual-switch-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T07:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second post in my series about Hyper-V management with PowerShell I will explain how to create a Hyper-V virtual switch with PowerShell. In my previous post I explained how to install Hyper-V with PowerShell.
Virtual switch types
Create a Hyper-V virtual switch with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer on Neurodiversity in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/primer-on-neurodiversity-in-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/primer-on-neurodiversity-in-cybersecurity?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guest who? Insecure Azure Defaults!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3871</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/azure-guest-users-and-insecure-defaults/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T12:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Azure has an insecure default guest user setting, and your organization is probably using it. The default settings Azure provides would allow any user within the organization (including guest users) to invite guest users from any domain, bypassing any central identity management solutions (e.g. Okta, Auth0) and onboarding processes. Additionally, an attacker may use […]
The post Guest who? Insecure Azure Defaults! appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sportsman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAPSUS$: Recent techniques, tactics and procedures]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15637</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/04/28/lapsus-recent-techniques-tactics-and-procedures/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post describes the techniques, tactics and procedures we observed during recent LAPSUS$ incidents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RIFT: Research and Intelligence Fusion Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Execute Commands Using The API]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=10822</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/04/28/cortex-xsoar-tips-tricks-execute-commands-using-the-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Every automated task in Cortex XSOAR relies on executing commands from integrations or automations either in a playbook or directly in the incident war room or playground. But what if you wanted to incorporate a command or automation from Cortex XSOAR into your own custom scripts? For that you can use the API. In … Continue reading Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Execute Commands Using The API →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wstinkens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Hyper-V with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565480</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/wiki/install-hyper-v-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T07:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first post of my series about managing Hyper-V with PowerShell I will outline how to install Hyper-V Server and the Hyper-V role with PowerShell.
Install Hyper-V with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Red Teamer’s Guide to Analyzing Propaganda, Part 1]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:6269778d4a79d3621fc90f82</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/red-team-guide-analyzing-propaganda-part1"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T00:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korzybski to the rescue once again! In part 1, we look at how two-valued 
orientation can shape and constrain thinking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Ransomware Side-loads Cobalt Strike Beacon with Legitimate VMware Utility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=65951</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/lockbit-ransomware-side-loads-cobalt-strike-beacon-with-legitimate-vmware-utility/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long-running LockBit ransomware attempts to evade Windows ETW, AMSI and EDR by leveraging legitimate VMware logging command line utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Haughom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confused by agents? We've cleaned up our jargon ...]]></title>
        <id>confused-by-agents-weve-cleaned-up-our-jargon</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/confused-by-agents-weve-cleaned-up-our-jargon"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking to Burp Suite Enterprise Edition users, one thing has come up time and time again as a blocker to your understanding of the product. This has been our use of the term "agent" when describing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite Enterprise Edition: config tips for scanning success]]></title>
        <id>burp-suite-enterprise-edition-config-tips-for-scanning-success</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/burp-suite-enterprise-edition-config-tips-for-scanning-success"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite Enterprise Edition is the dynamic web vulnerability scanner that can help you to secure your whole portfolio. To help you achieve that, this article contains some advice on how to optimize]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SecureAuth Announces New Behavioral Modeling Patents to Fortify Passwordless Continuous Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=42291</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/secureauth-announces-new-behavioral-modeling-patents-to-fortify-passwordless-continuous-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T10:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovative Method of Biobehavioral Credentials Deliver Frictionless Authentication to Prevent Fraud using Dynamic Level of Assurance IRVINE, Calif. – April 25 2022 – SecureAuth, a leader in next-generation access management and authentication, announces that the United States Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) granted the company four groundbreaking methods for authenticating users’ claimed identities for frictionless […]
The post SecureAuth Announces New Behavioral Modeling Patents to Fortify Passwordless Continuous Authentication appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jendres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python module Paramiko for managing CISCO devices: Installation and usage example]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565450</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/python-module-paramiko-for-managing-cisco-devices-installation-and-usage-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T09:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python module Paramiko enables you to leverage Python to automate the management of CISCO routers and switches. In this guide, I will explain how to install Paramiko via pip and provide a usage example. The module makes Python act as an SSH client or server, enabling us to automate any device to which we can connect via SSH.
Python module Paramiko for managing CISCO devices: Installation and usage example first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Tips to Successfully Prepare for the SSAP Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/4-tips-to-successfully-prepare-for-the-ssap-exam</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/4-tips-to-successfully-prepare-for-the-ssap-exam?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SANS Security Awareness Professional (SSAP) is the world’s leading industry-recognized credential that signifies that the holder has the knowledge and expertise to build, maintain and measure a mature security awareness program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Machine Learning Part 2: Attacking White Box Models]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1a10bbb4a2ae</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/learning-machine-learning-part-2-attacking-white-box-models-1a10bbb4a2ae?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post, I went through a very brief overview of some machine learning concepts, talked about the Revoke-Obfuscation project…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudGoat goes Serverless:   A walkthrough of Vulnerable Lambda Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=24469</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/cloud-security/cloudgoat-vulnerable-lambda-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CloudGoat goes Serverless:  
 A walkthrough of Vulnerable Lambda Functions appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mitch Fentz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real World Cryptography Conference 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15612</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/04/26/real-world-cryptography-conference-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IACR’s annual Real World Cryptography (RWC) conference took place in Amsterdam a few weeks ago. It remains the best venue for highlights of cryptographic constructions and attacks for the real world. While the conference was fully remote last year, this year it was a 3-day hybrid event, live-streamed from a conference center in charming … Continue reading Real World Cryptography Conference 2022 →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marie-Sarah Lacharite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving the state of go-fuzz]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102101</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/04/26/improving-the-state-of-go-fuzz/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Christian Presa Schnell During my winternship, I used the findings from recent Go audits to make several improvements to go-fuzz, a coverage-based fuzzer for projects written in Go. I focused on three enhancements to improve the effectiveness of Go fuzzing campaigns and provide a better experience for users. I contributed to fixing type alias […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export and import passwords in Firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565439</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/export-and-import-passwords-in-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T10:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since version 80, Firefox has allowed you to import passwords in CSV format. This can be used, for example, to export passwords from Firefox and transfer them to another PC. If you format the data accordingly, you can also import them from other programs, such as password managers.
Export and import passwords in Firefox first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to VirtualBox security research]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2022/04/26/vbox-fuzzing.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2022/04/26/vbox-fuzzing.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
This article introduces VirtualBox research and explains how to build a coverage-based fuzzer, focusing on the emulated network device drivers. In the examples below, we explain how to create a harness for the non-default network device driver PCNet. The example can be readily adjusted for a different network driver or even different device driver components.
We are aware that there are excellent resources related to this topic - see [1], [2]. However, these cover the fuzzing process from a high-level perspective or omit some important technical details. Our goal is to present all the necessary steps and code required to instrument and debug the latest stable version of VirtualBox (6.1.30 at the time of writing). As the SVN version is out-of-sync, we download the tarball inste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exodus Wants to help CISA Shields Up]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=1979</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2022/04/25/exodus-wants-to-help-cisa-shields-up/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=exodus-wants-to-help-cisa-shields-up"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Shields Up in response to looming Russian Cyberattacks, Exodus Intelligence wants to help The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) recently launched the #ShieldsUp Campaign to provide organizations resources and recommended actions to heighten their security posture in light of the Russian invasion of Ukraine.  Evolving intelligence indicates that the Russian Government is exploring ... Read more Exodus Wants to help CISA Shields Up
The post Exodus Wants to help CISA Shields Up appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passwordless authentication with FIDO2 and Azure Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565423</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/passwordless-authentication-with-fido2-and-azure-active-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting rid of unsecure password authentication is becoming a priority for many businesses. Companies using Microsoft's Azure Active Directory have many options to implement passwordless authentication. One of these is using a FIDO2 security key.
Passwordless authentication with FIDO2 and Azure Active Directory first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SecureAuth Latest Release Delivers Enhanced Passwordless Authentication with Improved User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=42283</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/secureauth-latest-release-delivers-enhanced-passwordless-authentication-with-improved-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations Now Have the Ability to Use Common FIDO2 Experience Across Browsers, Conditional Passwordless, Hybrid and Cloud Deployment for Azure AD Support As we emerge from the pandemic, trends of digital transformation with a dispersed workforce and a complete restructuring of Information Technology (IT) and Operational Technology (OT) architecture accelerates the need for security and […]
The post SecureAuth Latest Release Delivers Enhanced Passwordless Authentication with Improved User Experience appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jendres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which DFIR Summit Mascots do you want to see as Lego giveaways this year? Vote now!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/which-dfir-mascots-do-you-want-to-see-as-legos-at-the-dfir-summit</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/which-dfir-mascots-do-you-want-to-see-as-legos-at-the-dfir-summit?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-04-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us this year at the 2022 SANS DFIR Summit Live Online or attend in Austin! If you’ve attended before, you know you’ll walk away from the summit with a story, connection, and maybe even one of those limited edition DFIR Mascot Legos. If it’s your first time attending, we look forward to meeting you at the most comprehensive DFIR event of the year!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: re-search.py Version 0.0.19]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9061</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/04/23/update-re-search-py-version-0-0-19/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a Python3 stdin fix for re-search.py, my tool to search with regular expressions. re-search_V0_0_19.zip (http)MD5: 4007A3E5540871221B55591B50E2239BSHA256: 263236ABE75B93F1F999474D690A9EB2575EBE42CED8F369FF98B349A5116D11]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing PESieve and Moneta (The "easy" way....?)]]></title>
        <id>6261df5f5d194b003d1aa9e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.arashparsa.com/bypassing-pesieve-and-moneta-the-easiest-way-i-could-find/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T05:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table of Contents
Introduction
Moneta and the first IOC
Moneta and the final IOC
The PeSieve Bypass
Conclusion

TLDR; POC is here: https://github.com/waldo-irc/YouMayPasser/.  Usage isn't super straight forward but I'd rather it wasn't.  Good Luck!

Introduction

The title]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arash's Security Thoughts n Stuff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home-Grown Red Team: Bypassing Windows 11 Defenses With Covenant C2 and Nimcrypt2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2557a0e3dfff</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-bypassing-windows-11-defenses-with-covenant-c2-and-nimcrypt2-2557a0e3dfff?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T03:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know your question. Why would anybody want to use Covenant C2? It’s not supported, it’s outdated and everybody has moved on! Let’s at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing an AWS Lambda function using Go (Golang)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565404</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/writing-an-aws-lambda-function-using-go-golang/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T08:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last article, titled "What is serverless computing? An introduction to AWS Lambda," we took a detailed look at what serverless computing does. Taking the next step, we will create a working example in AWS Lambda using the Go programming language (often referred to as Golang).
Writing an AWS Lambda function using Go (Golang) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Beer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Російсько-український конфлікт. Кіберресурсний центр]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ukraine-russia-conflict-cyber-resource-center-Ukrainian</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ukraine-russia-conflict-cyber-resource-center-Ukrainian?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Отримайте доступ до ресурсів, які допоможуть вашій організації орієнтуватися в кіберризиках, пов’язаних з російсько-українським конфліктом.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infosec Salaries – the myth and the reality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8060</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/04/21/infosec-salaries-the-myth-and-the-reality/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while someone drops a salary bomb discussion on social media and the speculations follow. The salary bomb value du jour it is the mythical 450K USD […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home-Grown Red Team: Testing Common AV Evasion With PE Packers On Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/a2a9e873fe13</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-testing-common-av-evasion-with-pe-packers-on-windows-11-a2a9e873fe13?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T21:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing AV solutions is essential for initial access, lateral movement and full domain compromise. Over the last couple of years, we’ve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, It’s Tough but We’re Tougher]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:6261aae07c5b1305fcf07ef1</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/red-teaming-tough-and-tougher"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T19:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Times are volatile, and everyone we encounter seems slightly on edge. In an 
environment like this, it’s no surprise that red teaming is tough. But 
that’s no excuse for us to throw up our hands. It just means we need to 
revisit our fundamental mission and work harder than ever to refine our red 
teaming methods and manners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nokoyawa Ransomware | New Karma/Nemty Variant Wears Thin Disguise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=65892</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/nokoyawa-ransomware-new-karma-nemty-variant-wears-thin-disguise/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nemty developers have created a new, flawed update to the Karma ransomware variant in a bid to avoid detection and mislead attribution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonis Terefos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Wix Improves Their Security Posture with Ethical Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/how-wix-improves-their-security-posture-ethical-hackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/how-wix-improves-their-security-posture-ethical-hackers"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing risk is fundamental to Wix’s approach to cybersecurity, and as the threat landscape evolves, they turn to HackerOne Bounty to protect their security posture. Since 2018, Wix has invited tens of thousands of ethical hackers worldwide to ensure new and existing features are secure. We recently met with two Wix security team members to learn how they leverage ethical hackers to detect risks before they become threats and how vulnerability insights help strengthen their security posture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export and import to and from Excel with the PowerShell module ImportExcel]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565380</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/export-and-import-to-and-from-excel-with-the-powershell-module-importexcel/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T12:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ImportExcel is a PowerShell module that allows you import to or export data directly from Excel spreadsheets without having Microsoft Excel installed on your computer. In this tutorial, you'll learn to work with Import-Excel and Export-Excel. The ImportExcel module runs on Windows, Linux, or Mac and now can be used in Azure functions and GitHub Actions. Simply put, if you need to generate reports for work, you must learn this module.
Export and import to and from Excel with the PowerShell module ImportExcel first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Kanakos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abusing Azure Container Registry Tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1f407bfaa465</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/abusing-azure-container-registry-tasks-1f407bfaa465?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T18:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro and Prior Work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitigating the top 10 security threats to GCP using the CIS Google Cloud Platform Foundation Benchmark￼]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15507</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/04/20/mitigating-the-top-10-security-threats-to-gcp-using-the-cis-google-cloud-platform-foundation-benchmark%ef%bf%bc/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T16:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As one of the proud contributors to the newest version of the CIS Google Cloud Platform Foundation Benchmark, I wanted to raise awareness about the new version release of this benchmark [1] by the Center for Internet Security (CIS) and how it can help a company to set a strong security baseline or foundation for … Continue reading Mitigating the top 10 security threats to GCP using the CIS Google Cloud Platform Foundation Benchmark￼ →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viktor Gazdag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New XSS vectors]]></title>
        <id>new-xss-vectors</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/new-xss-vectors"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transition based events without style blocks So, recently, I was updating our XSS cheat sheet to fix certain vectors that had been made obsolete by browser updates. Whilst looking at the vectors, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amarna: Static analysis for Cairo programs]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102012</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/04/20/amarna-static-analysis-for-cairo-programs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Filipe Casal We are open-sourcing Amarna, our new static analyzer and linter for the Cairo programming language. Cairo is a programming language powering several trading exchanges with millions of dollars in assets (such as dYdX, driven by StarkWare) and is the programming language for StarkNet contracts. But, not unlike other languages, it has its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fcasal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMB port number: Ports 445, 139, 138, and 137 explained]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565296</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/smb-port-number-ports-445-139-138-and-137-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T09:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SMB port number is TCP 445. If you've heard people saying the port number is 139, they could be partially correct. Let’s understand the SMB ports 445, 139, 138, and 137 in detail.
SMB port number: Ports 445, 139, 138, and 137 explained first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating an engineering workstation – Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=10257</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/04/20/investigating-an-engineering-workstation-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our third blog post (part one and two are referenced above) we will focus on information we can get from the projects itself. You may remember from Part 1 that a project created with the TIA Portal is not a single file. So far we talked about files with the “.apXX” extension, like “.ap15_1” … Continue reading Investigating an engineering workstation – Part 3 →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olaf Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HackerOne 2022 Attack Resistance Report: A Security Survey—How to Close Your Organization's Attack Resistance Gap]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/company-news/announcing-hackerone-2022-attack-resistance-report-security-survey-how-close-your</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/company-news/announcing-hackerone-2022-attack-resistance-report-security-survey-how-close-your"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T23:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, HackerOne published The 2022 Attack Resistance Report: A HackerOne Security Survey. Our research revealed an increasing gap—the attack resistance gap—between what organizations can defend and what they need to defend. The gap is the result of four components prevalent across organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware the Fast-Roping Acrobats]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:625ef1a08e149d6e728ac939</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/fast-roping-acrobats"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, the astonishing adventures of see-in-the-dark acrobats might make a 
great movie, but it’s probably not what your red team client needs to worry 
about. Let them see the movie, and you can both fret about phishing 
instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HyperGuard Part 3 – More SKPG Extents]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=446342</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/hyperguard-part-3-more-skpg-extents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hyperguard-part-3-more-skpg-extents"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[…]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Miami 2022 Results]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:62583670c7df64794d977aa5</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/4/14/pwn2own-miami-2022-results"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Miami for 2022 is underway, and we’ve already seen some amazing research demonstrated. Stay tuned to this blog for updated results, picture, and videos from the event. We’ll be posting it all here - including the most recent Master of Pwn leaderboard. 
Master of Pwn standings as of Apr 19, 18:20 Eastern
SUCCESS - 20urdjk was able to execute their DoS attack against Unified Automation C++ Demo Server. They earn $5,000 and 5 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Sam Thomas (@_s_n_t) from @pentestltd combined an auth bypass and a deserialization bug to get code execution. They win $20,000 and 20 points towards Master of Pwn.
SUCCESS - Or Peles, Omer Kaspi and Uriya Yavnieli from JFrog Security Research leveraged a Use-After-Free (UAF) bug to create a DoS on the Unified Automation C++ Demo S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The More You Know, The More You Know You Don’t Know]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/04/the-more-you-know-more-you-know-you.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/04/the-more-you-know-more-you-know-you.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw');.lst-kix_qhs0t3wlsx02-8>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_qhs0t3wlsx02-8}ol.lst-kix_h2vtkcla8l9d-2.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_h2vtkcla8l9d-2 0}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-1{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_h2vtkcla8l9d-3>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_h2vtkcla8l9d-3}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-0{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-2{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-5{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-4{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-7{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_czzguda5pqu4-1>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_czzguda5pqu4-1}ul.lst-kix_9i24fh2252ug-6{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_jdourvkzhmg1-7>li{counter-increment…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethical Hackers Help A.S. Watson Address Digital Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/how-ethical-hackers-help-watson-address-digital-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/how-ethical-hackers-help-watson-address-digital-risk"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently met with A.S. Watson’s Chief Information Security Officer (CISO), Feliks Voskoboynik, to learn how ethical hackers have helped with digital transformation and enabled his team to harden their attack surface. Read on to learn Feliks’ advice on including a bug bounty program as part of a security strategy, the lessons ethical hackers have provided, and what best practices he can share with other CISOs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SMB protocol: All you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565304</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/the-smb-protocol-all-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T14:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SMB protocol is a client–server communication protocol that has been used by Windows since the beginning for sharing files, printers, named pipes, and other network resources. SMB stands for "server message block." Apart from regular resource sharing, SMB is also useful for inter-process communication (IPC), such as in mailslots.
The SMB protocol: All you need to know first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Попередження про загрозу російських кібератак. Що робити зараз, щоб посилити стійкість роботи своїх систем]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/impending-russian-cyberattacks-harden-your-systems-Ukrainian</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/impending-russian-cyberattacks-harden-your-systems-Ukrainian?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Існують кроки, які ви можете зробити зараз, щоб зміцнити свій кіберзахист.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS FOR500: Windows Forensic Analysis -  Updated for Windows 11 and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-for500-updated-for-windows-11-and-beyond</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-for500-updated-for-windows-11-and-beyond?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new release of the FOR500 Windows Forensic Analysis course includes a significant focus to support the new Windows 11 operating system and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Miami 2022 Schedule]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:62582b6c65d0942eedf62692</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/4/14/p2omiami-2022-schedule"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T23:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[¡Bienvenidos de nuevo a Miami!
Welcome to Pwn2Own Miami 2022! This year’s ICS-focused event promises to be three days of great research and exploits, as we have 32 total entries from 11 contestants. As always, we began our contest with a random drawing to determine the order of attempts. If you missed it, you can watch the replay here. 
The complete schedule for the contest is below (all times Eastern [GMT -4:00]). 
Note: All times subject to change - You can see the results and live updates here once they become available. Entries marked with a 📷 icon will be live streamed on YouTube, Twitch, and Twitter.
Tuesday, April 19
09:30 - 20urdjk targeting Unified Automation C++ Demo Server with a DoS in the OPC UA Server category
10:30 -  @_s_n_t from @pentestltd targeting Inductive Automation …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create and read SCVMM custom properties with PowerShell and the VMM Console]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1565275</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-and-read-scvmm-custom-properties-with-powershell-and-the-vmm-console/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T16:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, I will show you how to add, remove, and read Microsoft's System Center Virtual Machine Manager (SCVMM) custom properties with PowerShell and the Virtual Machine Manager Console.
Create and read SCVMM custom properties with PowerShell and the VMM Console first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Pazik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Frozen Heart vulnerability in PlonK]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=101936</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/04/18/the-frozen-heart-vulnerability-in-plonk/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T11:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jim Miller In part 1 of this blog post, we disclosed critical vulnerabilities that break the soundness of multiple implementations of zero-knowledge proof systems. This class of vulnerability, which we dubbed Frozen Heart, is caused by insecure implementations of the Fiat-Shamir transformation that allow malicious users to forge proofs for random statements. In part […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tool: pngdump.py (Beta)]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9054</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/04/18/new-tool-pngdump-py-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T07:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a new tool I’m releasing as beta: pngdump.py. It’s a tool to analyze PNG files. Unlike jpegdump, you can not yet select items for further analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A blueprint for evading industry leading endpoint protection in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://vanmieghem.io/blueprint-for-evading-edr-in-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://vanmieghem.io/blueprint-for-evading-edr-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About two years ago I quit being a full-time red team operator. However, it still is a field of expertise that stays very close to my heart. A few weeks ago, I was looking for a new side project and decided to pick up an old red teaming hobby of mine: bypassing/evading endpoint protection solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vincent Van Mieghem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.13]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9048</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/04/17/update-1768-py-version-0-0-13/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-17T15:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of 1768.py brings option -H to include file hashes, introduces shellcode type detection and has updated statistics. 1768_v0_0_13.zip (http)MD5: F7E85586045AA76C573E010E6FF5F701SHA256: 33B43A5AB059556C17083E824D407891CD14544B5CA416223020076C5878D310]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anti-VM trick that is kinda… personal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8047</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/04/16/the-anti-vm-trick-that-is-kinda-personal/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T21:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have written a lot about anti-vm tricks, and while this topic is so worn out that almost feels like kicking a dead horse I felt there is still a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: cut-bytes.py Version 0.0.14]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9037</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/04/16/update-cut-bytes-py-version-0-0-14/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T08:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of cut-bytes.py adds access to the read data for Python expressions in prefix and suffix options. cut-bytes_V0_0_14.zip (http)MD5: EC3434DAAEE06C6F35BD57B77F86833FSHA256: BCCCE7A73C921BD2CC195155A3A709FBAD7ADC0A267288A4F7F58695A2F103D1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NTLMquic]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/ntlmquic/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/ntlmquic/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we'll dig into just how SMB over QUIC works, answer some of the immediate questions around which attacks are feasible, and show how we can repurpose some existing tooling to capture NTLM handshakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>