<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-03T00:34:49.887Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in August]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10147</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/09/02/overview-of-content-published-in-august-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in August: Blog posts: Update: sortcanon.py Version 0.0.3 Update: emldump.py Version 0.0.12 Quickpost: Analysis of PDF/ActiveMime Polyglot Maldocs Quickpost: PDF/ActiveMime Maldocs YARA Rule SANS ISC Diary entries: PDFiD: False Positives Revisited Analysis of RAR Exploit Files (CVE-2023-38831)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: The Offensive Clipboard Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c66f336f2c11</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-the-offensive-clipboard-revisited-c66f336f2c11?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn’t going to be a long post, but I think it’s a really cool concept that I have wanted to implement for a while. This isn’t a new…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Static Pods in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576258</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/static-pods-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article of this Kubernetes tutorial, you learned how to encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest. In today's post, I will introduce you to Static Pods, a special type of Pod in Kubernetes that is not managed by the Kubernetes control plane. Instead, Static Pods are directly managed by kubelet on a specific node.
Static Pods in Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You're Doing Pentesting Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging the power of the pentester community and the efficiency of a Pentest as a Service (PTaaS) platform, pentesting can add real value to your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Chin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You're Doing Pentesting Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging the power of the pentester community and the efficiency of a Pentest as a Service (PTaaS) platform, pentesting can add real value to your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Chin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging VSCode Extensions for Initial Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3259</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2023/08/leveraging-vscode-extensions-for-initial-access/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction On a recent red team engagement, MDSec were tasked with crafting a phishing campaign for initial access. The catch was that the in-scope phishing targets were developers with technical...
The post Leveraging VSCode Extensions for Initial Access appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dsregcmd: Troubleshoot and manage Azure Active Directory (Microsoft Entra ID) joined devices]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576240</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/dsregcmd-troubleshoot-and-manage-azure-active-directory-microsoft-entra-id-joined-devices/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use dsregcmd to manage Azure Active Directory-joined devices. This post covers examples of getting device state, including status, device details, tenant details, user state, SSO state, joining and unjoining, displaying debug information for verbose output, and listing and deleting Windows Account Manager accounts. Notice that Microsoft rebranded Azure Active Directory to Microsoft Entra ID. In this post I will use both brand names interchangeably.
dsregcmd: Troubleshoot and manage Azure Active Directory (Microsoft Entra ID) joined devices first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZeroQlik: Achieving Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via HTTP Request Tunneling and Path Traversal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4806</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/qlik-sense-technical-exploit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations.  Recently, we decided to take a look at Qlik Sense Enterprise, a data analytics solution similar to Tableau. The recent exploitation of vulnerabilities in the […]
The post ZeroQlik: Achieving Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via HTTP Request Tunneling and Path Traversal appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HITB Phuket 2023 – Exploiting the Lexmark PostScript Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32844</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/31/hitb-phuket-2023-exploiting-the-lexmark-postscript-stack/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Adams presented this talk at HITB Phuket on the 24th August 2023. The talk detailed how NCC Exploit Development Group (EDG) in Pwn2Own 2022 Toronto was able to exploit two different PostScript vulnerabilities in Lexmark printers. The presentation is a good primer for those interested in further researching the Lexmark PostScript stack, and also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Session Hijacking Visual Exploitation (SHVE): An Innovative Open-Source Tool for XSS Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/31/introducing-session-hijacking-visual-exploitation.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/31/introducing-session-hijacking-visual-exploitation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings, folks! Today, we’re thrilled to introduce you to our latest tool: Session Hijacking Visual Exploitation, or SHVE. This open-source tool, now available on our GitHub, offers a novel way to hijack a victim’s browser sessions, utilizing them as a visual proxy after hooking via an XSS or a malicious webpage. While some exploitation frameworks, such as BeEF, do provide hooking features, they don’t allow remote visual interactions.
SHVE’s interaction with a victim’s browser in the security context of the user relies on a comprehensive design incorporating multiple elements. These components, each fulfilling a specific function, form a complex, interconnected system that allows a precise and controlled session hijacking. Let’s take a closer look at each of them:
VictimServer: This comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybercrime-intelligence-FOR589</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybercrime-intelligence-FOR589?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence course will teach you how to effectively anticipate, prevent, and mitigate potential cybercrime threats, while also helping law enforcement agencies and governments to combat cybercrime and prosecute cybercriminals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career Development for Security Awareness, Behavior, and Culture Professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/career-development-for-security-awareness-behavior-and-culture-professionals</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/career-development-for-security-awareness-behavior-and-culture-professionals?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute offers these key courses to help security awareness and culture professionals develop in their careers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Into OSINT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-get-into-osint</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-get-into-osint?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn various methods to find OSINT resources and communities, figure out how to practice techniques and build your skillset, and learn how you can get a job in OSINT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC568: Approaching the Software Supply Chain like Jack Byrnes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sec568-approaching-the-software-supply-chain-like-jack-byrnes</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sec568-approaching-the-software-supply-chain-like-jack-byrnes?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about product security testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Entropy/Rust Cryptography Review]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32756</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/30/public-report-entropy-rust-cryptography-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the summer of 2023, Entropy Cryptography Inc engaged NCC Group’s Cryptography Services team to perform a cryptography and implementation review of several Rust-based libraries implementing constant-time big integer arithmetic, prime generation, and secp256k1 (k256) elliptic curve functionality. Two consultants performed the review within 40 person-days of effort, which included retesting and report generation. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible yum module: Install RHEL/CentOS packages]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576221</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/ansible-yum-module-install-the-rhelcentos-packages/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T15:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible yum module manages packages using the yum package manager on CentOS and RPM-based Linux distributions, such as RHEL, CentOS, Fedora, and Rocky Linux. The Ansible yum module allows you to interact with the yum package manager and perform all basic package management tasks, such as installing, removing, and updating the packages.
Ansible yum module: Install RHEL/CentOS packages first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending Against Ransomware in Industrial Control Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/defending-against-ransomware-industrial-control-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/defending-against-ransomware-industrial-control-systems?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging ICS612 and the SANS Five Critical Cybersecurity Controls]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolution of Cybercriminal Operations in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/evolution-of-cybercriminal-operations-in-2023-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/evolution-of-cybercriminal-operations-in-2023-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SANS FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence course authors examined the latest key findings from the CrowdStrike 2023 threat hunting report and highlighted the top cybercriminal trends that defenders should pay attention to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: PDF/ActiveMime Maldocs YARA Rule]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10141</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/29/quickpost-pdf-activemime-maldocs-yara-rule/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a YARA rule I developed to detect PDF/ActiveMime maldocs I wrote about in “Quickpost: Analysis of PDF/ActiveMime Polyglot Maldocs“. It looks for files that start with %PDF- (this header can be obfuscated) and contain string QWN0aXZlTWlt (string ActiveMim in BASE64), possibly obfuscated with whitespace characters. The regex used to detect characters QWN0aXZlTWlt interspersed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix “The WinRM client cannot process the request”]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576203</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/fix-the-winrm-client-cannot-process-the-request/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T16:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work on Windows, one of the common errors you might encounter is when the WinRM client cannot process a request. Windows Remote Management (WinRM) is a Windows built-in remote management protocol that helps exchange information between different systems. For instance, you can spot it being used in Exchange, WSUS, and Microsoft Teams, especially when you're running PowerShell scripts and other third-party tools.
Fix “The WinRM client cannot process the request” first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealing the Targets and Rules for the First Pwn2Own Automotive]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64ecedcf9c27c149ad0a75b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/8/28/revealing-the-targets-and-rules-for-the-first-pwn2own-automotive"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T15:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here.
 
Earlier this year, I announced the ZDI, along with our cohorts at VicOne, will host a new Pwn2Own contest focused on automotive systems – Pwn2Own Automotive – at the upcoming Automotive World conference in Tokyo, Japan, held on January 24th – 26th, 2024. Today, we are releasing the targets and payouts for this inaugural event. As a reminder, we have three primary goals in hosting this event:
1.     Provide an avenue to encourage automotive research. We want to offer a place where researchers can submit and be financially rewarded for reports targeting various products and platforms.
2.     Incentivize vendors to participate in the security research community. We want to connect our global community of security researchers with a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloated Binaries | How to Detect and Analyze Large macOS Malware Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=83921</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/bloated-binaries-how-to-detect-and-analyze-large-macos-malware-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T13:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Massive malware binaries are becoming more common on macOS and can cause problems for detection and analysis. Here's how we can successfully deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Stokes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Hak5 Gear In 2023 With Microsoft Defender For Endpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2ca386bf09d3</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-hak5-gear-in-2023-with-microsoft-defender-for-endpoint-2ca386bf09d3?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T12:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! Today we’ll take a look at some of the tools out there by Hak5. If you’re not familiar with Hak5, they are a company that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Apollo GraphQL server with Semgrep]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104947</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/29/secure-your-apollo-graphql-server-with-semgrep/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T12:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vasco Franco tl;dr: Our publicly available Semgrep ruleset has nine new rules to detect misconfigurations of versions 3 and 4 of the Apollo GraphQL server. Try them out with semgrep --config p/trailofbits! When auditing several of our clients’ Apollo GraphQL servers, I kept finding the same issues over and over: cross-site request forgery (CSRF) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Analysis of PDF/ActiveMime Polyglot Maldocs]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10122</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/29/quickpost-analysis-of-pdf-activemime-polyglot-maldocs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T10:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jpcert reported a new type of maldoc: “MalDoc in PDF – Detection bypass by embedding a malicious Word file into a PDF file –“. These maldocs are PDF files that embed a Word document (ActiveMime) in MIME format. ActiveMime documents can be analyzed by combining my emldump.py tool and oledump.py. ActiveMime documents were heavily obfuscated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: emldump.py Version 0.0.12]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10116</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/29/update-emldump-py-version-0-0-12/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T10:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update to emldump.py adds a new feature to fix (-F) some obfuscations. For the moment, only one obfuscation method is fixed (many are already ignored with option -f –filter), used in polyglot PDF/Word files. emldump_V0_0_12.zip (http)MD5: 3847B92460C0485E1238C47C29EF9DE1SHA256: AFDFB8E78AE7DE56F50EA73D69705B6DACB425FFBD40D6997D64C7C75E3D8A0D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIAM AG23: Algebraic Geometry with Friends]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32720</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/29/siam-ag23-algebraic-geometry-with-friends/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently returned from Eindhoven, where I had the pleasure of giving a talk on some recent progress in isogeny-based cryptography at the SIAM Conference on Applied Algebraic Geometry (SIAM AG23).…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giacomo Pope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Instance Metadata Services (IMDS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-instance-metadata-services-imds-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-instance-metadata-services-imds-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A misunderstood but deeply important feature to lock down when deploying workloads in cloud. Learn about Cloud Instance Metadata Services (IMDS) in this blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Data Exfiltration Vulnerabilities in LLM apps (Bing Chat, ChatGPT, Claude)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/video-data-exfiltration-vulns-in-llm-applictions/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/video-data-exfiltration-vulns-in-llm-applictions/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This video highlights the various data exfiltration vulnerabilities I discovered and responsibly disclosed to Microsoft, Anthropic, ChatGPT and Plugin Developers.
It also briefly discusses mitigations various vendors put in place (and triage decisions).
   Thanks to MSRC, Anthropic and Zapier for addressing vulnerabilities to help protect their users.
Let’s hope it inspires OpenAI to mitigate the image markdown injection issue finally as well. It’s rated as a CVSS High scored vulnerability basically and was first reported to them on April, 9th 2023 - the triage decision was “won’t fix”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VDPs Are Good For the Government — and Good For Business]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/congress-legislation-federal-contractors-vdp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/congress-legislation-federal-contractors-vdp"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress recently introduced the Federal Cybersecurity Vulnerability Reduction Act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576188</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/encrypt-kubernetes-secrets-at-rest/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T15:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, you learned that Kubernetes Secrets are not really secure by default; that is, they are stored in an etcd datastore in plaintext. etcd is a central key–value store where Kubernetes stores all cluster information in an unencrypted form. If security is a concern in your environment, you need to follow some manual steps to encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest.
Encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iVerify is now an independent company!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105015</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/28/iverify-is-now-an-independent-company/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T11:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re proud to announce that iVerify is now an independent company following its four-year incubation at Trail of Bits. Originally developed in-house to ensure that our personal phones, which store data essential to our work and private lives, were secured to the standards of security professionals, iVerify quickly showed that it could be valuable to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Guido</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5G security – how to minimise the threats to a 5G network]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32319</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/28/5g-security-how-to-minimise-the-threats-to-a-5g-network/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To ensure security of new 5G telecom networks, NCC Group has been providing guidance, conducting code reviews, red team engagements and pentesting 5G standalone and non-standalone networks since 2019. As with any network various attackers are motivated by different reasons. An attacker could be motivated to either gain information about subscribers on an operator’s network […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>philipmarsdennccgroupcom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: sortcanon.py Version 0.0.3]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10092</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/27/update-sortcanon-py-version-0-0-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T17:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some new options for my tool sortcanon.py to handle more inputs. A bit of context: when one sorts a list of IPv4 addresses as text, one gets a result as follows. Take this list: Just sorting this gives this result: The IPv4 address starting with 185 comes first, because by default, sorting is string based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in July]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10090</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/26/overview-of-content-published-in-july-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T08:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in July: Blog posts: Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.27 SANS ISC Diary entries: YARA Error Codes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing better Yara rules in 2023…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8661</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/08/26/writing-better-yara-rules-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T00:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post I mused about an impossible task – how to consolidate a large, unorganized yara ruleset (that lots of us, admittedly, collect and hoard – just downloading it all, randomly, from all the corners of the internet … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lolbins for connoisseurs…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8694</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/08/25/lolbins-for-connoisseurs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are all quite fixated on a purity of lolbins. Best if it is a hidden/undocumented/unexpected behavior of a native OS binary that can be abused for some nefarious purposes. I, obviously, love these the most, too. However… Living Off … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Windows 11 productivity features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576163</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/the-best-windows-11-productivity-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T14:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows 11 productivity features discussed in this article are helpful for enhancing your workflow and getting the most out of the native Windows experience. In this post, I will outline Snap layouts, Task View, widgets, focus sessions, voice typing, improved clipboard, and Microsoft Teams.
The best Windows 11 productivity features first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real World Cryptography Conference 2023 – Part II]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32477</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/25/real-world-cryptography-conference-2023-part-ii/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a brief interlude, filled with several articles from the Cryptography Services team, we’re back with our final thoughts from this year’s Real World Cryptography Conference. In case you missed it, check out Part I for more insights. Interoperability in E2EE Messaging A specter is haunting Europe – the specter of platform interoperability. The EU […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Henry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner’s Guide to Adversary Emulation with Caldera]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=15762</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/08/25/a-beginners-guide-to-adversary-emulation-with-caldera/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Target Audience The target audience for this blog post is individuals who have a basic understanding of cybersecurity concepts and terminology and looking to expand their knowledge on adversary emulation. This post delves into the details of adversary emulation with the Caldera framework exploring the benefits it offers. By catering to a beginner to intermediate … Continue reading A Beginner’s Guide to Adversary Emulation with Caldera →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantinos Pantazis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A broken marriage. Abusing mixed vendor Kerberos stacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27492</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/a-broken-marriage-abusing-mixed-vendor-kerberos-stacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T05:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first DEF CON talk was nerve-racking but something I would definitely put myself through again. In hindsight I should have submitted a 45-minute talk as there were some elements […]
A broken marriage. Abusing mixed vendor Kerberos stacks first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Foundation to a Strong Security Culture: Feeling Safe and Included]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-foundation-to-a-strong-security-culture-feeling-safe-and-included</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-foundation-to-a-strong-security-culture-feeling-safe-and-included?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The permissions on the certificate template do not allow the current user to enroll for this type of certificate]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576142</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/the-permissions-on-the-certificate-template-do-not-allow-the-current-user-to-enroll-for-this-type-of-certificate/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When requesting an SSL certificate from Active Directory Certificate Services, the process may fail due to a lack of permission for the Web Server template or a template derived from it. This issue can be particularly confusing when the user has administrative privileges.
The permissions on the certificate template do not allow the current user to enroll for this type of certificate first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – SonicWall Global Management System (GMS) & Analytics – Multiple Critical Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32219</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/24/technical-advisory-sonicwall-global-management-system-gms-analytics-multiple-critical-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection Issues Security Filter Bypass – CVE-2023-34133 Description The GMS web application was found to be vulnerable to numerous SQL injection issues. Additionally, security mechanisms that were in place to help prevent against SQL Injection attacks could be bypassed. Impact An unauthenticated attacker could exploit these issues to extract sensitive information, such […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rich Warren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Nosey Parker Update to v0.14.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4794</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/nosey-parker-v0-14-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week we published a new release of Nosey Parker, our fast and low-noise secrets detector. The v0.14.0 release adds significant features that make it easier for a human to review findings, and a number of smaller features and changes that improve signal-to-noise. The full release notes are available here. Release highlights File names and […]
The post Announcing Nosey Parker Update to v0.14.0 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-dark-web-threat-hunting-blockchain-forensics</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-dark-web-threat-hunting-blockchain-forensics?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence course will teach you how to effectively anticipate, prevent, and mitigate potential cybercrime threats, while also helping law enforcement agencies and governments to combat cybercrime and prosecute cybercriminals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-dark-web-threat-hunting-blockchain-forensics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-dark-web-threat-hunting-blockchain-forensics/?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence course will teach you how to effectively anticipate, prevent, and mitigate potential cybercrime threats, while also helping law enforcement agencies and governments to combat cybercrime and prosecute cybercriminals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Security Awareness: Managing Human Risk Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-security-awareness-managing-human-risk-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-security-awareness-managing-human-risk-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Security Awareness: Managing Human Risk Summit 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-cybercrime-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-cybercrime-intelligence?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence course will teach you how to effectively anticipate, prevent, and mitigate potential cybercrime threats, while also helping law enforcement agencies and governments to combat cybercrime and prosecute cybercriminals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juplink RX4-1500 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2158</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/08/23/juplink-rx4-1500-stack-based-buffer-overflow-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T21:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-b5185f25 A stack-based buffer overflow exists in Juplink RX4-1500, a WiFi router. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to achieve code execution as root. Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-b5185f25 MITRE: CVE-2023-41028 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:A/AC:L/Au:S/C:C/I:C/A:C CVSSv2 Score: 7.7 Vendor References The affected product is end-of-life and no patches are available. Discovery Credit Exodus Intelligence Disclosure Timeline ... Read more Juplink RX4-1500 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability
The post Juplink RX4-1500 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten sed command examples]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576130</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/ten-sed-command-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to manipulate text in Linux using the powerful sed command. This post covers sed command examples of finding and replacing text based on text matching, case-insensitive operations and position, deleting lines based on position and pattern, appending text, writing to a new file, and printing specific lines.
Ten sed command examples first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-35150: Arbitrary Code Injection in XWiki.org XWiki]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64e508402d244533b97a0bce</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/8/22/cve-2023-35150-arbitrary-code-injection-in-xwikiorg-xwiki"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Simon Humbert and Lucas Miller of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in the XWiki free wiki software platform. This bug was originally discovered by Michael Hamann with public Proof-of-Concept (PoC) code provided by Manuel Leduc. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an authenticated attacker to perform an arbitrary code injection on affected systems. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2023-35150, with a few minimal modifications.
A code injection vulnerability has been reported in the XWiki.Org XWiki. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation when rendering a link in the Invitation Application.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeaPFRogging PFR Implementations]]></title>
        <id>https://ncc-blog.pixelpreview.net/?p=26709</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/23/leapfrogging-pfr-implementations/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T13:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in October of 2022, this announcement by AMI caught my eye. AMI has contributed a product named “Tektagon Open Edition” to the Open Compute Project (OCP).  Tektagon OpenEdition is an open-source Platform Root of Trust (PRoT) solution with foundational firmware security features that detect platform firmware corruption, recover the firmware and protect firmware integrity. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Boone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bishop Fox Recap - Hacker Summer Camp 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/bishop-fox-recap-hacker-summer-camp-2023</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/bishop-fox-recap-hacker-summer-camp-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a Bishop Fox recap of the 2023 Hacker Summer Camp in Las Vegas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Engineer’s Guide to Blockchain Finality]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104911</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/23/the-engineers-guide-to-blockchain-finality/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T11:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Benjamin Samuels Many security-critical off-chain applications use a simple block delay to determine finality: the point at which a transaction becomes immutable in a blockchain’s ledger (and is impossible to “undo” without extreme economic cost). But this is inadequate for most networks, and can become a single point of failure for the centralized exchanges, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to a create a Kubernetes Secret]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576107</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-a-create-a-kubernetes-secret/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T14:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Kubernetes Secret is a resource that is used to store sensitive information, such as passwords, authentication tokens, API keys, and TLS certificates, within a cluster. Storing such information in plain text is problematic, which is why a Secret can be used instead of Kubernetes ConfigMaps.
How to a create a Kubernetes Secret first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dancing Offbit: The Story of a Single Character Typo that Broke a ChaCha-Based PRNG]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30601</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/22/dancing-offbit-the-story-of-a-single-character-typo-that-broke-a-chacha-based-prng/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Random number generators are the backbone of most cryptographic protocols, the crucial cornerstone upon which the security of all systems rely, yet they remain often overlooked. This blog post presents a real-world vulnerability discovered in the implementation of a Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) based on the ChaCha20 cipher. Discovery of a biased PRNG During a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Bottinelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Details of CVE-2023-30988 - IBM Facsimile Support Privilege Escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/08/22/2023-08-22-Facsimile-Support-CVE-2023-30988/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/08/22/2023-08-22-Facsimile-Support-CVE-2023-30988/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preface]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silent Signal Techblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The most hated man on the internet. Lessons to learn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27455</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/the-most-hated-man-on-the-internet-lessons-to-learn/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago I was scouring Netflix and stumbled across the 2022 The most hated man on the internet docuseries. What’s that all about then? The show is about Hunter Moore […]
The most hated man on the internet. Lessons to learn first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus Crossley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Penumbra Labs R1CS Implementation Review]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32669</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/21/public-report-penumbra-labs-r1cs-implementation-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T15:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2023 Penumbra Labs engaged NCC Group’s Cryptography Services team to perform an implementation review of their Rank-1 Constraint System (R1CS) code and the associated zero-knowledge proofs within the Penumbra system. These proofs are built upon decaf377 and poseidon377, which have been previously audited by NCC Group, with a corresponding public report. The review […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Henry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New features in Windows 11 23H2]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576088</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-features-in-windows-11-23h2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T15:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Windows update, which Microsoft refers to as a big annual update, is Windows 11 23H2. It will offer numerous new features, which I will discuss in this article. Microsoft has not yet announced the release date; however, we expect to see it in September or October 2023.
New features in Windows 11 23H2 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security For Everyone - 2023 Update]]></title>
        <id>64df49ab6a136707b78d65a2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/security-for-everyone-zth05/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T10:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will go through some of the steps you can take as an individual to secure the accounts that mean the most to you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope for the Best, Prepare for the Worst: How to prepare for cloud DFIR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/hope-for-the-best-prepare-for-the-worst-how-to-prepare-for-cloud-dfir</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/hope-for-the-best-prepare-for-the-worst-how-to-prepare-for-cloud-dfir?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[n this blog post, we provide specific steps that can be taken to significantly improve your organization's cloud incident response efficiency and efficacy. We focused on expanding cloud logging capabilities, providing access and resources to responders, and developing an understanding of your cloud environment. This list is by no means exhaustive, and is instead meant to provide a starting point for your cloud DFIR journey, and strengthen your organization’s overall security posture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MBR2GPT: Convert MBR to GPT]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576074</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/mbr2gpt-convert-mbr-to-gpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T17:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to convert a Master Boot Record (MBR) to a GUID partition table (GPT) using the MBR2GPT tool.
MBR2GPT: Convert MBR to GPT first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying Multivariate Cryptography]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32537</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/18/demystifying-multivariate-cryptography/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T16:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the name suggests, multivariate cryptography refers to a class of public-key cryptographic schemes that use multivariate polynomials over a finite field. Solving systems of multivariate polynomials is known to be NP-complete, thus multivariate constructions are top contenders for post-quantum cryptography standards. In fact, 11 out of the 50 submissions for NIST’s call for additional […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>smarkelon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Cloud Security Exchange 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloud-security-exchange-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloud-security-exchange-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out these graphic recordings created in real-time throughout the event for SANS Cloud Security Exchange 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethical Hackers Are Helping Security Leaders Navigate the Budget Crunch]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/ethical-hackers-help-ciso-budget</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/ethical-hackers-help-ciso-budget"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders are using ethical hackers to help address strains and challenges in their security programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Intuition for Lattice-Based Signatures – Part 2: Fiat-Shamir with Aborts]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31656</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/17/building-intuition-for-lattice-based-signatures-part-2-fiat-shamir-with-aborts/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This two-part blog series aims to build some intuition for the main techniques that are used to construct lattice-based signatures, focusing in particular on the techniques underlying Falcon and Dilithium, the two lattice-based signature schemes selected for standardization by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST). In part 1 of this two-part blog […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elenabakoslang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Ubuntu packages with the Ansible apt module]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576054</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-ubuntu-packages-with-the-ansible-apt-module/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T13:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the Ansible apt module to manage packages that use the apt package manager on Debian-based Linux distributions, such as Ubuntu. The module allows you to perform all basic package management operations, such as installing, removing, and updating the packages.
Install Ubuntu packages with the Ansible apt module first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Entanglement | DLL Hijacking in the Asian Gambling Sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=83550</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/chinese-entanglement-dll-hijacking-in-the-asian-gambling-sector/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors abuse Adobe Creative Cloud, Edge, and other executables vulnerable to DLL hijacking in campaign targeting the Southeast Asian gambling sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InQL v5: A Technical Deep Dive]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/17/inql-v5.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/17/inql-v5.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to pull back the curtain on the latest iteration of our
widely-used Burp Suite extension - InQL.
Version 5 introduces significant enhancements and upgrades, solidifying its
place as an indispensable tool for penetration testers and bug bounty hunters.
Introduction
The Journey So Far: From Jython to Kotlin    
The Challenges of Converting a Burp Extension Into Kotlin
Sidestepping the need for stickytape
Introducing GQLSpection: The Core of InQL v5.x
New Features    
Points of Interest
Improved Logging
In-line Annotations
The Future of InQL and GraphQL Security
InQL: A Great Project for Students and Contributors
Conclusion



Introduction
The cybersecurity landscape is in a state of constant flux. As GraphQL adoption
surges, the demand for an adaptable, resilient testing tool …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: SMB Pivots With Havoc C2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/554362101d27</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-smb-pivots-with-havoc-c2-554362101d27?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! Today we’re going to talk about some lateral movement techniques with Havoc C2 using SMB pivots. SMB pivots are great for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export certificate as CER, DER, P7B, or PFX]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576032</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/export-certificate-as-cer-der-p7b-or-pfx/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When transferring a certificate to another computer, it is common practice to export it from the cert store and then import it on the target system. The available export formats depend on whether you want to transfer the private key as well and whether the private key is exportable.
Export certificate as CER, DER, P7B, or PFX first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Track installer changes, improve PC performance with Mirekusoft Install Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576015</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/track-installer-changes-impove-pc-performance-with-mirekusoft-install-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirekusoft Install Monitor allows you to track all changes made to your system by a Windows installer. The tool helps improve PC performance through proactive system monitoring and thorough uninstallation features. You can easily manage startup programs, and the Install Monitor's backup feature allows you to restore a previous version of an application after an upgrade.
Track installer changes, improve PC performance with Mirekusoft Install Monitor first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Approximately 2000 Citrix NetScalers backdoored in mass-exploitation campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32628</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/15/approximately-2000-citrix-netscalers-backdoored-in-mass-exploitation-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fox-IT (part of NCC Group) has uncovered a large-scale exploitation campaign of Citrix NetScalers in a joint effort with the Dutch Institute of Vulnerability Disclosure (DIVD). An adversary appears to have exploited CVE-2023-3519 in an automated fashion, placing webshells on vulnerable NetScalers to gain persistent access. The adversary can execute arbitrary commands with this webshell, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Global Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Ready for the New NIST Control Around Public Disclosure Programs?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-vdp-control</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-vdp-control"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new NIST control requires SaaS vendors to “establish a public reporting channel for receiving reports of vulnerabilities in organizational systems and system components.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blake Entrekin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 cloud backup]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575994</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-11-cloud-backup/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May 2023, Microsoft announced a cloud-powered OS Backup and Restore for Windows 11. The initial version was released in Windows 11 version 23466 and is referred to as Windows Backup.
Windows 11 cloud backup first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you pass the Rekt test?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104675</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/14/can-you-pass-the-rekt-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T08:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the biggest challenges for blockchain developers is objectively assessing their security posture and measuring how it progresses. To address this issue, a working group of Web3 security experts, led by Trail of Bits CEO Dan Guido, met earlier this year to create a simple test for profiling the security of blockchain teams. We […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scorpion CBS show. Plane hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27384</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/scorpion-cbs-show-plane-hack/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T05:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having got on a bit of a roll with dismantling plane hacking in the media with the MH370 documentary critique, it’s probably time to tear apart the pilot episode of […]
Scorpion CBS show. Plane hack first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Die Hard 2. Or how not to hack airplanes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27406</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/die-hard-2-or-how-not-to-hack-airplanes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T05:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How could I criticise possibly the best action movie series of all time? Well, it’s to help dispel myths about hacking planes. TV shows and films help set a narrative […]
Die Hard 2. Or how not to hack airplanes first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAPS 2.0 Internals]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/LAPSv2-Internals/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/LAPSv2-Internals/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T10:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, LAPS 2.0 was released by Microsoft, and thankfully it now comes built-in to Windows. This time it comes ready for use with Active Directory, as well as being supported in Azure AD aka Entra ID. In this post, we’ll look at how LAPS 2.0 for Active Directory works under the hood, so you can make those fresh recommendations to your clients, and prepare yourself for the inevitable question... “But we just deployed LAPS.. what does LAPS 2.0 do differently?!”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Function: Decrypting Azure Function App Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=30784</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/cloud-penetration-testing/what-the-function-decrypting-azure-function-app-keys/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying an Azure Function App, access to supporting Storage Accounts can lead to disclosure of source code, command execution in the app, and decryption of the app’s Access Keys.
The post What the Function: Decrypting Azure Function App Keys  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Elling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Git/GitHub beginner tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575983</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/a-gitgithub-beginner-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:32:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a popular version control system in the DevOps world, and GitHub is an online platform where developers can collaborate with their Git repositories. In this Git/GitHub beginner's tutorial, you'll learn how to get started without requiring any new knowledge about version control systems.
A Git/GitHub beginner tutorial first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SysPWN – VR for Pwn2Own]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32581</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/11/syspwn-vr-for-pwn2own/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T08:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Plaskett (@alexjplaskett) presented a talk on the 10th of August 2023 at @SysPWN covering vulnerability research for Pwn2Own. The first section of the talk covered a high-level perspective of the event, personal history, and teams. It then discussed some considerations needing to be made when deciding on target, experiences, and learnings from the competition. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Plaskett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brand-New Course LDR521: Security Culture for Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/brand-new-course-ldr521-security-culture-for-leaders</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/brand-new-course-ldr521-security-culture-for-leaders?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SANS Security Culture course has been significantly updated - everything from the name of the course to the content, labs, and handouts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SanerNow: Detect security anomalies]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575854</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sanernow-detect-security-anomalies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SanerNow's Continuous Posture Anomaly Management (CPAM) allows you to detect misconfigurations and security anomalies using machine learning and deep analysis. With the myriad of devices and infrastructure configurations that organizations have spread across on-premises and hybrid cloud environments, it's challenging to provide visibility to your security posture in a consolidated, seamless way using traditional tools.
SanerNow: Detect security anomalies first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Site Takeover via SCCM’s AdminService API]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d932e22b2bf</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/site-takeover-via-sccms-adminservice-api-d932e22b2bf?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T17:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tl:dr: The SCCM AdminService API is vulnerable to NTLM relaying and can be abused for SCCM site takeover.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garrett Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Konstellation: A Tool for RBACpacking in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4760</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/introducing-konstellation-for-rbacpacking-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T13:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author presented this paper and corresponding tool at Black Hat: Arsenal 2023 on August 10, 2023. For a more general overview of Konstellation and its capabilities vis a vis Kubernetes RBAC, please see our earlier companion post.  Kubernetes Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) is a mechanism for controlling access to resources in a Kubernetes cluster. […]
The post Konstellation: A Tool for RBACpacking in Kubernetes appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New techniques and tools for web race conditions]]></title>
        <id>new-techniques-and-tools-for-web-race-conditions</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/new-techniques-and-tools-for-web-race-conditions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T06:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For too long, web race-condition attacks have focused on a tiny handful of scenarios. Testing for them is inherently unreliable, compounded by known challenges relating to time constraints and network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Thinking Episode 31: Alex Chapman - The Man of Many Crits]]></title>
        <id>https://ajxchapman.github.io/media/2023/08/10/ctbb.html</id>
        <link href="https://ajxchapman.github.io/media/2023/08/10/ctbb.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chapman's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Blog Series - Blog 2: Architecting for Zero Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-blog-2-architecting-zero-trust</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-blog-2-architecting-zero-trust?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Blog Series - Blog 2: Architecting for Zero Trust]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking With Your Nemesis]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7861f75fcab4</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/hacking-with-your-nemesis-7861f75fcab4?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T20:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first post in this series, On (Structured) Data, we talked about the gap area of offensive structured data and ended with the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing the state machine: the true potential of web race conditions]]></title>
        <id>smashing-the-state-machine</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/smashing-the-state-machine"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For too long, web race condition attacks have focused on a tiny handful of scenarios. Their true potential has been masked thanks to tricky workflows, missing tooling, and simple network jitter hiding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SEC Cyber Rules Incentivize Proactive Security Measures]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/new-sec-cybersercurity-rules</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/new-sec-cybersercurity-rules"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently finalized a regulation that imposes increased transparency related to cybersecurity risk management, governance, and incidents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleep computer (remotely) from the command line]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575833</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sleep-computer-remotely-from-the-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T15:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, you might want to send a computer into power-saving mode remotely or from the command line. The onboard utilities offer limited options for this, and PowerShell offers none at all. As alternatives, two free utilities from Microsoft's Sysinternals and NirSoft get the job done.
Sleep computer (remotely) from the command line first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advisory | NetModule Router Software Race Condition Leads to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://pentest.blog/?p=2687</id>
        <link href="https://pentest.blog/advisory-netmodule-router-software-race-condition-leads-to-remote-code-execution/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T12:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction NetModule Router Software (NRSW) is a Linux-based software solution developed by NetModule for managing data connections across various devices. It applies to a various devices, including stationary and mobile routers, gateways, and IoT devices. NRSW provides consistent configuration processes and functions across all NetModule devices. It includes security features and supports over-the-air updates. NetModule […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nuri Çilengir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use our suite of eBPF libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104838</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/09/use-our-suite-of-ebpf-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg Trail of Bits has developed a suite of open-source libraries designed to streamline the creation and deployment of eBPF applications. These libraries facilitate efficient process and network event monitoring, function tracing, kernel debug symbol parsing, and eBPF code generation. Previously, deploying portable, dependency-free eBPF applications posed significant challenges due to Linux kernel […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PNG Steganography from First Principles]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/png-steganography/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/png-steganography/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T10:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steganography is experiencing a revival as a wrapper for delivering payloads. In this post we'll go back to basics and show just how steganography can be applied to a PNG image using the common least significant bit (LSB) encoding technique. No magic... just raw information... and a little C++.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Citrix Workspace with SecureAuth’s Arculix: A New Standard in Passwordless Continuous Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=49115</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/enhancing-citrix-workspace-with-secureauths-arculix-a-new-standard-in-passwordless-continuous-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T10:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This was co-authored by Faranak Talebi, Integrations Engineer at SecureAuth. In the digital era, the seamless integration of various platforms is crucial for efficient and secure operations. SecureAuth’s Arculix, an award-winning platform in next-gen passwordless continuous authentication, is setting new standards in this domain. Today, we announce how Arculix enhances the capabilities of Citrix […]
The post Enhancing Citrix Workspace with SecureAuth’s Arculix: A New Standard in Passwordless Continuous Authentication appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Badge of Shame - Breaking Into Secure Facilities with OSDP]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/breaking-into-secure-facilities-with-osdp</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/breaking-into-secure-facilities-with-osdp"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about five exploitable vulnerabilities we've identified in OSDP and share what defenders can do about them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Petro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability disclosure in aviation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27409</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/vulnerability-disclosure-in-aviation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T05:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We joined Boeing and United Airlines on a panel recently at the RSA Conference to talk about vulnerability disclosure in the aviation world. The engagement we are now seeing between […]
Vulnerability disclosure in aviation first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Engineer Salary, Skills, and Career Path]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/network-engineer-salary-skills-and-career-path</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/network-engineer-salary-skills-and-career-path?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about a network engineer's salary, skills, and career path]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco call handler with Cisco Unity Connection messaging]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575699</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/cisco-call-handler-with-cisco-unity-connection-messaging/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T20:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many businesses rely on a caller attendant to manage or route phone calls for their business or call center. If you have ever called a business and received an automated greeting like "Press 1 for Sales, press 2 for Accounting," you have encountered a caller attendant. In a previous article, we looked at the components of the Cisco Unified Communication Manager System. In this article, we will dive deeper and look at how the caller handler is built using Cisco Unity Connection Server.
Cisco call handler with Cisco Unity Connection messaging first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The August 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64cc1aed8ada730e80dab699</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/8/8/the-august-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T17:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings from hacker summer camp! Black Hat and DEFCON start this week, but let’s kick everything off with Patch Tuesday and the latest security offerings from Adobe and Microsoft. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. If you’d rather watch the video recap, you can check it out here.
Adobe Patches for August 2023
For August, Adobe released four patches addressing 37 CVEs in Adobe Acrobat and Reader, Commerce, Dimension, and the Adobe XMP Toolkit SDK. A total of 28 of these CVEs came through the ZDI program. The update for Reader is the largest, clocking in with 30 CVEs. The most severe of these are rated Critical and would allow code execution when opening a specially crafted PDF. The update for Commerce fixe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BloodHound Community Edition: A New Era]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d64689806e90</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/bloodhound-community-edition-a-new-era-d64689806e90?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel BIOS Advisory – Memory Corruption in HID Drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32552</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/08/intel-bios-advisory-memory-corruption-in-hid-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T12:28:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I will be focusing on two additional BIOS vulnerabilities. The first bug impacts the Bluetooth keyboard driver (HidKbDxe in BluetoothPkg) and the second bug impacts a touch panel driver (I2cTouchPanelDxe in AlderLakePlatSamplePkg).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Boone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing BitSight Automation Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=15881</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/08/08/introducing-bitsight-automation-tool/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glossary Entity A part of an organization that can be assessed as a single figure. Subsidiary Same as an Entity on BitSight’s side. Group Cluster A complex. It can contain entities/subsidiaries, or Groups, or more Group Clusters. Group A structure that can contain Entities. Glossary Introduction In this blog post you will be introduced to … Continue reading Introducing BitSight Automation Tool →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantinos Papanagnou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne and the OWASP Top 10 for LLM: A Powerful Alliance for Secure AI]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/owasp-llm-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/owasp-llm-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is HackerOne’s perspective on the Top 10 list for LLM vulnerabilities and how organizations can prevent these critical security risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manjesh S.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resultant Set of Policy (RSoP), Group Policy Results, and Group Policy Modeling]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575444</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/resultant-set-of-policy-rsop-group-policy-results-and-group-policy-modeling/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T15:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Resultant Set of Policy (RSOP) snap-in of the Microsoft Management Console (MCC) helps troubleshoot Group Policy settings. Group Policy Results and Group Policy Modeling are the corresponding features of the Group Policy Management Console (GPMC).
Resultant Set of Policy (RSoP), Group Policy Results, and Group Policy Modeling first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comrades in Arms? | North Korea Compromises Sanctioned Russian Missile Engineering Company]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=83314</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/comrades-in-arms-north-korea-compromises-sanctioned-russian-missile-engineering-company/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean threat actors attempt to further missile program by compromising sanctioned Russian defense company with OpenCarrot backdoor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Role of Mentorship in Cyber Threat Intelligence (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-role-of-mentorship-in-cyber-threat-intelligence-part-2-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-role-of-mentorship-in-cyber-threat-intelligence-part-2-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we can all benefit from professional mentorship, mentoring needs will vary from person to person based largely on where they are in their career. In this blog series we introduced mentorship concepts, the role and responsibilities of mentors and mentees, and provided resources on areas to engage to find prospective mentors, both formally through organizational program and through industry specific events or initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis and Exploitation of CVE-2023-3519]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/analysis-exploitation-cve-2023-3519</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/analysis-exploitation-cve-2023-3519"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our latest blog offers additional analysis and exploitation of CVE-2023-3519, a critical remote code execution vulnerability in Citrix ADC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Gross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What To Expect When You’re “Expecting” — Purple Team Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c6879655fe1</id>
        <link href="https://cedowens.medium.com/what-to-expect-when-youre-expecting-purple-team-edition-c6879655fe1?source=rss-fd791048dac0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T20:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post describes how “expect” routines can be used to help make Purple Team exercises more efficient and repeatable. In particular…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Owens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Fall 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2153</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/08/04/public-mobile-exploitation-training-fall-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T16:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Exploitation Training We are pleased to announce that the researchers of Exodus Intelligence will be providing publicly available training in person on November 14 2023 in London, England. This 4 day course is designed to provide students with both an overview of the Android attack surface and an in-depth understanding of advanced vulnerability and exploitation topics. Attendees ... Read more Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Fall 2023
The post Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Fall 2023 appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Browser Exploitation Training – Fall 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2154</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/08/04/public-browser-exploitation-training-fall-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T16:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browser Exploitation Training We are pleased to announce that the researchers of Exodus Intelligence will be providing publicly available training in person on November 14 2023 in London, England. This 4 day course is designed to provide students with both an overview of the current state of the browser attack surface and an in-depth understanding of advanced vulnerability ... Read more Public Browser Exploitation Training – Fall 2023
The post Public Browser Exploitation Training – Fall 2023 appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find enabled local Group Policy settings with rsop.msc and PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575415</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-enabled-local-group-policy-settings-with-rsopmsc-and-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T15:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to GPO troubleshooting, you might want to find settings that are configured by local Group Policy. With rsop.msc, a graphical tool is available for this purpose. However, it is generally more efficient to generate a report using gpresult.exe and evaluate it with PowerShell.
Find enabled local Group Policy settings with rsop.msc and PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>