<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-10-20T00:51:24.660Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond good ol’ Run key, Part 143]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9551</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/10/19/beyond-good-ol-run-key-part-143/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This entry is a bit convoluted, but it’s still quite interesting. I have discovered it today only to google around and find out someone posted the info about it back in 2013. So, I will describe what they did in … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[advpack.dll and IEAdvpack.dll logging capability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9547</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/10/19/advpack-dll-and-ieadvpack-dll-logging-capability/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a very old hack out there that enables logging for the advpack.dll and IEAdvpack.dll DLLs. Many of their functions include the logging, so enabling this may help to pick up some old-school forensic logs. Of course, the value … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Obfuscation with Permutations]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5702</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/10/18/shellcode-obfuscation-with-permutations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents Introduction Affine Transformation Linear Congruential Generator (LCG) Inversive Congruential Generator (ICG) Modular Multiplication Affine Permutation References Appendix Affine Cipher Affine Hash Modular Involutions 1. Introduction In a previous post on masking, shuffling data was suggested as an … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change AWS EC2 CPU options post launch]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587734</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/change-aws-ec2-cpu-options-post-launch/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T08:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS has recently added the ability to change EC2 CPU options after launch. This feature lets you modify the number of vCPUs and thread configuration of an EC2 instance post-launch. Previously, altering the vCPU count was only feasible when starting a new instance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Process Spectre Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/cross_process_spectre_exploitation.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/cross_process_spectre_exploitation.php"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, researcher Johannes Wikner details the first end-to-end cross-process Spectre exploit against a real userland target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Process Spectre Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/cross_process_spectre_exploitation.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/cross_process_spectre_exploitation.php"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, researcher Johannes Wikner details the first end-to-end cross-process Spectre exploit against a real userland target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 24.10: Gnome 47, Kernel 6.11, APT 3.0 and more]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587768</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/ubuntu-2410-gnome-47-kernel-611-apt-30-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 24.10 has arrived, offering a range of new features, updates, and enhancements. As a non-LTS (Long Term Support) release, it provides only nine months of support for updates and fixes, unlike the extended support period available for LTS versions. However, despite its shorter support duration, Ubuntu 24.10 delivers a host of impressive features, making it a standout release for users seeking the latest in cutting-edge technology. Additionally, this release celebrates 20 years since Ubuntu's debut and includes special anniversary-themed Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convert to Azure Premium SSD v2 Disks with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587683</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/convert-to-azure-premium-ssd-v2-disks-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Premium SSD v2 disks, currently in public preview, provide enhanced throughput and IOPS at a lower cost than earlier versions. You can convert existing disks to Premium SSD v2 using PowerShell. However, it's crucial to understand the specific limitations and requirements beforehand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Influence Ops | Twisting Tales of Volt Typhoon at Home and Abroad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=107173</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/chinas-influence-ops-twisting-tales-of-volt-typhoon-at-home-and-abroad/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's CVERC attempts to attribute Volt Typhoon activities to the U.S., but the fact-free claims reveal much about the PRC's real agenda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dakota Cary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 State of ICS/OT Cybersecurity: Our Past and Our Future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-2024-state-of-ics-ot-cybersecurity-our-past-and-our-future</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-2024-state-of-ics-ot-cybersecurity-our-past-and-our-future?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 State of ICS/OT report shows our industry’s growth since 2019 and offers insight into how we may improve going into 2029.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICS/OT Cybersecurity & AI: Considerations for Now and the Future (Part II)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ics-ot-cybersecurity-ai-considerations-for-now-and-the-future-part-ii</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ics-ot-cybersecurity-ai-considerations-for-now-and-the-future-part-ii?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating AI into ICS/OT cybersecurity and engineering processes presents opportunities for enhanced efficiency, resiliency, and safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying SQL Injections in a GraphQL API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3206</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/identifying-sql-injections-in-a-graphql-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T19:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Many vulnerabilities in modern web applications occur due to the improper handling of user-supplied input. Command injection, cross-site scripting, XML External Entity (XXE) injections, and SQL injections all emerge from the downstream effects of unsanitized user input. SQL injection has held a high-ranking spot on the OWASP top 10 list since its inception. Despite […]
The post Identifying SQL Injections in a GraphQL API appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenneth King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix public Wi-Fi error “msftconnecttest.com  – This site can’t be reached”]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587754</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/fix-public-wi-fi-error-msftconnecttestcom-this-site-cant-be-reached/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When connecting to a public Wi-Fi, such as in a hotel or airport, Windows automatically tests the connection by accessing msftconnecttest.com. If the network provider requires your registration, you may encounter an error when accessing msftconnecttest.com instead of being redirected to the intended captive portal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudGoat: New Scenario and Walkthrough (sns_secrets)]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25394</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/cloudgoat-sns_secrets/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CloudGoat: New Scenario and Walkthrough (sns_secrets) appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Ramsbey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Early Cascade Injection: From Windows Process Creation to Stealthy Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=4697</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2024/10/15/introducing-early-cascade-injection-from-windows-process-creation-to-stealthy-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Guido Miggelenbrink at Outflank
Introduction
In this blog post we introduce a novel process injection technique named Early Cascade Injection, explore Windows process creation, and identify how several Endpoint Detection and Response systems (EDRs) initialize their in-process detection capabilities. This new Early Cascade Injection technique targets the user-mode part of process creation and combines elements of the well-known Early Bird APC Injection technique with the recently published EDR-Preloading technique by Marcus Hutchins [1]. Unlike Early Bird APC Injection, this new technique avoids queuing cross-process Asynchronous Procedure Calls (APCs), while having minimal remote process interaction. This makes Early Cascade Injection a stealthy process injection technique that is effective against top tier EDRs while avoiding detection.

To provide insights into Early Cascade Injection’s internals,
Tags: Early Cascade injection, EarlyCascade, EDR Evasion, EDR userland initialisation, EDR-Preloading, Injection, Windows process ceation
Read full post
The post Introducing Early Cascade Injection: From Windows Process Creation to Stealthy Injection appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dima van de Wouw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off the Fox Den Bookshelf: Security and Tech Books We Love]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/2024-security-tech-books</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/2024-security-tech-books"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've polled our team and are back with our 2024 cybersecurity book recommendations to help you level up your cybersecurity skills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BEC-ware the phish (part 1). Investigating incidents in M365]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29874</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/bec-ware-the-phish-part-1-investigating-incidents-in-m365/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Review the key artefacts to ensure the best possible telemetry is available in the case of a Business Email Compromise (BEC). Keep an eye on data retention, where necessary […]
BEC-ware the phish (part 1). Investigating incidents in M365 first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Rabin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use HackerOne’s Global Vulnerability Policy Map]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/public-policy/global-vulnerability-policy-map</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/public-policy/global-vulnerability-policy-map"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T22:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use HackerOne's Global Vulnerability Policy Map to keep up with evolving VDP mandates and recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Woolslayer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Active Directory from compromised passwords with Enzoic 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587655</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/protecting-active-directory-from-compromised-passwords-with-enzoic-35/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T15:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For organizations utilizing Active Directory infrastructure, having a tool to identify commonly used or compromised passwords is important both for securing your environment and complying with the newest guidelines from NIST, HITRUST, NYDFS, and others. Enzoic for Active Directory 3.5 introduces new features that assist organizations in detecting weak or compromised passwords and implementing enhanced complexity requirements for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sweet16 – the oldbin lolbin called setup16.exe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9516</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/10/12/the-sweet16-the-oldbin-lolbin-called-setup16-exe/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t even know how to start. I wrote about old InstallShield setup before, and today’s topic is very similar – the old, yet still present setup file residing (on Win10, 11) in the following location: c:\windows\SysWOW64\setup16.exe Running it gives … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Council Adopts Cyber Resilience Act]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/public-policy/eu-council-cyber-resilience-act</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/public-policy/eu-council-cyber-resilience-act"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T21:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the EU Council's Cyber Resilience Act, where we're headed, and what we believe should happen next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authd: Cloud-Based OIDC authentication for Ubuntu Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587526</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/authd-cloud-based-oidc-authentication-for-ubuntu-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Historically, Linux daemons such as SSSD (System Security Services Daemon) have facilitated access to remote identity and authentication services like LDAP, Kerberos, FreeIPA, and Active Directory. Authd, recently announced for general availability, takes this approach further by harnessing the cloud. Authd, with initial integration for Microsoft’s Entra ID (previously known as Azure AD), introduces capabilities such as multi-factor authentication (MFA) and conditional access to your local setup. Currently, it is available exclusively for Ubuntu desktops and servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measure Your AI Risk Preparedness with This Interactive Self-Assessment Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/ai-security-readiness-quiz</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/ai-security-readiness-quiz"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HackerOne's AI Risk Readiness Self-Assessment Tool helps measure your AI security and compliance preparedness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Windows Server 2025 S2D cluster lab with Hyper-V and PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587352</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/build-a-windows-server-2025-s2d-cluster-lab-with-hyper-v-and-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To explore Storage Spaces Direct (S2D) in Windows Server 2025, you can set up a lab environment using virtual machines with Hyper-V and PowerShell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing Gradio 5, Hugging Face’s ML GUI framework]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108392</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/10/10/auditing-gradio-5-hugging-faces-ml-gui-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a joint post with the Hugging Face Gradio team; read their announcement here! You can find the full report with all of the detailed findings from our security audit of Gradio 5 here. Hugging Face hired Trail of Bits to audit Gradio 5, a popular open-source library that provides a web interface that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imposter syndrome in cyber security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29836</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/imposter-syndrome-in-cyber-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Imposter syndrome is the belief that you are undeserving of your achievements Anyone can be affected by it There are ways to cope What is imposter syndrome? Imposter syndrome […]
Imposter syndrome in cyber security first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Recruitment Process: What to Expect When You Apply at HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/recruitment-process-what-expect-when-you-apply-hackerone</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/recruitment-process-what-expect-when-you-apply-hackerone"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T22:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer Managed Planned Failover for Azure Storage using PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587313</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/customer-managed-planned-failover-for-azure-storage-using-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T19:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently, in Preview, the Customer Managed Planned Failover feature allows you to manage and execute a planned failover of your Azure Storage account. This guide demonstrates how to perform this using PowerShell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentesting for Internal Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/internal-network-pentests</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/internal-network-pentests"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T17:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to optimize internal network pentesting through community-driven pentesting as a service (PTaaS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul De Baldo V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to handle vulnerability reports in aviation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29855</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-to-handle-vulnerability-reports-in-aviation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Always thank researchers for reporting vulnerabilities. Acknowledging their efforts can set the right tone. Lead all communications with researchers. Don’t let legal or PR teams take over. Provide regular […]
How to handle vulnerability reports in aviation first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PTP Aviation Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Insights from Steve Sims' Keynote on the Current Threat Landscape and AI in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/key-insights-from-steve-sims-keynote-on-the-current-threat-landscape-and-ai-in-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/key-insights-from-steve-sims-keynote-on-the-current-threat-landscape-and-ai-in-cybersecurity?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations must stay vigilant and continuously adapt their security strategies to address both the opportunities and challenges presented by AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How an IDOR Vulnerability Led to User Profile Modification]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/idor-vulnerability-deep-dive</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/idor-vulnerability-deep-dive"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T20:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the ins and outs of IDOR vulnerabilities and how one exploitation led to malicious user profile modification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Pratt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The October 2024 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:670568dfdef3e375888ba8fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/10/8/the-october-2024-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the spooky season, and there’s nothing spookier than security patches – at least in my world. Microsoft and Adobe have released their latest patches, and no bones about it, there are some skeletons in those closets. Take a break from your regular activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts. If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for October 2024
For October, Adobe released nine patches addressing 52 CVEs in Adobe Substance 3D Painter, Commerce, Dimension, Animate, Lightroom, InCopy, InDesign, Substance 3D Stager, and Adobe FrameMaker. Two of these bugs were submitted through the ZDI program. The largest and most urgent of these patches covers 22 CVEs in Adobe Commerce, which i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 24H2 Group Policy: 81 new settings for SMB, updates, printing, Defender, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587383</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-11-24h2-group-policy-81-new-settings-for-smb-updates-printing-defender-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T15:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 24H2 introduces several Group Policy settings to manage its new features centrally. Windows Defender receives 26 new settings, and many focus on enhancing SMB security. The new settings also control reboots after updates and the transition to Windows Protected Print.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: The Electric Energy Consumption Of LLMs – No GPU]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10565</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/10/08/quickpost-the-electric-energy-consumption-of-llms-no-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend asked me if I had used a GPU for my tests described in blog post “Quickpost: The Electric Energy Consumption Of LLMs”. Because he had tried running an LLM on a machine without GPU, and it was too slow. I did a quick test, just redoing previous test but without GPU (by setting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS S3 Conditional Writes: The –if-none-match parameter]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587298</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/aws-s3-conditional-writes-the-if-none-match-parameter/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T16:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS has recently introduced support for conditional writes in S3 storage. This feature enables S3 to verify whether an object exists before creating it, which helps prevent accidental overwriting of existing objects during data uploads. This capability is particularly useful for distributed applications that simultaneously access and write data to S3. In this article, I will showcase how to use the newly introduced --if-none-match parameter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: The Electric Energy Consumption Of LLMs]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10545</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/10/06/quickpost-the-electric-energy-consumption-of-llms/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T19:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve read claims that AI queries require a lot of energy. Today I heard another claim on the Nerdland Podcast (a popular science podcast here in Belgium): “letting ChatGPT write an email of 100 words requires 70 Wh” (if you’re interested, that’s said at 00:28:05 in this episode). I though to myself: that’s a lot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server 2025 Network ATC: Automatically configure networks in a cluster using intends]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587099</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-server-2025-automatically-configure-networks-in-a-cluster-with-network-atc/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up management, compute, and storage networks in a Windows cluster can be challenging and error-prone. Network ATC automates this process. Available in Azure Stack HCI since version 21H2, it is now integrated into Windows Server 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HUMINT and its Role within Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/humint-and-its-role-within-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/humint-and-its-role-within-cybersecurity?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog explores HUMINT's role in cybersecurity, detailing its implementation, benefits, and potential risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP ModSecurity: Web Application Firewall (WAF) for IIS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587242</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/owasp-modsecurity-web-application-firewall-waf-for-iis/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T22:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP ModSecurity is an open-source Web Application Firewall (WAF) that protects web servers from common attacks. ModSecurity inspects all incoming requests to prevent attacks such as Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), SQL Injection, or Remote Code Execution. The software supports Apache, Nginx, and IIS on Windows Server. This guide demonstrates how to set up the firewall on a Windows Server 2025. You'll need to use version 2.9.7 since newer versions (3.x and above) are not yet available for Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Fuzzing: A Dav1d Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/10/effective-fuzzing-dav1d-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/10/effective-fuzzing-dav1d-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw);.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-8>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-0>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-2>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-1>li:before{content:"\0025cb   …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Pwn2Own Automotive: More Autel Maxicharger Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66fd98460cdf9c480a4f9050</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/10/2/from-pwn2own-automotive-more-autel-maxicharger-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post highlights two additional vulnerabilities in the Autel Maxicharger that were exploited at Pwn2Own Automotive 2024. Details of the patches are also included.
Autel has been informed and has deployed a firmware update (v1.35) to address both of these issues. If you want to read about other Autel bugs reported at Pwn2Own, you check out our earlier blog here.
The First Vulnerability: CVE-2024-23967 (ZDI-CAN-23230)
Researchers from Computest Sector 7 identified and exploited a stack-based buffer overflow in v1.32 of the Autel firmware. This vulnerability stems from the decoding of base64 encoded data that can be controlled by an attacker. The encoded data is decoded into a fixed-size stack buffer with no bounds checks, leading to a stack buffer overflow and remote code execution.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Guids to guide the ID of samples’ capabilities or unique (attributable) properties…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9496</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/10/02/using-guids-to-guide-the-id-of-samples-capabilities-or-unique-attributable-properties/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T23:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago Karsten asked me what tool did I use for GUID extraction. I replied that it was my own old tool written waaaay before yara’s birth. In this post I will elaborate on this bit a bit… … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restore classic context menu in Windows 11 Explorer using Group Policy or PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587175</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/restore-classic-context-menu-in-windows-11-explorer-using-group-policy-or-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alongside the revamped Start Menu, one of the most noticeable changes in Windows 11 is the redesigned context menu in File Explorer. However, these modifications are not merely aesthetic – they also restrict its functionality. You can deploy a registry key using Group Policy Preferences to restore the classic context.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All that JavaScript for… spear phishing?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18719</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/10/02/all-that-javascript-for-spear-phishing/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO employs several hunting rules in multiple Threat Intelligence Platforms and other sources, such as VirusTotal. As you can imagine, there is no lack of APT (Advanced Persistent Threat) campaigns, cybercriminals and their associated malware families and campaigns, phishing, and so on. But now and then, something slightly different and perhaps novel passes by. In … Continue reading All that JavaScript for… spear phishing? →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bart Parys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing the Gaps: How Attack Path Management Improves Vulnerability Management Programs]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/41177a557368</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/closing-the-gaps-how-attack-path-management-improves-vulnerability-management-programs-41177a557368?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In conversation: Pete McKernan & Luke Luckett]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in September]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10543</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/10/02/overview-of-content-published-in-september-8/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content: Here is an overview of content I published in September: SANS ISC Diary entries: Wireshark 4.4: Converting Display Filters to BPF Capture Filters Protected OOXML Text Documents Python & Notepad++ Password Cracking & Energy: More Dedails Wireshark 4.4’s IP Address Functions YARA 4.5.2 Release YARA-X’s Dump Command]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Pollution in Ruby: A Deep Dive into Exploiting Recursive Merges]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/10/02/class-pollution-ruby.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/10/02/class-pollution-ruby.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
In this post, we are going to explore a rarely discussed class of vulnerabilities in Ruby, known as class pollution. This concept is inspired by the idea of prototype pollution in JavaScript, where recursive merges are exploited to poison the prototype of objects, leading to unexpected behaviors. This idea was initially discussed in a blog post about prototype pollution in Python, in which the researcher used recursive merging to poison class variables and eventually global variables via the __globals__ attribute.
In Ruby, we can categorize class pollution into three main cases:
Merge on Hashes: In this scenario, class pollution isn’t possible because the merge operation is confined to the hash itself.
Merge on Attributes (Non-Recursive): Here, we can poison the instance varia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dotnet Source Generators in 2024 Part 1: Getting Started]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/76d619b633f5</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/dotnet-source-generators-in-2024-part-1-getting-started-76d619b633f5?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T18:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Owens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerToys Workspaces: Group Windows apps]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587120</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-powertoys-workspaces-group-windows-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest PowerToys update introduced Workspaces, enabling users to open a group of applications in predefined positions with just one click. This post will explain how to use the Workspaces feature and showcase its key features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing the software supply chain with the SLSA framework]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108366</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/10/01/securing-the-software-supply-chain-with-the-slsa-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Cliff Smith Software supply chain security has been a hot topic since the Solarwinds breach back in 2020. Thanks to the Supply-chain Levels for Software Artifacts (SLSA) framework, the software industry is now at the threshold of sustainably solving many of the biggest challenges in securely building and distributing open-source software. SLSA is a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airbus Navblue Flysmart LPC-NG issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29805</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/airbus-navblue-flysmart-lpc-ng-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T05:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LPC-NG or Less Paper Cockpit – Next Generation is an electronic flight bag (EFB) application offered by Navblue, a part of Airbus. It’s used for calculating engine thrust requirements (perf) on […]
Airbus Navblue Flysmart LPC-NG issues first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PTP Aviation Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing the Grid: Lessons from China's Cyberattacks on U.S. Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/securing-the-grid-lessons-from-chinas-cyberattacks-on-u-s-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/securing-the-grid-lessons-from-chinas-cyberattacks-on-u-s-providers?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revelations about "Salt Typhoon" highlight that cyber threats targeting essential services are not a future concern—they are here and happening now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Find Broken Access Control Vulnerabilities in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/community/find-broken-access-control-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/community/find-broken-access-control-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T18:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the ins and outs of broken access control vulnerabilities and how to find them in your security research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Stevens @hakluke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in the Windows 11 24H2 update: Download and install, AI features, sudo for Windows, checkpoint updates, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587165</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-the-windows-11-24h2-update-download-and-install-ai-features-sudo-for-windows-checkpoint-updates-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T14:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 24H2, the yearly feature update, is now available for high-end AI-capable devices, with a broader rollout to other PCs in the next few weeks. This article explores the features introduced in the update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can you protect your data, privacy, and finances if your phone gets lost or stolen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29775</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-can-you-protect-your-data-privacy-and-finances-if-your-phone-gets-lost-or-stolen/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T05:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steps to take when your device is lost or stolen TL;DR This is a guide to help prepare for a situation where your mobile device is lost or stolen, including […]
How can you protect your data, privacy, and finances if your phone gets lost or stolen? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambros Zannettos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS CloudSecNext Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS CloudSecNext Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIS2: Next Step Forward on EU Security Requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/public-policy/nis2-eu-security-requirements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/public-policy/nis2-eu-security-requirements"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T23:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about the next NIS2 Directive, what it means for you, and how to be compliant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server 2025 upgrade: Feature update versus clean install]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586886</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-server-2025-upgrade-feature-update-versus-clean-install/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T15:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft provides two primary options for migrating to Windows Server 2025: performing a clean install (fresh install, wipe and load) or a feature update (in-place upgrade). Although the upgrade is quicker and less complicated, it is irreversible and comes with a risk of failure. Windows Server 2025 adopts the same upgrade strategy as Windows 11, with Microsoft's recommended method being an in-place update. Terms like feature update, upgrade, and in-place update are used interchangeably.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Evidence Collection: DFIR's 2024 Mobile and Cloud Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/advanced-evidence-collection-dfir-s-2024-mobile-and-cloud-shift</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/advanced-evidence-collection-dfir-s-2024-mobile-and-cloud-shift?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about how the increasing use of mobile and cloud technologies affects digital forensics and incident response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 4 – No Argument Constructor]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66f4669df5bec45c78ea5ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/25/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-4-no-argument-constructor"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of 4 blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details.
In this final part, I ’am going to describe the PowerShell Remoting ConvertViaNoArgumentConstructor conversion mechanism, which I underestimated at the beginning of my research. It allowed me to find 3 more vulnerabilities, even after the Exchange PowerShell attack surface had been significantly hardened by switching to a strict allow list of types. The vulnerabilities I found were:  
•	CVE-2023-36050 – XXE (File Read)
•	CVE-2023-36039 – NTLM Relaying
•	CVE-2023-36035 – NTLM Relaying  
At least at that time, Microsoft was taking seriously NTLM relaying vulnerabilities in Exchange, because it could lead…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install the AWS Secrets Manager Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587053</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-install-the-aws-secrets-manager-agent/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T14:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS has recently unveiled the open-source release of the Secrets Manager Agent. This local HTTP service is designed to be installed within various compute environments. Its purpose is to fetch secrets from Secrets Manager and cache them in memory for efficient application access. This approach offers a simplified and consistent method to consume secrets across diverse environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Direct Memory Access (DMA) attacks. Risks, techniques, and mitigations in hardware hacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29725</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/direct-memory-access-dma-attacks-risks-techniques-and-mitigations-in-hardware-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T05:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Direct Memory Access (DMA) attacks are a powerful class of attack that give read and write access to the memory of a target system, bypassing the main CPU to […]
Direct Memory Access (DMA) attacks. Risks, techniques, and mitigations in hardware hacking first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Rabin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Applications of GenAI in a SOC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/practical-applications-of-genai-in-a-soc</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/practical-applications-of-genai-in-a-soc?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few standout candidates for the application of GenAI with Data Loss Prevention (DLP) alerts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Subdomain Takeovers 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/community/guide-subdomain-takeovers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/community/guide-subdomain-takeovers"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by experienced security researcher EdOverflow, this blog provides an understanding of subdomain configurations with current resources and tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EdOverflow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set the default search engine in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox with Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586965</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/set-the-default-search-engine-in-chrome-edge-and-firefox-with-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T19:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All browser vendors configure a default search engine that handles queries entered into the address bar. Microsoft provides Bing, Google uses its own search engine, and Mozilla partners with Google. The default search engines can be changed through Group Policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Streamline Your SDLC With Hai]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/streamline-sdlc-with-hai</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/streamline-sdlc-with-hai"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T17:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hai streamlines the SDLC with the tools to maintain consistency, automate tasks, and improve overall efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office 2024 (LTSC): new features, pricing, and the stability tax]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586901</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-office-2024-ltsc-new-features-pricing-and-the-stabilty-tax/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has officially announced Office LTSC 2024, the newest iteration of its Long-Term Servicing Channel (LTSC) suite. This article examines the new features in Office 2024, compares the standard to the LTSC edition, and breaks down their respective pricing models. Finally, I’ll explain why Microsoft leverages the hefty LTSC price tag and the new AI feature to lure you toward a Microsoft 365 subscription.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broken Hill: A Productionized Greedy Coordinate Gradient Attack Tool for Use Against Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/brokenhill-attack-tool-largelanguagemodels-llm</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/brokenhill-attack-tool-largelanguagemodels-llm"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough the GCG attack at a high level and be introduced to Broken Hill – Bishop Fox’s newly-released tool that can perform the GCG attack against a variety of popular LLMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lincoln</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Pwn2Own Automotive for 2025]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66f1c5f7542ca37795298f1d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/23/announcing-pwn2own-automotive-for-2025"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here.
Earlier this year we held our inaugural Pwn2Own Automotive contest, and it was a rousing success. On our biggest-ever stage (literally), we awarded $1,323,750 over the three-day event as researchers from around the globe demonstrated 49 unique zero days. Today, we’re excited to announce that we will be returning to Tokyo and the Automotive World conference for Pwn2Own Automotive 2025. The event will be held on January 22-24, 2025, and we have some exciting challenges planned for our second year.
As always, we’re pleased to be working with our cohorts over at VicOne again. Their help was instrumental in the success we had at our first event, and we’re glad to be partnering with them once more. Tesla also returns as a sponsor. They …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backdooring Azure Automation Account Packages and Runtime Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25550</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/backdooring-azure-automation-account-packages-and-runtime-environments/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Automation Accounts can allow an attacker to persist in the associated packages that support runbooks. Learn how attackers can maintain access to an Automation Account. 
The post Backdooring Azure Automation Account Packages and Runtime Environments  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Fosaaen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few notes on AWS Nitro Enclaves: Attack surface]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108306</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/24/notes-on-aws-nitro-enclaves-attack-surface/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Paweł Płatek In the race to secure cloud applications, AWS Nitro Enclaves have emerged as a powerful tool for isolating sensitive workloads. But with great power comes great responsibility—and potential security pitfalls. As pioneers in confidential computing security, we at Trail of Bits have scrutinized the attack surface of AWS Nitro Enclaves, uncovering potential […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Security: The 6 biggest challenges AppSec teams face, and how to solve them.]]></title>
        <id>api-security-the-6-biggest-challenges-appsec-teams-face-and-how-to-solve-them</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/api-security-the-6-biggest-challenges-appsec-teams-face-and-how-to-solve-them"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T10:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AppSec teams face a wide range of challenges when securing their API estate against attack threats. In our recent webinar, which demonstrated the enhanced API scanning features in Burp Suite Enterpris]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v4.3: SSO, JSON Fields, and Reporting with BloodHound]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/976835a7edba</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-v4-3-sso-json-fields-and-reporting-with-bloodhound-976835a7edba?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T18:53:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Ghostwriter v4.3’s new features and how to integrate tools like BloodHound]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Maddalena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Docker Desktop 4.34: MSI installer, host networking, auto disk space reclamation, NVIDIA AI workbench, Compose Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586859</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-docker-desktop-434-msi-installer-for-windows-host-networking-auto-disk-space-reclamation-for-wsl2-nvidia-ai-workbench-integration-compose-bridge-and-improved-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, we discussed the new features in Docker Desktop 4.33. This post will cover what's new in Docker Desktop 4.34.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptina RaaS | From Unsellable Cast-Off to Enterprise Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=105715</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/kryptina-raas-from-unsellable-cast-off-to-enterprise-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptina's adoption by Mallox affiliates complicates malware tracking as ransomware operators blend different codebases into new variants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Business Risks of Ignoring ICS Security: Five Critical Takeaways from Industry Experts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-business-risks-of-ignoring-ics-security-five-critical-takeaways-from-industry-experts</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-business-risks-of-ignoring-ics-security-five-critical-takeaways-from-industry-experts?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog summarizing five takeaways from a discussion between four SANS industrial control systems (ICS) security experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32 goes to hell…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9481</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/21/rundll32-goes-to-hell/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T22:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parsing command line invocations is fun, because it’s impossible to do it right (all the time). Imagine a test DLL that exports a function called foobar. We place this DLL in c:\test directory and name it like this: test.dll, #666 … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dexray v2.34]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9479</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/20/dexray-v2-34/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T21:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have updated the code to fix a few bugs that Роман Д. pointed out. Thank you Роман! Download the latest version here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spyware Injection Into Your ChatGPT's Long-Term Memory (SpAIware)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-macos-app-persistent-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-macos-app-persistent-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explains an attack chain for the ChatGPT macOS application. Through prompt injection from untrusted data, attackers could insert long-term persistent spyware into ChatGPT’s memory. This led to continuous data exfiltration of any information the user typed or responses received by ChatGPT, including any future chat sessions.
 OpenAI released a fix for the macOS app last week. Ensure your app is updated to the latest version.
Let’s look at this spAIware in detail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Copilot responses with identical PDF and DOCX content: Causes and solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586793</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/different-copilot-responses-with-identical-pdf-and-docx-content-causes-and-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T15:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saving identical text as both a Word file and a PDF leads to different responses from Copilot because of the fragmented nature of PDF files. Here's why this occurs and how to modify your prompt for more consistent results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicki Borell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New website address and RSS Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34806</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/08/13/new-website-address-and-rss-feed/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that all of NCC Group’s latest research findings and articles are now hosted on our website at the following link: NCC Group Research Blog. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/) To stay up-to-date with our latest research, you can also subscribe to our RSS feed here: NCC Group Research Blog RSS Feed. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/feed/) Be sure to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>R.Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side-by-Side with HelloJackHunter: Unveiling the Mysteries of WinSxS]]></title>
        <id>65f5ceb78792421d3c2272e4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/hellojackhunter-exploring-winsxs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T09:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores Windows Side-by-Side (WinSxS) and DLL hijacking, deep-diving some tooling I've written and some of the fun along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>