<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-08-30T00:48:52.798Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a custom MCP server using Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599957</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/building-a-custom-mcp-server-using-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Model Context Protocol (MCP) makes building intelligent integrations between large language models (LLMs) and cloud services easier. By combining MCP with Azure Functions, developers can expose serverless tools that LLMs can securely call in real time. This article describes how to set up Azure Functions as a custom MCP server, extend it with custom tools, and connect it to clients such as VS Code in Agent Mode.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cache Me If You Can (Sitecore Experience Platform Cache Poisoning to RCE)]]></title>
        <id>68b0b163babdd60001c1f94b</id>
        <link href="https://labs.watchtowr.com/cache-me-if-you-can-sitecore-experience-platform-cache-poisoning-to-rce/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the main purpose of a Content Management System (CMS)?
We have to accept that when we ask such existential and philosophical questions, we’re also admitting that we have no idea and that there probably isn’t an easy answer (this is our excuse, and we&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydlo (@chudyPB)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rage Against the Authentication State Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2025/06/14/gitblit-cve-CVE-2024-28080/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2025/06/14/gitblit-cve-CVE-2024-28080/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blogpost describes our journey through discovering CVE-2024-28080, an authentication bypass vulnerability in Gitblit, “an open-source, pure Java stack for managing, viewing, and serving Git repositories”. The vulnerability affects the SSH service and can only be exploited for users that have at least one public key assigned to their account. Version 1.10 released on 14 June 2025 fixes this and two other vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silent Signal Techblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf MCP Integration: Missing Security Controls Put Users at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-dangers-lack-of-security-controls-for-mcp-server-tool-invocation/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-dangers-lack-of-security-controls-for-mcp-server-tool-invocation/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T19:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of my default test cases for coding agents is to check how MCP integration looks like, especially if the agent can be configured to allow setting fine-grained controls for tools.
Sometimes there are basic security controls missing.
Especially when running an agent on your local computer. Stakes are much higher. And it seems important to empower users to be able to configure which actions an AI should be able to take automatically, and which ones should be suggestions that the user reviews before executing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Terminal v1.23 and v1.24: new features and installation]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599867</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-terminal-v123-and-v124-new-features-and-installation/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T14:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released Windows Terminal version 1.23 as a stable update, and version 1.24 as the latest preview, both bringing major improvements to the popular command-line tool. These versions introduce a completely new windowing architecture, expanded settings in the user interface, and other powerful enhancements for productivity and customization. In this article, we’ll explore what’s new in these updates and to how to install the latest stable and preview builds through Microsoft Store, winget, choco, and scoop.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The year so far: How Burp Suite DAST is leveling up enterprise security in 2025]]></title>
        <id>the-year-so-far-how-burp-suite-dast-is-leveling-up-enterprise-security-in-2025</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/the-year-so-far-how-burp-suite-dast-is-leveling-up-enterprise-security-in-2025"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T12:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise security teams are under more pressure than ever to secure sprawling application estates, without slowing down delivery. That's why, over the first half of 2025, we've delivered some of our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intern projects that outlived the internship]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/28/intern-projects-that-outlived-the-internship/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/28/intern-projects-that-outlived-the-internship/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our business operations intern at Trail of Bits built two AI-powered tools that became permanent company resources—a podcast workflow that saves 1,250 hours annually and a Slack exporter that enables efficient knowledge retrieval across the organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report: Meta Whatsapp message summarization service]]></title>
        <id>9120d3d9-3398-4dfa-a0e1-59f3efde5fd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/research-blog/public-report-meta-whatsapp-message-summarization-service/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T00:51:19.734Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce hallucination risk by prompting multiple AI models simultaneously with Chorus]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599833</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/reduce-hallucination-risk-by-prompting-multiple-ai-models-simultaneously-with-chorus/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T19:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chorus app is built to send prompts to multiple AI models from different providers simultaneously. You can also query several search engines with each prompt. Both methods significantly reduce the risk of hallucinations.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Referral Beware, Your Rewards are Mine (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25934</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/referral-beware-your-rewards-are-mine-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T17:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Referral Beware, Your Rewards are Mine (Part 1) appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Whit Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cline: Vulnerable To Data Exfiltration And How To Protect Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/cline-vulnerable-to-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/cline-vulnerable-to-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T15:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cline is quite a popular AI coding agent, according to the product website it has 2+ million downloads and over 47k stars on GitHub.
Unfortunately, Cline is vulnerable to data exfiltration through the rendering of markdown images from untrusted domains in the chat box.
This allows an adversary to exfiltrate sensitive user information during a prompt injection attack by reading sensitive data (e.g. .env file) and appending its contents to the URL of an image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top Reasons Security Leaders Choose Red Teaming]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/top-reasons-security-leaders-choose-red-teaming</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/top-reasons-security-leaders-choose-red-teaming"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders are turning to red teaming to test defenses against real-world adversaries. From validating investments to sharpening blue team skills, discover why this strategy is becoming a must-have for organizations serious about cyber resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start hacking Bluetooth Low Energy today! (part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42663</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/start-hacking-bluetooth-low-energy-today-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T11:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR   We made it beep for free (ish)  In part one we started hacking Bluetooth and made a little £2 key-finder beep using only Android and Linux. If you haven’t read that post, I would recommend it as a primer to the devices, BLE and what we’re doing, but TLDR we got them to go […]
The post Start hacking Bluetooth Low Energy today! (part 2)  appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement EIP-7730 today]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/27/implement-eip-7730-today/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/27/implement-eip-7730-today/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-7730 enables hardware wallets to decode transactions into human-readable formats, eliminating blind signing vulnerabilities with minimal implementation effort for dApp developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The entire internet is broken": ethical hacking expert John Hammond meets James Kettle]]></title>
        <id>the-entire-internet-is-broken-ethical-hacking-expert-john-hammond-meets-james-kettle</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/the-entire-internet-is-broken-ethical-hacking-expert-john-hammond-meets-james-kettle"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T09:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a brand-new collaboration between ethical hacking and AppSec expert John Hammond and world-renowned security researcher James Kettle, the pair explore how tens of millions of websites are compromis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The One Where We Just Steal The Vulnerabilities (CrushFTP CVE-2025-54309)]]></title>
        <id>68ae8c5fb4241b00012712fe</id>
        <link href="https://labs.watchtowr.com/the-one-where-we-just-steal-the-vulnerabilities-crushftp-cve-2025-54309/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T04:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 18, 2025, users of CrushFTP woke up to an announcement:
https://www.crushftp.com/crush11wiki/Wiki.jsp?page=CompromiseJuly2025
As we’ve all experienced in 2025, 2025 has been the year of vendors burying their heads in the sand with regard to in-the-wild exploitation, even in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perplexity Comet: A rising AI browser star]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599769</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/perplexity-comet-a-rising-ai-browser-star/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-26T19:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post, I discussed Perplexity's aim to transform the familiar blinking web we've known for decades. It brings to mind the early days of Google, when many questioned the need for another search engine since AltaVista already did a good job. Although Comet appears to be just another Chromium-based web browser, the AI powering the browser under the hood has the same disruptive potential as Google's PageRank algorithm once did.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Kiro: Arbitrary Code Execution via Indirect Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/aws-kiro-aribtrary-command-execution-with-indirect-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/aws-kiro-aribtrary-command-execution-with-indirect-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-26T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the day AWS Kiro was released, I couldn’t resist putting it through some of my Month of AI Bugs security tests for coding agents.
AWS Kiro was vulnerable to arbitrary command execution via indirect prompt injection. This means that a remote attacker, who controls data that Kiro processes, could hijack it to run arbitrary operating system commands or write and run custom code.
In particular two attack paths that enabled this with AWS Kiro were identified:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Style Exfiltration: leaking data with chained CSS conditionals]]></title>
        <id>inline-style-exfiltration</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/inline-style-exfiltration"/>
        <updated>2025-08-26T12:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I discovered how to use CSS to steal attribute data without selectors and stylesheet imports! This means you can now exploit CSS injection via style attributes! Learn how below: Someone asked if you c]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detection Engineering: Practicing Detection-as-Code – Documentation – Part 4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=20884</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2025/08/26/detection-engineering-practicing-detection-as-code-documentation-part-4/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sufficiently documenting our detections is essential in detection engineering as it provides context around the the purpose, detection logic, and expected behaviour of each detection rule. Just as important as documenting individual detections is tracking how the overall detection library evolves. In this part we are looking into how we can tackle both of those issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stamatis Chatzimangou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI browser Comet with efficient ad blocking, Perplexity’s deception and hypocrisy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599710</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/ai-browser-comet-with-efficient-ad-blocking-perplexitys-deception-and-hypocrisy/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-25T19:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perplexity's new AI-powered Comet web browser, initially exclusive to Max subscribers at $200 monthly, is now accessible to Pro subscribers for $20. I tested it and am impressed—both by Perplexity's hypocrisy and Comet's truly innovative browsing experience. This post shares my rant against Perplexity, while my next post will praise Comet, the first browser on the battlefield in the new browser war.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Prompt Injection Exposes Manus' VS Code Server to the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/manus-ai-kill-chain-expose-port-vs-code-server-on-internet/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/manus-ai-kill-chain-expose-port-vs-code-server-on-internet/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-25T11:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will cover a powerful, easy to use, autonomous agent called Manus. Manus is developed by the Chinese startup Butterfly Effect, headquartered in Singapore.
This post demonstrates an end-to-end indirect prompt injection attack leading to a compromise of Manus’ dev box.
This is achieved by tricking Manus to expose it’s internal VS Code Server to the Internet, and then sharing the URL and password with the atacker. Specifically, this post demonstrates that:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speedrunning the New York Subway]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/25/speedrunning-the-new-york-subway/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/25/speedrunning-the-new-york-subway/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We optimized the route for visiting every NYC subway station using algorithms from combinatorial optimization, creating a 20-hour tour that beats the existing world record by 45 minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Deep Research Agents Can Leak Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/chatgpt-deep-research-connectors-data-spill-and-leaks/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/chatgpt-deep-research-connectors-data-spill-and-leaks/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-25T01:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, many of our favorite AI chatbots have gotten autonomous research capabilities. This allows the AI to go off for an extended period of time, while having access to tools, such as web search, integrations, connectors and also custom-built MCP servers.
This post will explore and explain in detail how there can be data spill between connected tools during Deep Research. The research is focused on ChatGPT but applies to other Deep Research agents as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sneaking Invisible Instructions by Developers in Windsurf]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-sneaking-invisible-instructions-for-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-sneaking-invisible-instructions-for-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-23T23:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine a malicious instruction hidden in plain sight, invisible to you but not to the AI. This is a vulnerability discovered in Windsurf Cascade, it follows invisible instructions. This means there can be instructions in a file or result of a tool call that the developer cannot see, but the LLM does.
Some LLMs interpret invisible Unicode Tag characters as instructions, which can lead to hidden prompt injection.
As far as I can tell the Windsurf SWE-1 model can also “see” these invisible characters, but the SWE-1 is not yet capable of interpreting them as instructions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf: Memory-Persistent Data Exfiltration (SpAIware Exploit)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-spaiware-exploit-persistent-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-spaiware-exploit-persistent-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-22T22:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second post about Windsurf Cascade we are exploring the SpAIware attack, which allows memory persistent data exfiltration. SpAIware is an attack we first successfully demonstrated with ChatGPT last year and OpenAI mitigated.
While inspecting the system prompt of Windsurf Cascade I noticed that it has a create_memory tool.
Creating Memories The question that immediately popped into my head was if this tool will require human approval when Cascade creates a long-term memory, or if it is added automatically.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access remote Ollama AI models through an SSH tunnel]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599644</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/access-remote-ollama-ai-models-through-an-ssh-tunnel/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-22T13:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous Ollama series post, I explained how to access self-hosted AI models in Ollama via HTTP. While this method provides convenient connectivity from different apps, it's only secure for on-premises Ollama hosts. For remote internet access, you can set up an SSH tunnel. Alternatively, you can securely connect from GitHub Copilot to your self-hosted AI models by using Microsoft's VS Code extension Remote - SSH.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote HTTP access to self-hosted Ollama AI models]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599577</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/remote-http-access-to-self-hosted-ollama-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-21T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post in the Ollama series with OpenAI OSS models, I explained how to install Ollama on an Ubuntu EC2 instance. If you followed my guide, you now have everything set up to remotely access gpt-oss-20b on your self-hosted Ollama installation via HTTP. I will also showcase how to connect to remote AI models in VS Code using popular coding assistants like Cline and Roo Code, as well as through AI apps such as the local Ollama client, BoltAI, and Anything LLM.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Talent Shortage to Cybersecurity Talent Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/talent-shortage-to-cybersecurity-talent-pipeline</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/talent-shortage-to-cybersecurity-talent-pipeline"/>
        <updated>2025-08-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity faces a paradox: millions of jobs go unfilled while eager newcomers struggle to break in. This blog explores why the gap exists—and how mentorship, realistic hiring, and early-career programs can transform the shortage into a sustainable talent pipeline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weaponizing image scaling against production AI systems]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/21/weaponizing-image-scaling-against-production-ai-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/21/weaponizing-image-scaling-against-production-ai-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll detail how attackers can exploit image scaling on Gemini CLI, Vertex AI Studio, Gemini’s web and API interfaces, Google Assistant, Genspark, and other production AI systems. We’ll also explain how to mitigate and defend against these attacks, and we’ll introduce Anamorpher, our open-source tool that lets you explore and generate these crafted images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hijacking Windsurf: How Prompt Injection Leaks Developer Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-data-exfiltration-vulnerabilities/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/windsurf-data-exfiltration-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-21T09:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first post in a series exploring security vulnerabilities in Windsurf. If you are unfamiliar with Windsurf, it is a fork of VS Code and the coding agent is called Windsurf Cascade.
The attack vectors we will explore today allow an adversary during an indirect prompt injection to exfiltrate data from the developer’s machine.
These vulnerabilities are a great example of Simon Willison’s lethal trifecta pattern.
Overall, the security vulnerability reporting experience with Windsurf has not been great.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start hacking Bluetooth Low Energy today! (part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42572</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/start-hacking-bluetooth-low-energy-today-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-21T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Before you start First off, before we start  Bluetooth hacking can be confusing, there are lots of references to tools that are a bit outdated, scripts that don’t run, and more. The actual Bluetooth specs are huge, but honestly, who cares as long as you can make a device do a thing? If we […]
The post Start hacking Bluetooth Low Energy today! (part 1) appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox VE 9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599530</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/proxmox-ve-90/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-20T17:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post, I covered the new features in Proxmox Backup Server 4.0. Released simultaneously, Proxmox Virtual Environment (VE) 9.0 also merits attention. It runs on Debian 13 Trixie with Kernel 6.14 and includes updated QEMU, LXC, ZFS, and Ceph versions. More significantly, it introduces modifications affecting storage management, networking, and high availability within your virtual setup. This article examines these updates more closely, providing commands and examples you can test on your own system.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer for VS Code Vulnerable to Invisible Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amazon-q-developer-interprets-hidden-instructions/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amazon-q-developer-interprets-hidden-instructions/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Amazon Q Developer VS Code Extension (Amazon Q) is a very popular coding agent, with over 1 million downloads.
In previous posts we showed how prompt injection vulnerabilities in Amazon Q could lead to:
Exfiltration of sensitive information from the user’s machine , and also to a System compromise by running arbitrary code Today we will show how an attack can leverage invisible Unicode Tag characters that humans cannot see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guess Who Would Be Stupid Enough To Rob The Same Vault Twice? Pre-Auth RCE Chains in Commvault]]></title>
        <id>68a59bffbd2093000187b2fb</id>
        <link href="https://labs.watchtowr.com/guess-who-would-be-stupid-enough-to-rob-the-same-vault-twice-pre-auth-rce-chains-in-commvault/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-20T10:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back, and we’ve finished telling everyone that our name was on the back of Phrack!!!!1111
Whatever, nerds.
Today, we're back to scheduled content. Like our friendly neighbourhood ransomware gangs and APT groups, we've continued to spend irrational amounts of time]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydlo (@chudyPB)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DLL ForwardSideloading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=10115</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2025/08/19/dll-forwardsideloading/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T22:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some DLLs export functions (via export table) that are just forwarding execution to functions implemented in other libraries. It’s a very common practice and one of the most known forwards are: kernel32.dll HeapAlloc -> NTDLL.RtlAllocateHeapkernel32.dll HeapReAlloc -> NTDLL.RtlReAllocateHeapkernel32.dll HeapSize -> … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer: Remote Code Execution with Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amazon-q-developer-remote-code-execution/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amazon-q-developer-remote-code-execution/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T21:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Amazon Q Developer VS Code Extension (Amazon Q) is a popular coding agent, with over 1 million downloads.
The extension is vulnerable to indirect prompt injection, and in this post we discuss a vulnerability that allowed an adversary (or also the AI for that matter) to run arbitrary commands on the host without the developer’s consent.
The resulting impact of the vulnerability is the same as CVE-2025-53773 that Microsoft fixed in GitHub Copilot, however AWS did not issue a CVE when patching the vulnerabiliy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Ollama with OpenAI gpt-oss-20b on Ubuntu within an EC2 instance]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599486</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-ollama-with-openai-gpt-oss-20b-on-ubuntu-within-an-ec2-instance/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T16:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post, I explained why you might want to run OpenAI gpt-oss-20b or gpt-oss-120b on your own virtual machine and how to select an appropriate EC2 instance type. Today, I will show you how to install Ollama via script or snap on Ubuntu within an EC2 instance. Most steps can be adapted for other cloud providers, on-premises setups, or Linux distributions with minor modifications. I will also briefly discuss the benefits of running open-weight models on an EC2 instance with Ollama compared to Bedrock, SageMaker, vLLM, or Hugging Face Transformers.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware the false false-positive: how to distinguish HTTP pipelining from request smuggling]]></title>
        <id>how-to-distinguish-http-pipelining-from-request-smuggling</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/how-to-distinguish-http-pipelining-from-request-smuggling"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T14:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes people think they've found HTTP request smuggling, when they're actually just observing HTTP keep-alive or pipelining. This is usually a false positive, but sometimes there's actually a real]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marshal madness: A brief history of Ruby deserialization exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/20/marshal-madness-a-brief-history-of-ruby-deserialization-exploits/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/20/marshal-madness-a-brief-history-of-ruby-deserialization-exploits/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post traces the decade-long evolution of Ruby Marshal deserialization exploits, demonstrating how security researchers have repeatedly bypassed patches and why fundamental changes to the Ruby ecosystem are needed rather than continued patch-and-hope approaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of the Honeypot Account: Making the Unusual Look Normal]]></title>
        <id>https://adsecurity.org/?p=4510</id>
        <link href="https://adsecurity.org/?p=4510"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T01:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally posted on the Trimarc Content Hub on August 6, 2020.Updated here with authentication PowerShell code on August 18, 2025. ADSecurity.org is the new home for this article and all updates will occur here. I have had the idea for a post describing how to best create a honeypot (or honeytoken) account … 
Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Metcalf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Password Spraying with Security Event Auditing]]></title>
        <id>https://adsecurity.org/?p=4517</id>
        <link href="https://adsecurity.org/?p=4517"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally posted on the Trimarc Content Hub on February 10, 2017. A common method attackers leverage as well as many penetration testers and Red Teamers is called “password spraying”. Password spraying is interesting because it’s automated password guessing. This automated password guessing against all users typically avoids account lockout since the logon … 
Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Metcalf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at RTEMS Security]]></title>
        <id>413e3ca1-eead-47c1-9b7b-b6fc54638306</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/research-blog/a-look-at-rtems-security/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-19T00:54:50.279Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trivial C# Random Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2025/08/19/trivial-exploit-on-C-random.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2025/08/19/trivial-exploit-on-C-random.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting random number generators requires math, right? Thanks to C#’s
Random, that is not necessarily the case! I ran into an HTTP 2.0 web service
issuing password reset tokens from a custom encoding of (new Random()).Next(min, max) output. 
This led to a critical account takeover.
Exploitation did not require scripting, math or libraries. Just several clicks
in Burp. While I had source code, I will show a method of discovering and
exploiting this vulnerability in a black-box or bug-bounty style engagement.
The exploit uses no math, but I do like math. So, there is a bonus section on how to
optimize and invert Random.
The Vulnerability
I can’t share the client code, but it was something like this:

var num = new Random().Next(min, max);
var token = make_password_reset_token(num);
save_r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer: Secrets Leaked via DNS and Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amazon-q-developer-data-exfil-via-dns/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amazon-q-developer-data-exfil-via-dns/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-18T19:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next three posts will cover high severity vulnerabilities in the Amazon Q Developer VS Code Extension (Amazon Q Developer), which is a very popular coding agent, with over 1 million downloads.
It is vulnerable to prompt injection from untrusted data and its security depends heavily on model behavior.
At a high level Amazon Q Developer can leak sensitive information from a developer’s machine, e.g. API keys, to external servers via DNS requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running OpenAI gpt-oss-20b and gpt‑oss-120b in AWS on your own EC2 instance]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599438</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/running-openai-gpt-oss-20b-and-gptoss-120b-in-aws-on-your-own-ec2-instance/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-18T16:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI recently released its first open-weight models,  gpt-oss-20b and gpt‑oss-120b, which you can download and run with Ollama. If security and privacy are essential when using AI models, you might not want to use the vendor's chat UI or API. The most powerful AI models require significant computing power and memory, and many desktop devices cannot run these models. Although Ollama was not designed with remote connections in mind, it is still possible. In this series, I will explain how to install OpenAI's open-weight models using Ollama and connect to them remotely from various applications, including VS Code GitHub Copilot. In this first post, I will outline how to choose the right size for your virtual machine, using EC2 instance types in AWS as an example.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Exfiltration via Image Rendering Fixed in Amp Code]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amp-code-fixed-data-exfiltration-via-images/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amp-code-fixed-data-exfiltration-via-images/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-17T11:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we discuss a vulnerability that was present in Amp Code from Sourcegraph by which an attacker could exploit markdown driven image rendering to exfiltrate sensitive information.
This vulnerability is common in AI applications and agents, and it’s actually similar to one we discussed last year in GitHub Copilot which Microsoft fixed.
Exploit Demonstration For the proof-of-concept I use a pre-existing demo that created a longer time ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond good ol’ Run key, Part 150]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=10106</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2025/08/17/beyond-good-ol-run-key-part-150/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-17T00:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I decided to add this post to this old series, but the scope of this post is – as you will find out soon – much wider. You will find servercoreshell.exe program to be present on both Windows Server 2022 … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amp Code: Invisible Prompt Injection Fixed by Sourcegraph]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amp-code-fixed-invisible-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amp-code-fixed-invisible-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-16T19:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we will look at Amp, a coding agent from Sourcegraph. The other day we discussed how invisible instructions impact Google Jules.
Turns out that many client applications are vulnerable to these kinds of attacks when they use models that support invisible instructions, like Claude.
Invisible Unicode Tag Characters Interpreted as Instructions We have talked about hidden prompt injections quite a bit in the past, and so I’m keeping this short.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should Security Solutions Be Secure? Maybe We're All Wrong - Fortinet FortiSIEM Pre-Auth Command Injection (CVE-2025-25256)]]></title>
        <id>689f5b2e35ca1100010c094c</id>
        <link href="https://labs.watchtowr.com/should-security-solutions-be-secure-maybe-were-all-wrong-fortinet-fortisiem-pre-auth-command-injection-cve-2025-25256/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-15T16:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday, but we’re here today with unscheduled content - pushing our previously scheduled shenanigans to next week.
Fortinet is no stranger to the watchTowr Labs research team. Today we’re looking at CVE-2025-25256 - a pre-authentication command injection in FortiSIEM that lets an attacker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sina Kheirkhah (@SinSinology)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox Backup Server 4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599368</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/proxmox-backup-server-40/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-15T13:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox Backup Server (PBS) 4.0 is here with a new Debian 13 base, updated kernel, native S3-compatible storage, and useful improvements for managing backups. This release gives you more choices for where to store data and simplifies tasks like using removable drives or syncing to off-site locations. In this post, I will walk you through crucial new features, show the commands you can run, and provide a short upgrade checklist.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Discovery with LLM-Powered Patch Diffing]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/vulnerability-discovery-with-llm-powered-patch-diffing</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/vulnerability-discovery-with-llm-powered-patch-diffing"/>
        <updated>2025-08-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read our most recent research to see how LLMs can assist in scaling patch diffing workflows, saving valuable time in a crucial race against attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud token abuse turns speculative plan into remote code execution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42531</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/terraform-token-abuse-speculative-plan/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-15T10:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Introduction On a Red Team engagement we entered a busy multicloud estate. AWS, GCP and Azure were all used, with Terraform Cloud orchestrating every change. That brings speed and consistency, but it also concentrates risk. If an attacker finds the weak point, one credential can unlock a lot of power. Background Terraform is HashiCorp’s […]
The post Terraform Cloud token abuse turns speculative plan into remote code execution appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Jules is Vulnerable To Invisible Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/google-jules-invisible-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/google-jules-invisible-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-15T09:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Gemini models quite reliably interpret hidden Unicode Tag characters as instructions. This vulnerability, first reported to Google over a year ago, has not been mitigated at the model or API level, hence now affects all applications built on top of Gemini.
This includes Google’s own products and services, like Google Jules.
Hopefully, this post helps raise awareness of this emerging threat.
Invisible Prompt Injections in GitHub Issues When Jules is asked to work on a task, such as a GitHub issue, it is possible to plant invisible instructions into a GitHub issue to add backdoor code, or have it run arbitrary commands and tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft AI Shell Preview 6: Significant improvements for the AI-enhanced PowerShell admin]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599336</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-ai-shell-preview-6-significant-improvements-for-the-ai-enhanced-powershell-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-14T16:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The key new feature in the just-released AI Shell Preview 6 is run_command_in_terminal, among several new built-in tools that allow the AI model to run commands and review outputs directly in your PowerShell terminal. Additionally, AI Shell now supports local and remote MCP servers, transforming it into a versatile AI assistant across Windows, Mac, and Linux.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jules Zombie Agent: From Prompt Injection to Remote Control]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/google-jules-remote-code-execution-zombai/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/google-jules-remote-code-execution-zombai/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-14T11:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post, we explored two data exfiltration vectors that Jules is vulnerable to and that can be exploited via prompt injection. This post takes it further by demonstrating how Jules can be convinced to download malware and join a remote command & control server.
This research was performed in May 2025 and findings were shared with Google.
Remote Command & Control - Proof Of Concept The basic attack chain follows the classic AI Kill Chain:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Jules: Vulnerable to Multiple Data Exfiltration Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/google-jules-vulnerable-to-data-exfiltration-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/google-jules-vulnerable-to-data-exfiltration-issues/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-14T01:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores data exfiltration attacks in Google Jules, an asynchronous coding agent. This is the first of three posts that will highlight my research on Google Jules in May 2025. All information provided was also shared with Google at that time.
This first post will focus on data exfiltration, the lethal trifecta.
But let’s first talk about Jules’ system prompt.
Jules’ System Prompt and Multiple Agents To grab the system prompt I just asked it to write it into a file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Know What You Did (in Azure) Last Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=28093</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/azure-resource-attribution-via-tenant-id-enumeration/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-13T20:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At DEF CON 33, NetSPI presented a talk about how Azure resources supporting Entra ID authentication expose tenant IDs, enabling attackers to attribute cloud resources to specific organizations at scale.
The post We Know What You Did (in Azure) Last Summer appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Fosaaen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Gmail Connector: OpenAI’s next flop?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599276</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/chatgpt-gmail-connector-openais-next-flop/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-13T15:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ChatGPT Gmail connector was first released in June 2025 for Plus, Pro, Team, Enterprise, and Edu users. However, because of alleged data protection rules, users in the European Economic Area, Switzerland, and the UK were excluded. OpenAI is now deploying connectors for Gmail, Google Calendar, Google Drive, and GitHub across Europe for all plans—notably after Anthropic released their MCP connectors weeks ago in Europe without such concerns, suggesting OpenAI's initial data protection claims were merely pretextual or that MCP has no priority status for the AI company. The announcement mentions Google Contacts, but this connector isn't yet accessible in my ChatGPT with a Plus plan. I tested the Gmail Connector, and following GPT-5's disastrous launch, it appears OpenAI released another flop immediately afterward.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot: Remote Code Execution via Prompt Injection (CVE-2025-53773)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/github-copilot-remote-code-execution-via-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/github-copilot-remote-code-execution-via-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-12T21:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is about an important, but also scary, prompt injection discovery that leads to full system compromise of the developer’s machine in GitHub Copilot and VS Code.
It is achieved by placing Copilot into YOLO mode by modifying the project’s settings.json file.
As described a few days ago with Amp, a vulnerability pattern in agents that might be overlooked is that if an agent can write to files and modify its own configuration or update security-relevant settings it can lead to remote code execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The August 2025 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:689b8068d2db2e3dfead7274</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2025/8/12/the-august-2025-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2025-08-12T18:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve made it through hacker summer camp and made our way to the second Tuesday of the month. Adobe and Microsoft seemed to have survived as well, as they released their latest security patches. Take a break from your scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts. If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check out the Patch Report webcast on our YouTube channel. It should be posted within a couple of hours after the release.
Adobe Patches for August 2025
For August, Adobe released 13 bulletins addressing 68 unique CVEs in Commerce, Substance 3D Viewer, Animate, Illustrator, Photoshop, Substance 3D Modeler, Substance 3D Painter, Substance 3D Sampler, InDesign, InCopy, Substance 3D Stager, FrameMaker, and Dime…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is logged in to PowerShell? Alternatives to whoami]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599237</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/who-is-logged-in-to-powershell-alternatives-to-whoami/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-12T12:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are working with PowerShell, you will often face the question: "Under which user is my script running?" In other words, you want to know who is logged in. Many admins use the whoami command on the Command Prompt (cmd). However, PowerShell provides native alternatives to whoami that give you the username and domain.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shedding Light on PoisonSeed’s Phishing Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=21232</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2025/08/12/shedding-light-on-poisonseeds-phishing-kit/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Findings: Introduction As first reported by SilentPush, PoisonSeed is a threat actor whose TTPs closely align with Scattered Spider and CryptoChameleon, groups that are part of “The Com,” a young, English-speaking threat actor community. They engage in phishing attacks to obtain login information from CRM and bulk email service providers, allowing them to export … Continue reading Shedding Light on PoisonSeed’s Phishing Kit →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Efstratios Lontzetidis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GPT-5: Another crash into the AI Wall]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599189</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/gpt-5-another-crash-into-the-ai-wall/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-11T18:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is flooded with complaints from GPT-5 users, prompting OpenAI's CEO to reintroduce GPT-4o as an alternative. This marks the third setback following the departure of chief scientist Ila Sukestver, who led GPT development until version 4. One likely cause of user frustration is that, following Altman's recent boasts, everyone anticipated a major advance towards "AGI," but we are merely observing another crash into the AI Wall.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Security at Scale: The AppExchange Story]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/building-security-at-scale-the-appexchange-story</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/building-security-at-scale-the-appexchange-story"/>
        <updated>2025-08-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our interview hosted by Bishop Fox CEO Vinnie Liu with guests Brendan O’Connor, CEO of AppOmni and James Dolph, CISO at Guidewire, we uncovered the fascinating origin story of Salesforce's AppExchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude Code: Data Exfiltration with DNS]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/claude-code-exfiltration-via-dns-requests/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/claude-code-exfiltration-via-dns-requests/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-11T11:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we cover Claude Code and a high severity vulnerability that Anthropic fixed in early June. The vulnerability allowed an attacker to hijack Claude Code via indirect prompt injection and leak sensitive information from the developer’s machine, e.g. API keys, to external servers by issuing DNS requests.
Prompt Injection Hijacks Claude When reviewing or interacting with untrusted code or processing data from external systems, Claude Code can be hijacked to run bash commands that allow leaking of sensitive information without user approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entra & Azure Elevated Access Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://adsecurity.org/?p=4455</id>
        <link href="https://adsecurity.org/?p=4455"/>
        <updated>2025-08-10T19:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early 2020, I published an article on how a Global Administrator could gain control of Azure resources, that no one would know about it, and how this access would persist even after removing them from Global Administrator. From that article: “While Azure leverages Azure Active Directory for some things, Azure AD roles don’t directly … 
Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Metcalf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenHands ZombAI Exploit: Prompt Injection To Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/openhands-remote-code-execution-zombai/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/openhands-remote-code-execution-zombai/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-10T11:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we have another post about OpenHands from All Hands AI. It is a popular agent, initially named “OpenDevin”, and recently the company also provides a cloud-based service. Which is all pretty cool and exciting.
Prompt Injection to Full System Compromise However, as you know, LLM powered apps and agents are vulnerable to prompt injection. That also applies to OpenHands and it can be hijacked by untrusted data, e.g. from a website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits' Buttercup wins 2nd place in AIxCC Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/09/trail-of-bits-buttercup-wins-2nd-place-in-aixcc-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/09/trail-of-bits-buttercup-wins-2nd-place-in-aixcc-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-09T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our team won the runner-up prize of $3M at DARPA’s AI Cyber Challenge, demonstrating Buttercup’s world-class automated vulnerability discovery and patching capabilities with remarkable cost efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenHands and the Lethal Trifecta: How Prompt Injection Can Leak Access Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/openhands-the-lethal-trifecta-strikes-again/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/openhands-the-lethal-trifecta-strikes-again/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-09T10:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day, another AI data exfiltration exploit. Today we talk about OpenHands, formerly referred to as OpenDevin. It’s created by All-Hands AI.
The OpenHands agent renders images in chat, which enables zero-click data exfiltration.
Simon Willison recently gave this data exfiltration attack pattern a great name: Lethal Trifecta.
We discuss this specific image based attack technique frequently. Sometimes a message must be repeated multiple times to raise awareness and become mainstream knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new browser war – Does ‘fair use’ kill the open web?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599132</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/the-new-browser-war-does-fair-use-kill-the-open-web/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T17:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post, I covered Microsoft’s new Edge Copilot Mode, introducing only one significant change. However, shifting Copilot from the sidebar to the center in Edge is more than just a design update. Microsoft’s move marks the first strategic step in the unfolding new browser war involving Google, OpenAI, and Perplexity—companies that exploit broad 'fair use' claims to harvest web content for their own greedy gain. But the upcoming battles aren’t just about who controls the web’s entry point—it could signal the beginning of the end of the web as we know it. The fall of Google’s dominance as the web’s central policymaker now seems inevitable. Once the dust settles from the new browser war, a decentralized web shaped by independently communicating AI agents might emerge. Think that’s far-fetched? Keep reading.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Chrome renderer code exec to kernel with MSG_OOB]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/08/from-chrome-renderer-code-exec-to-kernel.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/08/from-chrome-renderer-code-exec-to-kernel.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=4mNYFHt_IKFsPe52toizHz0e5qzIIUg9OvSRGeMDk3I);ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-5{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-6{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-7{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-8{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-1{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-2{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-3{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_kxp4t4ucwvdt-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_kxp4t4ucwvdt-4}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-4{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_kxp4t4ucwvdt-2>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_kxp4t4ucwvdt-2}.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-1>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_paptt0jg97k9-1}ol.lst-kix_paptt0jg97k9-5.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Kill Chain in Action: Devin AI Exposes Ports to the Internet with Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/devin-ai-kill-chain-exposing-ports/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/devin-ai-kill-chain-exposing-ports/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T07:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today let’s explore Devin’s system prompt a bit more. Specifically, an interesing tool that I discovered when reading through it.
Hidden in Devin’s capabilities is a tool that can open any local port to the public Internet. That means, with the right indirect prompt injection nudge, Devin can be tricked into publishing sensitive files or services for anyone to access.
This tunneling feature can be invoked without a human in the loop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thumbnail forensics. DFIR techniques for analysing Windows Thumbcache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42497</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/thumbnail-forensics-dfir-techniques-for-analysing-windows-thumbcache/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T05:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Introduction Windows thumbnail cache, or thumbcache, is a well-known forensic artifact, but often one that is overlooked. The thumbcache stores small previews of images, videos and documents and can persist even after the original files are deleted, which offers analysts an opportunity to uncover traces of user activity. In this blog, we will show […]
The post Thumbnail forensics. DFIR techniques for analysing Windows Thumbcache appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Bursell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buttercup is now open-source!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/08/buttercup-is-now-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/08/buttercup-is-now-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that DARPA’s AI Cyber Challenge (AIxCC) has officially ended, we can finally make Buttercup, our CRS (Cyber Reasoning System), open source!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Training Specialist Models: Automating Malware Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=5657</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2025/08/07/training-specialist-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T19:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post complements the presentation I gave at Black Hat USA 2025.
Can a small, self-hosted LLM outperform state-of-the-art models at evasive malware development?
In this technical deep dive, we explore how reinforcement learning with verifiable rewards (RLVR) enables training compact specialist models that rival large generalists in domain-specific tasks.
In the first half of this post, we’ll break down the LLM training process and recent opportunities created by RLVR. The second half details our training methodology for Dante-7B, a 7 billion parameter model that generates functional, evasive Cobalt Strike shellcode loaders capable of bypassing Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE). We’ve released Dante-7B on Hugging Face, complete with a demo app so anyone can experiment with the model.

Introduction
The best models from OpenAI,
Tags: AI
Read full post
The post Training Specialist Models: Automating Malware Development appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Avery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OAuthSeeker: Leveraging OAuth Phishing for Initial Access and Lateral Movement on Red Team Engagements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5825</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/oauthseeker-leveraging-oauth-phishing-for-initial-access-and-lateral-movement-on-red-team-engagements/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T17:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview The Praetorian Labs team recently conducted research into potential initial access vectors for red team engagements, focusing on attack techniques leveraging malicious applications distributed through platforms like the Microsoft Store. This included OAuth applications, malicious Outlook extensions, and other types of applications that could be delivered via the Windows Store. As part of this […]
The post OAuthSeeker: Leveraging OAuth Phishing for Initial Access and Lateral Movement on Red Team Engagements appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Copeland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate a DHCP Server to Windows Server 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599068</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/migrate-a-dhcp-server-to-windows-server-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T15:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol (DHCP) server handles automatic IP address assignment within a company network. This article explains how to transfer the DHCP server role to Windows Server 2025 using PowerShell, covering the export and import of DHCP scopes, leases, and reservations to facilitate a seamless migration with minimal disruption to users and systems.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Devin AI Can Leak Your Secrets via Multiple Means]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/devin-can-leak-your-secrets/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/devin-can-leak-your-secrets/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T15:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we show how an attacker can make Devin send sensitive information to third-party servers, via multiple means. This post assumes that you read the first post about Devin as well.
But here is a quick recap: During an indirect prompt injection Devin can be tricked into download malware and extract sensitive information on the machine. But there is more…
Let’s explore how Devin can leak sensitive information and send it to a third-party server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIxCC finals: Tale of the tape]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/07/aixcc-finals-tale-of-the-tape/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/07/aixcc-finals-tale-of-the-tape/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the AIxCC winner has not yet been announced, differences in the finalists’ approaches show that there are multiple viable paths forward to using AI for vulnerability detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/1.1 Must Die: What This Means for AppSec Leadership]]></title>
        <id>http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-appsec-leadership</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-appsec-leadership"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T22:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Black Hat USA and DEFCON 2025, PortSwigger's Director of Research, James Kettle, issued a stark warning: request smuggling isn't dying out, it's evolving and thriving. Despite years of defensive ef]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/1.1 Must Die: What This Means for In-House Pentesters]]></title>
        <id>http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-in-house-pentesters</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-in-house-pentesters"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T22:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Black Hat USA and DEFCON 2025, PortSwigger's Director of Research, James Kettle, issued a stark warning: request smuggling isn't dying out, it's evolving and thriving. Despite years of defensive ef]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/1.1 Must Die: What This Means for Bug Bounty Hunters]]></title>
        <id>http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-bug-bounty-hunters</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-bug-bounty-hunters"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T22:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Black Hat USA and DEFCON 2025, PortSwigger's Director of Research, James Kettle, issued a stark warning: request smuggling isn't dying out, it's evolving and thriving. Despite years of defensive ef]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/1.1 Must Die: What This Means for Contract Pentesters and MSSPs]]></title>
        <id>http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-contract-pentesters-and-mssps</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/http-1-1-must-die-what-this-means-for-contract-pentesters-and-mssps"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T22:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Black Hat USA and DEFCON 2025, PortSwigger's Director of Research, James Kettle, issued a stark warning: request smuggling isn't dying out, it's evolving and thriving. Despite years of defensive ef]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Desync Delusion: Are You Really Protected Against HTTP Request Smuggling?]]></title>
        <id>the-desync-delusion-are-you-really-protected-against-http-request-smuggling</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/the-desync-delusion-are-you-really-protected-against-http-request-smuggling"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T22:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hidden Threat That's Slipping Past Your Security HTTP request smuggling remains one of the most dangerous yet frequently overlooked web vulnerabilities today. Despite being a widely known issue si]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/1.1 must die: the desync endgame]]></title>
        <id>http1-must-die</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/http1-must-die"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T22:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract Upstream HTTP/1.1 is inherently insecure and regularly exposes millions of websites to hostile takeover. Six years of attempted mitigations have hidden the issue, but failed to fix it. This p]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Download OpenAI open-weight models gpt-oss:20/gpt-oss:120 in Ollama and use in VS Code GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1599028</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/download-openai-open-weight-models-gpt-oss20gpt-oss120-in-ollama-and-use-in-vs-code-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T18:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has just released its first open-weight models, gpt-oss:20 and gpt-oss:120, enabling you to run these surprisingly powerful models locally, which benefits security and privacy. I downloaded gpt-oss:20 and tested it on my laptop using Ollama and within VS Code with GitHub Copilot. To my surprise, the 20 billion parameter model gpt-oss:20 responded to my prompt.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Level Fingerprinting: Tools, Logic, and Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/next-level-fingerprinting-tools-logic-and-tactics</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/next-level-fingerprinting-tools-logic-and-tactics"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how combining AI-assisted research with real-world data and signature normalization can significantly improve fingerprinting capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost Calls: Abusing Web Conferencing for Covert Command & Control (Part 2 of 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5086</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/ghost-calls-abusing-web-conferencing-for-covert-command-control-part-2-of-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T12:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part one, we discussed the architecture of web conferencing applications, with a specific focus on Zoom’s architecture to support web conferencing at a massive global scale. Part two will discuss the approach we developed to support tunneling traffic through Zoom and Microsoft Teams using the TURN protocol.  Let’s start with a quick recap of […]
The post Ghost Calls: Abusing Web Conferencing for Covert Command & Control (Part 2 of 2) appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost Calls: Abusing Web Conferencing for Covert Command & Control (Part 1 of 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5083</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/ghost-calls-abusing-web-conferencing-for-covert-command-control-part-1-of-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T12:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the middle of a particularly tight red team engagement, we hit a familiar wall. Our long-term implant was rock solid—quiet, persistent, and thoroughly under the radar. But when it came time to pivot into something more interactive—proxy traffic, tunnel HVNC, relay NTLM—we started running into limits. The channel that worked so well for low-and-slow […]
The post Ghost Calls: Abusing Web Conferencing for Covert Command & Control (Part 1 of 2) appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Spent $500 To Test Devin For Prompt Injection So That You Don't Have To]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/devin-i-spent-usd500-to-hack-devin/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/devin-i-spent-usd500-to-hack-devin/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T08:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we cover Devin from Cognition, the first AI Software Engineer.
We will cover Devin proof-of-concept exploits in multiple posts over the next few days. In this first post, we show how a prompt injection payload hosted on a website leads to a full compromise of Devin’s DevBox.
GitHub Issue To Remote Code Execution By planting instructions on a website or GitHub issue that Devin processes, it can be tricked to download malware and launch it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt injection engineering for attackers: Exploiting GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/06/prompt-injection-engineering-for-attackers-exploiting-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/06/prompt-injection-engineering-for-attackers-exploiting-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt injection pervades discussions about security for LLMs and AI agents. But there is little public information on how to write powerful, discreet, and reliable prompt injection exploits. In this post, we will design and implement a prompt injection exploit targeting GitHub’s Copilot Agent, with a focus on maximizing reliability and minimizing the odds of detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid Breach: Social Engineering to Remote Access in 300 Seconds]]></title>
        <id>a3c928e5-d12a-4f8d-9ea5-8bdbc263bd9f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/research-blog/rapid-breach-social-engineering-to-remote-access-in-300-seconds/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T01:00:24.029Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to enable Edge Copilot Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598976</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-enable-edge-copilot-mode/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T13:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Edge Copilot Mode, announced a few days ago, Copilot shifts from being just an AI assistant to becoming the main browser interface. Now front and center in Microsoft's browser, Copilot has evolved into a serious ChatGPT competitor. In this post, I explain how to enable Edge Copilot Mode and discuss whether it introduces any new features compared to the previous version of Copilot in Edge.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amp Code: Arbitrary Command Execution via Prompt Injection Fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amp-agents-that-modify-system-configuration-and-escape/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/amp-agents-that-modify-system-configuration-and-escape/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T13:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sandbox-escape-style attacks can happen when an AI is able to modify its own configuration settings, such as by writing to configuration files.
That was the case with Amp, an agentic coding tool built by Sourcegraph.
The AI coding agent could update its own configuration and:
Allowlist bash commands or Add a malicious MCP server on the fly to run arbitrary code This could have been exploited by the model itself, or during an indirect prompt injection attack as we will demonstrate in this post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP Request Smuggling Explained: with seasoned bug bounty hunter NahamSec and world-class researcher James Kettle]]></title>
        <id>http-request-smuggling-explained-with-seasoned-bug-bounty-hunter-nahamsec-and-world-class-researcher-james-kettle</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/http-request-smuggling-explained-with-seasoned-bug-bounty-hunter-nahamsec-and-world-class-researcher-james-kettle"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T11:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how attackers can compromise modern websites by exploiting invisible cracks in HTTP infrastructure to win big bounties? In his latest video, NahamSec walks through the basics of request]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncovering memory corruption in NVIDIA Triton (as a new hire)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/04/uncovering-memory-corruption-in-nvidia-triton-as-a-new-hire/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/04/uncovering-memory-corruption-in-nvidia-triton-as-a-new-hire/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my first month at Trail of Bits as an AI/ML security engineer, I found two remotely accessible memory corruption bugs in NVIDIA’s Triton Inference Server during a routine onboarding practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Contract Scams | Ethereum Drainers Pose as Trading Bots to Steal Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=125939</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/smart-contract-scams-ethereum-drainers-pose-as-trading-bots-to-steal-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T10:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto scammers use fake YouTube bots, AI videos, and obfuscated smart contracts to steal $900K+, targeting unwary traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to transfer files in AWS using SSM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42464</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-to-transfer-files-in-aws-using-ssm/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T08:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The Problem You’ve done a build review on a host and need to get files from a host, or need to access an application, for example, a Nessus instance running internally. There’s always evidence generated, but generally the hosts you’re working on may have outbound Internet access blocked by a firewall, or they are […]
The post How to transfer files in AWS using SSM appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detection Engineering: Practicing Detection-as-Code – Validation – Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=20012</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2025/08/05/detection-engineering-practicing-detection-as-code-validation-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this part, we focus on implementing validation checks to improve consistency and ensure a minimum level of quality within the detection repository. Setting up validation pipelines is a key step, as it helps enforce the defined standards, reduce errors, and ensure that detections are reliable and consistent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stamatis Chatzimangou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reset forgotten ESXi 7.x / 8.x root password – A recovery guide]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598901</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/reset-forgotten-esxi-7x-8x-root-password-a-recovery-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T17:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you forget the root password for ESXi, VMware recommends reinstalling ESXi. In smaller environments without automated rollouts and central profiles, you must then configure all settings manually. Alternatively, you can reset the password using an unofficial method.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oops Safari, I think You Spilled Something!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2334</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2025/08/04/oops-safari-i-think-you-spilled-something/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T15:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In February 2023, researchers at Exodus Intelligence discovered a bug in the Data Flow Graph (DFG) compiler of WebKit, the browser engine used by Safari. This bug, CVE-2024-44308, was patched by Apple in November 2024. While it was alive, its exploit was chained with PAC and APRR bypasses on Apple Silicon to yield renderer ... Read more Oops Safari, I think You Spilled Something!
The post Oops Safari, I think You Spilled Something! appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost in the Zip | New PXA Stealer and Its Telegram-Powered Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=128686</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/ghost-in-the-zip-new-pxa-stealer-and-its-telegram-powered-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PXA Stealer uses advanced evasion and Telegram C2 to steal global victim data, fueling a thriving cybercrime market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Walter, Alex Delamotte, Beazley Security’s Francisco Donoso, Sam Mayers, Tell Hause &amp; Bobby Venal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cursor IDE: Arbitrary Data Exfiltration Via Mermaid (CVE-2025-54132)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/cursor-data-exfiltration-with-mermaid/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/cursor-data-exfiltration-with-mermaid/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T07:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cursor is a popular AI code editor. In this post I want to share how I found an interesting data exfiltration issue, the demo exploits built and how it got fixed.
When using Cursor I noticed that it can render Mermaid diagrams.
Cursor Renders Mermaid Diagrams If you are not familiar with Mermaid, it has a simple syntax:
graph TD User --> Computer This will create a diagram as follows:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Filesystem MCP Server: Directory Access Bypass via Improper Path Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/anthropic-filesystem-mcp-server-bypass/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/anthropic-filesystem-mcp-server-bypass/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-03T08:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago I was looking at the filesystem MCP server from Anthropic.
The server allows to give an AI, like Claude Desktop, access to the local filesystem to read files or edit them and so forth.
I was curious about access control and in the documentation there is a configuration setting to set allowedDirectories, which the AI should be allowed access to:
As you can see the example shows two folders being allowlisted for access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turning ChatGPT Codex Into A ZombAI Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/chatgpt-codex-remote-control-zombai/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/chatgpt-codex-remote-control-zombai/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-02T07:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we cover ChatGPT Codex as part of the Month of AI Bugs series.
ChatGPT Codex is a cloud-based software engineering agent that answers codebase questions, executes code, and drafts pull requests.
In particular, this post will demonstrate how Codex is vulnerable to prompt injection, and how the use of the “Common Dependencies Allowlist” for Internet access enables an attacker to recruit ChatGPT Codex into a malware botnet.
The ZombAI attack arrives at ChatGPT Codex today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in July]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10969</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2025/08/01/overview-of-content-published-in-july-10/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T19:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in July: Blog posts: Quickpost: Doorbell & Condensation Quickpost: 12V Portable Power Station SANS ISC Diary entries: Wireshark 4.4.8 Released WinRAR MoTW Propagation Privacy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows-MCP: Automating the Windows GUI with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598815</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-mcp-automating-the-windows-gui-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T19:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows-MCP is an open-source MCP server that enables AI agents to control the Windows operating system, supporting tasks such as file navigation, application launching, and GUI automation. It features mouse/keyboard input tools, clipboard management, and window and app state detection. I tested Windows-MCP, one of the extensions listed in Anthropic Claude Desktop that can be installed using the free plan.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exfiltrating Your ChatGPT Chat History and Memories With Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/chatgpt-chat-history-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/chatgpt-chat-history-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T15:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we demonstrate how a bypass in OpenAI’s “safe URL” rendering feature allows ChatGPT to send personal information to a third-party server. This can be exploited by an adversary via a prompt injection via untrusted data.
If you process untrusted content, like summarizing a website, or analyze a pdf document, the author of that document can exfiltrate any information present in the prompt context, including your past chat history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unconventional Innovator Scholarship]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/01/the-unconventional-innovator-scholarship/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/08/01/the-unconventional-innovator-scholarship/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits founder Dan Guido establishes a $2,500 scholarship at his alma mater, Mineola High School, to recognize students who demonstrate the hacker spirit through self-driven learning, creative problem-solving, and unconventional technological exploration. The scholarship celebrates tomorrow’s security innovators who push boundaries and think differently about technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Hardcoding Passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=21450</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2025/08/01/stop-hardcoding-passwords/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive into CyberArk’s Central CredentialProvider (CCP) Introduction Hardcoded credentials are still among the most critical and overlooked security flaws in modern software development. From leaked Git repos to reverse-engineered binaries, static passwords are easy targets. They also make rotation and access control almost impossible. Enter CyberArk’s Central Credential Provider (CCP): a secure, centralized … Continue reading Stop Hardcoding Passwords →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikolaos Grigoropoulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Returns to Ireland with a One Million Dollar WhatsApp Target]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:688ad635ba75553b33467fd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2025/7/30/pwn2own-returns-to-ireland-with-a-one-million-dollar-whatsapp-target"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T19:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here. 

Last year, we moved our consumer-focused Pwn2Own event to our offices in Cork, Ireland, and the event could not have gone better. Despite some dreary Irish skies, much fun was had as researchers from around the world demonstrated their best exploits – and we were reminded that electricity works a little differently in Europe. With that in mind, we’re excited to return to Cork this fall for yet another great Pwn2Own event. We’ll also be returning to some of the great pubs Ireland has to offer in the evenings and wrapping the event up at the historic Cork City Goal.
As you might have guessed from the title, we’re excited to announce that Meta is co-sponsoring this year’s event, and they are hoping to see some great WhatsApp exploi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Server real-time monitoring with Grafana]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598781</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sql-server-real-time-monitoring-with-grafana/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T16:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grafana offers enterprise-grade Microsoft SQL Server monitoring without the high licensing costs, making it ideal for comprehensive database observability, proactive database health monitoring, troubleshooting, and capacity planning. In my previous blog, I explained how to install Grafana 12 on Windows. This post will outline how to connect Grafana to SQL Server for real-time monitoring.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hijacking multi-agent systems in your PajaMAS]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/31/hijacking-multi-agent-systems-in-your-pajamas/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/31/hijacking-multi-agent-systems-in-your-pajamas/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re releasing pajaMAS: a curated set of MAS hijacking demos that illustrate important principles of MAS security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crack the Riddle, Secure the Oasis: Core NetWars Version 11 is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/crack-the-riddle-secure-the-oasis-core-netwars-version-11-is-here</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/crack-the-riddle-secure-the-oasis-core-netwars-version-11-is-here?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2025-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about SANS Institute's new Core NetWars Version 11]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding on ChunkyIngress - Clippy Goes Rogue (GoClipC2)]]></title>
        <id>663cbd24748ff8079069f78f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/clippy-goes-rogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-15T10:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoClipC2: A covert Windows clipboard-based C2 channel for VDI/RDP environments. Bypasses network monitoring with encrypted Base64 messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cost Savings of Fixing Security Flaws in Development]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/cost-savings-fixing-security-flaws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/cost-savings-fixing-security-flaws"/>
        <updated>2025-02-25T18:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Mateer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Approach to Proving Cybersecurity Value (That Isn’t ROI)]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/new-approach-proving-cybersecurity-value</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/new-approach-proving-cybersecurity-value"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T23:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we are excited to announce our white paper on Return on Mitigation (RoM), a framework we designed to quantify the financial impact of security programs in a way that speaks to business leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>joseph@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 Years of Partnership: Snap and HackerOne Reach $1M in Bounties]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/hackerone-and-snap-celebrating-10-years</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/hackerone-and-snap-celebrating-10-years"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T19:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Snap, security is more than a priority—it’s a core mission. Over the past decade, Snap has partnered with HackerOne to build and sustain a robust bug bounty program. This collaboration has led to major milestones, including paying security researchers over $1M in bounties. To celebrate this achievement and their 10-year partnership, we spoke with Jim Higgins, Snap's Chief Information Security Officer, Vinay Prabhushankar, Snap’s Security Engineering Manager, and Ilana Arbisser, Snap’s Privacy Engineer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women@ Kicks Off the Year with a Vision Board Event]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/women-kicks-year-vision-board-event</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/women-kicks-year-vision-board-event"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T18:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gain Actionable, Data-backed Insights with HackerOne Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/gain-actionable-data-backed-insights-hackerone-recommendations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/gain-actionable-data-backed-insights-hackerone-recommendations"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T23:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if your security program could self-optimize: analyze trends, identify weak points, and proactively propose actionable steps to strengthen defenses? With HackerOne Recommendations, it can.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Collins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, Hackbots: How AI Is Shaping the Future of Vulnerability Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/welcome-hackbots-how-ai-shaping-future-vulnerability-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/welcome-hackbots-how-ai-shaping-future-vulnerability-discovery"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Hackbots and how are they impacting vulnerability discovery and the researcher community?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DORA Compliance Is Here: What Financial Entities Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/dora-compliance-here-what-financial-entities-should-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/dora-compliance-here-what-financial-entities-should-know"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T17:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new DORA regulation: everything your organization needs to know about its impact and how to comply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vanessa Booth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>