<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-02-17T00:44:02.272Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How-to: Make Your Own Cert With Web OpenSSL]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9701</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/02/17/how-to-make-your-own-cert-with-web-openssl/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I explain how to create certificates with OpenSSL on your Windows computer in my blog post “How-to: Make Your Own Cert With OpenSSL on Windows (Reloaded)“. If you can’t or don’t want to install OpenSSL, there is a solution now with Web OpenSSL. With Web OpenSSL, you can just run OpenSSL and the commands in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rustproofing Linux (Part 4/4 Shared Memory)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18659</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/02/16/rustproofing-linux-part-4-4-shared-memory/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T19:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a four part blog post series that starts with Rustproofing Linux (Part 1/4 Leaking Addresses). Shared memory is often used to share data without the performance hit of copying. Whenever a shared resource is consumed by one component while being modified by another component, there is potential for Time-Of-Check-Time-Of-Use (TOCTOU) or Double Fetch … Continue reading Rustproofing Linux (Part 4/4 Shared Memory) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Domen Puncer Kugler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating More Secure Cloud Environments with Microsoft and Synack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16017</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/creating-secure-cloud-environments-with-microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T15:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cloud moves fast, software development moves fast and attackers move fast too. Can your cloud governance keep up? Setting up security controls correctly at the start of a cloud migration project won’t work in the long-term with rapidly changing cloud environments. Cloud security benchmarks must be continuously followed to be effective, requiring frequent testing […]
The post Creating More Secure Cloud Environments with Microsoft and Synack appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Copeland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pivoting with Azure Automation Account Connections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=29393</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/cloud-penetration-testing/azure-automation-account-connections/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover a helpful function for enumerating potential pivot points from an existing Azure Automation Account with Contributor level access.
The post Pivoting with Azure Automation Account Connections appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Fosaaen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage and secure your endpoints in hybrid environments with ManageEngine Endpoint Central]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570182</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-and-secure-your-endpoints-in-hybrid-environments-with-manageengine-endpoint-central/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T13:34:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how ManageEngine Endpoint Central (formerly ManageEngine Desktop Central) provides the tools and automation needed for managing endpoints, patching, deploying software, and installing operating systems in today's hybrid remote work environments.
Manage and secure your endpoints in hybrid environments with ManageEngine Endpoint Central first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Readline crime: exploiting a SUID logic bug]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103852</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/02/16/suid-logic-bug-linux-readline/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By roddux // Rory M I discovered a logic bug in the readline dependency partially reveals file information when parsing the file specified in the INPUTRC environment variable. This could allow attackers to move laterally on a box where sshd is running, a given user is able to login, and the user’s private key is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Teaming: The Ultimate Sanity Check for Security Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/red-teaming-sanity-check</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/red-teaming-sanity-check"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to take control of security program investments with Red Teaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trevin Edgeworth, Mark MacDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIP26 Espionage | Threat Actors Abuse Cloud Infrastructure in Targeted Telco Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=76591</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/wip26-espionage-threat-actors-abuse-cloud-infrastructure-in-targeted-telco-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T10:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new threat cluster has been targeting telecommunication providers in the Middle East and abusing Microsoft, Google and Dropbox cloud services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: process-binary-file Version 0.0.9]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9940</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/02/16/update-process-binary-file-version-0-0-9/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a bug fix update. python-templates_V0_0_10.zip (http)MD5: 29806A562411E4584455746C8CE41BABSHA256: CC520C26BE6E59F48AEA639EC477983333D75F91FFE295915DB4711C275E26DB]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Security Awareness Professional: A New Look for the SSAP Digital Badge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-security-awareness-professional-a-new-look-for-the-ssap-digital-badge</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-security-awareness-professional-a-new-look-for-the-ssap-digital-badge?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the expansion of the curriculum in this area comes a small but significant update to the SSAP digital credential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run WSUS cleanup as a scheduled task]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570142</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/run-wsus-cleanup-as-a-scheduled-task/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T17:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing updates that are no longer needed or that have been replaced is important to keep WSUS in a healthy state. However, in the daily routine, admins often forget to execute the wizard for WSUS cleanup manually. Hence, it is more reliable if you set up a scheduled task for it.
Run WSUS cleanup as a scheduled task first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Server-side prototype pollution: Black-box detection without the DoS]]></title>
        <id>server-side-prototype-pollution</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/server-side-prototype-pollution"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Server-side prototype pollution is hard to detect black-box without causing a DoS. In this post, we introduce a range of safe detection techniques, which we've also implemented in an open source Burp]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abusing Azure App Service Managed Identity Assignments]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c3adefccff95</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/abusing-azure-app-service-managed-identity-assignments-c3adefccff95?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T16:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Azure B2C – Crypto Misuse and Account Compromise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4425</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/azure-b2c-crypto-misuse-and-account-compromise/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T15:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Azure Active Directory B2C service contained a cryptographic flaw which allowed an attacker to craft an OAuth refresh token with the contents for any user account. An attacker could redeem this refresh token for a session token, thereby gaining access to a victim account as if the attacker had logged in through a legitimate […]
The post Technical Advisory – Azure B2C – Crypto Misuse and Account Compromise appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exodus Intelligence has been authorized by the CVE Program as a CVE Numbering Authority (CNA).]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2065</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/02/14/exodus-intelligence-has-been-authorized-by-the-cve-program-as-a-cve-numbering-authority-cna/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=exodus-intelligence-has-been-authorized-by-the-cve-program-as-a-cve-numbering-authority-cna"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T02:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exodus Intelligence has been authorized by the CVE Program as a CVE Numbering Authority (CNA). Exodus Intelligence, the leader in Vulnerability Research, today announced it has been authorized by the CVE Program as a CVE Numbering Authority (CNA).  As a CNA, Exodus is authorized to assign CVE IDs to newly discovered vulnerabilities and publicly disclose ... Read more Exodus Intelligence has been authorized by the CVE Program as a CVE Numbering Authority (CNA).
The post Exodus Intelligence has been authorized by the CVE Program as a CVE Numbering Authority (CNA). appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: cut-bytes.py Version 0.0.16]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9937</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/02/15/update-cut-bytes-py-version-0-0-16/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new version of cut-bytes.py, I add support for custom Python transforms (options -P and -S), pyzipper and fixed a bug. cut-bytes_V0_0_16.zip (http)MD5: 04E6E0E46C6698127BAE443AF5CEF0F6SHA256: 0657F6A6837CEC9F3E9E50551F8861D19B70305A4B7C3C409D561C3462550D24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cybersecurity-leadership-curriculum</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cybersecurity-leadership-curriculum?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Curriculum which is developing cyber security managers and leaders worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rustproofing Linux (Part 3/4 Integer Overflows)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18658</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/02/14/rustproofing-linux-part-3-4-integer-overflows/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T21:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a four part blog post series that starts with Rustproofing Linux (Part 1/4 Leaking Addresses). In the C programming language, integer types can be a bit confusing. Portability issues can arise when the same code is used in multiple hardware architectures or operating systems. For example, int is usually 32-bit, but could also … Continue reading Rustproofing Linux (Part 3/4 Integer Overflows) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Domen Puncer Kugler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The February 2023 Security Update Overview]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63e17166890ebd566367657f</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/2/14/the-february-2023-security-update-overview"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T18:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the second patch Tuesday of 2023. On this romantic holiday, Microsoft and Adobe have released their latest security patches as Valentine’s gifts for us all. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities (or Pwn2Own Miami) and join us as we review the details of their latest security offerings.
Adobe Patches for February 2023
For February, Adobe released nine patches addressing 28 CVEs in Adobe Photoshop, Substance 3D Stager, Animate, InDesign, Bridge, FrameMaker, Connect, and After Effects. A total of 21 of these were reported by ZDI vulnerability researcher Mat Powell. Probably the most interesting fix is for PhotoShop. This patch fixes five bugs, three of which are rated Critical. An attacker could get arbitrary code execution if they can convince a user on an affected…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAKIVO Backup & Replication v10.8 with new cloud and MSP features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570121</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/nakivo-backup-replication-v108-with-new-cloud-and-msp-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T16:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NAKIVO Backup & Replication v10.8 delivers excellent new cloud and managed service provider (MSP) features, allowing businesses to meet modern data protection challenges.
NAKIVO Backup & Replication v10.8 with new cloud and MSP features first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Miami 2023 - Day One Results]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63e2cb3f3fc4dd669e134b36</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/2/14/pwn2own-miami-2023-day-one-results"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T15:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first day of Pwn2Own Miami for 2023. We’ll be updating this blog in real time as results become available. For this year’s event, each round will receive the full payout for unique entries. We’ll update this blog throughout the day with results as they come in.
All results current as of 1615 Eastern (GMT -5)
SUCCESS - Claroty was able to execute their DoS attack against the Inductive Automation Ignition. They earn $5,000 and 5 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS – Team ECQ used a Null Pointer Deref to complete their DoS attack against Softing edgeConnector Siemens. They earn $5,000 and 5 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS – Claroty used a four-bug chain in their attack against the Triangle Microworks SCADA Data Gateway. They earn $20,000 and 20 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - 20urdjk was able to execute their RCE attack against the Inductive Automation Ignition. They earn $20,000 and 20 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Claroty used a resource exhaustion to demonstrate their DoS attack against the PTC KepServerEx. They earn $5,000 and 5 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Claroty used a resource exhaustion to demonstrate their DoS attack against the OPC Foundation OPC UA .NET Standard. They earn $5,000 and 5 Master of Pwn points.
That wraps up the first day of Pwn2Own Toronto 2022! We awarded $60,000 for 6 unique bugs during the first day of the contest. We’ll continue posting results and videos to Twitter, YouTube, Mastodon, LinkedIn, and Instagram, so follow us on your favorite flavor of social media for the latest news from the event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cURL audit: How a joke led to significant findings]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103815</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/02/14/curl-audit-fuzzing-libcurl-command-line-interface/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T13:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Maciej Domanski In fall 2022, Trail of Bits audited cURL, a widely-used command-line utility that transfers data between a server and supports various protocols. The project coincided with a Trail of Bits maker week, which meant that we had more manpower than we usually do, allowing us to take a nonstandard approach to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fill the Gaps in Your Cybersecurity Program with On-Demand Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16013</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/fill-the-gaps-with-on-demand-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T11:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Pentesting Doesn’t Always Cover All Your Bases Continuous vs. On-Demand Testing In a previous article we described the benefits of doing continuous pentesting in a strategic cybersecurity program.  Frequent product changes and updates, rapidly changing cloud infrastructures, and a seemingly never-ending train of newly-introduced vulnerabilities all point to the need for continuous vigilance and […]
The post Fill the Gaps in Your Cybersecurity Program with On-Demand Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[60%+ Performance Improvements with Continuous Profiling and Library Matching – Part 1/2 on Combining Dynamic and Static Analysis for Performance Optimisation]]></title>
        <id>http://sean.heelan.io/?p=2665</id>
        <link href="https://sean.heelan.io/2023/02/14/combining-static-and-dynamic-analysis-in-performance-optimisation-part-1-60-improvements-with-continuous-profiling-and-library-matching/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T10:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first post in a two part series on combining static and dynamic analyses for performance optimisation. I’ve split them up as otherwise it’ll be horrifically long, and the second post will be online later this week. This post lays out some high level context, discusses why we should combine analyses, and has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>seanhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: xor-kpa.py Version 0.0.7]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9934</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/02/14/update-xor-kpa-py-version-0-0-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I added extra plaintexts for the modulus of Cobalt Strike’s public RSA key. xor-kpa_V0_0_7.zip (http)MD5: FB8155E56234648CC3AFFD890BFE9043SHA256: 069DCA2A1901D448DBF2CF202B5CE49846EFCBAACB73BF35B20AA085AAB31BA9]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Miami 2023 - The Full Schedule]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63e170290c3cba1d23922bba</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/2/13/pwn2own-miami-2023-the-full-schedule"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T22:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[¡Bienvenidos a Miami!
Welcome to Pwn2Own Miami for 2023! We’ve got another exciting event with 16 entries target 11 different targets. As always, we began our contest with a random drawing to determine the order of attempts. If you missed it, you can watch the replay here. 
The complete schedule for the contest is below (all times Eastern [GMT -5:00]). 
Note: All times subject to change
Tuesday, February 14 - 0930
Claroty Research - Team82 targeting the Inductive Automation Ignition - DoS in the OPC UA Server category for $5,000 and 5 Master of Pwn points
Tuesday, February 14 - 1030
Team ECQ targeting the Softing edgeConnector Siemens - DoS in the OPC UA Server category for $5,000 and 5 Master of Pwn points
Tuesday, February 14 - 1130
Claroty Research - Team82 targeting the Triangle Microw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: file-magic.py Version 0.0.6]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9929</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/02/13/update-file-magic-py-version-0-0-6/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T18:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of file-magic.py adds a definition to identify OneNote .one files: And adds support for pyzipper. file-magic_V0_0_6.zip (http)MD5: 2C564E9B215672BA9352934C8B91B0ECSHA256: 6102CE6788EB17B17AB3C0AB054FE9ECA2C557E9349A7ACF9612759CC5C6CA97]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macvlan network driver: Assign MAC address to Docker containers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570086</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/macvlan-network-driver-assign-mac-address-to-docker-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T13:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The macvlan network driver allows you to assign a MAC address to Docker containers, which enables your containerized application to connect directly to your physical network.
Macvlan network driver: Assign MAC address to Docker containers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing - It's No Longer About Malware (or Even Email)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/phishing-its-no-longer-about-malware-or-even-email</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/phishing-its-no-longer-about-malware-or-even-email?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber attackers have continued to adapt their phishing methods to the changing technological and social landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: pdf-parser.py Version 0.7.8]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9918</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/02/12/update-pdf-parser-py-version-0-7-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-12T12:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small feature update for pdf-parser.py Statistics include unreferenced objects now: pdf-parser_V0_7_8.zip (http)MD5: 7BBEA9497666397CBBB88B012A710210SHA256: FE393865861E00B48124B99CD5AEBBB5A632F1FBD883F4E4044DF8C8FA75BE9D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimising an eBPF Optimiser with Prodfiler (Repost)]]></title>
        <id>http://sean.heelan.io/?p=2604</id>
        <link href="https://sean.heelan.io/2023/02/10/optimising-an-ebpf-optimiser-with-prodfiler-repost/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T17:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you almost 2x your application’s performance with zero code changes? Read on to find out! This is a repost of a blog I originally wrote on prodfiler.com on October 4th 2021. Prodfiler was acquired by Elastic is is now the Elastic Universal Profiler. In this post I will walk through how we can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>seanhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telemetry Layering]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/89185b5348ba</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/telemetry-layering-89185b5348ba?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T15:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSUS cleanup aborting: Increase timeout for database and IIS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570063</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/wsus-cleanup-aborting-increase-timeout-for-database-and-iis/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T12:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If many expired or superseded updates have accumulated in WSUS, then the server cleanup wizard will hang. The problem is often difficult to solve, but promising measures include a longer timeout for the IIS and the database, and more memory for the IIS AppPool.
WSUS cleanup aborting: Increase timeout for database and IIS first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Leveraging dynamic sections – text]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12998</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/02/10/cortex-xsoar-tips-tricks-leveraging-dynamic-sections-text/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Cortex XSOAR is a security oriented automation platform, and one of the areas where it stands out is customization. A recurring problem in a SOC (Security Operation Center) is data availability. As a SOC Analyst, doing a thorough analysis of a security incident requires having access to many pieces of information in order to … Continue reading Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Leveraging dynamic sections – text →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Danjoux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From DevOops! to DevSecOps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/from-devoops-to-devsecops</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/from-devoops-to-devsecops?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part one of a four-part blog series about what’s needed to shake, shimmy, and shift left]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Cloud Log Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/aws-cloud-log-extraction</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/aws-cloud-log-extraction?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we discussed the acquisition of AWS CloudTrails logs stored in S3 buckets. Specifically, we provided three different methods of obtaining the logs: the web console, the CLI, and API-based tools. Regardless of the method most suited for your use case, extracting these logs will allow for a more in-depth analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploits Explained: Default Credentials Still a Problem Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16007</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/default-credentials-still-a-problem-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T18:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popeax is a member of the Synack Red Team. Often people think security research requires deep knowledge of systems and exploits, and sometimes it does, but in this case all it took was some curiosity and a Google search to find an alarmingly simple exploit using default credentials. On a recent host engagement, I discovered […]
The post Exploits Explained: Default Credentials Still a Problem Today appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SRT Community</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Code Review With ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18880</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/02/09/security-code-review-with-chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T17:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR: Don’t use ChatGPT for security code review. It’s not meant to be used that way, it doesn’t really work (although you might be fooled into thinking it does), and there are some other major problems that make it impractical. Also, both the CEO of OpenAI and ChatGPT itself say that you shouldn’t. Large Language … Continue reading Security Code Review With ChatGPT →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chrisanley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASM: The Best Defense is a Good Offense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4419</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/the-best-defense-is-a-good-offense/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About 10 years ago, security was relatively simple because everything occurred on premises. Change releases were tightly controlled by a change ticket and review process. In contrast, current networks consist of auto-scaling containers that run in Kubernetes clusters and even serverless clusters like AWS Lambda. We have transitioned from constrained environments that humans closely scrutinized […]
The post ASM: The Best Defense is a Good Offense appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 12 Hacking Influencers to Follow]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/12-hacking-influencers</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/12-hacking-influencers"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this blog to learn about our favorite influencers to follow on the hacker scene.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Britt Kemp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage BitLocker centrally with AppTec360 EMM]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570053</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-bitlocker-centrally-with-apptec360-emm/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T11:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AppTec360 Enterprise Mobility Management (EMM) is not only suitable for managing mobile devices but also PCs. For PCs, the Swiss company follows Microsoft's concept of "modern management" via MDM interfaces. Its BitLocker module allows unattended encryption and offers key management.
Manage BitLocker centrally with AppTec360 EMM first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Radonic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence - What to Tell Your Workforce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/artificial-intelligence-what-to-tell-your-workforce</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/artificial-intelligence-what-to-tell-your-workforce?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not sure what to share or communicate to your workforce about Artificial Intelligence?  Here are some key points you can share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v3.2 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5acb517f154c</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-v3-2-release-5acb517f154c?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T17:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SpecterOps has released Ghostwriter v3.2 with some significant enhancements we think you’ll like. We overhauled how you interact with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Maddalena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Proof Your IAM with Arculix – Purified AI/ML Continuous Passwordless Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=47036</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/future-proof-your-iam-with-arculix-purified-ai-ml-continuous-passwordless-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T15:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up on a dairy farm, my great grandpa would speak of a time when he didn’t have pasteurizing equipment. Customers then had to trust the dairy farmer was milking cows with clean hands, using a clean bucket, and placing the milk in clean milk bottles before being placed on the shelf. If our dairy became known […]
The post Future Proof Your IAM with Arculix – Purified AI/ML Continuous Passwordless Authentication appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jendres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Owning Two Hosts at the Same Time: Abusing Inductive Automation Ignition’s Custom Deserialization]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63e12991399ae276125218e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/2/6/pwn2owning-two-hosts-at-the-same-time-abusing-inductive-automation-ignitions-custom-deserialization"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T15:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Miami 2022 was a fine competition. At the contest, I successfully exploited three different targets. In this blog post, I would like to show you my personal best research of the competition: the custom deserialization issue in Inductive Automation Ignition. 
There are several things that make this vulnerability interesting, including the following:
·       It exists in a custom deserialization routine, which seems to derive some inspiration from the Java XMLDecoder.
·       It allows you to gain Remote Code Execution on two hosts at the same time: the client where the malicious project file is initially loaded, as well as the server that ultimately handles the file.
·       There is a nice platform that can help an attacker deliver the malicious file to potential victims.
·       I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rustproofing Linux (Part 2/4 Race Conditions)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18655</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/02/08/rustproofing-linux-part-2-4-race-conditions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T15:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a four part blog post series that starts with Rustproofing Linux (Part 1/4 Leaking Addresses). This post uses a simple example to demonstrate a class of vulnerability that we encounter quite frequently when auditing kernel drivers and firmware. It’s a race condition, or more precisely a TOCTOU vulnerability. The complete vulnerable C driver … Continue reading Rustproofing Linux (Part 2/4 Race Conditions) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Domen Puncer Kugler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 web hacking techniques of 2022]]></title>
        <id>top-10-web-hacking-techniques-of-2022</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/top-10-web-hacking-techniques-of-2022"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T14:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Top 10 Web Hacking Techniques of 2022, the 16th edition of our annual community-powered effort to identify the most important and innovative web security research published in the last]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Data Studio vs. SQL Server Management (SSMS)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570039</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/azure-data-studio-vs-sql-server-management-ssms/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T13:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your Windows systems administration work touches SQL Server products, you need to know when Azure Data Studio is the right fit over the time-tested and venerable SQL Server Management Studio (SSMS).
Azure Data Studio vs. SQL Server Management (SSMS) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Let’s Make Some OneNote Phishing Attachments]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/a14f4ef6ccc4</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-read-team-lets-make-some-onenote-phishing-attachments-a14f4ef6ccc4?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T21:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous blog post I showed how we can use LNK files to launch initial access payloads. In the weeks since, Microsoft has seemed to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outsmart Cybercriminals with Proactive Attack Surface Management (ASM)]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/outsmart-cybercriminals-proactive-attack-surface-management-asm</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/outsmart-cybercriminals-proactive-attack-surface-management-asm"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T19:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is ASM Important?
Your attack surface is the sum of all entry points an attacker could use to access your systems, applications, devices, or ne]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Microsoft 365 with SCOM and the NiCE Active 365 Management Pack]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1570014</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/monitoring-microsoft-365-with-scom-and-the-nice-active-365-management-pack/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T14:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NiCE Active 365 Management Pack for System Center Operations Manager (SCOM) tracks availability, activity, performance, security checks, and health by performing end-to-end probes. The management pack supports SharePoint Online, Exchange Online and Exchange hybrid, OneDrive, and Teams (including call quality). It includes metrics and checks for license usage, Azure AD Connect, and even Azure AD service principals.
Monitoring Microsoft 365 with SCOM and the NiCE Active 365 Management Pack first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ruben Zimmermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cl0p Ransomware Targets Linux Systems with Flawed Encryption | Decryptor Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=76058</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/cl0p-ransomware-targets-linux-systems-with-flawed-encryption-decryptor-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T10:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An in-the-wild ELF variant of Cl0p ransomware shows the gang is looking beyond traditional Windows targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonis Terefos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Causing incidents with in-flight entertainment systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26461</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/causing-incidents-with-in-flight-entertainment-systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T06:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some odd things have happened on airplanes recently. The voice on the PA system on an American Airlines flight was one of these. Before the airline put out a response, we were asked […]
Causing incidents with in-flight entertainment systems first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rustproofing Linux (Part 1/4 Leaking Addresses)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18577</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/02/06/rustproofing-linux-part-1-4-leaking-addresses/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T22:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust is a programming language guaranteeing memory and thread safety while still being able to access raw memory and hardware. This sounds impossible, and it is, that’s why Rust has an unsafe keyword which allows a programmer to dereference a raw pointer and perform some other dangerous operations. The dangerous code is effectively contained to … Continue reading Rustproofing Linux (Part 1/4 Leaking Addresses) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Domen Puncer Kugler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Tools: From Our Lab to Your Fingertips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4415</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/open-source-tools-from-our-lab/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T20:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core decisions we’ve made at Praetorian is to maximize efficiency and effectiveness. In pursuit of this, we carefully select and implement automation and technical solutions for tasks that don’t need human attention. The key is choosing thoughtfully developed tech and tools; when we can’t find what we need, we create it ourselves! […]
The post Open Source Tools: From Our Lab to Your Fingertips appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker AFK: Rhynorater]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-afk-rhynorater</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-afk-rhynorater"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T18:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's hacker Rhynorater
JXoaT: Where did you first hear about hacking? What was your first exposure to it?
Rhynorater: So, my first exp]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local password manager with Bitwarden unified]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569988</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/local-password-manager-with-bitwarden-unified/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T15:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitwarden unified self-hosted deployment is an excellent local password manager. In this post, I will explain the difference between Bitwarden unified and Bitwarden standard, outline the installation of Bitwarden unified, and show you how to configure your new local password manager.
Local password manager with Bitwarden unified first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synack’s Top 5 Vulnerabilities Found in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15997</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/top-5-vulnerabilities-found-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T11:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT and Cybersecurity leaders need the clearest picture of their networks and assets to understand if their organizations are at risk and what to do about it. When it comes to looking ahead at zero day vulnerabilities, it can be helpful for leaders to first look back to understand the collective strengths and weaknesses of […]
The post Synack’s Top 5 Vulnerabilities Found in 2022 appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michelle Welch Fuller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in January]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9916</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/02/04/overview-of-content-published-in-january-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-04T18:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in January: Blog posts: New Tool: onedump.py Update: process-binary-file Version 0.0.8 Analyzing Malicious OneNote Documents SANS ISC Diary entries: YARA v4.3.0-rc1 –skip-larger Wireshark 4.0.3 Released Detecting (Malicious) OneNote Files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Custom Mach-O Memory Loader for macOS - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/building-a-mach-o-memory-loader-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/building-a-mach-o-memory-loader-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-04T10:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog we'll look at what it takes to construct an in-memory loader for Mach-O bundles within MacOS Ventura without using dyld. We'll walk though the lower-level details of what makes up a Mach-O file, how dyld processes load commands to map areas into memory, and how we can emulate this to avoid writing payloads to disk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning 102: Attacking Facial Authentication with Poisoned Data]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18546</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/02/03/machine-learning-102-attacking-facial-authentication-with-poisoned-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T19:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post is the second in a series related to machine learning, and demonstrates exactly how a data poisoning attack might work to insert a backdoor into a facial authentication system. The simplified system has similarities to that which the TSA is running a proof of concept trial at the Detroit and Atlanta airports. As background, … Continue reading Machine Learning 102: Attacking Facial Authentication with Poisoned Data →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambassador Spotlight: Encryptsaan123]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/ambassador-spotlight-encryptsaan123</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/ambassador-spotlight-encryptsaan123"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T16:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyze Windows memory usage with RAMMap]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569976</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/analyze-windows-memory-usage-with-rammap/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have a performance issue, random access memory (RAM) is usually the second thing to check right after the CPU counters. Let's see how you can analyze Windows memory usage with RAMMap, a tool from the Sysinternals suite.
Analyze Windows memory usage with RAMMap first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploits Explained: Java JMX’s Exploitation Problems and Resolutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15983</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/exploits-explained-java-jmxs-exploitation-problems-and-resolutions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T18:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicolas Krassas is a member of the Synack Red Team and has earned distinctions such as SRT Envoy and Guardian of Trust. Of all the Synack targets, my favorite ones are always host assessments. There, one can find a multitude of services with different configurations, versions and usage. One that always caused me trouble was […]
The post Exploits Explained: Java JMX’s Exploitation Problems and Resolutions appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SRT Community</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extending LVM space in Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569958</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/extending-lvm-space-in-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T13:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you ever install Ubuntu Linux with the default LVM (logical volume manager) partition layout and give it a really small disk size to begin with? This usually happens while setting up an EC2 instance in AWS, since the root volume gets 8 GB EBS storage by default. After using your instance for some time, you realize that there is no free space left on the disk. In this post, I will cover how to extend the LVM space in Ubuntu Linux.
Extending LVM space in Ubuntu first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MalVirt  | .NET Virtualization Thrives in Malvertising Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=76167</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/malvirt-net-virtualization-thrives-in-malvertising-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T10:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET malware loaders distributed through malvertising are using obfuscated virtualization for anti-analysis and evasion in an ongoing campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[ru] Зеркалирование GitHub-проектов в 2023 году]]></title>
        <id>https://a13xp0p0v.github.io/2023/02/01/mirroring-github-projects-ru.html</id>
        <link href="https://a13xp0p0v.github.io/2023/02/01/mirroring-github-projects-ru.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[По ряду причин я решил зеркалировать свои открытые GitHub-проекты на другие платформы совместной разработки. Сделать это оказалось не так просто. В этой короткой статье описаны трудности, с которыми мне пришлось столкнуться, и итоговое рабочее решение.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Popov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoofy: An Email Domain Spoofing Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/spoofy-email-domain-spoofing</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/spoofy-email-domain-spoofing"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, take a deep dive into Spoofy, an opensource tool that offers bulk domain lookup based on DMARC and SPF records.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Minikube to get started with Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569922</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-minikube-to-get-started-with-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T13:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minikube is a lightweight local Kubernetes engine for macOS, Linux, and Windows. You can use Minikube as a test bed, or if you are new to Kubernetes, explore how to configure and deploy pods. In this post, I will explain how to install Minikube on Ubuntu 22.04, and I will teach you how to take your first steps with Kubernetes.
Install Minikube to get started with Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond a VDP: How a Challenge Brings Proactive Security to Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/beyond-vdp-how-challenge-brings-proactive-security-your-agency</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/beyond-vdp-how-challenge-brings-proactive-security-your-agency"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Disclosure Programs create an effective means for researchers and other users to report discovered vulnerabilities and weaknesses. Becau]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare AD synchronization with Azure Active Directory using IdFix]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569903</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/prepare-ad-synchronization-with-azure-active-directory-using-idfix/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T13:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations are migrating their on-premises email to Microsoft 365. One of the necessary steps is synchronizing your local directory with Azure Active Directory. The IdFix tool from Microsoft is meant to help correct issues before synchronizing your directory.
Prepare AD synchronization with Azure Active Directory using IdFix first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Modelling Cloud Platform Services by Example: Google Cloud Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15677</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/01/31/threat-modelling-cloud-platform-services-by-example-google-cloud-storage/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T01:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction The consumption of cloud services has grown rapidly over the last few years and one of the major providers to benefit from this growth is Google Cloud Platform (GCP). The security challenges faced by small/medium companies and enterprises when deploying new services into the cloud can often be daunting, so to get a better … Continue reading Threat Modelling Cloud Platform Services by Example: Google Cloud Storage →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Wolstencroft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PowerToys for Windows 10 and Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569889</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/powertoys-for-windows-10-and-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T17:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you haven't yet begun using the PowerToys tools for Windows 10 and 11 to accelerate your workflows as a Windows system administrator, you should. Let Tim show you how and why.
PowerToys for Windows 10 and Windows 11 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirroring GitHub projects in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://a13xp0p0v.github.io/2023/01/29/mirroring-github-projects.html</id>
        <link href="https://a13xp0p0v.github.io/2023/01/29/mirroring-github-projects.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-29T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many reasons, I want to mirror my public GitHub projects on other collaboration platforms. This short article describes my difficulties with it and a working solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Popov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite roadmap update: January 2023]]></title>
        <id>burp-suite-roadmap-update-january-2023</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/burp-suite-roadmap-update-january-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T14:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Believe it or not, it's January once again. And this can mean only one thing - it's time to update you on the changes we've got in store for Burp Suite over the next six months.     But this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recommended security settings and new group policies for Microsoft Edge (from 107 on)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569862</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/recommended-security-settings-and-new-group-policies-for-microsoft-edge-from-107-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T14:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft last updated its security baseline for Edge browser 107, but it is still valid for the current versions. It contains the manufacturer's recommended group policy settings to increase security. However, none of the most recent policies are included in the list.
Recommended security settings and new group policies for Microsoft Edge (from 107 on) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Packetlabs Ltd delivers advanced testing capabilities with Burp Suite Certified Practitioners]]></title>
        <id>packetlabs-ltd-delivers-advanced-testing-capabilities-with-burp-suite-certified-practitioners</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/packetlabs-ltd-delivers-advanced-testing-capabilities-with-burp-suite-certified-practitioners"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T11:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched the Burp Suite Certified Practitioner (BSCP) certification at the end of 2021 due to growing demand from Burp Suite Professional customers. Spanning everything from classic vulnerability c]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Strategic Pentesting in Your Vulnerability Management Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15924</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/how-to-deploy-strategic-pentesting-in-your-vulnerability-management-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T20:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Test to Find the Exploitable Vulnerabilities and Their Root Causes Vulnerability Management in Your Cybersecurity Program Today’s complex software systems often include code that leaves them vulnerable to attack by hackers who are always looking for a way to break in. And even with a system with no inherent vulnerabilities, a misconfiguration or careless deployment […]
The post How to Deploy Strategic Pentesting in Your Vulnerability Management Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grappling with the Unpredictable Second-Order Effects of LLM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4381</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/second-order-effects-of-llm/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T15:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yogi Berra was (among other things) an incredible quote machine, and he’s often credited with the following gem: “It’s tough to make predictions, especially about the future.” Yes indeed. Seeing how the world will unfold is incredibly difficult because of how convoluted second-order effects can become. So, with the legendary Mr. Berra providing me with […]
The post Grappling with the Unpredictable Second-Order Effects of LLM appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backup in Proxmox VE]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569795</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/backup-in-proxmox-ve/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T14:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integrated backup feature in Proxmox VE allows you to perform a backup of selected or all VMs at once. Unlike snapshots, backups are independent copies of original data that can be stored either locally or remotely so that you can recover from almost any kind of failure.
Backup in Proxmox VE first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Automotive: Bringing Researchers and Auto Manufacturers Together]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63d0798d3ab8241a1eb0a6e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/1/24/pwn2own-automotive-bringing-researchers-and-auto-manufacturers-together"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T12:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today at the Automotive World conference in Tokyo, Japan, I presented a talk in the Cyber Security from the Perspectives of Hackers and Automakers track.  During this presentation, I announced the ZDI will host a new Pwn2Own contest focused on automotive systems – Pwn2Own Automotive. This contest will be held at next year’s Automotive World in January 2024. Tokyo has hosted many Pwn2Own competitions in the past, and we’re excited to return with a new event focusing solely on automotive components and technologies. In doing this, we have three primary goals for the contest:
1.     Provide an avenue to encourage automotive research. We want to offer a place where researchers can submit and be financially rewarded for reports targeting various products and platforms.
2.     Incentivize vendor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Semgrep with Jupyter Notebook files]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18690</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/01/26/using-semgrep-with-jupyter-notebook-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T01:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you frequently deliver source code review assessments of products, including machine learning components, I’m sure you are used to reviewing Jupyter Notebook files (usually python). Although I spend most of my time reviewing the source code manually, I also use static analysis tools such as semgrep, using both public and private rules. This tool … Continue reading Using Semgrep with Jupyter Notebook files →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Selvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The What & How of Role Role-Based Training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-what-how-of-role-role-based-training</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-what-how-of-role-role-based-training?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Role-based training is playing a bigger and bigger role in the world of security awareness and managing human risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video Tutorial: Hijacking SSH Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/video-hijacking-ssh-agent/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/video-hijacking-ssh-agent/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T17:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I got the feedback to create more tutorials and videos, and I thought SSH Agent Hijacking on Linux and macOS (which I wrote about before here) would make a good one.
The video tutorial is here.

If you like this kind of content, then comment or like the video on YouTube and I’ll create more.
Hope it’s useful to get a good basic understanding of this TTP, and help build detections for it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At the Edge of Tier Zero: The Curious Case of the RODC]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ef5f1799ca06</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/at-the-edge-of-tier-zero-the-curious-case-of-the-rodc-ef5f1799ca06?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T14:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Elad Shamir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EzAdsPro BlackBox Advisory]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/ezadspro-blackbox-advisory</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/ezadspro-blackbox-advisory"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this high risk advisory to learn how EzAdsPro "BlackBox" application allowed directory listing resulting in unauthorized information disclosure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Petro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snapshots in Proxmox VE]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569761</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/snapshots-in-proxmox-ve/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T11:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The snapshot feature is available on every virtualization platform—whether you use Proxmox, Hyper-V, VMware or other virtualization tool. A snapshot enables you to preserve the state of a virtual machine, including virtual memory, virtual disks, and settings. Proxmox VE allows you to create live snapshots of the VM so that you can roll back to the point in time when something went wrong.
Snapshots in Proxmox VE first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Dealing with dates]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=11154</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/01/25/cortex-xsoar-tips-tricks-dealing-with-dates/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction As an automation platform, Cortex XSOAR fetches data that represents events set at defined moments in time. That metadata is stored within Incidents, will be queried from various systems, and may undergo conversions as it is moves from machines to humans. With its various integrations, Cortex XSOAR ingests datetimes from sources that use different … Continue reading Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Dealing with dates →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Danjoux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom of the Pipeline: Abusing Self-Hosted CI/CD Runners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4366</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/introducing-gato-for-ci-cd-exploitation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T15:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Throughout numerous Red Teams in 2022, a common theme of Source Control Supply Chain attacks in GitHub repositories has emerged. After many hours manually hunting for and exploiting these attack paths, we’ve built an all-in-one toolkit called Gato (Github Attack Toolkit) for finding and attacking repositories where these misconfigurations are present. We released the […]
The post Phantom of the Pipeline: Abusing Self-Hosted CI/CD Runners appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save and access the BitLocker recovery key in the Microsoft account]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569718</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/save-and-access-the-bitlocker-recovery-key-in-the-microsoft-account/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T14:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft offers several options for storing the recovery key when activating BitLocker. Traditionally, you could print it out or save it to a file. The Microsoft account has also been available for this purpose for some time now. From there, it can be read on almost any device from anywhere.
Save and access the BitLocker recovery key in the Microsoft account first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DragonSpark | Attacks Evade Detection with SparkRAT and Golang Source Code Interpretation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=75516</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/dragonspark-attacks-evade-detection-with-sparkrat-and-golang-source-code-interpretation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T10:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cluster of attacks SentinelLabs tracks as DragonSpark uses a novel technique, Golang source code interpretation, to avoid detection while also deploying a little-known tool called SparkRAT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSINT your OT suppliers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26478</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/osint-your-ot-suppliers/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T06:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is much talk about supply chain security and reviewing your suppliers for cyber security. But how much information do they intentionally and unintentionally leak about your organisation online? We […]
OSINT your OT suppliers first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Gee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tampering User Attributes In AWS Cognito User Pools]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/01/24/tampering-unrestricted-user-attributes-aws-cognito.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/01/24/tampering-unrestricted-user-attributes-aws-cognito.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From The Previous Episode… Did you solve the CloudSecTidbit Ep. 1 IaC lab?
Solution
The challenge for the data-import CloudSecTidbit is basically reading the content of an internal bucket. The frontend web application is using the targeted bucket to store the logo of the app.
The name of the bucket is returned to the client by calling the /variable endpoint:

$.ajax({
    type: 'GET',
    url: '/variable',
    dataType: 'json',
    success: function (data) {
        let source_internal = `https://${data}.s3.amazonaws.com/public-stuff/logo.png?${Math.random()}`;
        $(".logo_image").attr("src", source_internal);
    },
    error: function (jqXHR, status, err) {
        alert("Error getting variable name");
    }
});


The server will return something like:

"data-internal-private-202207…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blast from the Past: How Attackers Compromised Zimbra With a Patched Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/blast-from-the-past--how-attackers-compromised-zimbra-with-a-patched-vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/blast-from-the-past--how-attackers-compromised-zimbra-with-a-patched-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T20:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, I worked on a vulnerability in Zimbra (CVE-2022-41352 - my AttackerKB analysis for Rapid7) that turned out to be a new(-ish) exploit path for a really old bug in cpio - CVE-2015-1194. But that was patched in 2019, so what happened? (I posted this as a tweet-thread awhile back, but I decided to flesh it out and make it into a full blog post!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkullSecurity Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activation Context Cache Poisoning: Exploiting CSRSS for Privilege Escalation]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63c6f74267d7b774dae03f15</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/1/23/activation-context-cache-poisoning-exploiting-csrss-for-privilege-escalation"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in July of 2022, the Windows CSRSS process entered the consciousness of the infosec community as the source of several local privilege escalation vulnerabilities in Microsoft Windows. The first public information appeared on July 12 with the release of the patch for CVE-2022-22047, which was being actively exploited. Shortly thereafter, Microsoft published an article providing some technical details and revealing that the threat actor involved was an Austrian hack-for-hire group tracked by Microsoft as KNOTWEED. Fortuitously, these developments coincided with closely related research I had been conducting, and in that same month, I reported to Microsoft two additional vulnerabilities affecting the same component. These have now been patched as CVE-2022-37987 and CVE-2022-37989 res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Zuckerbraun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Windows security and optimization features with Microsoft’s free PC Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569701</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-windows-security-and-optimization-features-with-microsofts-free-pc-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T14:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applications such as CCleaner and other utilities have been popular for years as a quick and easy way for users to scan for and clear out temporary files, caches, logs, and other files to boost performance. Microsoft has released a new utility called PC Manager, which provides interesting features, including performance and security apps, in one location for Windows 10 and 11 PCs.
Manage Windows security and optimization features with Microsoft’s free PC Manager first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing NCC Group’s Cryptopals Guided Tour: Set 2]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18354</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/01/23/announcing-ncc-groups-cryptopals-guided-tour-set-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to NCC Group’s Cryptopals guided tour! This post is the second in a series of eight installments (previously) covering the solutions to the Cryptopals Crypto Challenges. For those who don’t know, Cryptopals is a series of eight sets of challenges covering common cryptographic constructs and common attacks on them. You can read … Continue reading Announcing NCC Group’s Cryptopals Guided Tour: Set 2 →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Sohl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS CTI Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cti-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cti-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) Summit 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing Malicious OneNote Documents]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9889</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/01/22/analyzing-malicious-onenote-documents/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-22T18:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About a week ago, I was asked if I had tools for OneNote files. I don’t, and I had no time to take a closer look. But last Thursday night, I had some time to take a look. I looked at this OneNote maldoc sample. I opened the file in the binary editor I use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: process-binary-file Version 0.0.8]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9885</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/01/22/update-process-binary-file-version-0-0-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-22T09:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New functions and classes have been added to process-binary-file.py. python-templates_V0_0_9.zip (http)MD5: 7C5E8602F225735015E9A431C5818762SHA256: CAEEEBB1E402E5127A431446A01BBE607B22AA0EB1F6FA12B8E7703275BE6F15]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tool: onedump.py]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9877</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/01/22/new-tool-onedump-py/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-22T09:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a new tool (based on my Python template for binary files) to analyze OneNote files. This version is limited to handling embedded files (for the moment). As I might still make significant changes to the user interface, I’ve put this tool in my GitHub beta repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excelling at Excel, Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8391</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/01/22/excelling-at-excel-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-22T00:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most common use cases we come across during our malware analysis exercises is a ROI-driven comparison of features between many samples of the same malware family. Yes, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yara rules pageant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8386</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/01/21/yara-rules-pageant/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-21T00:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago I posted a very specific question on Twitter and Mastodon: You’ve got gazillion of random yara rules stored inside many random .yar files scattered around many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – U-Boot – Unchecked Download Size and Direction in USB DFU (CVE-2022-2347)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17930</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/01/20/technical-advisory-u-boot-unchecked-download-size-and-direction-in-usb-dfu-cve-2022-2347/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T20:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary U-Boot is a popular and feature-rich bootloader for embedded systems. It includes optional support for the USB Device Firmware Update (DFU) protocol, which can be used by devices to download new firmware, or upload their current firmware. The U-Boot DFU implementation does not bound the length field in USB DFU download setup packets, and … Continue reading Technical Advisory – U-Boot – Unchecked Download Size and Direction in USB DFU (CVE-2022-2347) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sultan Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Bypassing Applocker, UAC and Getting Administrative Persistence]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/88b85c81343e</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-bypassing-applocker-uac-and-getting-administrative-persistence-88b85c81343e?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T18:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! In my previous post, I showed how we can bypass default Applocker rules using LNK files to get a Havoc beacon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Multiple Vulnerabilities in the Galaxy App Store (CVE-2023-21433, CVE-2023-21434)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18591</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/01/20/technical-advisory-multiple-vulnerabilities-in-the-galaxy-app-store-cve-2023-21433-cve-2023-21434/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T14:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Galaxy App Store is an alternative application store that comes pre-installed on Samsung Android devices. Several Android applications are available on both the Galaxy App Store and Google App Store, and users have the option to use either store to install specific applications. Two vulnerabilities were uncovered with the Galaxy App Store application: Technical … Continue reading Technical Advisory – Multiple Vulnerabilities in the Galaxy App Store (CVE-2023-21433, CVE-2023-21434) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Gannon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CISO’s Guide to Building a Strategic Relationship with the BOD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4370</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/ciso-strategic-relationship-with-bod/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T14:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A chief information security officer’s (CISO’s) role ultimately is to help their organization’s board of directors (BOD) understand the potential impact of cyber threats on the organization. When this strategic relationship is successful, the BOD can make informed decisions about risk management, including capital allocation and spending relative to industry peers. Effective communication to this […]
The post A CISO’s Guide to Building a Strategic Relationship with the BOD appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Recovery Services vault: Ironing out the confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569686</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/azure-recovery-services-vault-ironing-out-the-confusion/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T13:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure offers a variety of backup and disaster recovery solutions. Let Tim iron out some common confusions about these entities and services: Azure Recovery Services vault, Azure Site Recovery, Azure Backup, and Azure Backup vault. In addition, you will learn important concepts for working with the Azure Recovery Services vault: Azure region dependency, content portability, and deletion workflow.
Azure Recovery Services vault: Ironing out the confusion first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abusing Adopted Authority on IBM i]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/01/20/abusing-adopted-authority-on-ibm-i/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/01/20/abusing-adopted-authority-on-ibm-i/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our first blog post of 2023, we continue our series about penetration testing IBM i. This time we look into how the so-called Adopted Authority mechanism can be abused for privilege escalation if privileged scripts are not implemented with enough care.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silent Signal Techblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-35690: Unauthenticated RCE in Adobe ColdFusion]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63c873a78ec28c353417c563</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/1/18/cve-2022-35690-unauthenticated-rce-in-adobe-coldfusion"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Lucas Miller and Dusan Stevanovic of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in Adobe ColdFusion. This bug was originally reported to the ZDI program by a researcher known as rgod. The vulnerability is due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. Successful exploitation could lead to arbitrary code execution at the level of SYSTEM. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2022-35690, with a few minimal modifications.
A memory corruption vulnerability exists in Adobe ColdFusion. This vulnerability is due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can resu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting null-dereferences in the Linux kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/01/exploiting-null-dereferences-in-linux.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/01/exploiting-null-dereferences-in-linux.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw');ol.lst-kix_3558t16xb2i9-3.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_3558t16xb2i9-3 0}.lst-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-8>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-8,lower-roman) ". "}ol.lst-kix_ehkygwr8rii2-3.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_ehkygwr8rii2-3 0}ol.lst-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-6.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-6 0}.lst-kix_3558t16xb2i9-5>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_3558t16xb2i9-5}.lst-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-7>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-7,lower-latin) ". "}.lst-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-1>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-1}.lst-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-2>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_dt3x5t4funnl-2,lower-roman) ". "}.lst-kix_ehkygwr8rii2-5>li{counter-increment:lst…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker AFK: InsiderPhD]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-afk-insiderphd</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-afk-insiderphd"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's hacker InsiderPhD
JXoaT: My first question is always, "What was your first experience with hacking?" What really opened the door to y]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 5 Cybersecurity Vulnerabilities for Government Agencies in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15914</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/the-top-5-cybersecurity-vulnerabilities-for-government-agencies-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T16:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Government agencies are faced with cybersecurity challenges from all sides. Digital transformation initiatives can expose weak points in an attack surface, putting pressure on agencies’ IT teams to get it just right. And from insider threats to persistent vulnerabilities within networks and operating systems, public sector leaders feel the urgency to obtain a clear picture […]
The post The Top 5 Cybersecurity Vulnerabilities for Government Agencies in 2022 appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All-time High Cybersecurity Attrition + Economic Uncertainty = Happy(ish) New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2050</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/01/19/all-time-high-cybersecurity-attrition-economic-uncertainty-happyish-new-year/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=all-time-high-cybersecurity-attrition-economic-uncertainty-happyish-new-year"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T15:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All-time High Cybersecurity Attrition + Economic Uncertainty = Happy(ish) New Year As 2023 fires up, so do the attrition numbers across the Cybersecurity vertical.  With bonuses being paid and cybersecurity professionals searching for the next great job, vulnerability management teams are understaffed with growing concerns around finding qualified cybersecurity candidates to fill once occupied roles.  ... Read more All-time High Cybersecurity Attrition + Economic Uncertainty = Happy(ish) New Year 
The post <strong>All-time High Cybersecurity Attrition + Economic Uncertainty = Happy(ish) New Year</strong>  appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Bishop: Clustering Web Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18527</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/01/19/project-bishop-clustering-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T14:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by Jose Selvi and Thomas Atkinson If you are a Machine Learning (ML) enthusiast like us, you may recall our blogpost series from 2019 regarding Project Ava, which documented our experiments in using ML techniques to automate web application security testing tasks. In February 2020 we set out to build on Project Ava with … Continue reading Project Bishop: Clustering Web Pages →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Selvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reopen apps after Windows startup]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569666</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/reopen-apps-after-windows-startup/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T13:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most users work with several apps at the same time. In the past, they had to reopen apps manually after a startup. Since Windows 10, the operating system has automated this task, albeit in an inconsistent manner. And there is only limited central management for this feature.
Reopen apps after Windows startup first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing the eBPF Verifier]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103761</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/01/19/ebpf-verifier-harness/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Laura Bauman During my internship at Trail of Bits, I prototyped a harness that improves the testability of the eBPF verifier, simplifying the testing of eBPF programs. My eBPF harness runs in user space, independently of any locally running kernel, and thus opens the door to testing of eBPF programs across different kernel versions. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Using LNK Files To Bypass Applocker]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3fb1ecae291f</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-using-lnk-files-to-bypass-applocker-3fb1ecae291f?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T20:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows LNK file is just one of the many ways to get easy execution while bypassing Applocker and some AV. While this isn’t a new…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne Named a Leader in Penetration Testing as a Service (PTaaS) GigaOm Radar Report]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/hackerone-named-leader-penetration-testing-service-ptaas-gigaom-radar-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/hackerone-named-leader-penetration-testing-service-ptaas-gigaom-radar-report"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The report provides a technical evaluation of key PTaaS vendor offerings in the market. A select group of seven vendors were invited to participate in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Ryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Defender’s Guide to Windows Services]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/67c1711ecba7</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/the-defenders-guide-to-windows-services-67c1711ecba7?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T15:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s dangerous to find malicious services alone! Take this!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IIS and Exchange Server security with Windows Extended Protection (WEP)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569649</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/iis-and-exchange-server-security-with-windows-extended-protection-wep/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T13:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little-known extension helps to increase the security of Windows Authentication to prevent credential relay or "man in the middle" attacks in Exchange Server and Internet Information Server (IIS). Microsoft is using Windows Extended Protection with modern security updates to enhance the built-in authentication capabilities found in Windows Server.
IIS and Exchange Server security with Windows Extended Protection (WEP) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, No Case Studies—But . . .]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e7cf012af19807518fba2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/sorry-no-case-study"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend of the site recently suggested that we create a current-issue case 
study using our updated risk discovery approach. “It’s a great idea,” we 
replied and immediately started kicking around ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pointillism of Daily Events]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2c8f009baa12346d3711f</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/pointillism-daily-events"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Baker’s book Human Smoke brilliantly illustrates a unique approach 
to historical narrative. It also underscores the need to remember that 
every artist paints with intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ready for What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2aa91391dcb70804f9850</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/getting-ready-whats-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new age of giant monsters, advanced awareness of classical 
surprise—that one big tipping moment—no longer suffices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Your ‘Free Cells’ Mindfully]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62deb6110fd7f314e5696ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/manage-free-cells"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accommodate but don’t fight the limitations you can’t control, recognize 
those you can influence and leverage, and don't imagine you have more free 
cells than you actually do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popski’s Planning]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d81b5affdc983dd1f616f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/popskis-planning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British officer Vladimir Peniakoff’s approach to planning might sound a bit 
unorthodox at first, but it aligns nicely with Patton’s view of 
intelligence and speaks to an enduring need to understand front-line 
conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a New Game Board]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d5b6db0343fb487527fc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/time-for-a-new-game-board"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need a more flexible game board where players can explore hypergame 
strategies—in other words, a game board where the strategist can play the 
hero for a change. We’ve built it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survivors Exceeded the Minimum]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62cf11283f1bdb1191fcdf9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/survivors-exceeded-minimum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T18:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every surprise is a cunning thunderbolt. Some surprises creep up 
slowly, rusting away former resilience until a simple nudge reveals the 
rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>