<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-11T00:51:04.483Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.71]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9675</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/11/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-71/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new plugin and an updated plugin. Plugin plugin_dttm is a plugin for Word documents: it searches for Dop structures. They contain DTTM timestamps. And plugin plugin_metadata has been updated to parse digital signatures (option -s). oledump_V0_0_71.zip (http)MD5: BA1142136F28DB218BADEAA642EA0EA9SHA256: FA09766D138A1AA60523B487D947BF29222D409CF1FCE078DE61BF62768A5950]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypting Shellcode using SystemFunction032/033]]></title>
        <id>https://osandamalith.com/?p=4293</id>
        <link href="https://osandamalith.com/2022/11/10/encrypting-shellcode-using-systemfunction032-033/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T22:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a while, I’m publishing a blog post which made me interested. With the recent tweets about the uncodumented SystemFunction032 Win32 API function, I decided to quickly have a look at it. The first thing I noted after Googling this function was the source code from ReactOS. Seems like other SystemFunctions from 001 got other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Osanda Malith Jayathissa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release – Web3 Decoder Burp Suite Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17917</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/11/10/tool-release-web3-decoder-burp-suite-extension/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T19:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Decoder is a Burp Suite Extension that allows to decode “web3” JSON-RPC calls that interact with smart contracts in a EVM blockchain. As it is said that a picture is worth a thousand words, the following two screenshots shows a Raw JSON-RPC call, and its decoded function call: Background When auditing a DApp (Decentralized … Continue reading Tool Release – Web3 Decoder Burp Suite Extension →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimize Noise With Human-Led API Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15745</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/minimize-noise-with-human-led-api-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we released a new API Pentesting product that allows you to test your headless API endpoints through the Synack Platform. Before the release, we conducted more than 100 requests for headless API pentests, indicating a growing need from our customers. This new capability provides an opportunity to get human-led testing and proof-of-coverage on […]
The post Minimize Noise With Human-Led API Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Torio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Are Digital Technologies Eroding the Principle of Distinction in War?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=73009</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/are-digital-technologies-eroding-the-principle-of-distinction-in-war/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T14:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent conflicts, digital technology has become weaponized, eroding the traditional barriers that divide the roles of civilians and combatants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look out! Divergent representations are everywhere!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103122</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/11/10/divergent-representations-variable-overflows-c-compiler/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T12:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Andreas Kellas Trail of Bits recently published a blog post about a signed integer overflow in certain versions of SQLite that can enable arbitrary code execution and result in a denial of service. While working on proof-of-concept exploits for that vulnerability, we noticed that the compiler’s representation of an important integer variable is semantically […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tobgreg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use splatting and PSBoundParameters to pass parameters in PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568608</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/use-splatting-and-psboundparameters-to-pass-parameters-in-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T02:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The automatic variable PSBoundParameters stores the parameters that you explicitly passed to a function in a hash table. With the help of splatting, you can use this PowerShell feature to simplify passing of parameters to functions.
Use splatting and PSBoundParameters to pass parameters in PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffery Hicks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: pdf-parser.py Version 0.7.7]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9669</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/10/update-pdf-parser-py-version-0-7-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a small update: you can now select which hash algorithm to use for option -H by setting environment variable DSS_DEFAULT_HASH_ALGORITHMS. And the statistics options (-a) also display a list of objects with streams. pdf-parser_V0_7_7.zip (http)MD5: BCAE193F171184F979603DFB1380FF43SHA256: 576C429FA88CF0A7A110DAB25851D90670C88EC4CD7728329E754E06D8D26A70]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Certificates and Pwnage and Patches, Oh My!]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8ae0f4304c1d</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/certificates-and-pwnage-and-patches-oh-my-8ae0f4304c1d?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO EXCELS IN MITRE ATT&CK® MANAGED SERVICES EVALUATION]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12916</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/11/09/nviso-excels-in-mitre-attck-managed-services-evaluation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As one of the only EU-based Cyber Security companies, NVISO successfully participated in a first-of-its-kind, MITRE-led, evaluation of Managed Security Services (MSS). The inaugural MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK® Evaluations for Managed Security Services ran in June 2022 and its results have been published today. NVISO performed excellently in the evaluation, demonstrating services that are at or … Continue reading NVISO EXCELS IN MITRE ATT&CK® MANAGED SERVICES EVALUATION →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Tischer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting web message misconfigurations for cross-domain credential theft]]></title>
        <id>detecting-web-message-misconfigurations-for-cross-domain-credential-theft</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/detecting-web-message-misconfigurations-for-cross-domain-credential-theft"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We released a new version of Burp recently on the Early Adopter channel that updates DOM Invader to help find cross-domain secrets. In this post we are going to show you how to use DOM Invader to dete]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visualizing MISP Threat Intelligence in Power BI – An NVISO TI Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12719</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/11/09/visualizing-misp-threat-intelligence-in-power-bi-an-nviso-ti-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T13:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog we will explain how to use the functionality of Power BI to visualize your MISP data in a interactive and useful way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Nixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales of Windows detection opportunities for an implant framework]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17946</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/11/09/tales-of-windows-detection-opportunities-for-an-implant-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T09:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slides from a fifteen minute lightening talk on detection opportunities for implant framework behaviour on Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Whitehouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud-based patch management with Action1]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568594</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/cloud-based-patch-management-with-action1/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T05:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Action1 cloud-native platform provides IT teams with powerful patch management features and is free for the first 100 endpoints.
Cloud-based patch management with Action1 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The November 2022 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6369b7f687c1821a09667d41</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/11/8/the-november-2022-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the penultimate Patch Tuesday of 2021. As expected, Adobe and Microsoft have released their latest security updates and fixes to the world. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security offerings.
Adobe Patches for November 2022
For November, Adobe released no patches at all. They’ve released as few as one in the past, but this is the first month in the last six years where they had no fixes at all. Perhaps the U.S. elections play a factor, as Patch Tuesday hasn’t fallen on Election Day since 2016. Whatever the cause, enjoy a month of no Adobe updates.
Microsoft Patches for November 2022
This month, Microsoft released 64 new patches addressing CVEs in Microsoft Windows and Windows Components; Azure and Azure R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inspector, or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Testing in Prod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4276</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/inspector-prod-testing-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T16:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Recently, I’ve shifted from primarily performing red team engagements to assisting in the development of Chariot, Praetorian’s attack surface management (ASM) and continuous automated red teaming (CART) product offering. Our Praetorian Labs team has developed multiple tools to support Chariot and our Services organization. One of these, a subsystem for the core asset enumeration […]
The post Inspector, or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Testing in Prod appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Can Be the Hero or Villain of Your Cybersecurity Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15732</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/reporting-can-be-the-hero-or-villain-of-your-cybersecurity-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T16:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting is a critical but often-overlooked component of cybersecurity testing The overall goals of nearly any technology can be summed up by the title of a song by the popular French music duo Daft Punk: “Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger.” New technologies are commonly judged against two or more of these characteristics. Applying this to cybersecurity […]
The post Reporting Can Be the Hero or Villain of Your Cybersecurity Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We sign code now]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103080</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/11/08/sigstore-code-signing-verification-software-supply-chain/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T12:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William Woodruff Sigstore announced the general availability of its free and ecosystem-agnostic software signing service two weeks ago, giving developers a way to sign, verify and protect their software projects and the dependencies they rely on. Trail of Bits is absolutely thrilled to be a part of the project, and we spoke about our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install, remove, list, and set default printer with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568575</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-remove-list-and-set-default-printer-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T03:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With PowerShell, you can easily install a printer driver, add a printer to the repository, and then add a local or shared network printer to your Windows installation. In this post, I will also explain how you can list printers, add a printer port, set the default printer, and remove a printer with PowerShell.
Install, remove, list, and set default printer with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emanuel Halapciuc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocGholish Diversifies and Expands Its Malware Staging Infrastructure to Counter Defenders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=73094</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/socgholish-diversifies-and-expands-its-malware-staging-infrastructure-to-counter-defenders/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T13:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SocGholish operators continue to infect websites at a massive scale, and the threat actor is ramping up its infrastructure to match.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Testing A USB Fridge]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9650</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/06/quickpost-testing-a-usb-fridge/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T14:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple years ago, I received a USB fridge from NVISO’s Secret Santa. It uses a Peltier element with a fan. I did the following test: overnight, I let the fridge run for 12 hours. It contained an Aluminum can filled with water at room temperature (around 17° C). I used a power meter to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi not working? Analyze with free Wi-Fi stumblers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568549</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/wi-fi-is-not-working-analyze-with-free-wi-fi-stumblers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T04:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your Wi-Fi isn't working? When it comes to building out, configuring, and troubleshooting a wireless network, there are valuable tools that help with all three of these tasks. Utilities that allow you to analyze wireless networks are called Wi-Fi stumblers.
Wi-Fi not working? Analyze with free Wi-Fi stumblers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BYODC - Bring Your Own Domain Controller]]></title>
        <id>62b32a307518be0764f856d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/byodc-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T17:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BYODC or bring your own domain controller is a post-exploitation technique and another option for performing a DCSync in a more opsec safe manner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Powerful Clipboard: Analysis of a Samsung in-the-wild exploit chain]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/a-very-powerful-clipboard-samsung-in-the-wild-exploit-chain.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/a-very-powerful-clipboard-samsung-in-the-wild-exploit-chain.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maddie Stone, Project Zero

Note: The three vulnerabilities discussed in this blog were all fixed in Samsung’s March 2021 release. They were fixed as CVE-2021-25337, CVE-2021-25369, CVE-2021-25370. To ensure your Samsung device is up-to-date under settings you can check that your device is running SMR Mar-2021 or later.

As defenders, in-the-wild exploit samples give us important insight into what attackers are really doing. We get the “ground truth” data about the vulnerabilities and exploit techniques they’re using, which then informs our further research and guidance to security teams on what could have the biggest impact or return on investment. To do this, we need to know that the vulnerabilities and exploit samples were found in-the-wild. Over the past few years there’s been tremendo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Appreciation Month: Badge Awards]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-appreciation-month-badge-awards</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-appreciation-month-badge-awards"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T15:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating the accomplishments of hackers is something we want to do year-round. However, we decided we wanted to root Cyber Security Awareness mon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory passwords: All you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568529</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/active-directory-passwords-all-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T06:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Windows administrators need to know the essential concepts of Active Directory passwords: how passwords are stored in Active Directory, how password authentication works, and how to manage Active Directory passwords. A common task for admins is to reset users' passwords, which you can do with the GUI or PowerShell. However, in large networks, a self-service solution is required. Computer account passwords are another topic that administrators have to be familiar with.
Active Directory passwords: All you need to know first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta Ransomware | Attacks Deploy Custom EDR Evasion Tools Tied to FIN7 Threat Actor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=72977</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/black-basta-ransomware-attacks-deploy-custom-edr-evasion-tools-tied-to-fin7-threat-actor/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T09:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta operational TTPs are described here in full detail, revealing previously unknown tools and techniques and a link to FIN7.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Cocomazzi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Format time and date output of PowerShell New-TimeSpan]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568502</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/format-time-and-date-output-of-powershell-new-timespan/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T06:42:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My function, Get-TimespanPretty, allows you to view the time span—the difference between two time points or dates—in a compact, user-friendly format. It is built on top of the New-TimeSpan cmdlet, which offers details as output that you usually need. With Get-TimespanPretty, you can simply pipe the output (TimeSpan object) of New-TimeSpan or Measure-Command to Get-TimespanPretty. It's easy to use, and there's no need for complex reworking of scripts that may include such commands.
Format time and date output of PowerShell New-TimeSpan first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emanuel Halapciuc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker AFK: the_arch_angel]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-afk-thearchangel</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-afk-thearchangel"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T15:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's hacker the_arch_angel 
JXoaT: What was your first experience with hacking growing up? 
the_arch_angel: I actually didn't do any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gregor Samsa: Exploiting Java's XML Signature Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/gregor-samsa-exploiting-java-xml.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/gregor-samsa-exploiting-java-xml.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T11:41:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Felix Wilhelm, Project Zero

Earlier this year, I discovered a surprising attack surface hidden deep inside Java’s standard library: A custom JIT compiler processing untrusted XSLT programs, exposed to remote attackers during XML signature verification. This post discusses CVE-2022-34169, an integer truncation bug in this JIT compiler resulting in arbitrary code execution in many Java-based web applications and identity providers that support the SAML single-sign-on standard. 
OpenJDK fixed the discussed issue in July 2022. The Apache BCEL project used by Xalan-J, the origin of the vulnerable code, released a patch in September 2022. 

While the vulnerability discussed in this post has been patched , vendors and users should expect further vulnerabilities in SAML.

From a security resea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Found My Next Mission In Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15655</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/how-i-found-my-next-mission-in-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T07:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Granger is a Technical Manager in Operations, Federal. He has 18 years of service and is currently in Officer Training School for the Air Force. I was a freshman in high school when September 11th, 2001 happened. I will never forget my principal’s somber voice on the intercom telling us matter-of-factly that a terrorist […]
The post How I Found My Next Mission In Cybersecurity appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trevor Granger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring Defender Exploit Guard network protection]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568490</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configuring-defender-exploit-guard-network-protection/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T03:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the features of Defender Exploit Guard is network protection. It blocks communication with dangerous domains or IP addresses at the system level. Network protection can be configured via group policies, PowerShell, or Intune.
Configuring Defender Exploit Guard network protection first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect With Us!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/SANS-Social-Channels-Podcasts</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/SANS-Social-Channels-Podcasts?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS cyber security curriculum channels are the best way to stay up-to-date on all our free content and course updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nighthawk 0.2.1 – Haunting Blue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3188</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2022/11/nighthawk-0-2-1-haunting-blue/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T14:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1st 2022 This Halloween week brings our third and final Nighthawk release for the year and its packed with exciting new features, backed by MDSec’s world class research and...
The post Nighthawk 0.2.1 – Haunting Blue appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring Up: How to Architect a Systematic Security Program – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4259</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/measure-against-your-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T13:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series , we discussed how organizations can go about selecting a framework for implementation. In order to effectively measure your organization against the selected framework, the organization must take five crucial steps before doing any assessment or analysis. Define the rating scale Define the rating criteria Determine how to address […]
The post Measuring Up: How to Architect a Systematic Security Program – Part 2 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing into the Synack Red Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15657</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/growing-into-the-synack-red-team/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T11:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mohammad Jassim is a 17-year-old member of the Synack Red Team.  In 2017, I was that rare seventh grader who had Ubuntu installed on their laptop. Typing “sudo apt-get install software-center” every chance I got boosted my ego – I was practically Mr. Robot! At this rate, I thought nothing could stop me from taking […]
The post Growing into the Synack Red Team appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SRT Community</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disable UAC with Group Policy and set PIN in Windows Hello]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568470</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/disable-uac-with-group-policy-and-set-pin-in-windows-hello/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T04:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User Account Control helps to implement proper permission levels for users accessing systems. Instead of needing administrator privileges, UAC allows admins to set up standard user permissions for users and escalate privileges in a granular way. In corporate networks, admins can use Group Policy to configure various UAC settings, including disabling UAC. Thanks to Windows Hello, you can now use a PIN for UAC.
Disable UAC with Group Policy and set PIN in Windows Hello first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in October]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9648</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/01/overview-of-content-published-in-october-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in October: Blog posts: Quickpost: Standby Power Consumption Of An Old Linear Power Supply Update: base64dump.py Version 0.0.24 Update: rtfdump.py Version 0.0.12 Quickpost: Testing A Lemon Battery Update: byte-stats.py Version 0.0.9 The Making Of: qa-squeaky-toys.docm Quickpost: BruCON Travel Charger YouTube videos: Analysis of a Malicious HTML File […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: UAC Bypass On Windows Defender For Endpoint With HighBorn]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e9ea16546029</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-uac-bypass-on-windows-defender-for-endpoint-with-highborn-e9ea16546029?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T18:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The days of running fodhelper are over, but there are a lot of ways to bypass UAC without alterting Defender or even Defender for Endpoint…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check out our new Microcorruption challenges!]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17819</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/10/31/check-out-our-new-microcorruption-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T17:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Microcorruption challenges created by Nick Galloway and Davee Morgan Today we are releasing several new challenges for the embedded security CTF, Microcorruption. These challenges highlight types of vulnerabilities that NCC Group’s Hardware and Embedded Systems practice have discovered in real products. The new challenges provide a simple interface to explore these vulnerabilities without having … Continue reading Check out our new Microcorruption challenges! →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerabilities in Apache Batik Default Security Controls – SSRF and RCE Through Remote Class Loading]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:635c21bed89bad67e748dfc8</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/10/28/vulnerabilities-in-apache-batik-default-security-controls-ssrf-and-rce-through-remote-class-loading"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T16:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
I stumbled upon the Apache Batik library while researching other Java-based products. It immediately caught my attention, as this library parses Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) files and transforms them into different raster graphics formats (i.e., PNG, PDF, or JPEG). I was even more encouraged when I looked at the Batik documentation. It was obvious that such a library could be prone to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) issues (e.g., loading of images from remote resources). However, the documentation shows that Batik can also:
·      Execute JavaScript through the Rhino interpreter.
·      Load and execute remote Java classes.
Those are some neat features! On the other hand, Apache Batik protects its users from both SSRF and remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities throug…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Defender’s Guide to the Windows Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/febe241abc75</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/the-defenders-guide-to-the-windows-registry-febe241abc75?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T15:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Paine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Get Caught in the Dark: How to Build Better Documentation for Security Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/build-better-documentation</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/build-better-documentation"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we share our recommendations for improving technical documentation guidelines and strategies for security teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Doering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari is hot-linking images to semi-random websites]]></title>
        <id>safari-is-hot-linking-images-to-semi-random-websites</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/safari-is-hot-linking-images-to-semi-random-websites"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every image is potentially a URL on Safari, thanks to over-enthusiastic OCR (Optical Character Recognition). This means you can link any image to an external website - and Safari might already be send]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synack Expands Security Platform with Adversarial API Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15644</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/synack-expands-security-platform-with-adversarial-api-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synack, the premier security testing platform, has launched an API pentesting capability powered by its global community of elite security researchers. Organizations can now rely on the Synack platform for continuous pentesting coverage across “headless” API endpoints that lack a user interface and are increasingly exposed to attackers. “Synack’s human-led, adversarial approach is ideal for […]
The post Synack Expands Security Platform with Adversarial API Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: BruCON Travel Charger]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9616</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/10/31/quickpost-brucon-travel-charger/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my BruCON speaker goodie bag, I found a travel adapter & USB charger: I already have a similar travel adapter, but this BruCON travel adapter has one extra important feature for me: a USB C port. As I still had my setup ready for testing the electrical energy consumption of devices, I quickly tested […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sysinternals Process Monitor: Real-time file system, registry, and process monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568451</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sysinternals-process-monitor-real-time-file-system-registry-and-process-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T06:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sysinternals Process Monitor runs on a Windows device and uses a filter driver to log real-time file system, registry, and process/thread monitoring. It is a vital tool for troubleshooting Windows and combines the capabilities of two older Sysinternals tools: filemon and regmon.
Sysinternals Process Monitor: Real-time file system, registry, and process monitoring first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rankin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PAWNYABLE UAF Walkthrough (Holstein v3)]]></title>
        <id>https://h0mbre.github.io/PAWNYABLE_UAF_Walkthrough/</id>
        <link href="https://h0mbre.github.io/PAWNYABLE_UAF_Walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Human Machine Interface</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 22H2: New Group Policy settings and updated Security Baseline, no ADK]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568426</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-10-22h2-new-group-policy-settings-and-updated-security-baseline-no-adk/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T02:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released version 22H2 of Windows 10 (Windows 10 2022 Update). It offers practically no new features for end users but introduces some changes that are relevant for admins. These include extensive alignment of group policies and the security baseline with Windows 11 22H2.
Windows 10 22H2: New Group Policy settings and updated Security Baseline, no ADK first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Making Of: qa-squeaky-toys.docm]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9635</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/10/28/the-making-of-qa-squeaky-toys-docm/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[qa-squeaky-toys.docm is a challenge I made for CSCBE 2022. It’s a Word document with VBA code. But the VBA code has been “cleaned” by an anti-virus. I was inspired by a real maldoc cleaned by a real anti-virus: “Maldoc Cleaned by Anti-Virus“. Here is how I made this challenge. I created a .docm file with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geolocation Resources for OSINT Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/geolocation-resources-for-osint-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/geolocation-resources-for-osint-investigations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are numerous free tools and resources to help boost your geolocation and vehicle tracking skills to further your OSINT investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Getting System On Windows 11 With Havoc C2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cc4bb089d22</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-getting-system-on-windows-11-with-havoc-c2-cc4bb089d22?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T20:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Havoc C2 has quickly become one of my favorite open source C2s. It’s features offer everything that you need to complete a pentest or red…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RC4 Is Still Considered Harmful]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/10/rc4-is-still-considered-harmful.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/10/rc4-is-still-considered-harmful.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T19:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By James Forshaw, Project Zero

I've been spending a lot of time researching Windows authentication implementations, specifically Kerberos. In June 2022 I found an interesting issue number 2310 with the handling of RC4 encryption that allowed you to authenticate as another user if you could either interpose on the Kerberos network traffic to and from the KDC or directly if the user was configured to disable typical pre-authentication requirements.

This blog post goes into more detail on how this vulnerability works and how I was able to exploit it with only a bare minimum of brute forcing required. Note, I'm not going to spend time fully explaining how Kerberos authentication works, there's plenty of resources online. For example this blog post by Steve Syfuhs who works at Microsoft is a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Success Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-success-managers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hacker-success-managers"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T16:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Hacker Success Managers 
Earlier this year, we released a blog that shared foundational changes on our Community Team. One of our goals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesse@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes, New Insights from SANS Hacker Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/sans-behind-the-scenes</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/sans-behind-the-scenes"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get inside the mind of a hacker with highlights from our webcast, Hacker Insights Revealed; New SANS Survey Results]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battling the Next Log4j: How to Prepare Your Security Team While Avoiding Burnout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15611</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/battling-the-next-log4j/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the anniversary of Log4j looming, it is a good time to reflect on the wider significance of the vulnerability that had security teams scrambling in December 2021. What can the response to the flaw in a widely used Apache Software Foundation logging tool tell us about the state of global IT security? Most importantly, […]
The post Battling the Next Log4j: How to Prepare Your Security Team While Avoiding Burnout appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Preston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free: Dastardly from Burp Suite]]></title>
        <id>free-dastardly-from-burp-suite</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/free-dastardly-from-burp-suite"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Dastardly - a free, lightweight web application security scanner for your CI/CD pipeline, from the makers of Burp Suite. Secure web development ain't easy Ensuring your code is written sec]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coming very soon: Dastardly, from Burp Suite]]></title>
        <id>coming-very-soon-dastardly-from-burp-suite</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/coming-very-soon-dastardly-from-burp-suite"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New product alert! Dastardly is a free, lightweight web application security scanner for your CI/CD pipeline - and it's going to be landing in the next few days. It'll check your application for seven]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage auto reply messages with CodeTwo Email Signatures for Office 365 (Microsoft 365)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568404</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-auto-reply-messages-with-codetwo-email-signatures-for-office-365-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T03:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeTwo Email Signatures for Office 365 provides centralized management for email signatures in Microsoft 365 and has recently added a new auto reply feature.
Manage auto reply messages with CodeTwo Email Signatures for Office 365 (Microsoft 365) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize Your SOC with ServiceNow and Synack]]></title>
        <id>https://synackmarkestg.wpengine.com/?p=15491</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/optimize-your-soc-with-servicenow-and-synack/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T16:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow, a leading provider of management tools for security and IT operations, has joined forces with Synack to help Security Operations Center (SOC) operators spot and correct gaps in vulnerability detection and protection. Enterprises rely on ServiceNow to monitor, manage and respond to security incidents from across their hybrid infrastructure. By cohesively gathering, correlating and […]
The post Optimize Your SOC with ServiceNow and Synack appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Copeland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Self-Hosted GitHub Runner to Self-Hosted Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4262</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/self-hosted-github-runners-are-backdoors/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T13:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) systems are powerful and configurable tools within modern environments. At Praetorian, we are seeing organizations migrate to SaaS solutions like GitHub (GitHub.com) as their source code management and CI/CD solution, instead of on-premises tools like BitBucket, Bamboo, and Jenkins. On our Red Team engagements , we routinely employ […]
The post From Self-Hosted GitHub Runner to Self-Hosted Backdoor appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet PortSwigger's first women in tech scholars]]></title>
        <id>meet-portswiggers-first-women-in-tech-scholars</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/meet-portswiggers-first-women-in-tech-scholars"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T12:43:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PortSwigger recently launched a scholarship scheme, specifically directed at creating opportunities for young women to kick-start their tech career. Our scholarships offer paid work opportunities, tai]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autodial(DLL)ing Your Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3178</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2022/10/autodialdlling-your-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of the AutodialDLL registry subkey (located in HKLM\\SYSTEM\\CurrentControlSet\\Services\\WinSock2\\Parameters) as a persistence method has been previously documented by @Hexacorn in his series Beyond good ol’ Run key, (Part 24)....
The post Autodial(DLL)ing Your Way appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One shell to HANDLE them all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.blackarrow.net/?p=2493</id>
        <link href="https://www.blackarrow.net/token-handles-abuse-one-shell-to-handle-them-all/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T09:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New approach to escalate privileges by abusing open token handles after compromising a web app
La entrada One shell to HANDLE them all se publicó primero en BlackArrow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kurosh Dabbagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install VMware ESXi on Dell PowerEdge]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568377</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-vmware-esxi-on-dell-poweredge/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T03:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to install and configure VMware ESXi on a Dell PowerEdge server. I will also give you a few tips on how to buy an affordable server that is capable of running ESXi. For this guide, I used a PowerEdge R620 with two Intel Xeon e5-2697 v2 and 128 GB of DDR3 for 350€. The machine is capable of hosting VMware ESXi.
Install VMware ESXi on Dell PowerEdge first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane van Gulick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Five Most Dangerous New Attack Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-five-most-dangerous-new-attack-techniques</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-five-most-dangerous-new-attack-techniques?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous RSA Conference keynote presentations on the most dangerous new attack techniques in use today and how to prepare for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stranger Strings: An exploitable flaw in SQLite]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102981</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/10/25/sqlite-vulnerability-july-2022-library-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Andreas Kellas Trail of Bits is publicly disclosing CVE-2022-35737, which affects applications that use the SQLite library API. CVE-2022-35737 was introduced in SQLite version 1.0.12 (released on October 17, 2000) and fixed in release 3.39.2 (released on July 21, 2022). CVE-2022-35737 is exploitable on 64-bit systems, and exploitability depends on how the program is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The dangers of trust policies in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12616</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/10/25/the-dangers-of-trust-policies-in-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Everyone that has used Amazon Web Services (AWS) knows that the cloud environment has a unique way of granting access to users and resources. This is done by allowing users and/or resources to temporarily assume roles. These kinds of actions are possible because of trust policies that are assigned to those roles. A trust … Continue reading The dangers of trust policies in AWS →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Mangelschots</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Defender SmartScreen, activate enhanced phishing protection]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568352</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configure-defender-smartscreen-activate-enhanced-phishing-protection/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T06:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft includes several Windows security components under the term "Defender." One of them is Defender SmartScreen, which aims to protect users from visiting dangerous websites and downloading malicious programs. In Windows 11 2022, additional protection against password theft was added.
Configure Defender SmartScreen, activate enhanced phishing protection first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian Jira Align, Version 10.107.4 Advisory]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/jira-align-advisory</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/jira-align-advisory"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read to learn details about the Atlassian Jira Align, Version 10.107.4 Advisory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Shafer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to enhance security to your Access Management and Authentication while reducing friction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=46194</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/how-to-add-more-controls-to-your-access-management-and-authentication-solution/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing access to your applications, infrastructure and data can no longer be done exclusively at a network level. With the adoption of cloud services and remote working, ensuring the right people have access to the right resources at the right time mostly comes down to one thing: Securing your Identity. efficiently and frictionlessly. Today, in […]
The post How to enhance security to your Access Management and Authentication while reducing friction appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jendres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: byte-stats.py Version 0.0.9]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9626</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/10/24/update-byte-stats-py-version-0-0-9/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of byte-stats.py, my tool to generate statistics for (binary) data, comes with an update to report the longest: byte-stats_V0_0_9.zip (http)MD5: 9187073EB63DE78BDACA1A3AB096DD19SHA256: 6BC1F8A6FDAA4E8484B6C86E38E214BCBF24AB20F80C92D8AEE3C5EA402D2F0C]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Testing A Lemon Battery]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9597</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/10/22/quickpost-testing-a-lemon-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T21:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a chat with my colleagues, we were joking about charging smartphones with a lemon battery. And I actually wanted to know what magnitude of electrical energy we were talking about. So I connected a lemon battery to an electronic load: I took a lemon, inserted a zinc and copper piece of metal (a couple […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: rtfdump.py Version 0.0.12]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9594</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/10/22/update-rtfdump-py-version-0-0-12/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T11:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This version adds support for ZIP files encrypted with AES, via the pyzipper module. rtfdump_V0_0_12.zip (http)MD5: C3D4F69908A49265E3877D4338462534SHA256: A40CC2744DE2D4C5956F5FD306357E7E105EC693B8BEA6E7E006C48EC78055BB]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use curl on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568325</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-use-curl-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T05:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curl (client URL) is a command-line tool powered by the libcurl library to transfer data to and from the server using various protocols, such as HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, FTPS, IMAP, IMAPS, POP3, POP3S, SMTP, and SMTPS. It is highly popular for automation and scripts due to its wide range of features and protocol support. In this article, you will learn how to use curl in Windows with various examples. Let’s get started.
How to use curl on Windows first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Things Right]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/making-things-right</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/making-things-right"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know HackerOne has had a Make It Right fund for years?
Often, programs and hackers come to agreeable solutions on reports according to in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effecting positive change in the Internet of Things]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26055</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/effecting-positive-change-in-the-internet-of-things/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T05:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Way back when… We started our journey back in the day when the IoT was in its infancy. Our first published research was in June 2015 with a post about […]
Effecting positive change in the Internet of Things first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary in the Kernel Mine: Exploiting and Defending Against Same-Type Object Reuse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/exploiting_and_defending_against_same_type_object_reuse.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/exploiting_and_defending_against_same_type_object_reuse.php"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog covers a difficult-to-defend subclass of use-after-free vulnerabilities in the Linux kernel, grsecurity's defense for it, and why our defense required compiler plugin involvement.  Included PoC exploits demonstrate the power and simplicity of this kind of vulnerability, as well as the effectiveness of grsecurity's defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary in the Kernel Mine: Exploiting and Defending Against Same-Type Object Reuse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/exploiting_and_defending_against_same_type_object_reuse.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/exploiting_and_defending_against_same_type_object_reuse.php"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog covers a difficult-to-defend subclass of use-after-free vulnerabilities in the Linux kernel, grsecurity's defense for it, and why our defense required compiler plugin involvement.  Included PoC exploits demonstrate the power and simplicity of this kind of vulnerability, as well as the effectiveness of grsecurity's defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PenTest Magazine Open Source Toolkit: ropci]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ropci-pentest-magazine-open-source-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ropci-pentest-magazine-open-source-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great news!
An article about ropci is in the latest open issue of the Pentest Magazine!

The article has a lot more info then my ropci blog post or the info on the ropci Github repo.
Get your copy and check it out! It also has an article about Nuclei, one of my favorite tools.
Cheers.
Link: https://pentestmag.com/product/pentest-open-source-pentesting-toolkit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROPC - So, you think you have MFA?]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ropci-so-you-think-you-have-mfa-azure-ad/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ropci-so-you-think-you-have-mfa-azure-ad/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will highlight a pattern I have seen across multiple production Microsoft Azure Active Directory tenants which led to MFA bypasses using ROPC.
The key take-away: Always enforce MFA! Sounds easy, but there are often misconfigurations and unexpected exceptions. So, test your own AAD tenant for ROPC based MFA bypass opportunities.
Github: https://github.com/wunderwuzzi23/ropci
Update: The latest open issue of Pentest Magazine has a ropci article. Check it out.
What is ROPC?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing Mimecast URL and File Inspection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=28656</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/social-engineering/bypassing-mimecast-email-defenses/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how we successfully bypassed Mimecast URL and file inspection features and worked with the email security company to remediate the issues.
The post Bypassing Mimecast URL and File Inspection appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sayler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resilient storage with Storage Spaces]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568304</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/resilient-storage-with-storage-spaces/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T10:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Historically, businesses have used RAID technologies to avoid data loss when disks fail. However, Windows Server offers a pure software-based alternative for resilient storage called Storage Spaces. It combines internal and attached drives to a single storage pool, where you can create virtual volumes. This feature supports multiple options for data redundancy.
Resilient storage with Storage Spaces first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Engineering dos and don’ts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26030</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/social-engineering-dos-and-donts/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T05:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day, another success at sneaking into a building and pretending to be staff. I do so love drinking other people’s expensive office coffee. No fruit bowls though. Close, but […]
Social Engineering dos and don’ts first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v3.1 Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/47cfcccd6b02</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-v3-1-now-available-47cfcccd6b02?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v3.1 is now available! This release introduces several new features along with a host of minor improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Maddalena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Vulnerabilities in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/vulnerabilities-2022</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/vulnerabilities-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your organization concerned with security vulnerabilities? Read on as we examine publicly disclosed reports to understand the most frequent vulnerability types, the highest-disclosed bounties, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlos Yanez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-3236: Sophos Firewall User Portal and Web Admin Code Injection]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63485beb0002466f71875024</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/10/19/cve-2022-3236-sophos-firewall-user-portal-and-web-admin-code-injection"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Guy Lederfein and Dusan Stevanovic of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched code injection vulnerability in the Sophos Firewall. The bug is due to improper validation of JSON keys submitted in the “JSON” parameter sent to the Controller endpoint. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could result in remote code execution with the privileges of the root user. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2022-3236, with a few minimal modifications.
Sophos recently patched a code injection vulnerability in Sophos Firewall v19.0 MR1 (19.0.1) and previous. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of JSON keys submitted in the “json” parameter sent to the Controlle…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3 connection contamination: an upcoming threat?]]></title>
        <id>http-3-connection-contamination</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/http-3-connection-contamination"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently documented a dangerous reverse-proxy behaviour called first-request routing, which enables host-header attacks on back-end systems. In this post, I'll show how first-request routing also en]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UserAccountControl attribute: Checking and configuring security settings for Active Directory accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568274</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/useraccountcontrol-attribute-checking-and-configuring-security-settings-for-active-directory-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UserAccountControl attribute can be used to configure several account settings in Active Directory. This applies, for example, to the expiration date of passwords or to Kerberos delegation. An AD audit should check this attribute regularly. This can be done using PowerShell, and there is a cmdlet for changing flags.
UserAccountControl attribute: Checking and configuring security settings for Active Directory accounts first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office Online Server Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3163</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2022/10/microsoft-office-online-server-remote-code-execution/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Office Online Server is the next generation of Office Web Apps Server; it provides a browser based viewer/editor for Word, PowerPoint, Excel and OneNote documents. The product can be...
The post Microsoft Office Online Server Remote Code Execution appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moto E20 Readback Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25859</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/moto-e20-readback-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T05:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The Motorola E20 is an entry-level smartphone that uses a Unisoc system-on-chip. Motorola holds around 10% of the US smartphone market, though the sales of the E20 as a […]
Moto E20 Readback Vulnerability first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Lodge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our new scanner for Text4Shell]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/?p=1796</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2022/10/18/our-new-scanner-for-text4shell/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T19:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some say, CVE-2022-42889 is the new Log4Shell, for which we developed our own tool to enumerate affected hosts back in 2021. Others like Rapid7 argue that it may not be as easy to exploit like Log4Shell. Regardless of the severity and exploitability of this vulnerability, we quickly morphed a clone of our Log4Shell plugin into … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dnet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See Your Cyber Defenses with an Adversarial Perspective Using Red Teaming and Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15358</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/red-teaming-and-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T15:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Complementary Benefits of Red Teaming and Pentesting Deploying Complementary Cybersecurity Tools In our previous article, we talked about the growing number of cybersecurity tools available on the market and how difficult it can be to choose which ones you need to deploy to protect your information and infrastructure from cyberattack. That article described how […]
The post See Your Cyber Defenses with an Adversarial Perspective Using Red Teaming and Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting the Mediation Team at H1-702]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/meeting-mediation-team-h1-702</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/meeting-mediation-team-h1-702"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T15:28:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello world, we are the Mediation Team.
For those who don’t know what we do - we are here to help the ethical hacking community and custome]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices for Identity and Access Management When Using Google Cloud Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4253</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/iam-best-practices-gcp/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Praetorian, one of our top priorities is looking over each client’s Identity and Access Management (IAM) structure. Several of our large clients use Google Cloud Provider (GCP), which is one of the top three cloud providers with about eight percent of the cloud services market share. During our work with GCP, we have noticed […]
The post Best Practices for Identity and Access Management When Using Google Cloud Provider appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We do Windows now]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102963</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/10/18/microsoft-windows-security-research-team/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T11:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Trail of Bits, we pride ourselves on building tools that everyone can use to help improve the security ecosystem. Given how ingrained Microsoft is with a large portion of our work — binary analysis, cryptography, cloud security — our teams’ research and development has resulted in numerous tool releases for the public to incorporate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cobian Backup revived: Cobian Reflector]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568262</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/cobian-backup-revived-cobian-reflector/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T10:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cobian Backup is a popular freeware backup tool. Its version 11 has been around since 2012. Recently, Luis Cobian, the author of the tool, released its brand-new version, Cobian Reflector. In this post, you will find all you need to know to get started with Reflector
Cobian Backup revived: Cobian Reflector first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Value of GIAC Cloud Security and Penetration Testing Certifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/explore-the-value-of-giac-cloud-security-and-penetration-testing-certifications</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/explore-the-value-of-giac-cloud-security-and-penetration-testing-certifications?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eighty two percent of organizations prefer hiring candidates with certifications — from cloud security to penetration testing, and far beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAM BAM - Recovering Web Tokens From Office]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/wam-bam/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/wam-bam/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post looks at the recent trend of pulling Azure tokens from Office process memory and tries to identify just how these tokens were loaded, how Office handles a Microsoft Account (MSA), and how we can recover cached credentials from the Token Broker Cache.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploits Explained: A Spy’s Perspective On Your Network]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15293</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/exploits-explained-a-spys-perspective-on-your-network/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T14:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremiah Roe is a Synack Solutions Architect forthe Federal and DoD space and We’re In! Podcast host. As a solutions architect, he helps organizations understand and implement effective security from an offensive perspective. He has an extensive background including work in the Marine Corps, network penetration testing, red team operations, wargaming and threat modeling. What […]
The post Exploits Explained: A Spy’s Perspective On Your Network appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremiah Roe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring the cloud clipboard in Windows 10/11 with Group Policy and PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568247</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configuring-the-cloud-clipboard-in-windows-1011-with-group-policy-and-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Windows 10 1809, Microsoft introduced a clipboard with multiple entries and added the ability to sync its contents among several devices. This cloud clipboard poses certain security risks, such as data leakage. However, it can be restricted by using Group Policy.
Configuring the cloud clipboard in Windows 10/11 with Group Policy and PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toner Deaf – Printing your next persistence (Hexacon 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17751</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/10/17/toner-deaf-printing-your-next-persistence-hexacon-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday 14th of October 2022 Alex Plaskett (@alexjplaskett) and Cedric Halbronn (@saidelike) presented Toner Deaf – Printing your next persistence at Hexacon 2022. This talk demonstrated remote over the network exploitation of a Lexmark printer and persistence across both firmware updates and reboots. The slides for this talk are now available here: The full … Continue reading Toner Deaf – Printing your next persistence (Hexacon 2022) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Plaskett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TTP Diaries: SSH Agent Hijacking]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ttp-diaries-ssh-agent-hijacking/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ttp-diaries-ssh-agent-hijacking/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T18:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some neat TTPs that I don’t use frequently, and if the time arises, I need to dig up details again. So, I figured to write some of them down, starting with SSH Agent Hijacking.
What is SSH Agent Hijacking? Short story, if you have keys added to an SSH Agent an adversary with root permissions can use them. If you forward the SSH Agent to another host, an adversary with root permission on that other host can exploit and leverage your keys as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ansible Galaxy?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568223</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/what-is-ansible-galaxy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T12:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Galaxy is your source for community content for Ansible, a popular multipurpose automation tool. In Ansible Galaxy, you can find roles and collections for just about any configuration management scenario. Don't see a role or collection that meets your needs, but have the know-how to build a solution? You can also share your creations with the broader community. In this article, I will teach you how to get started with Ansible Galaxy.
What is Ansible Galaxy? first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Kindle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GIAC Introduces Industry-First Cloud Forensic Responder (GCFR) Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/giac-introduces-industry-first-cloud-forensic-responder-gcfr-certification</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/giac-introduces-industry-first-cloud-forensic-responder-gcfr-certification?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re in the field of cloud incident response and analysis, put this industry-leading certification on your to-do list and validate your skills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: base64dump.py Version 0.0.24]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9589</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/10/13/update-base64dump-py-version-0-0-24/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T19:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a small update, to add extra statistical information for decoded items. base64dump_V0_0_24.zip (http)MD5: 47FDC47A9235CEF2DF95D1FC12BC166ESHA256: FAF376E267CE6937BAB7544EA4AF9DD40499886992E7DA3855C16C73C02276B1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing HackerOne Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/introducing-hackerone-assets</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/introducing-hackerone-assets"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding where the critical flaws lie within your organization's attack surface is critical—but complicated. After all, your attack surface includes your infrastructure, network, software, applications, devices, and the extended supply chain. But it doesn’t stop there. Digital transformation, cloud adoption, the shift to remote work, mergers and acquisitions (M&A), and shadow IT further muddy the waters for today’s security leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corb3nik Introduces His Tool: Caido]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/corb3nik-introduces-his-tool-caido</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/corb3nik-introduces-his-tool-caido"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, who is Corb3nik?
My name is Ian, also known as Corb3nik on social media. I’m a long time CTF enthusiast and bug bounty hunter. Currentl]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesse@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Duo 2FA: Two-factor authentication for RDP]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568197</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/duo-2fa-two-factor-authentication-for-rdp/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, you will learn how to enable two-factor authentication (2FA) for Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP). We will use Duo 2FA, a commercial security service from Duo Security, now owned by Cisco.
Duo 2FA: Two-factor authentication for RDP first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MS Enterprise app management service RCE. CVE-2022-35841]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25759</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/ms-enterprise-app-management-service-rce-cve-2022-35841/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T05:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR A remote command execution and local privilege escalation vulnerability has been fixed by Microsoft as part of September’s patch Tuesday. The vulnerability, filed under CVE-2022-35841, affects the Enterprise App […]
MS Enterprise app management service RCE. CVE-2022-35841 first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIP19 Espionage | New Chinese APT Targets IT Service Providers and Telcos With Signed Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=71576</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/wip19-espionage-new-chinese-apt-targets-it-service-providers-and-telcos-with-signed-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:27:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Precision targeting of critical infrastructure industries indicates espionage-related activity by an unattributed Chinese-speaking threat group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, No Case Studies—But . . .]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e7cf012af19807518fba2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/sorry-no-case-study"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend of the site recently suggested that we create a current-issue case 
study using our updated risk discovery approach. “It’s a great idea,” we 
replied and immediately started kicking around ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pointillism of Daily Events]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2c8f009baa12346d3711f</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/pointillism-daily-events"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Baker’s book Human Smoke brilliantly illustrates a unique approach 
to historical narrative. It also underscores the need to remember that 
every artist paints with intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ready for What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2aa91391dcb70804f9850</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/getting-ready-whats-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new age of giant monsters, advanced awareness of classical 
surprise—that one big tipping moment—no longer suffices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Your ‘Free Cells’ Mindfully]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62deb6110fd7f314e5696ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/manage-free-cells"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accommodate but don’t fight the limitations you can’t control, recognize 
those you can influence and leverage, and don't imagine you have more free 
cells than you actually do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popski’s Planning]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d81b5affdc983dd1f616f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/popskis-planning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British officer Vladimir Peniakoff’s approach to planning might sound a bit 
unorthodox at first, but it aligns nicely with Patton’s view of 
intelligence and speaks to an enduring need to understand front-line 
conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a New Game Board]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d5b6db0343fb487527fc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/time-for-a-new-game-board"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need a more flexible game board where players can explore hypergame 
strategies—in other words, a game board where the strategist can play the 
hero for a change. We’ve built it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survivors Exceeded the Minimum]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62cf11283f1bdb1191fcdf9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/survivors-exceeded-minimum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T18:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every surprise is a cunning thunderbolt. Some surprises creep up 
slowly, rusting away former resilience until a simple nudge reveals the 
rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>