<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-07-29T01:06:04.291Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stack Overflows, Heap Overflows, and Existential Dread (SonicWall SMA100 CVE-2025-40596, CVE-2025-40597 and CVE-2025-40598)]]></title>
        <id>6887e41e2cf0ac0001ec74a6</id>
        <link href="https://labs.watchtowr.com/stack-overflows-heap-overflows-and-existential-dread-sonicwall-sma100-cve-2025-40596-cve-2025-40597-and-cve-2025-40598/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T21:38:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s 2025, and at this point, we’re convinced there’s a secret industry-wide pledge: every network appliance must include at least one trivially avoidable HTTP header parsing bug - preferably pre-auth. Bonus points if it involves sscanf.
If that’s the case, well done!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sina Kheirkhah (@SinSinology)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Month of AI Bugs 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/announcement-the-month-of-ai-bugs/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2025/announcement-the-month-of-ai-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T17:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year I spent a lot of time reviewing, exploiting and working with vendors to fix vulnerabilities in agentic AI systems.
As a result, I’m excited to announce the Month of AI Bugs 2025!
Goal Of The Initiative The main purpose of the Month of AI Bugs is to raise awareness about novel security vulnerabilities in agentic systems, primarily focusing on AI coding agents. Posts will cover both simple and advanced, sometimes even mind-boggling exploits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mount an NFS Share on Windows 11 with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598632</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/mount-an-nfs-share-on-windows-11-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T15:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Network File System (NFS) is a widely used file-sharing protocol in Linux environments. However, many Windows administrators may not know you can mount an NFS share easily on Windows 11 and Windows Server. This guide shows you step-by-step instructions on activating NFS for Windows and mounting a share using PowerShell.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We built the security layer MCP always needed]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/28/we-built-the-security-layer-mcp-always-needed/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/28/we-built-the-security-layer-mcp-always-needed/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re announcing the beta release of mcp-context-protector, a security wrapper for LLM apps using the Model Context Protocol (MCP). It defends against the line jumping attacks documented earlier in this blog series, such as prompt injection via tool descriptions and ANSI terminal escape codes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our capabilities. A story about what we can achieve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42417</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/our-capabilities-a-story-about-what-we-can-achieve/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T09:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Pwnie Awards The first firm to have ever won two Pwnie Awards (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pwnie_Awards) at Black Hat. We won them for the Bitfi disclosure, winning ‘worst vendor response’ to the vulnerabilities that we, and a broader group of researchers that we helped coordinate, discovered in the crypto wallet promoted by John McAfee Nation-state grade red […]
The post Our capabilities. A story about what we can achieve appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Bursell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Data Centre of the Future]]></title>
        <id>df5fdee3-a813-463d-a897-d86f45b46cd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/quantum-data-centre-of-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T01:03:28.877Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2025-20281: Cisco ISE API Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6882885dde584b7abd7f6e59</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2025/7/24/cve-2025-20281-cisco-ise-api-unauthenticated-remote-code-execution-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 25th, 2025, the Trend Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) received a report from Kentaro Kawane of GMO Cybersecurity by Ierae regarding a deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE). This pre-authentication vulnerability existed in the enableStrongSwanTunnel method of the DescriptionRegistrationListener class. While analyzing this vulnerability, I noticed that the same function was also vulnerable to command injection as root. Cisco patched this initially as CVE-2025-20281(ZDI-25-609), but also released CVE-2025-20337 (ZDI-25-607) to fully address the vulnerability. You’ll see why below.
Exploitation wasn't as straight forward as I'd originally hoped but was ultimately a lot more fun than a normal, run-of-the-mill command injection. In this blog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Gould</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is AI overhyped?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598577</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/is-ai-overhyped/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T15:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you skeptical about AI? Do you believe that AI is overhyped? Then, the latest episode of the Big Technology podcast is for you. AI champion Alex Kantrowitz and fierce AI critic Ed Zitron tackle the gap between AI hype and reality. However, both prominent journalists overlook an essential aspect when assessing AI's economic potential.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft’s New Sentinel Data Lake Actually Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=21388</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2025/07/25/why-microsofts-new-sentinel-data-lake-actually-matters/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T14:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a Cybersecurity Architect Who’s Seen the Struggles Firsthand Over the years, we’ve migrated more than a few SIEM environments to Microsoft Sentinel. And no matter how different the organizations were, the same headaches kept showing up: Let’s be real, Microsoft Sentinel has always been powerful, but calling it “cost-effective” felt like a bit of … Continue reading Why Microsoft’s New Sentinel Data Lake Actually Matters →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxim Deweerdt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting zero days in abandoned hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/25/exploiting-zero-days-in-abandoned-hardware/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/25/exploiting-zero-days-in-abandoned-hardware/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We successfully exploited two discontinued network devices at DistrictCon’s inaugural Junkyard competition in February, winning runner-up for Most Innovative Exploitation Technique. Our exploit chains demonstrate why end-of-life hardware poses persistent security risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Services 101]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42381</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/android-services-101/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T10:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR  What are Android services?  Android splits its communications into multiple components, some of which we’ve written about before.  One of these components is service, which is a generic component that runs in a background thread. It can be communicated with by the local program through common IPC mechanisms.  Foreground, background, and bound services explained   […]
The post Android Services 101  appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainspotting 2: The Unofficial Sequel to the 2018 Talk "Chainspotting" - OffensiveCon 2025]]></title>
        <id>adcd7526-66c4-4a8f-ad0b-fcb77f027b3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/chainspotting-2-the-unofficial-sequel-to-the-2018-talk-chainspotting-offensivecon-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T00:59:02.358Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCP S.A.F.E. How-to]]></title>
        <id>41b47b36-95e7-4de6-9975-c0bf4fe03492</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/ocp-safe-how-to/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T00:59:02.351Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous AI Agents: A hidden Risk in Insecure smolagents “CodeAgent” Usage]]></title>
        <id>b7e60509-f3ad-4bf3-99da-68132768f8cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/autonomous-ai-agents-a-hidden-risk-in-insecure-smolagents-codeagent-usage/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T00:58:53.708Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install NFS server on Windows Server 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598537</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-nfs-server-on-windows-server-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T20:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFS is a practical solution for copying data between Windows and Linux systems. It is particularly useful for managing heterogeneous networks. This post will guide you through installing an NFS server on Windows Server 2025, creating an NFS share, and mounting it from Linux or Mac.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake CAPTCHA led to LUMMA100725]]></title>
        <id>80d98709-87b1-498f-81dd-19ef2245dc37</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/fake-captcha-led-to-lumma100725/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T00:59:17.577Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure App Services Token Decryption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=27955</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/automating-azure-app-services-token-decryption/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to decrypt Azure App Services authentication tokens automatically using MicroBurst’s tooling to extract encrypted tokens for security testing.
The post Automating Azure App Services Token Decryption appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Fosaaen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered email search with Claude Gmail Search, Zapier MCP server, GongRzhe’s MCP Server, and Gemini in Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598441</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/ai-powered-email-search-with-claude-gmail-search-zapier-mcp-server-gongrzhe-s-mcp-server-and-gemini-in-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T17:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tested three MCP servers in Anthropic Claude  Sonnet 4: Claude Gmail Search, Zapier Gmail MCP server, and GongRzhe’s Gmail MCP Server. I also submitted the same search prompt to Gemini in Gmail. The results varied greatly. Only two AI tools passed my test, one failed, and the most promising MCP server turned out to be useless.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside EthCC[8]: Becoming a smart contract auditor]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/23/inside-ethcc8-becoming-a-smart-contract-auditor/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/23/inside-ethcc8-becoming-a-smart-contract-auditor/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At EthCC[8], Trail of Bits blockchain security engineer Nicolas Donboly laid out a clear, actionable path for aspiring smart contract auditors, drawing from his own experience transitioning from a non-technical background into a leading security role.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate Hyper-V from Windows Server 2019 Core to Windows Server 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598403</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/migrate-hyper-v-from-windows-server-2019-core-to-windows-server-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T21:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating a Hyper-V host from Windows Server 2019 Core to Windows Server 2025 requires attention beyond just the virtual machines. The host's configuration is equally essential and includes network cards, vSwitches, and default paths, all of which need to be transferred accurately. Using Windows PowerShell, you can export key settings and restore them on a new server.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaked data. Continuous glucose monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42357</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/leaked-data-continuous-glucose-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T05:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Closing the Loop Just before COVID struck the world, I was travelling through Colorado on a Sunday on a ski trip with some friends. My work phone pinged with a message from a colleague (the awesome @evstykas who has now moved on to do even more cool things with APIs). That’s not particularly common as […]
The post Leaked data. Continuous glucose monitoring appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Bursell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Claude desktop extensions, connectors vs. local, remote MCP servers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598333</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/anthropic-claude-connectors-desktop-extensions-vs-local-remote-mcp-servers/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T13:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has introduced two new concepts for connecting AI models to resources through MCP: desktop extensions and connectors. Extensions are available only on Claude Desktop (Windows and Mac), while connectors are supported on both the desktop and the Claude.ai web app. All desktop extensions are local MCP servers, but not all local MCP servers qualify as extensions. Conversely, all remote MCP servers are considered connectors; however, not all connectors are remote MCP servers. Although some theoretical documentation about these new concepts exists, I mainly categorized them based on how Claude Desktop organizes the different types of MCP servers.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting code copying at scale with Vendetect]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/21/detecting-code-copying-at-scale-with-vendetect/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/21/detecting-code-copying-at-scale-with-vendetect/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vendetect is our new open-source tool for detecting copied and vendored code between repositories. It uses semantic fingerprinting to identify similar code even when variable names change or comments disappear. More importantly, unlike academic plagiarism detectors, it understands version control history, helping you trace vendored code back to its exact source commit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy S24 Pwn2Own Ireland 2024]]></title>
        <id>9bec7d86-1b81-435f-92c0-1346bc45a86f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/samsung-galaxy-s24-pwn2own-ireland-2024/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T00:57:13.380Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masquerade: You Downloaded ScreenConnect not Grok AI!]]></title>
        <id>1e69fac9-e002-4c73-a146-cbbd6dcacfc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/masquerade-you-downloaded-screenconnect-not-grok-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T00:57:06.372Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Microsoft AI Shell on Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598039</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-microsoft-ai-shell-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T15:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released AI Shell v1.0.0‑preview.5, which provides a Windows-only security patch, while Preview 4 delivered substantial improvements—enhanced macOS side‑pane support in iTerm2, Entra ID authentication, expanded Invoke‑AIShell functionality (with new -PostCode, -CopyCode, and -Exit flags)—all based on community feedback to improve workflows across Azure OpenAI, macOS, and PowerShell. This article also explains how to install Microsoft AI Shell on macOS.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI Chatbots to examine leaked data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42325</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/using-ai-chatbots-to-examine-leaked-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T11:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR  Introduction  AI is proving to be a useful companion for analysing data at scale for forensic examiners (data that is already publicly available if not privately hosted). This involves building an AI chatbot system based on large language models (LLMs) and should only be used for legitimate, ethical purposes (e.g. for internal automation, security […]
The post Using AI Chatbots to examine leaked data  appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building secure messaging is hard: A nuanced take on the Bitchat security debate]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/18/building-secure-messaging-is-hard-a-nuanced-take-on-the-bitchat-security-debate/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/18/building-secure-messaging-is-hard-a-nuanced-take-on-the-bitchat-security-debate/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of Bitchat last week was met with a mixture of glowing praise and sharp criticism. Both extremes bear some truth, but they also miss the mark and reveal gaps in how we discuss security in emerging products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cracking Mifare Classic 1K: RFID, Charlie Cards, and Free Subway Rides]]></title>
        <id>0208e86c-4e3e-4ad7-a478-0cec97943a70</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/cracking-mifare-classic-1k-rfid-charlie-cards-and-free-subway-rides/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T00:58:19.897Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing container networks in Windows Server 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598189</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/managing-container-networks-in-windows-server-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T15:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server 2025 can run Windows and Hyper-V containers. The former share resources like the kernel with the host OS and have process-level isolation, while the latter run in virtual machines. To enable communication between containers and with physical systems, you must configure the network accordingly.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fox Den Pull List: Our Favorite Comics]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/fox-den-pull-list-our-favorite-comics</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/fox-den-pull-list-our-favorite-comics"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Bishop Fox, thinking like an adversary comes naturally. So it’s no surprise that comics—where power, perspective, and outsider thinking collide—resonate deeply with our team. Ahead of Comic-Con 2025, we asked our Foxes: what comics still stick with you?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detection Engineering: Practicing Detection-as-Code – Repository – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=19871</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2025/07/17/detection-engineering-practicing-detection-as-code-repository-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second part of the Practicing Detection-as-Code series, where we will cover some basic elements of designing a repository to develop, store, and deploy detections from. We'll go through several different aspects of the setup like the Git platform, branch strategy, repository structure, detections structure, taxonomies, and content packs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stamatis Chatzimangou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2025-4660: Forescout SecureConnector RCE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=27881</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/red-teaming/cve-2025-4660-forescout-secureconnector-rce/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-16T21:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the high-risk RCE vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector allows attackers to turn security agents into C2 channels.
The post CVE-2025-4660: Forescout SecureConnector RCE  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in VS Code GitHub Copilot: Command allow/deny lists, resubmit requests, MCP server catalog]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598205</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-vs-code-github-copilot-command-allowdeny-lists-resubmit-requests-mcp-server-catalog/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-16T18:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code version 1.102 introduced several useful new features in GitHub Copilot. Command allow/deny lists let you specify which commands the Copilot agent can execute without asking for permission. The resubmit feature enables you to edit a previous request and resubmit the prompt. Additionally, the new VS Code version includes various updates for managing MCP servers, including a curated catalog of MCP servers.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Async BOFs – “Wake Me Up, Before You Go Go”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=5516</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2025/07/16/async-bofs-wake-me-up-before-you-go-go/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-16T11:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous BOFs: Enabling New Use Cases for Red Team Operators
The introduction of Beacon Object Files (BOFs) by Cobalt Strike in 2020 revolutionized the capabilities of red team operators and developers, offering a standardized interface for operator code to run within, and interact with, an implant. However, the current BOF standard was designed for synchronous operations, limiting its potential applications.
Asynchronous BOFs Execution Would Enable New Red Team Capabilities
Within this blog we introduce the concept and initial design of real-time monitoring for events (e.g. sleep until an admin logs in, sleep until a user starts his password vault) for Beacon Object Files. This new asynchronous design allows operators to roll out a network of sensors and stream these events to the C2 server for further processing – all while the implant is sleepmasked.
Tags: Async, AsyncBOF, BeaconWakeup, BOF, Monitoring, RedTreat, SleepMask
Read full post
The post Async BOFs – “Wake Me Up, Before You Go Go” appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dima van de Wouw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report - Google Confidential Space Security Assessment]]></title>
        <id>45218355-9087-47f4-a86c-8b2fe3d661d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/public-report-google-confidential-space-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-16T00:58:49.665Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) from source]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597871</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/build-windows-subsystem-for-linux-wsl-from-source/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-15T15:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft recently open sourced Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) under the MIT license, allowing anyone to freely inspect, modify, build, or distribute its source code. This article guides you through building WSL 2.6 from source, using CMake, a popular build system generator, on Windows.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2025-4919: Corruption via Math Space in Mozilla Firefox]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:68754bb2a03b700b052b6c96</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2025/7/14/cve-2025-4919-corruption-via-math-space-in-mozilla-firefox"/>
        <updated>2025-07-15T14:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been an increase interest in the JavaScript engine vulnerabilities in order to compromise web browsers. Notably, vulnerabilities in JIT engines are among the most favorite ones as it provides strong primitives and well-known techniques are already available to facilitate compromise. At Pwn2Own Berlin 2025, Manfred Paul compromised the Mozilla Firefox renderer process using a vulnerability in IonMonkey but did not further escape the JavaScript engine sandbox. IonMonkey is the JavaScript JIT compiler for SpiderMonkey (the Firefox JavaScript and WebAssembly engine) This vulnerability is assigned CVE-2025-4919 and Mozilla swiftly fixed it in Mozilla Firefox 138.0.4 via Security Advisory 2025-36 in the following day. Trend Zero Day Initiative assigned ZDI-25-291 to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hossein Lotfi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repeater Strike: manual testing, amplified]]></title>
        <id>repeater-strike-manual-testing-amplified</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/repeater-strike-manual-testing-amplified"/>
        <updated>2025-07-15T13:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manual testing doesn't have to be repetitive. In this post, we're introducing Repeater Strike - a new AI-powered Burp Suite extension designed to automate the hunt for IDOR and similar vulnerabilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Framework 13. Press here to pwn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42300</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/framework-13-press-here-to-pwn/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-15T05:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR  Introduction  BIOS protection is the digital equivalent of a locked front door, but what if the doorbell doubled as a reset button?  The Framework 13 laptop has a chassis intrusion detection switch. It’s designed to notify the BIOS when the laptop body has been opened. However, the same switch can be manipulated to reset the […]
The post Framework 13. Press here to pwn  appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP to MCP Bridge]]></title>
        <id>a699c57f-8fe9-41b2-aab4-6c15a432ac8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/http-to-mcp-bridge/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-15T00:59:44.827Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[METR study: Is AI-assisted coding overhyped?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598080</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/metr-study-is-ai-assisted-coding-overhyped/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-14T15:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study by METR got a lot of attention online. It claims that developers often overestimate the productivity boost from AI tools. In a coding test, the researchers found that AI caused a 19% "slowdown" for developers. In my opinion, it's not AI coding that's overhyped, but rather the study's findings.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch the on-demand webinar: Shift left without the strain]]></title>
        <id>watch-the-on-demand-webinar-shift-left-without-the-strain</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/watch-the-on-demand-webinar-shift-left-without-the-strain"/>
        <updated>2025-07-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shifting security left promises faster, safer software delivery - but for many teams, that promise is undercut by painful scan performance, false positives, and pipeline friction. In our recent webina]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1 little known secret of advpack.dll, LaunchINFSection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=10076</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2025/07/12/1-little-known-secret-of-advpack-dll-launchinfsection/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-12T22:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, yet another oldie with a secret… The .inf files are as old as Windows itself, and their internal structure has been covered by many, and over at least last two decades. So, what’s new? Well… Ever heard of LoadAdvpackExtension … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond good ol’ Run key, Part 149]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=10073</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2025/07/11/beyond-good-ol-run-key-part-149/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-11T23:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is a nothing burger. I didn’t make it work, but I still want to document it. When I came across a ‘GPExtensionDLL’ entry expected under HKLM\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\MPSSVC\Parameters I got excited, because it looked like a typical undocumented registry entry … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot concepts: An overview of all services and tools]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1598019</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/github-copilot-concepts-an-overview-of-all-services-and-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-11T13:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of GitHub Copilot concepts continues to grow, and their similar names can easily confuse. This post offers an overview of all the concepts, along with a link to find more information. The main confusion stems from the Copilot tools on GitHub.com and GitHub Copilot in VS Code. Although there is some overlap, keeping these two areas separate is essential.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-Auth SQL Injection to RCE - Fortinet FortiWeb Fabric Connector (CVE-2025-25257)]]></title>
        <id>6870e205b33c16000103b2dc</id>
        <link href="https://labs.watchtowr.com/pre-auth-sql-injection-to-rce-fortinet-fortiweb-fabric-connector-cve-2025-25257/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-11T10:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to yet another day in this parallel universe of security.
This time, we’re looking at Fortinet’s FortiWeb Fabric Connector. “What is that?” we hear you say. That's a great question; no one knows.
For the uninitiated, or unjaded;
Fortinet’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sina Kheirkhah (@SinSinology)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sil3ncer Deployed – RCE, Porn Diversion, and Ransomware on an SFTP-only Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42281</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/sil3ncer-deployed-rce-porn-diversion-and-ransomware-on-an-sftp-only-server/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-11T05:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Introduction We investigated a ransomware incident on a Windows Server 2012 host running in an SFTP-only role. The attacker delivered an attack that combined remote code execution, persistence, tunnelling, and a diversionary visit to Pornhub, before launching a ransomware payload. Background & scope An easy way in The compromised server was running a Telerik […]
The post Sil3ncer Deployed – RCE, Porn Diversion, and Ransomware on an SFTP-only Server appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Bursell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory: Condeon CMS]]></title>
        <id>1b3bba93-cb5a-46ee-95cf-c2f46efef69a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/technical-advisory-condeon-cms/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-11T00:57:45.015Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crack the Riddle, Secure the Oasis: Core NetWars Version 11 is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/crack-the-riddle-secure-the-oasis-core-netwars-version-11-is-here</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/crack-the-riddle-secure-the-oasis-core-netwars-version-11-is-here?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2025-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about SANS Institute's new Core NetWars Version 11]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Microsoft Sovereign Cloud?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597977</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/what-is-microsoft-sovereign-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-10T18:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft recently announced Microsoft Sovereign Cloud, which is aimed at European customers. The main goal is to provide more autonomous solutions in a politically complex climate, including options that do not require a cloud connection. Nonetheless, detailed information about the product has yet to be disclosed.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Miedl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report - VeChainThor Galactica Security Assessment]]></title>
        <id>500f237d-5d48-40f2-9249-23e3c2c93f1e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/public-report-vechainthor-galactica-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-10T00:57:03.016Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Authorization Flaws in Java Spring via Source Code Review (SCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=27828</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/secure-code-review/authorization-flaws-java-spring-via-source-code-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-09T22:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how secure code review catches privilege escalation vulnerabilities in Java Spring apps that pentests miss - identify insecure patterns early.
The post Detecting Authorization Flaws in Java Spring via Source Code Review (SCR) appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayuri Bochare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free up RAM in Windows with taskkill, PowerShell, and Sysinternals RAMMap]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597912</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/free-up-ram-in-windows-with-taskkill-powershell-and-sysinternals-rammap/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-09T19:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freeing up RAM on Windows can significantly improve system performance, especially when certain applications consume excessive memory. In this guide, you’ll learn how to free up RAM using taskkill on the command prompt, PowerShell, wmic, and the free Sysinternals RAMMap tool, with step-by-step instructions for each method.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You’re Pen Testing AI Wrong: Why Prompt Engineering Isn’t Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/youre-pen-testing-ai-wrong-why-prompt-engineering-isnt-enough</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/youre-pen-testing-ai-wrong-why-prompt-engineering-isnt-enough"/>
        <updated>2025-07-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conventional pen testing methods fall short with LLMs. Static prompt tests miss adversarial context manipulation and latent model behaviors. Explore how to test AI systems like an attacker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where You Inject Matters: The Role-Specific Impact of Prompt Injection Attacks on OpenAI models]]></title>
        <id>baf4c73f-3041-41f0-9414-20f6bef7ee2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/where-you-inject-matters-the-role-specific-impact-of-prompt-injection-attacks-on-openai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-09T00:57:28.061Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The July 2025 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:686d524906e3011303d5b06d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2025/7/8/the-july-2025-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T17:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second Tuesday of the month, and as expected, Adobe and Microsoft have released their latest security patches. Take a break from your scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts. If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for July 2025
For July, Adobe (eventually) released 13 bulletins addressing 60 unique CVEs in Adobe ColdFusion, After Effects, Substance 3D Viewer, Audition, InCopy, InDesign, Connect, Dimension, Substance 3D Stager, Illustrator, FrameMaker, Experience Manager Forms, and Experience Manager Screens. The obvious place to start here is ColdFusion. It’s the only update listed as Priority 1 and addresses 13 CVEs, five of which are rated Critical. ColdFus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Microsoft Azure MCP Server in VS Code GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597826</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-microsoft-azure-mcp-server-in-vs-code-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T17:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure MCP Server allows AI agents like VS Code GitHub Copilot in Agent Mode to communicate with your Azure resources through natural language prompts. Azure MCP Server supports services such as Storage, Cosmos DB, Key Vault, and Logs.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigate your dependencies with Deptective]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/08/investigate-your-dependencies-with-deptective/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/08/investigate-your-dependencies-with-deptective/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deptective, our new open-source tool, automatically finds the packages needed to install software dependencies. It does so not based on the software’s self-reported requirements, but by observing what the software needs at runtime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PortSwigger at Black Hat &amp; DEF CON 33]]></title>
        <id>portswigger-at-black-hat-amp-def-con-33</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/portswigger-at-black-hat-amp-def-con-33"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T09:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Las Vegas. August. Protocols are getting torn apart. This summer, PortSwigger returns to Black Hat USA and DEF CON 33 with a host of new talks, events and ways to meet PortSwigger and the the teams be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detection Engineering: Practicing Detection-as-Code – Introduction – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=19831</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2025/07/08/detection-engineering-practicing-detection-as-code-introduction-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part we are going through the basic terminology and concepts of a Detection-as-Code approach in Detection Engineering. Throughout this series, we’ll dive deep into a wide range of concepts, strategies, and practical blueprints that you can adapt to fit your own workflows. From building a detection engineering repository to validating detections, automating documentation, and delivering them at scale to numerous managed environments. We’ll also explore how to effectively test and monitor your detections to ensure they stay reliable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stamatis Chatzimangou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set Sail: Remote Code Execution in SailPoint IQService via Default Encryption Key]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=27787</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/network-pentesting/remote-code-execution-sailpoint-iqservice/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T07:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NetSPI discovered a remote code execution vulnerability in SailPoint IQService using default encryption keys. Exploit details, discovery methods, and remediation guidance included. 
The post Set Sail: Remote Code Execution in SailPoint IQService via Default Encryption Key appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Juntunen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to conduct a Password Audit in Active Directory (AD)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42212</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-to-conduct-a-password-audit-in-active-directory-ad/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T05:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Introduction Weak or compromised passwords are still one of the most common ways attackers get into an organisation’s network. That’s why running password audits in Active Directory is so important. But smaller companies often don’t have the time, budget, or resources to do them regularly. This blog post gives you a step-by-step guide to […]
The post How to conduct a Password Audit in Active Directory (AD) appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Bursell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Grafana 12 on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597751</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-grafana-12-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T16:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grafana is an open-source platform for analytics and monitoring that allows you to visualize metrics, logs, and traces from any source. This blog post will walk you through installing the newly released Grafana 12 on Windows.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: 12V Portable Power Station]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10950</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2025/07/06/quickpost-12v-portable-power-station/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-06T09:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In blog post “My Fridge & My Portable Power Station” I managed to get a maximum of 778 Wh out of my portable power station with a rated capacity of 1260 Wh. Thinking that quite some power got lost in the AC inverter, I set out to measure the amount of power I can get […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond good ol’ Run key, Part 148]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=10068</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2025/07/05/beyond-good-ol-run-key-part-148/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T23:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing the very same binary (AggregatorHost.exe) that makes the persistence trick described in my previous post work, I noticed that there is one more Registry entry we can use as a persistence mechanism: HKLM\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Diagnostics\DiagTrack\TestHooks\TestUndockedAggregatorDll=<malware> Same as in the previous post, … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond good ol’ Run key, Part 147]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=10063</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2025/07/05/beyond-good-ol-run-key-part-147/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T23:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I mentioned TestHook at least twice in the past. I actually love this keyword/string, because it is associated with many undocumented internal Microsoft test frameworks that we can sometimes abuse. And many ‘TestHook’ string references are present in many binaries … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much More Must We Bleed? - Citrix NetScaler Memory Disclosure (CitrixBleed 2 CVE-2025-5777)]]></title>
        <id>686825056b759800016a46da</id>
        <link href="https://labs.watchtowr.com/how-much-more-must-we-bleed-citrix-netscaler-memory-disclosure-citrixbleed-2-cve-2025-5777/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T19:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before you dive into our latest diatribe, indulge us and join us on a journey.
Sit in your chair, stand at your desk, lick your phone screen - close your eyes and imagine a world in which things are great. It’s sunny outside, the birds are chirping, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sina Kheirkhah (@SinSinology)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Format hard drive: EaseUS Partition Master Free vs. Windows tools]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597711</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/format-hard-drive-easeus-partition-master-free-vs-windows-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T18:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows provides native tools for formatting hard drives, such as Disk Management, File Explorer, and DiskPart. Alternatively, you can use EaseUS Partition Master Free, which enables quick and easy formatting of hard drives and partitions.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet microchip scams and data leaks in the UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=42157</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/pet-microchip-scams-and-data-leaks-in-the-uk/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T05:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR We were recently on BBC Morning Live talking about issues with pet microchip data, helping some pet owners understand how they were being billed for services which they didn’t recall signing up for. There was so much more to this piece though, so we’ve written up our findings in more detail here. It’s a […]
The post Pet microchip scams and data leaks in the UK appeared first on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Bursell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Threads layout in Teams channel posts aims to simplify conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597601</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-threads-layout-in-teams-channel-posts-aims-to-simplify-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T15:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is adding a Threads layout to Teams channel posts. This feature introduces a new level of structure that enables more interactive conversations, similar to social networks like Facebook or X.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Miedl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD Training from the Front Lines: Offensive Security at Black Hat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5603</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/ci-cd-training-from-the-front-lines-offensive-security-at-black-hat/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T15:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Red Team has explored and exploited vulnerabilities in the CI/CD space over the last several years, resulting in numerous successful offensive operations, open-source tool development, and presentations at Black Hat, DEF CON, and Schmoocon. With organizations increasingly relying on automated deployment pipelines, securing CI/CD infrastructure has become more critical than ever — yet many […]
The post CI/CD Training from the Front Lines: Offensive Security at Black Hat appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 25H2: enablement package with valuable new features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597632</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-11-25h2-enablement-package-with-valuable-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T16:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 25H2 is scheduled for release in fall 2025. Windows Insider Program members can try out the update early in the Dev channel. Notably, Windows 11 25H2 isn’t a traditional in-place upgrade; it’s an enablement package, which is a minor update that unlocks dormant new features such as Quick Machine Recovery and Administrator Protection.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Elsberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buckle up, Buttercup, AIxCC’s scored round is underway!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/02/buckle-up-buttercup-aixccs-scored-round-is-underway/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/07/02/buckle-up-buttercup-aixccs-scored-round-is-underway/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our CRS (Cyber Reasoning System), Buttercup, is now competing in the one and only scored round of DARPA’s AI Cyber Challenge (AIxCC) against six other teams to see which autonomous AI-driven system can find and patch the most software vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Trail of Bits Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS NimDoor | DPRK Threat Actors Target Web3 and Crypto Platforms with Nim-Based Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=124926</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/macos-nimdoor-dprk-threat-actors-target-web3-and-crypto-platforms-with-nim-based-malware/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T09:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NimDoor shows how threat actors are continuing to explore cross-platform languages that introduce new levels of complexity for analysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Stokes &amp; Raffaele Sabato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlining Global Automotive Cybersecurity Governance to Accelerate Innovation, Assurance, and Compliance]]></title>
        <id>63a64173-3acd-448b-923a-6ae1a35410ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/streamlining-global-automotive-cybersecurity-governance-to-accelerate-innovation-assurance-and-compliance/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T00:56:30.927Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 MCP Security Tips]]></title>
        <id>42993a6f-3d6e-47f7-8ee2-8fdab3efb921</id>
        <link href="https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/5-mcp-security-tips/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T00:56:24.598Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Cyber Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Doorbell & Condensation]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10907</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2025/07/02/quickpost-doorbell-condensation/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember that I broke the filament of the light-bulb in my doorbell? Turns out there is another advantage to having a light-bulb in your doorbell: it prevents condensation: Quickpost info]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extracting Sensitive Information from Azure Load Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=27767</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/extracting-sensitive-information-azure-load-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T20:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Azure Load Testing's JMeter JMX and Locust support enables code execution, metadata queries, reverse shells, and Key Vault secret extraction vulnerabilities.
The post Extracting Sensitive Information from Azure Load Testing appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Fosaaen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini CLI: Free AI-powered terminal assistant for the IT admin]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597566</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/google-gemini-cli-free-ai-powered-terminal-assistant-for-the-it-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T16:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's new Gemini CLI allows up to 60 model requests per minute and 1,000 daily requests. Professional developers might hit these limits quickly, but many IT admins will find the free plan sufficient. Compared to Anthropic Claude Code and OpenAI Codex CLI, I find Google's open-source AI-powered terminal more useful for the AI-augmented admin.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitPhish: Automating Enterprise GitHub Device Code Phishing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5563</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/gitphish-automating-enterprise-github-device-code-phishing/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T12:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks ago, we published research on GitHub Device Code Phishing, a simple technique that can turn an eight-digit code and a phone call into a complete compromise of an organization’s GitHub repositories and software supply chain. While the concept is simple, executing these attacks often brings multiple layers of complexity, like building a convincing […]
The post GitPhish: Automating Enterprise GitHub Device Code Phishing appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in June]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10945</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2025/07/01/overview-of-content-published-in-june-10/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in June: Blog posts: Update: myjson-transform.py Version 0.0.2 Update: search-for-compression.py Version 0.0.4 Quickpost: Firefox Profiles and Multiple Instances Quickpost: emldump Bulk Extraction DSS_DEFAULT_HASH_ALGORITHMS Python Requirements for Didier Stevens Suite Quickpost: USB-C Couplers Update: pngdump.py Version 0.0.7 My Fridge & My Portable Power Station Update: pecheck.py Version 0.7.18 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL 2.6) goes open source]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1597466</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-subsystem-for-linux-wsl-26-goes-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T17:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first open-source WSL release, Windows Subsystem for Linux, is available for preview. WSL is a platform that enables you to run Linux distributions within Windows. This article looks at the new release, 2.6, the open-source shift, and highlights updates to the stable branch, 2.5.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOF Linting for Accelerated Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=5057</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2025/06/30/bof-linting-for-accelerated-development/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T07:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Beacon Object Files (BOFs) allows operators to extend the functionality of a C2 framework, though their development may sometimes involve hidden complexities that only become apparent after the BOF is executed. Today, we introduce a BOF linting tool to address some of the common pitfalls.
BOFs are lightweight, in-memory modules used in Cobalt Strike and other post-exploitation/C2 frameworks such as Outflank C2 and Core Impact.  They are object files produced by a C compiler (COFF). Cobalt Strike parses this file and acts as a linker and loader for its contents. This approach allows you to write code for use in Beacon, without tedious gymnastics to manage strings and dynamically call Win32 APIs.
BOFs are powerful and flexible, but their minimalistic design inherently comes with strict constraints.

Read full post
The post BOF Linting for Accelerated Development appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Van Bockhaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding on ChunkyIngress - Clippy Goes Rogue (GoClipC2)]]></title>
        <id>663cbd24748ff8079069f78f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/clippy-goes-rogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-15T10:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoClipC2: A covert Windows clipboard-based C2 channel for VDI/RDP environments. Bypasses network monitoring with encrypted Base64 messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cost Savings of Fixing Security Flaws in Development]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/cost-savings-fixing-security-flaws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/cost-savings-fixing-security-flaws"/>
        <updated>2025-02-25T18:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Mateer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Approach to Proving Cybersecurity Value (That Isn’t ROI)]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/new-approach-proving-cybersecurity-value</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/new-approach-proving-cybersecurity-value"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T23:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we are excited to announce our white paper on Return on Mitigation (RoM), a framework we designed to quantify the financial impact of security programs in a way that speaks to business leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>joseph@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 Years of Partnership: Snap and HackerOne Reach $1M in Bounties]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/hackerone-and-snap-celebrating-10-years</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/hackerone-and-snap-celebrating-10-years"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T19:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Snap, security is more than a priority—it’s a core mission. Over the past decade, Snap has partnered with HackerOne to build and sustain a robust bug bounty program. This collaboration has led to major milestones, including paying security researchers over $1M in bounties. To celebrate this achievement and their 10-year partnership, we spoke with Jim Higgins, Snap's Chief Information Security Officer, Vinay Prabhushankar, Snap’s Security Engineering Manager, and Ilana Arbisser, Snap’s Privacy Engineer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women@ Kicks Off the Year with a Vision Board Event]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/women-kicks-year-vision-board-event</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/women-kicks-year-vision-board-event"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T18:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gain Actionable, Data-backed Insights with HackerOne Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/gain-actionable-data-backed-insights-hackerone-recommendations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/gain-actionable-data-backed-insights-hackerone-recommendations"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T23:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if your security program could self-optimize: analyze trends, identify weak points, and proactively propose actionable steps to strengthen defenses? With HackerOne Recommendations, it can.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Collins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, Hackbots: How AI Is Shaping the Future of Vulnerability Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/welcome-hackbots-how-ai-shaping-future-vulnerability-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/welcome-hackbots-how-ai-shaping-future-vulnerability-discovery"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Hackbots and how are they impacting vulnerability discovery and the researcher community?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DORA Compliance Is Here: What Financial Entities Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/blog/dora-compliance-here-what-financial-entities-should-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/blog/dora-compliance-here-what-financial-entities-should-know"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T17:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new DORA regulation: everything your organization needs to know about its impact and how to comply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vanessa Booth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>