<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-29T06:10:53.087Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: rtfdump.py Version 0.0.11]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9571</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/28/update-rtfdump-py-version-0-0-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T21:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version of rtfdump, my tool to analyze RTF files, brings json output for options -O and -F. rtfdump_V0_0_11.zip (http)MD5: AFC884082B251BF288B05203DD5D4F69SHA256: CB3984924137897F75E62C3A835BB9197CBF1DDBD6BCFB3E18423999B06A36C8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco CUCM (CallManager) architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567924</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/cisco-cucm-callmanager-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T16:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most popular Voice Over IP systems is the Cisco Unified Communication Manager System. Cisco uses several abbreviations for its VOIP system: Cisco Unified (CM), CallManager, and CUCM. This intro will focus on the CUCM architecture; that is, I will explain the most important components and concepts you need to understand if you plan to deploy CallManager in your organization.
Cisco CUCM (CallManager) architecture first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploits Explained: 5 Unusual Authentication Bypass Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14808</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/exploits-explained-5-unusual-authentication-bypass-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T16:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ozgur Alp is a member of the Synack Red Team and has been awarded SRT of the Year 2021, Most Trusted Hacker 2021, Mentor of the Year 2022 and SRT Grand Champion for 2019, 2020 and 2021. Authentication bypass vulnerabilities are common flaws that exist in modern web applications—but they’re not always easy to find.  […]
The post Exploits Explained: 5 Unusual Authentication Bypass Techniques appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SRT Community</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Tale of IBM i (AS/400) Hacking]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/?p=1737</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2022/09/28/another-tale-of-ibm-i-as-400-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T13:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next journey takes us into the infrastructure of a bank. One element of the infrastructure was an IBM i (AS/400) server, and the only piece of information we got to conduct the penetration test was its IP address. We had been collecting a list of common application and service users during previous pentests, so … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know Your Enemy, Know Yourself: Examining the Mind of a Cyber Attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/examine-cyber-attacker-minds</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/examine-cyber-attacker-minds"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We partnered with SANS to bring you a groundbreaking report that explores the minds and methodologies of modern cyber adversaries. See what inspired our research and get access to the full report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wes Hutcherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attacking Encrypted HTTP Communications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25809</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/attacking-encrypted-http-communications/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T05:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The Reolink RLC-520A PoE camera obfuscates its HTTP communication by encrypting the POST body data. This level of security does defend against opportunistic attackers but falls short when defending […]
Attacking Encrypted HTTP Communications first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lovett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SANS Python Course | SEC673: Advanced Information Security Automation with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/new-sans-automation-course-sec673-advanced-information-security-automation-with-python</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/new-sans-automation-course-sec673-advanced-information-security-automation-with-python?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through immersive, hands-on labs, learn Python advanced coding techniques to build cybersecurity projects and automate information security tasks and security operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Hackerone’s Enhanced Pentest as a Service to Streamline Security Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/pentests/use-hackerones-enhanced-pentest-service-streamline-security-testing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/pentests/use-hackerones-enhanced-pentest-service-streamline-security-testing"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New capabilities improve pentesting to increase attack resistance
The enhanced features drive robust security testing practices with the ability to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Ryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whitepaper – Project Triforce: Run AFL On Everything (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17588</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/27/whitepaper-project-triforce-run-afl-on-everything-2017/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T19:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six years ago, NCC Group researchers Tim Newsham and Jesse Hertz released TriforceAFL – an extension of the American Fuzzy Lop (AFL) fuzzer which supports full-system fuzzing using QEMU – but unfortunately the associated whitepaper for this work was never published. Today, we’re releasing it for the curious reader and historical archives alike. While fuzzing … Continue reading Whitepaper – Project Triforce: Run AFL On Everything (2017) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprintx Tool: An Internship Project for the Real World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4173</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/fingerprintx/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T13:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Port fingerprinting can detect specific services running on a network, which makes it useful during penetration tests. It expands visibility into potential attack surfaces and vulnerabilities within the network environment. Over the summer, our interns worked towards developing a new tool for port fingerprinting services: Fingerprintx Fingerprintx is a port fingerprinting utility tool useful […]
The post Fingerprintx Tool: An Internship Project for the Real World appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom error message for access denied]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567902</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/custom-error-message-for-access-denied/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T12:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you access a file share in Windows and the conditions for access are not met, you are normally presented with a generic access denied message. It is actually possible to customize the error message to provide more meaningful and understandable output that aids with dynamic access control, rather than the simple "contact your network administrator," which will invariably result in a call to the service desk. However, there are a couple of limitations to this functionality.
Custom error message for access denied first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rankin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Flexible Way to Pentest Continuously: Synack90]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14828</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/a-flexible-way-to-pentest-continuously-synack90/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T18:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An astounding 82% of organizations believe they have experienced at least one data breach due to digital transformation, according to a recent survey. Fast paced cloud migrations have created new risks and challenges that require continuous monitoring of your digital assets. Attackers are now scanning for vulnerable endpoints within 15 minutes. Zero day vulnerabilities like […]
The post A Flexible Way to Pentest Continuously: Synack90 appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justine Desmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring Defender Antivirus: Exclusions, real-time protection, scans, and remediations]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567872</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configuring-defender-antivirus-exclusions-real-time-protection-scans-and-remediations/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T14:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On most PCs, Defender Antivirus runs with the default settings. However, Microsoft offers admins many options to customize the behavior of its security component. This can be used to improve compatibility with applications, optimize scanning, or change the response to threats.
Configuring Defender Antivirus: Exclusions, real-time protection, scans, and remediations first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZTH-CH4: Hook & Sling - Phishing For Gold]]></title>
        <id>5cf5c22a4581ca5ebe2263be</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/phishing-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T09:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To this date, phishing is one of the most prevalent first stages of entry to an organisation, a lot of threat actors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World’s Best Cyber Security Training Just Got Even Better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/new-ondemand-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/new-ondemand-announcement?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launch of the new SANS OnDemand platform brings new features, improves usability, and boosts accessibility. Learn more, and take it for a test drive with a free course demo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW DFIR COURSE IN DEVELOPMENT | FOR548: eDiscovery: Tactics for Conquering the Data Minefield]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/new-dfir-course-for548-ediscovery-tactics-for-conquering-the-data-minefield</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/new-dfir-course-for548-ediscovery-tactics-for-conquering-the-data-minefield?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR548: eDiscovery: Tactics for Conquering the Data Minefield course will teach students the controls put in place to govern the eDiscovery process, where and how the data is stored and how best to satisfy the collection requirements imposed upon them and their organizations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking A Look At PNG Files with pngdump.py Beta Version 0.0.3]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9556</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/25/taking-a-look-at-png-files-with-pngdump-py-beta-version-0-0-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T20:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a new beta version of my tool pngdump.py, a tool to analyze PNG files. I took a look at all files on MalwareBazaar with a PNG tag, and made updates to pngdump.py to handle them. I found 3 types of “PNG” files. First, files spoofing PNG files: files that are not PNG files, but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rise of Internet Bug Bounty]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/rise-internet-bug-bounty</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/rise-internet-bug-bounty"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T17:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a veteran hacker, someone who loves code review, or looking to get your first CVE? Then, I have something to share with you. Let's talk abou]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesse@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Docker on Windows 10 and Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567851</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-docker-in-windows-10-and-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T16:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is a platform for creating and deploying applications in self-sufficient containers. The installation of Docker is pretty easy in Linux, but this is usually not the case with Windows. In this post, I will show you how to install Docker in Windows 10 or Windows 11 in multiple ways. You'll learn there is indeed a way that makes the Docker Desktop installation in Windows as simple as in Linux.
Install Docker on Windows 10 and Windows 11 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Creating indicator relationships in integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12010</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/09/23/cortex-xsoar-tips-tricks-creating-indicator-relationships-in-integrations/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T08:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction When a Threat Intelligence Management (TIM) license is present in your Cortex XSOAR environment, the feature to create relationships between indicators is available. This allows you to describe how indicators relate to each other and use this relationship in your automated analysis of a security incident. In the previous blog post in this series, … Continue reading Cortex XSOAR Tips & Tricks – Creating indicator relationships in integrations →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wouter Stinkens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Void Balaur | The Sprawling Infrastructure of a Careless Mercenary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=70944</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/the-sprawling-infrastructure-of-a-careless-mercenary/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T23:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Void Balaur cyber mercenary group has thrived throughout 2022, attacking targets on a global scale with new phishing campaigns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mystery of Metador | An Unattributed Threat Hiding in Telcos, ISPs, and Universities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=70988</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/the-mystery-of-metador-an-unattributed-threat-hiding-in-telcos-isps-and-universities/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An elusive adversary is attacking high-value targets with impunity using novel malware frameworks and custom-built backdoors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Andrés Guerrero-Saade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release – Project Kubescout: Adding Kubernetes Support to Scout Suite]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17436</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/22/tool-release-project-kubescout-adding-kubernetes-support-to-scout-suite/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tl;dr You can now have Scout Suite scan not only your cloud environments, but your Kubernetes clusters. Just have your kubeconfig ready and run the following commands: $ pip3 install --user https://github.com/nccgroup/ScoutSuite/archive/develop.zip $ scout kubernetes Background NCC Group’s Container Orchestration Security Service (COSS) practice regularly conducts Kubernetes cluster configuration reviews spanning platform-managed Kubernetes clusters across … Continue reading Tool Release – Project Kubescout: Adding Kubernetes Support to Scout Suite →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liyun Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install the PfSense firewall on a virtual machine]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567797</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-install-the-pfsense-firewall-on-a-virtual-machine/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PfSense is a free open-source network firewall and router based on FreeBSD. PfSense is known for its reliability and comes with many features that only commercial firewalls offer. PfSense is included in many third-party free software packages. You can install PfSense on both physical and virtual machines. Appliances are also available.
How to install the PfSense firewall on a virtual machine first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Multiple Vulnerabilities in Juplink RX4-1800 WiFi Router (CVE-2022-37413, CVE-2022-37414)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17340</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/22/technical-advisory-multiple-vulnerabilities-in-juplink-rx4-1800-wifi-router-cve-2022-37413-cve-2022-37414/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juplink’s RX4-1800 WiFi router was found to have multiple vulnerabilities exposing its owners to potential intrusion in their local WiFi network and complete overtake of the device. An attacker can remotely take over a device after using a targeted or phishing attack to change the router’s administrative password, effectively locking the owner out of their … Continue reading Technical Advisory – Multiple Vulnerabilities in Juplink RX4-1800 WiFi Router (CVE-2022-37413, CVE-2022-37414) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Reed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement Arculix for Zero Trust Security and Continuous Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=45763</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/implement-arculix-for-zero-trust-security-and-continuous-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know a lot of buzzwords get thrown at you every day with products that want to help you implement Zero Trust, passwordless, adaptive and continuous authentication. But have you matured your identity and access management (IAM) implementation to check any of these initiatives off your list? We recently announced the release of Arculix, the […]
The post Implement Arculix for Zero Trust Security and Continuous Authentication appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(In)Secure by Design]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/in-secure-by-design</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/in-secure-by-design"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how your organization can improve application security by applying secure design patterns, avoiding anti-patterns, and adding security architecture analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bush, Shanni Prutchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making HTTP header injection critical via response queue poisoning]]></title>
        <id>making-http-header-injection-critical-via-response-queue-poisoning</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/making-http-header-injection-critical-via-response-queue-poisoning"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP header injection is often under-estimated and misclassified as a moderate severity flaw equivalent to XSS or worse, Open Redirection. In this post, I'll share a simple technique I used to take a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can’t stop me. MS Teams session hijacking and bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25777</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/you-cant-stop-me-ms-teams-session-hijacking-and-bypass/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T05:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How cleartext session tokens are stored in an unsecured directory that can be stolen and used to impersonate a Teams user. TL;DR Microsoft Teams stores unencrypted session tokens and cached […]
You can’t stop me. MS Teams session hijacking and bypass first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Masters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HoneyPoC is Dead - Long Live Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>632bb8838180697158e6932c</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/honeypoc-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T02:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This short blog post explains what each tool does and overviews the use/reason for the release. Release of AutoPoC and SandboxSpy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Tuning The Electric Energy Consumption Of My TV]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9528</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/22/quickpost-tuning-the-electric-energy-consumption-of-my-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR: reducing the sound volume level of our TV has no (significant) impact on its electric energy consumption, but reducing the back-lighting does. Here in Belgium, mainstream media is full of news with tips to reduce energy consumption. Some good tips, some bad tips … That’s mainstream media for you 🙂 Recently, there was an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cloud Security Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog outlining the new SANS Institute Cloud Security Curriculum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Five Most Dangerous New Attack Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-five-most-dangerous-new-attack-techniques</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-five-most-dangerous-new-attack-techniques?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous RSA Conference keynote presentations on the most dangerous new attack techniques in use today and how to prepare for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cybersecurity-leadership-curriculum</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cybersecurity-leadership-curriculum?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Curriculum which is developing cyber security managers and leaders worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW SANS DFIR COURSE | FOR577: LINUX Incident Response & Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-dfir-course-for577-linux-incident-response-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-dfir-course-for577-linux-incident-response-analysis?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux powers a vast range of business-critical systems across the globe. From webservers to database platforms, to network hardware to security appliances, Linux can often be found “under the hood” making sure the system just keeps working. FOR577: Linux Incident Response & Analysis course gives incident responders and forensic investigators the knowledge they need to understand how the systems work, how attackers compromise environments and how to respond and investigate in an effective manner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inserting data into other processes’ address space, part 1a]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8225</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/09/21/inserting-data-into-other-processes-address-space-part-1a/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T22:05:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I never thought I will write the part 1a of my old post, but here it is. As usual, I have not explored the below topic in-depth, but have certainly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MindShaRE: Analyzing BSD Kernels for Uninitialized Memory Disclosures using Binary Ninja]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6328da69c8594d3c90669eab</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/9/19/mindshare-analyzing-bsd-kernels-with-binary-ninja"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T16:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclosure of uninitialized memory is one of the common problems faced when copying data across trust boundaries. This can happen between the hypervisor and guest OS, kernel and user space, or across the network. The most common bug pattern noticed among these cases is where a structure or union is allocated in memory, and some of the fields or padding bytes are not initialized before copying it across trust boundaries. The question is, is it possible to perform variant analysis of such bugs?
The idea here is to perform a control flow insensitive analysis to track all memory store operations statically. Any memory region never written to is identified as uninitialized when the data from it is copied across trust boundaries.
Generalizing the code pattern for analysis
Consider the case of CV…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reno Robert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sentry: App monitoring for DevOps environments]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567765</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sentry-app-monitoring-for-devops-environments/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sentry is an app monitoring tool for DevOps environments  that is based on a stack of products such as Snuba, Kafka, and Nginx. It features proactive application monitoring to ensure that issues are addressed before they disrupt production environment.
Sentry: App monitoring for DevOps environments first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Borghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation for Active Directory, Microsoft 365, and Google Workspace with ManageEngine ADManager Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567752</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/automation-for-active-directory-microsoft-365-and-google-workspace-with-manageengine-admanager-plus/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T14:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how ManageEngine ADManager Plus allows easy management for on-premises Active Directory and cloud applications, such as Microsoft 365 and Google Workspace, as well as easy Active Directory automation and permission delegation.
Automation for Active Directory, Microsoft 365, and Google Workspace with ManageEngine ADManager Plus first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing a Hidden Virtual File System Capability That Emulates the Uroburos Rootkit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4153</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/developing-a-vfs-that-emulates-uroburos-rootkit/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years ago, I read the “Uroburos: The Snake Rootkit” [1] paper written by Artem Baranov and Deresz and was captivated by the hidden kernel-mode Virtual File System (VFS) functionality implemented within Uroburos. Later, I decided to learn Windows device driver programming and thought replicating this functionality within my own rootkit would be an […]
The post Developing a Hidden Virtual File System Capability That Emulates the Uroburos Rootkit appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: My Python Templates Version 0.0.8]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9524</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/20/update-my-python-templates-version-0-0-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update adds the option –trim to template process-text-files.py. python-templates_V0_0_8.zip (http)MD5: 6C845823BB8AC4DB42993B994E93AF66SHA256: 20EC1E6540DF31939686CA4B54C5312DF3724EB756B16BA724722C3196BDF93F]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get updates for Windows Server 2022 in WSUS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567734</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/get-updates-for-windows-server-2022-in-wsus/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T16:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past, Microsoft set up a separate product in WSUS for each version of Windows Server; this meant that admins could easily subscribe to the respective updates. This no longer applies to Windows Server 2022, which shares updates with Azure Stack HCI. The Azure editions of Server 2022 are not covered by them.
Get updates for Windows Server 2022 in WSUS first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Improving Security Through Infrastructure-as-Code]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=15695</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/19/a-guide-to-improving-security-through-infrastructure-as-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern organizations evolved and took the next step when they became digital. Organizations are using cloud and automation to build a dynamic infrastructure to support more frequent product release and faster innovation. This puts pressure on the IT department to do more and deliver faster. Automated cloud infrastructure also requires a new mindset, a change … Continue reading A Guide to Improving Security Through Infrastructure-as-Code →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viktor Gazdag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: strings.py Version 0.0.8]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9519</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/19/update-strings-py-version-0-0-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This version of my strings.py program adds option -N to select strings that end with a NUL character (C-strings). strings_V0_0_8.zip (http)MD5: 29015239E6385FFA63C2E33755C34CD9SHA256: 449AC9AA39A464D7C5883DED3FE9CB21A2E8E700F7763AD4199C25D37DCBD296]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gospray - Simple LDAP bind-based password spray tool]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/gospray-active-directory-ldap-password-spraying/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/gospray-active-directory-ldap-password-spraying/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T15:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a network and need credentials? Try password spraying the domain controller directly.
A few years ago, I wrote this password spray tool called gospray that was used succesfully in a couple of engagements since. It does an LDAP bind directly against the domain controller to validate credentials. This doesn’t require an SMB server (or other servers) as target. So, it’s pretty quiet and number of concurrent Go routines is configurable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tool: split-overlap.py]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9508</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/18/new-tool-split-overlap-py/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T12:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[split-overlap.py is a tool to split a binary file in parts of a given size. For example: split-overlap.py 1000 test.data When test.data is a binary file with size 2500 bytes, the above command will create 2 files of 1000 bytes and one file of 500 bytes. It’s also possible to split a file with some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stealing Access Tokens From Office Desktop Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://mrd0x.com/stealing-tokens-from-office-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://mrd0x.com/stealing-tokens-from-office-applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dumping tokens from Microsoft Office desktop applications' memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change Windows startup programs with Sysinternals Autoruns]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567711</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/change-windows-startup-programs-with-sysinternals-autoruns/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T15:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know there are more than 200 configuration locations for Windows startup programs? These are often used to launch malicious software without user interaction. In this post, you will learn how to discover and change Windows startup programs with Sysinternals autoruns.
Change Windows startup programs with Sysinternals Autoruns first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Unified HackerOne Scope Management with Burp Suite Support]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/application-security/introducing-unified-hackerone-scope-management-burp-suite-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/application-security/introducing-unified-hackerone-scope-management-burp-suite-support"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will start with the basics of defining scope and how ethical hackers and testers use it in their testing workflow. If you’re already famil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Matthews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender: Control updates for malware signatures using Group Policy or PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567697</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-defender-control-updates-for-malware-signatures-using-group-policy-or-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T14:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obtaining effective protection by virus scanners requires that they always use the latest definitions. Therefore, Microsoft Defender is not limited to getting its signature updates from the standard source for OS updates. Rather, you may specify several at once.
Microsoft Defender: Control updates for malware signatures using Group Policy or PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: virustotal-search.py Version 0.1.7]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9505</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/15/update-virustotal-search-py-version-0-1-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T07:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new option was added to limit the amount of requests: -l (–limitrequests). virustotal-search_V0_1_7.zip (http)MD5: BB6E9D480F7BCF0FD3F0CB8EED1B49FESHA256: AEFEB5761A5BBEE998FA20A68213316522C7554796F47EB8C7EB2A5DF1D4E73D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It pays to be Circomspect]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102699</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/09/15/it-pays-to-be-circomspect/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T04:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Fredrik Dahlgren, Staff Security Engineer In October 2019, a security researcher found a devastating vulnerability in Tornado.cash, a decentralized, non-custodial mixer on the Ethereum network. Tornado.cash uses zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs) to allow its users to privately deposit and withdraw funds. The proofs are supposed to guarantee that each withdrawal can be matched against a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common BitLocker errors]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567678</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/common-bitlocker-errors/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T20:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post, I explained how to enable BitLocker with PowerShell and how to unlock, suspend, resume, and disable BitLocker with PowerShell. You might face various errors while using BitLocker drive encryption. Since most errors are fixed using Group Policy settings, it is worth mentioning that all the BitLocker-related settings are available under the following Group Policy path:
Common BitLocker errors first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: An Inefficient Powerbank]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=8573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/14/quickpost-an-inefficient-powerbank/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tested a small powerbank that I have, and it’s very inefficient. It takes 10.07 Wh to charge: And it delivers 5.95 Wh when I discharge it (5V at 0.250 mA). So I only got 59% back of the energy I put in. This powerbank is quite old, it might have become so inefficient over […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New features in Windows 11 22H2 for professional users]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567642</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-features-in-windows-11-22h2-for-professional-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T19:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 22H2 is the first feature update for this operating system since its release last year. Accordingly, the focus is on removing some rough edges and improving the overall user experience. Nevertheless, the 22H2 release offers some innovations that are welcome for professional use.
New features in Windows 11 22H2 for professional users first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release – ScoutSuite 5.12.0]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17329</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/13/tool-release-scoutsuite-5-12-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T17:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the release of a new version of our open-source, multi-cloud auditing tool ScoutSuite (on Github)! This version includes multiple bug fixes, dependency updates and feature enhancements for AWS, Azure and GCP. It also adds and updates several rules for these three cloud providers, alongside improved finding templates and descriptions. The … Continue reading Tool Release – ScoutSuite 5.12.0 →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fernandogallegopinero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The September 2022 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:631e4c5d8dfb3f3abef70e2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/9/13/the-september-2022-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T17:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another Patch Tuesday is upon, and Adobe and Microsoft have released a bevy of new security updates. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security offerings.
Adobe Patches for September 2022
 For September, Adobe released seven patches addressing 63 in Adobe Experience Manager, Bridge, InDesign, Photoshop, InCopy, Animate, and Illustrator. A total of 42 of these bugs were reported by ZDI Sr Vulnerability Researcher Mat Powell. The update for InDesign is the largest patch this month, with eight Critical-rated and 10 Important-rated vulnerabilities receiving fixes. The most severe of these could lead to code execution if a specially crafted file is opened on an affected system. The patch for Photoshop fixes 10 CVEs, nine o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Framework Selection: How to Architect a Systematic Security Program – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4206</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/how-to-architect-a-systematic-security-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T13:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A need for public trust in information systems has driven continuous technological advances and new regulatory requirements, which have in turn made the global cyber threat landscape more complex and connected (see figure 1). As Boards of Directors, regulators, and the public become more aware of this interplay, organizations will need to evolve to address […]
The post Framework Selection: How to Architect a Systematic Security Program – Part 1 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: “Exploding Multimeter”]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9481</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/13/quickpost-exploding-multimeter/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made a mistake and destroyed my old multimeter. It’s a 30+ year old multimeter, and it had become very dirty because of all the dust it collected while I used it in a home renovation project, years ago. It was still functional, so I used it for years like that. But recently, after discovering […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing: CloudFox]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/introducing-cloudfox</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/introducing-cloudfox"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CloudFox, a command line tool created to help offensive security professionals find exploitable attack paths in cloud infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Art, Carlos Vendramini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synack Strengthens Integration to Microsoft Azure to Help Protect Hybrid Clouds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14646</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/synack-strengthens-integration-to-microsoft-azure/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T08:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synack Joins the Microsoft Intelligent Security Association (MISA) Synack has recently joined the Microsoft Intelligent Security Association (MISA) and integrated with Microsoft Sentinel. This means that Microsoft Sentinel users can now easily access Synack’s global team of security experts for on demand testing of cloud assets. MISA is an ecosystem of independent software vendors and […]
The post Synack Strengthens Integration to Microsoft Azure to Help Protect Hybrid Clouds appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Reasons to Attend Cyber Solutions Fest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/top-5-reasons-to-attend-cyber-solutions-fest-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/top-5-reasons-to-attend-cyber-solutions-fest-2022?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cyber security solutions are the draw, but there’s so much more to the event of which you’ll want to take advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Penumbra Labs Decaf377 Implementation and Poseidon Parameter Selection Review]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17322</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/12/public-report-penumbra-labs-decaf377-implementation-and-poseidon-parameter-selection-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T20:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the summer of 2022, Penumbra Labs, Inc. engaged NCC Group to conduct a cryptographic security assessment of two items: (i) the specification and two implementations of the decaf377 group, and (ii) a methodology and implementation of parameter generation for the Poseidon hash function. Decaf377 is a prime-order group obtained by applying the Decaf construction … Continue reading Public Report – Penumbra Labs Decaf377 Implementation and Poseidon Parameter Selection Review →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable BitLocker for Windows 10 and Windows 11 with Intune on multiple computers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567625</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-bitlocker-for-windows-10-and-windows-11-with-intune-on-multiple-computers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T16:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explains how you can enable BitLocker for Windows 10 and Windows 11 with Intune on multiple computers and devices.
Enable BitLocker for Windows 10 and Windows 11 with Intune on multiple computers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kostas Tzouvaras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WMI Internals Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/38e5dad016be</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/wmi-internals-part-3-38e5dad016be?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T14:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond COM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The seventh way to call a JavaScript function without parentheses]]></title>
        <id>the-seventh-way-to-call-a-javascript-function-without-parentheses</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/the-seventh-way-to-call-a-javascript-function-without-parentheses"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I thought I knew all the ways to call functions without parentheses: alert`1337` throw onerror=alert,1337 Function`x${'alert\x281337\x29'}x``` 'alert\x281337\x29'instanceof{[Symbol['hasInstance']]:eva]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maldoc Analysis Video – Rehearsed & Unrehearsed]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9476</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/10/maldoc-analysis-video-rehearsed-unrehearsed/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T21:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I record maldoc analysis videos, I have already analyzed the maldoc prior to recording, and I rehearse the recording. This time, I also recorded the unrehearsed analysis: when I take the first look at a maldoc I’ve not seen before. All in this video:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious Python Packages and Code Execution via pip download]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/python-package-manager-install-and-download-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/python-package-manager-install-and-download-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T23:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week I learned about a design flaw with pip download, which allows an adversary to run arbitrary code.
I assumed that running pip install means anything could happen, but pip download seems a bit surprising.
Both seem useful for red teaming though.
Background This post from Yehuda Gelb named Automatic Execution of Code Upon Package Download on Python Package Manager which the Security Now! podcast pointed me towards.
The post highlights that just running pip download can compromise your computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock, suspend, resume, and disable BitLocker with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567614</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/unlock-suspend-resume-and-disable-bitlocker-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T18:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post, I outlined how you can enable BitLocker with PowerShell and manage key protectors. Today, I will cover BitLocker management with PowerShell. In particular, I will describe how you can unlock, suspend, resume, and disable BitLocker with PowerShell.
Unlock, suspend, resume, and disable BitLocker with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for the Next Log4j in the Face of the Cyber Talent Gap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14628</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/preparing-for-the-next-log4j/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T16:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Log4j vulnerability emerged in December 2021, Synack and our clients’ security teams immediately sensed its urgency. The Synack Red Team began testing within hours of the initial discovery for our customer base.  Almost a year later, Log4j continues to show up in our pentesting results. Here are some quick stats from our findings: […]
The post Preparing for the Next Log4j in the Face of the Cyber Talent Gap appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Torio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Dolmen du roc de l’Arca]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9463</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/09/quickpost-dolmen-du-roc-de-larca/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While on holiday in Feilluns (France, Pyrénées-Orientales) in September 2021, I did search several dolmens. While the dolmen Caouno del Moro is easy to find (it is right next to a road, just follow the signs starting in the village), the nearby dolmen du roc de l’Arca is not so easy to find, as there […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different ways of gaining remote computer access]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567594</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/different-ways-of-gaining-remote-computer-access/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T18:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical support personnel, engineering teams, and security teams often need access to a remote computer involving both servers and workstations, using a variety of techniques. Three of the most common tools in a Windows environment are Microsoft Remote Desktop (RDP), VMware Console access, and Microsoft Management Console (MMC), but we can also use SMB shares, PowerShell remoting, and PsExec. This article will you give an overview of the most popular ways gaining remote computer access, along with some tips of what you can do if the remote connection fails.
Different ways of gaining remote computer access first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Greenhaus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riding the InfoRail to Exploit Ivanti Avalanche – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6318c49f3acd886cf432517c</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/9/7/riding-the-inforail-to-exploit-ivanti-avalanche-part-2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T16:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my first blog post covering bugs in Ivanti Avalanche, I covered how I reversed the Avalanche custom InfoRail protocol, which allowed me to communicate with multiple services deployed within this product. This allowed me to find multiple vulnerabilities in the popular mobile device management (MDM) tool. If you aren’t familiar with it, Ivanti Avalanche allows enterprises to manage mobile device and supply chain mobility solutions. That’s why the bugs discussed here could be used by threat actors to disrupt centrally managed Android, iOS and Windows devices. To refresh your memory, the following vulnerabilities were presented in the previous post:
 ·       Five XStream insecure deserialization issues, where deserialization was performed on the level of message handling.
·       A race con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving the Unredacter Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/unredacter-winner</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/unredacter-winner"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We asked you to take our Unredacter Challenge, in which we asked you to get creative and devise a way to solve our blurred secret message! Watch as Shawn A., one of our Unredacter Challenge winners, showcases his solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shawn Asmus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Detection: Tactical to Function]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/810c14798f63</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-detection-tactical-to-function-810c14798f63?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 6: What is a Procedure?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crimeware Trends | Ransomware Developers Turn to Intermittent Encryption to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=70617</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/crimeware-trends-ransomware-developers-turn-to-intermittent-encryption-to-evade-detection/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Partially encrypting victims' files improves ransomware speed and aids evasion. First seen in LockFile, the technique is now being widely adopted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEF CON 30. Hacking EFBs. Engine Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25546</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/def-con-30-hacking-efbs-engine-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T05:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At DEF CON 30 this year we demonstrated some vulnerabilities in electronic flight bags and the potential impact on flight safety. There’s plenty more detail of EFB security issues here. […]
DEF CON 30. Hacking EFBs. Engine Performance first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Lomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Sun Drying Biodegradable Waste]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9451</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/08/quickpost-sun-drying-biodegradable-waste/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As biodegradable waste contains a lot of water, I was wondering how much mass reduction I can achieve by exposing it to the sun (by evaporating some of the contained water). On a sunny day in March (Belgium), I weighed these fruit peels (I had just consumed the fruit): 66 grams Exposing it to sun […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mature ICS Security with Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/mature-ics-security-with-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/mature-ics-security-with-metrics?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason D. Christopher shares lessons learned through continually helping ICS security teams and their leaders better understand their security posture through measurement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release – Monkey365]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17236</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/07/tool-release-monkey365/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Juan Garrido Editor’s note: This tool was originally released at Black Hat USA 2022 (Arsenal) in August 2022, and was created by Juan Garrido (@silverhack). Monkey 365 is an Open Source security tool that can be used to easily conduct not only Microsoft 365, but also Azure subscriptions and Azure Active Directory security configuration reviews … Continue reading Tool Release – Monkey365 →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recover Active Directory domain controllers with nonauthoritative restore]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567566</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/recover-active-directory-domain-controllers-with-nonauthoritative-restore/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T15:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backing up domain controllers is a crucial part of any disaster recovery plan for organizations leveraging Active Directory on-premises. There are two types of restores: authoritative and nonauthoritative. Which one do you use where? We can perform both using Windows Server Backup. Let's look at this process with the nonauthoritative restore.
Recover Active Directory domain controllers with nonauthoritative restore first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get your SOCKS on with gTunnel]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4a70a9b82b24</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/get-your-socks-on-with-gtunnel-4a70a9b82b24?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T12:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tl;dr: Steps to setup a wicked fast SOCKS proxy with a tool called gTunnel written by hotnops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elliott Grey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerated Decision-making in Cybersecurity Requires Actionable Vulnerability Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14606</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/pentesting-for-government-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T11:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity officers tasked with finding and mitigating vulnerabilities in government organizations are already operating at capacity—and it’s not getting any easier. First, the constant push for fast paced, develop-test-deploy cycles continuously introduces risk of new vulnerabilities. Then there are changes in mission at the agency level, plus competing priorities to develop while simultaneously trying to […]
The post Accelerated Decision-making in Cybersecurity Requires Actionable Vulnerability Intelligence appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: hex-to-bin.py Version 0.0.6]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9448</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/07/update-hex-to-bin-py-version-0-0-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a small update: when non-hexadecimal characters are found, they are listed before an exception is raised. hex-to-bin_V0_0_6.zip (http)MD5: 9939263DCF538BBF5FC98DB2EC83F247SHA256: 94B2B23BCA5C000CA85EEE8AE1A16AEEDB77E72057111C8207A683BD4DDF4581]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started in Cybersecurity with a Non-Technical Background]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/getting-started-in-cybersecurity-with-a-non-technical-background</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/getting-started-in-cybersecurity-with-a-non-technical-background?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you considered a career as a cybersecurity professional, but weren’t really sure if you had the skillset needed for success? Many of the best security professionals bring non-technical backgrounds. In many cases having a non-technical background can actually be an advantage in the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICS Security Management VS. ICS Attack Targeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ics-security-management-vs-ics-attack-targeting</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ics-security-management-vs-ics-attack-targeting?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The increased targeting of control systems through impactful cyber-attacks has resulted in an attack surface more widely available and vulnerable to cyber-attacks. These attacks are created and deployed by adversaries-for-hire and rogue nation-states which have the means and motivation to disrupt operations and cause safety impacts. The good news - ICS/OT cyber security defense is totally doable - with an effective team and approach to risk management!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get More Out of the Synack Platform, Not Just Reports for Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14519</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/get-more-than-compliance/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T19:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform can help you check all your compliance boxes. Need a yearly pentest? We’ve got you covered. Need reports that compliance auditors and executives can easily understand? Find them in the Platform after testing is complete.  But when you use Synack’s capabilities only to satisfy compliance requirements, you’re missing out on the benefits […]
The post Get More Out of the Synack Platform, Not Just Reports for Compliance appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirsten Gibson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable BitLocker with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567551</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-bitlocker-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T18:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitLocker is a volume encryption technology that was first introduced in Windows Vista and Windows Server 2008. Like other Microsoft products, it also suffers from certain glitches, but many people around the globe rely on BitLocker Drive Encryption (BDE) to protect their data at rest.
Enable BitLocker with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharkbot is back in Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17151</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/06/sharkbot-is-back-in-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T18:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authored by Alberto Segura (main author) and Mike Stokkel (co-author) Editor’s note: This post was originally published on the Fox-IT blog. Introduction  After we discovered in February 2022 the SharkBotDropper in Google Play posing as a fake Android antivirus and cleaner, now we have detected a new version of this dropper active in the Google … Continue reading Sharkbot is back in Google Play  →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-34715: More Microsoft Windows NFS v4 Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:630fa3562ae588166e43b248</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/8/31/cve-2022-34715-more-microsoft-windows-nfs-v4-remote-code-execution"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T14:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Quintin Crist and Dusan Stevanovic of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in the Microsoft Windows operating system, originally discovered and reported by the researcher known as Arimura. The bug is the result of a dynamically allocated buffer created by an NFS function and is present only on Windows Server 2022. An unauthenticated attacker could exploit this bug to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. This is the third such NFS vulnerability in as many months. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2022-34715, with a few minimal modifications.
A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Windows Network File System.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safeguarding Memory in Higher-Level Programming Languages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4210</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/safeguarding-memory-in-higher-level-programming-languages/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T13:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider an application written in a higher-level language like Python, NodeJS, or C#. This application must handle sensitive data such as banking credentials, credit card data, health information, or network passwords. The application developers have already hardened the application against malicious users and are confident that it is not vulnerable to database injections, account takeovers, […]
The post Safeguarding Memory in Higher-Level Programming Languages appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to turn security research into profit: a CL.0 case study]]></title>
        <id>how-to-turn-security-research-into-profit</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/how-to-turn-security-research-into-profit"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever seen a promising hacking technique, only to try it out and struggle to find any vulnerable systems or non-duplicate findings? In this post, I'll take a concise look at the most effective]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: xor-kpa.py Version 0.0.6]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9440</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/06/update-xor-kpa-py-version-0-0-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an update for my tool to perform XOR known plaintext attacks: xor-kpa.py. The tool has been updated for Python 3, and 3 new plaintext have been added, all for Cobalt Strike configurations. cs-key is the header of the configuration entry for the public key. cs-key-dot is the header of the configuration entry for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up highly available file shares in Windows Server 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567533</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/setting-up-highly-available-file-shares-in-windows-server-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T16:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server 2022 has many robust enterprise features that allow IT admins to create resilient and highly available infrastructure services. With transparent failover, admins can take advantage of features found in SMB 3.0 and higher to provide continuous access to file shares.
Setting up highly available file shares in Windows Server 2022 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: translate.py Version 2.5.12]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9433</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/05/update-translate-py-version-2-5-12/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T15:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small update for my translate.py program. Python function Xor takes now 2 extra, optional arguments: hexadecimal: a boolean, by default False. When True, the key is provided as an hexadecimal string. rotation: an integer, by default 0 This is the number of bytes to rotate the key to the left. For example, when the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constant-Time Data Processing At a Secret Offset, Privacy and QUIC]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17161</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/05/constant-time-data-processing-at-a-secret-offset-privacy-and-quic/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction NCC Group Cryptography Services team assessed security aspects of several implementations of the QUIC protocol. During the course of their reviews, the team found a number of recurrent cryptography side channel findings of arguably negligible privacy risk to users, across these implementations. However, repetition in itself makes these findings somehow worth having a deeper … Continue reading Constant-Time Data Processing At a Secret Offset, Privacy and QUIC →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gérald Doussot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple IBM i (AS/400) hacking]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/?p=1586</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2022/09/05/simple-ibm-i-as-400-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T11:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you get the chance to take a look at the IT systems of financial institutions, telcos, and other big companies, where availability has been a key business concern for decades, you’ll find, that some critical operations run through some obscure systems, in many cases accessed via nostalgic green-on-black terminals, the intricacies of which only … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.70]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9428</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/04/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-70/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T15:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an update to plugin plugin_vba_dco.py, improving generalization and adding option -p. You can watch this maldoc analysis video to learn how to use the generalization feature of this plugin: oledump_V0_0_70.zip (http)MD5: D6EC4FD6B7BE60E01A98922BC06A1E8FSHA256: E9EE79501A08E896A601F1AFDDB6D3C05D9A2A1FD5899D44AC422DD79E4EF678]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe: JSX and JSXBIN files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8217</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/09/02/adobe-jsx-and-jsxbin-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T22:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote about older Adobe scripting before. I recently discovered that Adobe products support scripting using so-called ExtendScript language with code being stored either in a source-level JSX file, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: jpegdump.py Version 0.0.10]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9422</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/02/update-jpegdump-py-version-0-0-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T19:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update to jpegdump.py, my tool to analyze JPEG images, brings 2 small changes: Data between segments can be selected with suffix d. Like this: -s 10d This means: select the data between segments 9 and 10. And when option -E is used to add hash values, repeating hashes are marked with parentheses. jpegdump_V0_0_10.zip (http)MD5: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s Another Hole In Your SoC: Unisoc ROM Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16862</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/02/theres-another-hole-in-your-soc-unisoc-rom-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T18:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UNISOC (formerly Spreadtrum) is a rapidly growing semiconductor company that is nowadays focused on the Android entry-level smartphone market. While still a rare sight in the west, the company has nevertheless achieved impressive growth claiming 11% of the global smartphone application processor market, according to Counterpoint Research. Recently, it’s been making its way into some … Continue reading There’s Another Hole In Your SoC: Unisoc ROM Vulnerabilities →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilya Zhuravlev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up Remote Desktop Easy Print]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567514</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/setting-up-remote-desktop-easy-print/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T15:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One challenge with Remote Desktop printing is the issue of drivers. If users want to output documents on locally attached printers, for example, in work-from-home environments, organizations might have to deal with various printer models. Remote Desktop Easy Print offers a solution with a single driver.
Setting up Remote Desktop Easy Print first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2021-22 Synack Acropolis, Legends and Featured Envoy Mentors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14474</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/synack-red-team-awards-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T14:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trust. Honor. Excellence. These words are the foundational pillars for the Synack Acropolis and Synack Red Team. This past year, these core principles ushered in two new initiatives to address the rising cybersecurity talent gap and opportunity problems: Artemis Red Team and SRT Mentorship Program. The Artemis Red Team is focused on creating the world’s […]
The post Announcing the 2021-22 Synack Acropolis, Legends and Featured Envoy Mentors appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Rutan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When disclosure goes wrong. People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=24315</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/when-disclosure-goes-wrong-people/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T05:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My experience of vulnerability disclosure is that it is rarely as easy or simple as it could be. I had hoped that bug bounty programmes and vulnerability disclosure programmes (VDPs) […]
When disclosure goes wrong. People first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Standby Power Consumption Of My Bosch 18V Chargers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9410</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/02/quickpost-standby-power-consumption-of-my-bosch-18v-chargers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 2 Bosch 18V “power for all” chargers. A normal charger (AL 1830 CV) and a fast charger (AL 1880 CV). Measuring the power consumption of these 2 chargers in standby mode (plugged into a 230V outlet, but no battery connected) with a GPM-8310 powermeter, I obtained the following results: AL 1830 CV: 476,33 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Directory Services Restore Mode: DSRM password reset, recover Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567501</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/directory-services-restore-mode-dsrm-password-reset-recover-active-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T19:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever received the following error message when you tried to sign in on a domain controller? We can't sign you in with this credential because your domain isn't available. Scary, huh? With the help of Active Directory's Directory Services Restore Mode (DSRM), you can recover Active Directory by booting up in safe mode to restore a working configuration of your Active Directory. I hope you still know your DSRM password. If not, I show you how to reset the DSRSM password in this article.
Directory Services Restore Mode: DSRM password reset, recover Active Directory first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyPI Phishing Campaign | JuiceLedger Threat Actor Pivots From Fake Apps to Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=69799</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/pypi-phishing-campaign-juiceledger-threat-actor-pivots-from-fake-apps-to-supply-chain-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new threat actor is spreading infostealer malware through targeted attacks on developers and fraudulent cryptotrading applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitai Ben Shushan Ehrlich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in August]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9406</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/01/overview-of-content-published-in-august-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in August: Blog posts: Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.15 Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.16 YouTube videos: 1768.py’s Sanity Check Videoblog posts: 1768.py?s Sanity Check SANS ISC Diary entries: VBA Maldoc & UTF7 (APT-C-35) YARA 4.2.3 Released Sysinternals Updates: Sysmon v14.0 and ZoomIt v6.01 Dealing With False Positives when Scanning […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conference Talks – September/October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16685</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/01/conference-talks-september-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T15:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout September and October, members of NCC Group will be presenting their work at SANS CyberThreat, ResponderCon, BSides St John’s, ICMC, DevOps World, RootCon, and Hexacon. Ollie Whitehouse & Eric Shamper, “Enterprise IR:Live Free, live large” to be presented at Sans CyberThreat (September 12-13 2022) Balazs Bucsay, “Alternative way to detect mikatz” to be presented … Continue reading Conference Talks – September/October 2022 →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whitebox Security Assessments: Doing More with More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4151</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/benefits-of-a-whitebox-approach/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T13:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deciding on what type of security assessment to get, an organization should consider how much information they are willing to share. Several types of assessments exist, and the key differentiator is how much access an organization grants the testers from the beginning. The terms blackbox, greybox, and whitebox refer to whether a client chooses […]
The post Whitebox Security Assessments: Doing More with More appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Hackability to uncover a Chrome infoleak]]></title>
        <id>using-hackability-to-uncover-a-chrome-infoleak</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/using-hackability-to-uncover-a-chrome-infoleak"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been hacking browsers for over 15 years and one of the challenges I set myself was to find a SOP bypass or info leak in every major browser. Chrome was the last browser standing…until now. This p]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SETTLERS OF NETLINK: Exploiting a limited UAF in nf_tables (CVE-2022-32250)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16956</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/01/settlers-of-netlink-exploiting-a-limited-uaf-in-nf_tables-cve-2022-32250/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T08:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction netlink and nf_tables Overview Sets Expressions Set Expressions Stateful Expressions Expressions of Interest nft_lookup nft_dynset nft_connlimit Vulnerability Discovery CVE-2022-32250 Analysis Set Creation Set Deactivation Initial Limited UAF Write Exploitation Building an Initial Plan Offsets We Can Write at Into the UAF Chunk Hunting for Replacement Objects What Pointer Do We Want to Arbitrary Free? … Continue reading SETTLERS OF NETLINK: Exploiting a limited UAF in nf_tables (CVE-2022-32250) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Halbronn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Trust with a Vetted Team of Security Researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=14516</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/building-trust-with-a-vetted-team-of-security-researchers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T17:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s natural to wonder who makes up the Synack Red Team (SRT), our dedicated team of 1,500+ security researchers, and how they ended up finding vulnerabilities in our customers’ IT systems (with permission, of course).  Companies want assurance they’re not opening the front door to just anybody. Much like you wouldn’t want a stranger in […]
The post Building Trust with a Vetted Team of Security Researchers appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirsten Gibson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure Abuse Research — Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3e5bbe7a20c0</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/automating-azure-abuse-research-part-2-3e5bbe7a20c0?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, we looked at how to port functionality from the Azure GUI to PowerShell. Specifically, we looked at how to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing FreeBSD Kernel Modules in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16915</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/31/writing-freebsd-kernel-modules-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At present all major operating system kernels are written in C/C++, languages which provide no or minimal assistance in avoiding common security problems. Modern languages such as Rust provide better security guarantees by default and prevent many of the common classes of memory safety security bugs. In this post we will take a brief look … Continue reading Writing FreeBSD Kernel Modules in Rust →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find AD accounts with ChangePasswordAtLogon, set and enforce password change with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567476</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-ad-accounts-with-changepasswordatlogon-set-and-enforce-password-change-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Admins can prompt users to change their password at their next login. While it is easy to see the status of the corresponding attribute in AD Users and Computers, the procedure with PowerShell is a bit tricky. On the other hand, enforcing a password change with PowerShell is quite simple.
Find AD accounts with ChangePasswordAtLogon, set and enforce password change with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite price increases]]></title>
        <id>burp-suite-price-increases</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/burp-suite-price-increases"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T07:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are increasing prices for Burp Suite Professional and Burp Suite Enterprise Edition, due to a significant increase in costs caused by global inflation. The price of an annual Burp Suite Professiona]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, No Case Studies—But . . .]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e7cf012af19807518fba2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/sorry-no-case-study"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend of the site recently suggested that we create a current-issue case 
study using our updated risk discovery approach. “It’s a great idea,” we 
replied and immediately started kicking around ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pointillism of Daily Events]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2c8f009baa12346d3711f</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/pointillism-daily-events"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Baker’s book Human Smoke brilliantly illustrates a unique approach 
to historical narrative. It also underscores the need to remember that 
every artist paints with intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ready for What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2aa91391dcb70804f9850</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/getting-ready-whats-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new age of giant monsters, advanced awareness of classical 
surprise—that one big tipping moment—no longer suffices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Your ‘Free Cells’ Mindfully]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62deb6110fd7f314e5696ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/manage-free-cells"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accommodate but don’t fight the limitations you can’t control, recognize 
those you can influence and leverage, and don't imagine you have more free 
cells than you actually do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popski’s Planning]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d81b5affdc983dd1f616f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/popskis-planning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British officer Vladimir Peniakoff’s approach to planning might sound a bit 
unorthodox at first, but it aligns nicely with Patton’s view of 
intelligence and speaks to an enduring need to understand front-line 
conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a New Game Board]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d5b6db0343fb487527fc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/time-for-a-new-game-board"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need a more flexible game board where players can explore hypergame 
strategies—in other words, a game board where the strategist can play the 
hero for a change. We’ve built it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survivors Exceeded the Minimum]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62cf11283f1bdb1191fcdf9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/survivors-exceeded-minimum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T18:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every surprise is a cunning thunderbolt. Some surprises creep up 
slowly, rusting away former resilience until a simple nudge reveals the 
rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>