<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-07-09T00:39:02.324Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, ChatGPT Is Under Maintenance: Persistent Denial of Service through Prompt Injection and Memory Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-persistent-denial-of-service/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-persistent-denial-of-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T21:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you visit a website with ChatGPT, and suddenly, it stops working entirely!
In this post we show how an attacker can use prompt injection to cause a persistent denial of service that lasts across chat sessions for a user.
Hacking Memories Previously we discussed how ChatGPT is vulnerable to automatic tool invocation of the memory tool. This can be used by an attacker during prompt injection to ingest malicious or fake memories into your ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam Agent for Windows: backup job failed with VSS error 0x80042306]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584637</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/veeam-agent-for-windows-backup-job-failed-with-vss-error-0x80042306/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam Agent for Windows is a backup software for workstations and servers, and it is also available in a free edition. Like most backup programs, it creates snapshots using the Volume Shadow Copy Service (VSS), which it then backs up. However, this process can fail for various reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pen testing cruise ships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29219</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/pen-testing-cruise-ships/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New build ships contracted for build from 1st July 2024 must comply with IACS UR E26 & 27. What does this mean for assessing the cyber security of a cruise […]
Pen testing cruise ships first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Tierney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Threat Exposure Management for Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2814</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/continuous-threat-exposure-management-for-google-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T19:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 9th, 2020, an independent security firm discovered a trove of personal health information belonging to Pfizer patients on the public internet. The breach exposed unencrypted conversations between patients and providers of four different Pfizer products, including full names, home addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, and medical status details. The entry point of this […]
The post Continuous Threat Exposure Management for Google Cloud appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a Frida-based VBS API monitor, Take two]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9292</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/07/07/writing-a-frida-based-vbs-api-monitor-take-two/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T18:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post I introduced a simple VBS API Monitor developed using Frida framework. Today I did some more code analysis of vbscript.dll and I realized that in my previous post I made a naive assumption that arguments are … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a Frida-based VBS API monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9282</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/07/07/writing-a-frida-based-vbs-api-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T00:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love experimenting with Frida and I have presented a few different API Monitoring prototypes based on this framework a few times before… Today I will demonstrate how to write a quick & dirty VBS/VBScript (Visual Basic Script) API Monitor. … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: hash.py Version 0.0.13]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10521</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/07/07/update-hash-py-version-0-0-13/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a bugfix release for @files. hash_V0_0_13.zip (http)MD5: 43419BBB95FC1321EC6098AE369DEC26SHA256: 88BD3A7B71BB2C8579F49E76E8069E7A5A4B23DCF1DB1716E5E2C9F78BFF6D5B]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attack Surface Management: A Free Enablement Technology for Effective Continuous Threat Exposure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2806</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/attack-surface-management-free-enablement-technology-continuous-threat-exposure-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T19:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As digital landscapes continue to evolve daily, organizations are increasingly aware and focused on their attack surfaces to identify and mitigate potential risks. However, a troubling trend has emerged: companies are often compelled to pay bug hunters for exploiting vulnerabilities based on surface-level discoveries. At Praetorian, we challenge this norm by offering a free version […]
The post Attack Surface Management: A Free Enablement Technology for Effective Continuous Threat Exposure Management appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in June]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10519</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/07/06/overview-of-content-published-in-june-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T08:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in June: Blog posts: Update: file-magic.py Version 0.0.8 Update: hash.py Version 0.0.12 Update: myjson-filter.py version 0.0.6 Update: strings.py Version 0.0.9 Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.30 Update: count.py Version 0.3.2 Update: simple_listener.py Version 0.1.5 Update: what-is-new.py Version 0.0.4 Update: FileScanner Version 0.0.0.9 Update: pdf-parser.py Version 0.7.9 Update: base64dump.py version […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List groups in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584487</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/list-groups-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, I explained how to create and manage groups in Linux. Today, I will explore the various ways to list groups in Linux. The /etc/group and /etc/passwd files offer insights into user accounts and their primary groups. Commands like groups, id, compgen, and getent group are valuable tools for querying group information for specific users, listing all groups, and including network services in the group listings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing the Ask Astro LLM Q&A app]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107755</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/07/05/auditing-the-ask-astro-llm-qa-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we present the second of our open-source AI security audits: a look at security issues we found in an open-source retrieval augmented generation (RAG) application that could lead to chatbot output poisoning, inaccurate document ingestion, and potential denial of service. This audit follows up on our previous work that identified 11 security vulnerabilities in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Let’s Encrypt certificates on Windows with Certbot and export as PFX]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584575</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-lets-encrypt-certificates-on-windows-with-certbot-and-export-as-pfx/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T15:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Encrypt offers free certificates that are only valid for 90 days. Because manually renewing them every three months would be cumbersome, several solutions have been developed to automate this process. A popular software is Certbot, which is no longer supported on Windows but can be installed under WSL2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Microsoft Dev Home?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584532</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/what-is-microsoft-dev-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T16:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Dev Home is a new application that helps DevOps engineers monitor and manage their projects, set up test and development environments, and connect to cloud accounts such as GitHub or Azure. The platform features a customizable dashboard to oversee workflows, development tasks, and system performance. The Machine configuration tool lets you set up new environments or projects. The Dev Home extensions allow for personalized widgets and shared custom extensions. With Dev Drive, you can store project files and Git repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Security Review Methodology for Traeger Grill Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/methodology-for-traeger-grill-hack</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/methodology-for-traeger-grill-hack"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T22:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read for an in-depth analysis of the Traeger Grill hack, uncovering the vulnerabilities that could compromise your grill's security and how they were addressed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Cerne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traeger Grill D2 Wi-Fi Controller, Version 2.02.04]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/traeger-wifi-controller-advisory</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/traeger-wifi-controller-advisory"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T22:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover critical vulnerabilities in the Traeger Grill D2 Wi-Fi Controller that could impact your grill's security. Read our advisory to learn about the issues identified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Cerne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets Exposed: The Rise of GitHub as an Attack Vector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2730</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/secrets-exposed-the-rise-of-github-as-an-attack-vector/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T16:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at Chariot’s Capability to Protect On June 6, 2024, an anonymous user posted nearly 300 GB of stolen source code to 4chan. Per the user, the leak contained “basically all source code belonging to The New York Times”. The NYT later confirmed the leak and said the root case was an exposed GitHub […]
The post Secrets Exposed: The Rise of GitHub as an Attack Vector appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like Shooting Phish in a Barrel]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/926c1905bb4b</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/like-shooting-phish-in-a-barrel-926c1905bb4b?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T15:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing Link Crawlers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create and remove Linux group, add user, switch primary group]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584447</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-and-remove-linux-group-add-user-switch-primary-group/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T14:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux groups are essential for managing file permissions and user access to system resources. This guide covers how to create a Linux group using the groupadd command and delete a group with groupdel. You will also learn how to add users to groups using the usermod command and remove them with gpasswd. Additionally, the guide explains how to switch a user's primary group with the newgrp command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A hacking hat-trick: previewing three PortSwigger Research publications coming to DEF CON &amp; Black Hat USA]]></title>
        <id>a-hacking-hat-trick-previewing-three-portswigger-research-publications-coming-to-def-con-amp-black-hat-usa</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/a-hacking-hat-trick-previewing-three-portswigger-research-publications-coming-to-def-con-amp-black-hat-usa"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're delighted to announce three major research releases from PortSwigger Research will be published at both Black Hat USA and DEF CON 32. In this post, we'll offer a quick teaser of each talk, info]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of Passwords? Embrace the Future with Passkeys.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=17890</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/07/02/the-end-of-passwords-embrace-the-future-with-passkeys/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, unexpectedly, my personal Google account suggested using Passkeys for login. This is amazing, as Passkeys is the game-changer for cyber security because it could imply the solution to one of the biggest headaches in cyber security: password use. The problem with passwords. For decades, we have struggled with passwords as an authentication tool. They … Continue reading The End of Passwords? Embrace the Future with Passkeys. →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandre Baratin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RCE vulnerability in OpenSSH – RegreSSHion (CVE-2024-6387)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29212</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/rce-vulnerability-in-openssh-regresshion-cve-2024-6387/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The Qualys Threat Research Unit has found a high-severity vulnerability, filed under CVE-2024-6387, affects OpenSSH (Open Secure Shell), a networking utility often used for remote server management and secure […]
RCE vulnerability in OpenSSH – RegreSSHion (CVE-2024-6387) first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eime Adomaviciute</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-6387: RegreSSHion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2744</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/cve-2024-6387-regresshion/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T02:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, the Qualys Threat Research Unit (TRU) announced an unauthenticated remote code execution in OpenSSH’s sshd server. Cataloged as CVE-2024-6387, the vulnerability is a regression of CVE-2006-5051, hence its nickname: “RegreSSHion”. In addition to versions impacted by CVE-2006-5051, RegreSSHion affects OpenSSH 8.5p1 – 9.7p1. TRU determined the most recent version of OpenSSH (9.8p1) was not […]
The post CVE-2024-6387: RegreSSHion appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Client-Side Path Traversal to Perform Cross-Site Request Forgery - Introducing CSPT2CSRF]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/07/02/cspt2csrf.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/07/02/cspt2csrf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To provide users with a safer browsing experience, the IETF proposal named “Incrementally Better Cookies” set in motion a few important changes to address Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) and other client-side issues. Soon after, Chrome and other major browsers implemented the recommended changes and introduced the SameSite attribute. SameSite helps mitigate CSRF, but does that mean CSRF is dead?
While auditing major web applications, we realized that Client Side Path-Traversal (CSPT) can be actually leveraged to resuscitate CSRF for the joy of all pentesters.
This blog post is a brief introduction to my research. The detailed findings, methodologies, and in-depth analysis are available in the whitepaper.
This research introduces the basics of Client-Side Path Traversal, presenting source…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audit Group Policy changes in the event log using XML queries and PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584351</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/audit-group-policy-changes-in-the-event-log-using-xml-queries-and-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T17:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custom views in the Event Viewer allow you to filter the metadata of log entries based on various criteria. However, these filters do not assess the content of the log entry messages. To evaluate the log messages, you can extend filters using an XPath query. The examples below demonstrate how to audit Group Policy changes with XML queries, which you can further process with PowerShell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution on the Logsign Unified SecOps Platform]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6682dc0f1ce7c849eb57d3d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/1/getting-unauthenticated-remote-code-execution-on-the-logsign-unified-secops-platform"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T16:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, the Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) acquired several vulnerabilities in the Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. These were all reported to the ZDI by Mehmet INCE (@mdisec) from PRODAFT.com. According to Logsign’s website:
Logsign provides comprehensive visibility and control of your data lake by allowing security analysts to collect and store unlimited data, investigate and detect threats, and respond automatically.
Logsign offers a single, unified whole security operation platform to alleviate the challenges associated with deploying multiple cybersecurity tools while reducing the costs and complexities that come with managing them individually.
Logsign runs as a Python-based web server. Users have the ability to interact with the web server through a variety of APIs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yulin Sung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum is unimportant to post-quantum]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107734</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/07/01/quantum-is-unimportant-to-post-quantum/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Opal Wright You might be hearing a lot about post-quantum (PQ) cryptography lately, and it’s easy to wonder why it’s such a big deal when nobody has actually seen a quantum computer. But even if a quantum computer is never built, new PQ standards are safer, more resilient, and more flexible than their classical […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CapraTube Remix | Transparent Tribe’s Android Spyware Targeting Gamers, Weapons Enthusiasts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=100336</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/capratube-remix-transparent-tribes-android-spyware-targeting-gamers-weapons-enthusiasts/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T12:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SentinelLabs has identified four new CapraRAT APKs associated with suspected Pakistan state-aligned actor Transparent Tribe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NIS2 Alone Can’t Solve Information Sharing Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/why-nis2-alone-can-t-solve-information-sharing-issues</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/why-nis2-alone-can-t-solve-information-sharing-issues?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the new NIS2 Directive and information sharing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ring Around The Regex: Lessons learned from fuzzing regex libraries (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://secret.club/2024/06/30/ring-around-the-regex-1.html</id>
        <link href="https://secret.club/2024/06/30/ring-around-the-regex-1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, if you’re reading this, you probably know what fuzzing is. As an incredibly reductive summary: fuzzing is an automated, random testing process which tries to explore the state space (e.g., different interpretations of the input or behaviour) of a program under test (PUT; sometimes also SUT, DUT, etc.). Fuzzing is often celebrated as one of the most effective ways to find bugs in programs due to its inherently random nature, which defies human expectation or bias1. The strategy has found countless security-critical bugs (think tens or hundreds of thousands) over its 30-odd-years of existence, and yet faces regular suspicion from industry and academia alike. Mostly. Fuzzers can be overfit to certain applications, intentionally or not. &#8617;]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>secret club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An AWS Administrator Identity Crisis: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/919e6171ec0a</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/an-aws-administrator-identity-crisis-part-1-919e6171ec0a?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T16:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BLUF: Every attack path needs a destination. This is a formalized way of describing destinations in AWS. In cloud providers where we only…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hotnops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing HackerOne's Hai API: Revolutionize Your Workflow Automation with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/hai-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/hai-api"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T16:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Hai API: designed specifically for customers seeking efficient interaction and automation capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disable Copilot for Microsoft 365]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584400</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/disable-copilot-for-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T13:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 Copilot offers AI-powered capabilities integrated into popular Office applications such as Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Teams. This blog post explores what Copilot for Microsoft 365 is, its integration into Office apps, and reasons to consider disabling it. I'll also delve into specific services like Copilot Studio, Graph Connectors, and Intelligent Search, as well as provide guidance on disabling Copilot for specific apps or entirely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glastonbury ticket hijack vulnerability fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29197</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/glastonbury-ticket-hijack-vulnerability-fixed/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T12:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Glastonbury ticket website was vulnerable to a relatively simple attack that that allowed ticket theft and data leakage. What’s the issue? An attacker could scrape collaborative ticket buying websites […]
Glastonbury ticket hijack vulnerability fixed first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Cyber Threat Intelligence: Insights from Recent Nobelium Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-importance-of-cyber-threat-intelligence-insights-from-recent-nobelium-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-importance-of-cyber-threat-intelligence-insights-from-recent-nobelium-attacks?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog underscoring the importance of cyber threat intelligence in reference to the recent Nobelium attacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audit and disable NTLMv1]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584169</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/audit-and-disable-ntlmv1/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many legacy protocols, NTLM (NT LAN Manager) is now deemed insecure, yet disabling it entirely would likely lead to considerable disruptions. Nonetheless, disabling NTLM 1.0 significantly improves security. However, it is crucial to verify any dependencies beforehand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Registry Adventure #3: Learning resources]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/the-windows-registry-adventure-3.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/the-windows-registry-adventure-3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=4mNYFHt_IKFsPe52toizHz0e5qzIIUg9OvSRGeMDk3I);

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-0>li:before {
        content: "\0025cf   "
    }

    ul.lst-kix_pv42b0usiw40-7 {
        list-style-type: none
    }

    ul.lst-kix_pv42b0usiw40-8 {
        list-style-type: none
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-5>li:before {
        content: "\0025a0   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-4>li:before {
        content: "\0025cb   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-2>li:before {
        content: "\0025a0   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-3>li:before {
        content: "\0025cf   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-1>li:before {
        content: "\0025cb   "
    }

    ol.lst-kix_hmg5xw3mb42j-2.start {
        counter-reset: lst-ctn-kix_hmg5xw3mb42j-2 0
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Ecommerce Vulnerabilities: Reflected XSS]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/reflected-xss-ecommerce</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/reflected-xss-ecommerce"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an example from Shopify, learn about the impact of Reflected XSS vulnerabilities in e-commerce and how to remediate them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haoxi Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investing to deliver more]]></title>
        <id>investing-to-deliver-more</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/investing-to-deliver-more"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T11:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce a strategic investment from Brighton Park Capital (BPC), a leading growth equity firm with a track record of scaling innovative technology companies. This partnership will e]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Neurodiversity in Cybersecurity Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-neurodiversity-in-cybersecurity-summit</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-neurodiversity-in-cybersecurity-summit?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Neurodiversity in Cybersecurity Summit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Desktop 4.31: Air-Gapped Containers, Docker Build Cloud, GitHub Actions support, ARM support]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584271</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/docker-desktop-431-air-gapped-containers-docker-build-cloud-github-actions-support-arm-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T20:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Desktop 4.31 introduces a suite of powerful features aimed at enhancing security, performance, and usability. Key highlights include Air-Gapped Containers, allowing administrators to restrict container network access for heightened security. The release also integrates Docker Build Cloud, accelerating build processes by leveraging cloud infrastructure. Additionally, enhanced CI visibility with GitHub Actions and support for Windows on ARM (beta) expand development capabilities, while the new Compose File Viewer (beta) simplifies working with Compose files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Milestone of Excellence: Praetorian Security Inc. Named to Inc.’s Best Workplaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5771</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/milestone-excellence-named-incs-best-workplaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T18:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This recognition is more than just a badge of honor; it is a testament to what makes Praetorian an exceptional place to work. The dedication exhibited daily by each team member truly sets us apart, highlighting the organic culture shaped by our people and the unwavering support from everyone at our company. Why This Matters […]
The post A Milestone of Excellence: Praetorian Security Inc. Named to Inc.’s Best Workplaces appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentesting for NIST 800-53, FISMA, and FedRAMP]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-800-53-fisma-fedramp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-800-53-fisma-fedramp"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to address NIST 800-53, FISMA, and FedRAMP compliance with pentesting and the ethical hacker community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne Pentest Delivery Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChamelGang & Friends | Cyberespionage Groups Attacking Critical Infrastructure with Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=100293</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/chamelgang-attacking-critical-infrastructure-with-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors in the cyberespionage ecosystem are using ransomware for financial gain, disruption, distraction, misattribution, and the removal of evidence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski &amp; Julian-Ferdinand Vögele (Recorded Future)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2021-4440: A Linux CNA Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/cve-2021-4440_linux_cna_case_study.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/cve-2021-4440_linux_cna_case_study.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog serves as a case study into how the newly-formed Linux CNA (CVE Numbering Authority) has affected Linux kernel vulnerability management, through the mishandling of a vulnerability we reported this year in the upstream 5.10 LTS kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2021-4440: A Linux CNA Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/cve-2021-4440_linux_cna_case_study.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/cve-2021-4440_linux_cna_case_study.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog serves as a case study into how the newly-formed Linux CNA (CVE Numbering Authority) has affected Linux kernel vulnerability management, through the mishandling of a vulnerability we reported this year in the upstream 5.10 LTS kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create, configure, and delete system restore points with PowerShell, vssadmin.exe, and System Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584294</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-configure-and-delete-system-restore-points-with-powershell-vssadminexe-and-system-properties/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T19:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System restore points allow users to roll back Windows to an earlier state if problems arise. These points capture important system files, the registry, and drivers. In addition to using the System Properties applet, you can manage system restore points with PowerShell and vssadmin.exe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pride Month: Stories from Our LGBTQ+ Employees]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/pride-month-stories-our-lgbtq-employees</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/pride-month-stories-our-lgbtq-employees"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T16:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find XSS]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ethical-hacker/how-to-find-xss</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ethical-hacker/how-to-find-xss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researcher Haoxi Tan breaks down the best practices and tools for finding the different types of XSS vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haoxi Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Will Make you Phishers of Men]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/608268c4c669</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/i-will-make-you-phishers-of-men-608268c4c669?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T14:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Convincing Targets to Click Your Links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bug Bounty Reports Explained: The secret to finding many Criticals]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.ajxchapman.com/posts/2024/06/25/bbre.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.ajxchapman.com/posts/2024/06/25/bbre.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chapman's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPC Fuzzing with Snapshots]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/attack-and-defense/?p=268</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/attack-and-defense/2024/06/24/ipc-fuzzing-with-snapshots/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Process separation remains one of the most important parts of the Firefox security model and securing our IPC (Inter-Process Communication) interfaces is crucial to keep privileges in the different processes … Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Holler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traefik Proxy v3 review: WASM support, OpenTelemetry, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584229</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/traefik-review-proxy-v3-wasm-support-opentelemetry-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traefik Proxy 3, a container reverse proxy and load balancer, has been officially released. This article highlights the main new features, including WASM support, OpenTelemetry, Kubernetes Gateway API support, HTTP/3, SPIFFE, Tailscale, and gRPC-Web, which enhance performance, security, and observability for modern cloud-native applications. For those unfamiliar with Traefik, please take a look at this Traefik beginner's guide to help you get started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disarming Fiat-Shamir footguns]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107656</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/24/disarming-fiat-shamir-footguns/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Opal Wright The Fiat-Shamir transform is an important building block in zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs) and multi-party computation (MPC). It allows zero-knowledge proofs based on interactive protocols to be made non-interactive. Essentially, it turns conversations into documents. This ability is at the core of powerful technologies like SNARKs and STARKs. Useful stuff! But the Fiat-Shamir […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prototype Pollution: A Deep-Dive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=24772</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/web-application-pentesting/ultimate-guide-to-prototype-pollution/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T07:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Prototype Pollution – what it is, why it exists, and real examples of how it can be exploited.
The post Prototype Pollution: A Deep-Dive appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Jepson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Uncertainty to Strategy: A New Course to Master Cybersecurity Risk and Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/from-uncertainty-to-strategy-a-new-course-to-master-cybersecurity-risk-and-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/from-uncertainty-to-strategy-a-new-course-to-master-cybersecurity-risk-and-compliance?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the new SANS LDR519: Risk Management and Compliance course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating International Women in Engineering Day]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/celebrating-international-women-engineering-day</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/celebrating-international-women-engineering-day"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T16:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>debbie@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzer Development 4: Snapshots, Code-Coverage, and Fuzzing]]></title>
        <id>https://h0mbre.github.io/Lucid_Snapshots_Coverage/</id>
        <link href="https://h0mbre.github.io/Lucid_Snapshots_Coverage/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Human Machine Interface</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enter Sandbox 28: Automated access primitives extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8632</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/06/22/enter-sandbox-28-automated-access-primitives-extraction/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T23:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post about TI I hinted that malware sample sandboxing (f.ex. extracting configs, credentials, domains, emails, (S)FTP accounts) – identifying TTPs is a great TI data source… I must admit that there is so much juice to absorb … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deconstructing Logon Session Enumeration]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/0426b8452ef5</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/deconstructing-logon-session-enumeration-0426b8452ef5?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T18:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we define and create test cases for our purple team runbooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garrett White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Docker on Ubuntu 24.04]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584034</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-docker-on-ubuntu-2404/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T14:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Docker on Ubuntu 24.04 is straightforward with the right instructions. This post will walk you through removing any previous Docker versions, updating your system, installing the necessary prerequisites, and setting up the official Docker repository. Finally, you'll install Docker Engine, verify its service, add your user to the Docker group, and test the installation to ensure everything is set up correctly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EuroLLVM 2024 trip report]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107635</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/21/eurollvm-2024-trip-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Marek Surovič and Henrich Lauko EuroLLVM is a developer meeting focused on projects under the LLVM Foundation umbrella that live in the LLVM GitHub monorepo, like Clang and—more recently, thanks to machine learning research—the MLIR framework. Trail of Bits, which has a history in compiler engineering and all things LLVM, sent a bunch of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dodgy disks. My 32TB SSD Adventure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29161</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/dodgy-disks-my-32tb-ssd-adventure/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR “Hard drive” had reflashed firmware to make it look larger Buyer beware: Cheap storage may not be the value you think it is Background Earlier this year I found […]
Dodgy disks. My 32TB SSD Adventure first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Barradell-Johns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sales Development Representatives Win as a Team]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/sdr-win-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/sdr-win-team"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Naptime: Evaluating Offensive Security Capabilities of Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/project-naptime.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/project-naptime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=DFQxm4rd7fRHgM9OTejWVT5Vho6BE7M80rHXEVKqXWckOnM5xqt2DUw2f5lNcrroidEvLLi3H0BPvcL7ypcd6c76ZZ8PqJ7WOKqynLI9-xo);.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-8>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}ol.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}li.li-bullet-0:before{margin-left:-18pt;white-space:nowrap;display:inline-block;min-width:18pt}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}ol.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0 0}ul.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-7{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Privileged Identity Management Affects Conditional Access Policies]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/03371d06cfe3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/how-privileged-identity-management-affects-conditional-access-policies-03371d06cfe3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hope Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulseway 9.6: Enhanced remote control, advanced reporting, improved patch management, and more for comprehensive system monitoring and management]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584151</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/pulseway-96-enhanced-remote-control-advanced-reporting-improved-patch-management-and-more-for-comprehensive-system-monitoring-and-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pulseway is a cloud-based remote monitoring and management tool that enables administrators to conveniently oversee and manage systems from anywhere. Version 9.6 introduces various new features, including improved remote control performance, advanced custom reporting, bulk action capabilities, patch history tracking, new SNMP and service monitoring, enhanced patch management, improved automation, and better integration with Autotask.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HUMINT in a cyber world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29150</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/humint-in-a-cyber-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T05:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR HUMINT / Human Intelligence is gathered from a person in the location in question. It’s the sort of information we think of in the context of spying. A modern […]
HUMINT in a cyber world first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Gee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Single Sign-On Or Single Point of Failure?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/06/20/compromised-idp.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/06/20/compromised-idp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one can argue with the convenience that single sign-on (SSO) brings to users or the security and efficiency gains organizations reap from the lower administrative overhead. Gone are the days of individually managing multiple user accounts across numerous services. That said, have we just put all our eggs in one proverbial basket with regards to our SSO implementations? The results of our latest research remind us of why the saying cautions against doing this.
Threat modeling an IdP compromise
To help organizations assess their exposure in the event of an IdP compromise, we’re publishing a whitepaper that walks through these potential impacts. It examines how they differ depending on the privileges involved with the compromise. This includes the surprising impacts that even an unprivileg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Job management in Kubernetes 1.30: Understanding the new success/completion policies for indexed jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584106</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/job-management-in-kubernetes-130-understanding-the-new-successcompletion-policies-for-indexed-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Kubernetes 1.30, notable improvements have been made to job management, especially for indexed jobs. The newly introduced success/completion policies, succeededIndexes and succeededCount, offer more precise control over job success criteria. These policies provide enhanced flexibility and robustness, ensuring that specific job indexes or a sufficient number must succeed before the job is considered complete.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mercy Bassey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community-driven PTaaS vs. Traditional Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/ptaas-vs-traditional-pentest</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/ptaas-vs-traditional-pentest"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's the difference between traditional pentesting and community-driven pentest as a service (PTaaS)?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feeding the Phishes]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/276c3579bba7</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/feeding-the-phishes-276c3579bba7?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing Phishing Link Filters]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Themes from Real World Crypto 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107622</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/18/themes-from-real-world-crypto-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In March, Trail of Bits engineers traveled to the vibrant (and only slightly chilly) city of Toronto to attend Real World Crypto 2024, a three-day event that hosted hundreds of brilliant minds in the field of cryptography. We also attended three associated events: the Real World Post-Quantum Cryptography (RWPQC) workshop, the Fully Homomorphic Encryption (FHE) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable FIDO passkey authentication for IAM users in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1583997</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-fido-passkey-authentication-for-iam-users-in-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has recently introduced support for FIDO2 passkeys. Both root and IAM users can now utilize passkeys linked to a FIDO security key device or an authenticator. Beginning in July 2024, MFA is mandatory for root users. In this article, I will explain how to set up the IAM policy and show how to log into AWS using the fingerprint sensor on a Mac. However, the procedure described here should also work for other authenticators on Windows and Linux. Regrettably, the configuration procedure is complicated, and Amazon's passkeys guide is flawed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: emldump.py Version 0.0.14]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10513</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/06/18/update-emldump-py-version-0-0-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T11:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This small update for emldump adds support for UTF8 files that start with a BOM. emldump_V0_0_14.zip (http)MD5: 6DBA97A55A9BE0D94131F1F381868236SHA256: 99E1254011C6738FC44E559B4A29A8D40C79822A946F853D12EF23E035CEE97B]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instructor Spotlight: Sean Thomas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/instructor-spotlight-sean-thomas</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/instructor-spotlight-sean-thomas?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog spotlighting the SANS instructor, Sean Thomas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIS2 Compliance for OT: Strategic Implementation of ICS Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/nis2-compliance-for-ot-strategic-implementation-of-ics-controls</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/nis2-compliance-for-ot-strategic-implementation-of-ics-controls?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about NIS2 Compliance for operational technology and industrial control systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chariot Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5761</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/chariot-continuous-threat-exposure-management-ctem-updates/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T21:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our engineering team has been hard at work, reworking our flagship platform to enhance the Chariot platform to remain the most comprehensive and powerful CTEM platform on the market. So what’s new? Here are several new features recently added to Chariot: 1. Unmanaged Platform Chariot, Praetorian’s Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) solution, is now available […]
The post Chariot Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) Updates appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExpressionEngine, Version 7.3.15]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/expressionengine-v-7-3-15-vulnerability-2</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/expressionengine-v-7-3-15-vulnerability-2"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T15:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bishop Fox staff identified two vulnerabilities in Packet Tide’s ExpressionEngine version 7.3.15. The most severe issue allowed Bishop Fox staff to obtain access to a new administrator account in an instance of ExpressionEngine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthieu Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExpressionEngine, Version 7.3.15]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/expressionengine-v-7-3-15-vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/expressionengine-v-7-3-15-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T15:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bishop Fox staff identified two vulnerabilities in Packet Tide’s ExpressionEngine version 7.3.15. The most severe issue allowed Bishop Fox staff to obtain access to a new administrator account in an instance of ExpressionEngine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthieu Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install your own DHCP server in a VMware Workstation NAT network]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1583921</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-your-own-dhcp-server-in-a-vmware-workstation-nat-network/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Workstation provides three default network types, one of which is NAT. This option includes a built-in DHCP server, but its functionality is limited. Consequently, you might need to set up your own DHCP server within a virtual machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding mispriced opcodes with fuzzing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107580</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/17/finding-mispriced-opcodes-with-fuzzing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Max Ammann Fuzzing—a testing technique that tries to find bugs by repeatedly executing test cases and mutating them—has traditionally been used to detect segmentation faults, buffer overflows, and other memory corruption vulnerabilities that are detectable through crashes. But it has additional uses you may not know about: given the right invariants, we can use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS ICS Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ics-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ics-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS ICS Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight Essential Lessons for Resilient Supply Chain Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/eight-essential-lessons-for-resilient-supply-chain-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/eight-essential-lessons-for-resilient-supply-chain-security?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover eight essential lessons to fortify your supply chain security. Learn how collaboration, proactive risk management, quality assurance, and more can help your business build a resilient and secure supply chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Couple of Splunk/SPL Gotchas, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8463</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/06/15/couple-of-splunk-spl-gotchas-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T23:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been nearly 5 years since I dropped this old post about Splunk Gotchas. Okay, in fairness, I also covered SPL-based, path normalization in 2020 & bitmap-based hunting aka bitmap hunting here and here in 2024. Still… I thought it … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: python-per-line.py Version 0.0.12]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10510</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/06/15/update-python-per-line-py-version-0-0-12/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T10:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New option -O allows to use a function that receives a object per line as argument. Like option -n, option -O is used to invoke a single Python function taking one argument, but this time the argument is an object in stead of a string. The object has several properties: item is the line (string), […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Chat: From Prompt Injection to Data Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/github-copilot-chat-prompt-injection-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/github-copilot-chat-prompt-injection-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T05:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post highlights how the GitHub Copilot Chat VS Code Extension was vulnerable to data exfiltration via prompt injection when analyzing untrusted source code.
GitHub Copilot Chat GitHub Copilot Chat is a VS Code Extension that allows a user to chat with source code, refactor code, get info about terminal output, or general help about VS Code, and things along those lines.
It does so by sending source code, along with the user’s questions to a large language model (LLM).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of artifact collection and hoarding for the sake of forensic exclusivity… – Part 5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9222</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/06/14/the-art-of-artifact-collection-and-hoarding-for-the-sake-of-forensic-exclusivity-part-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T22:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow this series you should know by now that I am obsessing here not about the benefits of piracy, but about a new, powerful forensic capability: a truly actionable summary (extracted from the ever-growing evidence…). In my previous … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Apple’s On-Device and Server Foundation Models release]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107524</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/14/understanding-apples-on-device-and-server-foundations-model-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg Earlier this week, at Apple’s WWDC, we finally witnessed Apple’s AI strategy. The videos and live demos were accompanied by two long-form releases: Apple’s Private Cloud Compute and Apple’s On-Device and Server Foundations Models. This blog post is about the latter. So, what is Apple releasing, and how does it compare to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PCC: Bold step forward, not without flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107487</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/14/pcc-bold-step-forward-not-without-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Adelin Travers Earlier this week, Apple announced Private Cloud Compute (or PCC for short). Without deep context on the state of the art of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) security, some sensible design choices may seem surprising. Conversely, some of the risks linked to this design are hidden in the fine print. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Social Engineering Work? From Planning to Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/social-engineering-from-planning-to-execution</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/social-engineering-from-planning-to-execution"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the key points from our webcast, "How Does Social Engineering Work? in this recap blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTofu 1.7: State encryption, provider-defined functions, loopable import blocks, and improved CLI experience]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1583823</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/opentofu-17-state-encryption-provider-defined-functions-loopable-import-blocks-and-improved-cli-experience/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T14:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTofu, an open-source Terraform fork, announced the release of OpenTofu 1.7 with new features and improvements. Since version 1.6, the first stable release after the fork, over 100 community contributors and OpenTofu's core team joined hands to add the requested features, such as state encryption, provider-defined functions, loopable import blocks, and an improved CLI experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Burp Suite Professional chapter in the Testing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107482</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/14/announcing-the-burp-suite-professional-chapter-in-the-testing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Maciej Domanski Based on our security auditing experience, we’ve found that Burp Suite Professional’s dynamic analysis can uncover vulnerabilities hidden amidst the maze of various target components. Unpredictable security issues like race conditions are often elusive when examining source code alone. While Burp is a comprehensive tool for web application security testing, its extensive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MyJSON Tools]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10386</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/06/14/myjson-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I created a page with an intro to and overview of my MyJSON tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving forward in Android drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/driving-forward-in-android-drivers.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/driving-forward-in-android-drivers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=MXVwpSGzOOhqOc5hUWJbBLizfYjsfH9XaeDpmRKYJN5bV0WvE1cEyAoIq5yYZlSc);.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-7>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-7,lower-latin) ". "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-2>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-6>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-6,decimal) ". "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-8>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-8,lower-roman) ". "}.lst-kix_kbd3zqh16g9u-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_kbd3zqh16g9u-4}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-1>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}ol.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-3.start{co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Snowflake’s Access Landscape]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3bf232251945</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/mapping-snowflakes-access-landscape-3bf232251945?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because Every Snowflake (Graph) is Unique]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What HackerOne Customers Can Tell You About Securing Organizational Buy-In for Ethical Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/securing-organizational-buy-in</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/securing-organizational-buy-in"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HackerOne customers secure organizational buy-in for ethical hackers as part of their security program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Microsoft PowerToys: Advanced Paste and additional enhancements]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1583887</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-microsoft-powertoys-advanced-paste-and-additional-enhancements/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's newest release of PowerToys, a collection of sophisticated tools for Windows 10 and 11 users, introduces Advanced Paste. This feature leverages AI to transform copied content into a different format.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: InteractiveSieve Version 0.9.3.0]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10426</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/06/13/update-interactivesieve-version-0-9-3-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New features in this version of InteractiveSieve are: Load and Split With Load and Split; you can load a CSV file and split rows that have a field that contains more than one value, separated by a separator character. Take this example: Fields in column Methods can have more than one value: GET, POST and/or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Istio 1.22: Ambient mode, Gateway API, and Delta xDS for Kubernetes service mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1583818</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/istio-122-ambient-mode-gateway-api-and-delta-xds-for-kubernetes-service-mesh/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Istio is an open-source service mesh that controls how microservices share data, often integrated with Kubernetes to manage traffic and communication between services, but also capable of working with other deployment environments. It provides various functionalities such as traffic control, security measures (encryption, authentication, etc.), and monitoring. Recently, the introduction of Istio version 1.22 unveiled many interesting features, including an alternative for sidecar proxies, integration with Gateway API, incremental xDS for configuration distribution, and several other improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fly Phishing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7d4fb56ac325</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/fly-phishing-7d4fb56ac325?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bypass SPAM Filters]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stepping Stones – A Red Team Activity Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34352</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/06/12/stepping-stones-a-red-team-activity-hub/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Executive Summary NCC Group is pleased to open source a new tool built to help Red Teams log their activity for later correlation with the Blue Team’s own logging. What started as a simple internal web based data-collection tool has grown to integrate with Cobalt Strike and BloodHound to improve the accuracy and ease of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Tomkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: base64dump.py version 0.0.25]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10395</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/06/12/update-base64dump-py-version-0-0-25/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version adds a new post processing function to extract the longest string from the decoded payload (ExtractLongestString). Post processing functions take the decoded content, and replace it with the processed content. To view to original decoded content, the select option -s now supports suffix o. For example, to select the original decoded content […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allianz Cyber Talent Academy - The First Foundation to Bridge the Cybersecurity Skills Shortage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/allianz-cyber-talent-academy-bridge-the-cybersecurity-skills-shortage</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/allianz-cyber-talent-academy-bridge-the-cybersecurity-skills-shortage?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the Allianz Cyber Talent Academy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The June 2024 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66687be295dc3456498b5a43</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/6/11/the-june-2024-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somehow, we’ve made it to the sixth patch Tuesday of 2024, and Microsoft and Adobe have released their regularly scheduled updates. Take a break from your regular activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts. If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for June 2024
For June, Adobe released 10 patches addressing 165(!) CVEs in Adobe Cold Fusion, Photoshop,  Experience Manager, Audition, Media Encoder, FrameMaker Publishing Server, Adobe Commerce, Substance 3D Stager, Creative Cloud Desktop, and Acrobat Android. The fix for Experience Manager is by far the largest with a whopping 143 CVEs addressed. However, all but one of these bugs are simply cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lateral Movement with the .NET Profiler]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8772c86f9523</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/lateral-movement-with-the-net-profiler-8772c86f9523?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The accompanying code for this blogpost can be found HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Mayer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Windows setup from WinPE using autounattend.xml]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1583804</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/automate-windows-setup-from-winpe-using-autounattendxml/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T15:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When booting PCs from WinPE, you can run setup.exe with parameters and automate it with an answer file. This can partition the system drive without user interaction and skip the regional settings dialog. By additionally including an unattend.xml file in the image, you achieve a fully unattended installation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting ML models with pickle file attacks: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107459</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/11/exploiting-ml-models-with-pickle-file-attacks-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T15:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Boyan Milanov In part 1, we introduced Sleepy Pickle, an attack that uses malicious pickle files to stealthily compromise ML models and carry out sophisticated attacks against end users. Here we show how this technique can be adapted to enable long-lasting presence on compromised systems while remaining undetected. This variant technique, which we call […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[onwebkitplaybacktargetavailabilitychanged?! New exotic events in the XSS cheat sheet]]></title>
        <id>new-exotic-events-in-the-xss-cheat-sheet</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/new-exotic-events-in-the-xss-cheat-sheet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The power of our XSS cheat sheet is we get fantastic contributions from the web security community and this update is no exception. We had valuable contributions from Mozilla to remove events that no]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pumping Iron on the Musl Heap – Real World CVE-2022-24834 Exploitation on an Alpine mallocng Heap]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34674</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/06/11/pumping-iron-on-the-musl-heap-real-world-cve-2022-24834-exploitation-on-an-alpine-mallocng-heap/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pumping Iron on the Musl Heap – Real World CVE-2022-24834 Exploitation on an Alpine mallocng Heap Lua 5.1 Musl’s Next Generation Allocator – aka mallocng mallocng Cycling Offset Exploiting CVE-2022-24834 on the mallocng heap mallocng Heap Shaping Ensuring Correct Target Table->Array Distance Lua Table Confusion redis-server/libc ASLR Bypass and Code Execution Conclusion Resources Tools This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting ML models with pickle file attacks: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107441</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/06/11/exploiting-ml-models-with-pickle-file-attacks-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Boyan Milanov We’ve developed a new hybrid machine learning (ML) model exploitation technique called Sleepy Pickle that takes advantage of the pervasive and notoriously insecure Pickle file format used to package and distribute ML models. Sleepy pickle goes beyond previous exploit techniques that target an organization’s systems when they deploy ML models to instead […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: pdf-parser.py Version 0.7.9]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10388</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/06/11/update-pdf-parser-py-version-0-7-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I added option -j –jsonoutput to my pdf-parser.py tool. This option produces JSON output with the content of all of the streams, unfiltered. To have the filtered stream content as JSON output, include option -f. pdf-parser_V0_7_9.zip (http)MD5: E435A374A233C9DFEDA8A4E16887FB99SHA256: 99F50D4F030A5B3E9F9CBA20A7BB8C51FBA368526077CCA3466C784DA39D42DB]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v4.2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9fc10d77bf19</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-v4-2-9fc10d77bf19?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project Documents & Reporting Enhancements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Maddalena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enumerating System Management Interrupts]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34547</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/06/10/enumerating-system-management-interrupts/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System Management Interrupts (SMI) provide a mechanism for entering System Management Mode (SMM) which primarily implements platform-specific functions related to power management. SMM is a privileged execution mode with access to the complete physical memory of the system, and to which the operating system has no visibility. This makes the code running in SMM an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carles Pey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up EC2 instance access to an S3 bucket using IAM and OpenTofu]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1583723</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/setting-up-ec2-instance-access-to-an-s3-bucket-using-iam-and-opentofu/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial will teach you how to configure an EC2 instance to access an S3 bucket using the Terraform fork OpenTofu. The guide assumes familiarity with AWS and covers the essential steps, including creating an IAM role and policies and attaching them to an EC2 instance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: FileScanner Version 0.0.0.9]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10423</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/06/10/update-filescanner-version-0-0-0-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a small change to my FileScanner tool to make it long path aware. FileScanner_V0_0_0_9.zip (http)MD5: 2BCD526792C76890CC6EF7EED9396BE2SHA256: 9063221557F2EBACDC5B1CA977828250A2524B9795369AB4918B9287CAEB7DBF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EDR Internals for macOS and Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=4009</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2024/06/03/edr-internals-macos-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T15:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many public blogs and conference talks have covered Windows telemetry sources like kernel callbacks and ETW, but few mention macOS and Linux equivalents. Although most security professionals may not be surprised by this lack of coverage, one should not overlook these platforms. For example, developers using macOS often have privileged cloud accounts or access to intellectual property like source code. Linux servers may host sensitive databases or customer-facing applications. Defenders must have confidence in their tools for these systems, and attackers must understand how to evade them. This post dives into endpoint security products on macOS and Linux to understand their capabilities and identify weaknesses.

Endpoint detection and response (EDR) agents comprise multiple sensors: components that collect events from one or more telemetry sources. The agent formats raw telemetry data into a standard format and then forwards it to a log aggregator.
Tags: EDR, Linux, macOS
Read full post
The post EDR Internals for macOS and Linux appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Avery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side-by-Side with HelloJackHunter: Unveiling the Mysteries of WinSxS]]></title>
        <id>65f5ceb78792421d3c2272e4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/hellojackhunter-exploring-winsxs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T09:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores Windows Side-by-Side (WinSxS) and DLL hijacking, deep-diving some tooling I've written and some of the fun along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>