<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-18T00:31:27.549Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Intuition for Lattice-Based Signatures – Part 2: Fiat-Shamir with Aborts]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31656</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/17/building-intuition-for-lattice-based-signatures-part-2-fiat-shamir-with-aborts/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This two-part blog series aims to build some intuition for the main techniques that are used to construct lattice-based signatures, focusing in particular on the techniques underlying Falcon and Dilithium, the two lattice-based signature schemes selected for standardization by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST). In part 1 of this two-part blog […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elenabakoslang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Ubuntu packages with the Ansible apt module]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576054</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-ubuntu-packages-with-the-ansible-apt-module/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T13:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the Ansible apt module to manage packages that use the apt package manager on Debian-based Linux distributions, such as Ubuntu. The module allows you to perform all basic package management operations, such as installing, removing, and updating the packages.
Install Ubuntu packages with the Ansible apt module first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Entanglement | DLL Hijacking in the Asian Gambling Sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=83550</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/chinese-entanglement-dll-hijacking-in-the-asian-gambling-sector/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors abuse Adobe Creative Cloud, Edge, and other executables vulnerable to DLL hijacking in campaign targeting the Southeast Asian gambling sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InQL v5: A Technical Deep Dive]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/17/inql-v5.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/17/inql-v5.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to pull back the curtain on the latest iteration of our
widely-used Burp Suite extension - InQL.
Version 5 introduces significant enhancements and upgrades, solidifying its
place as an indispensable tool for penetration testers and bug bounty hunters.
Introduction
The Journey So Far: From Jython to Kotlin    
The Challenges of Converting a Burp Extension Into Kotlin
Sidestepping the need for stickytape
Introducing GQLSpection: The Core of InQL v5.x
New Features    
Points of Interest
Improved Logging
In-line Annotations
The Future of InQL and GraphQL Security
InQL: A Great Project for Students and Contributors
Conclusion



Introduction
The cybersecurity landscape is in a state of constant flux. As GraphQL adoption
surges, the demand for an adaptable, resilient testing tool …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: SMB Pivots With Havoc C2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/554362101d27</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-smb-pivots-with-havoc-c2-554362101d27?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! Today we’re going to talk about some lateral movement techniques with Havoc C2 using SMB pivots. SMB pivots are great for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export certificate as CER, DER, P7B, or PFX]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576032</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/export-certificate-as-cer-der-p7b-or-pfx/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When transferring a certificate to another computer, it is common practice to export it from the cert store and then import it on the target system. The available export formats depend on whether you want to transfer the private key as well and whether the private key is exportable.
Export certificate as CER, DER, P7B, or PFX first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Track installer changes, improve PC performance with Mirekusoft Install Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576015</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/track-installer-changes-impove-pc-performance-with-mirekusoft-install-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirekusoft Install Monitor allows you to track all changes made to your system by a Windows installer. The tool helps improve PC performance through proactive system monitoring and thorough uninstallation features. You can easily manage startup programs, and the Install Monitor's backup feature allows you to restore a previous version of an application after an upgrade.
Track installer changes, improve PC performance with Mirekusoft Install Monitor first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Approximately 2000 Citrix NetScalers backdoored in mass-exploitation campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32628</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/15/approximately-2000-citrix-netscalers-backdoored-in-mass-exploitation-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fox-IT (part of NCC Group) has uncovered a large-scale exploitation campaign of Citrix NetScalers in a joint effort with the Dutch Institute of Vulnerability Disclosure (DIVD). An adversary appears to have exploited CVE-2023-3519 in an automated fashion, placing webshells on vulnerable NetScalers to gain persistent access. The adversary can execute arbitrary commands with this webshell, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Global Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Ready for the New NIST Control Around Public Disclosure Programs?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-vdp-control</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-vdp-control"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new NIST control requires SaaS vendors to “establish a public reporting channel for receiving reports of vulnerabilities in organizational systems and system components.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blake Entrekin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 cloud backup]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575994</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-11-cloud-backup/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May 2023, Microsoft announced a cloud-powered OS Backup and Restore for Windows 11. The initial version was released in Windows 11 version 23466 and is referred to as Windows Backup.
Windows 11 cloud backup first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you pass the Rekt test?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104675</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/14/can-you-pass-the-rekt-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T08:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the biggest challenges for blockchain developers is objectively assessing their security posture and measuring how it progresses. To address this issue, a working group of Web3 security experts, led by Trail of Bits CEO Dan Guido, met earlier this year to create a simple test for profiling the security of blockchain teams. We […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scorpion CBS show. Plane hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27384</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/scorpion-cbs-show-plane-hack/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T05:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having got on a bit of a roll with dismantling plane hacking in the media with the MH370 documentary critique, it’s probably time to tear apart the pilot episode of […]
Scorpion CBS show. Plane hack first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Die Hard 2. Or how not to hack airplanes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27406</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/die-hard-2-or-how-not-to-hack-airplanes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T05:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How could I criticise possibly the best action movie series of all time? Well, it’s to help dispel myths about hacking planes. TV shows and films help set a narrative […]
Die Hard 2. Or how not to hack airplanes first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAPS 2.0 Internals]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/LAPSv2-Internals/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/LAPSv2-Internals/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T10:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, LAPS 2.0 was released by Microsoft, and thankfully it now comes built-in to Windows. This time it comes ready for use with Active Directory, as well as being supported in Azure AD aka Entra ID. In this post, we’ll look at how LAPS 2.0 for Active Directory works under the hood, so you can make those fresh recommendations to your clients, and prepare yourself for the inevitable question... “But we just deployed LAPS.. what does LAPS 2.0 do differently?!”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Function: Decrypting Azure Function App Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=30784</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/cloud-penetration-testing/what-the-function-decrypting-azure-function-app-keys/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying an Azure Function App, access to supporting Storage Accounts can lead to disclosure of source code, command execution in the app, and decryption of the app’s Access Keys.
The post What the Function: Decrypting Azure Function App Keys  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Elling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Git/GitHub beginner tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575983</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/a-gitgithub-beginner-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:32:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a popular version control system in the DevOps world, and GitHub is an online platform where developers can collaborate with their Git repositories. In this Git/GitHub beginner's tutorial, you'll learn how to get started without requiring any new knowledge about version control systems.
A Git/GitHub beginner tutorial first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SysPWN – VR for Pwn2Own]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32581</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/11/syspwn-vr-for-pwn2own/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T08:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Plaskett (@alexjplaskett) presented a talk on the 10th of August 2023 at @SysPWN covering vulnerability research for Pwn2Own. The first section of the talk covered a high-level perspective of the event, personal history, and teams. It then discussed some considerations needing to be made when deciding on target, experiences, and learnings from the competition. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Plaskett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brand-New Course LDR521: Security Culture for Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/brand-new-course-ldr521-security-culture-for-leaders</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/brand-new-course-ldr521-security-culture-for-leaders?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SANS Security Culture course has been significantly updated - everything from the name of the course to the content, labs, and handouts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SanerNow: Detect security anomalies]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575854</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sanernow-detect-security-anomalies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SanerNow's Continuous Posture Anomaly Management (CPAM) allows you to detect misconfigurations and security anomalies using machine learning and deep analysis. With the myriad of devices and infrastructure configurations that organizations have spread across on-premises and hybrid cloud environments, it's challenging to provide visibility to your security posture in a consolidated, seamless way using traditional tools.
SanerNow: Detect security anomalies first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Site Takeover via SCCM’s AdminService API]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d932e22b2bf</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/site-takeover-via-sccms-adminservice-api-d932e22b2bf?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T17:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tl:dr: The SCCM AdminService API is vulnerable to NTLM relaying and can be abused for SCCM site takeover.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garrett Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Konstellation: A Tool for RBACpacking in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4760</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/introducing-konstellation-for-rbacpacking-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T13:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author presented this paper and corresponding tool at Black Hat: Arsenal 2023 on August 10, 2023. For a more general overview of Konstellation and its capabilities vis a vis Kubernetes RBAC, please see our earlier companion post.  Kubernetes Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) is a mechanism for controlling access to resources in a Kubernetes cluster. […]
The post Konstellation: A Tool for RBACpacking in Kubernetes appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New techniques and tools for web race conditions]]></title>
        <id>new-techniques-and-tools-for-web-race-conditions</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/new-techniques-and-tools-for-web-race-conditions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T06:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For too long, web race-condition attacks have focused on a tiny handful of scenarios. Testing for them is inherently unreliable, compounded by known challenges relating to time constraints and network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Thinking Episode 31: Alex Chapman - The Man of Many Crits]]></title>
        <id>https://ajxchapman.github.io/media/2023/08/10/ctbb.html</id>
        <link href="https://ajxchapman.github.io/media/2023/08/10/ctbb.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chapman's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Blog Series - Blog 2: Architecting for Zero Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-blog-2-architecting-zero-trust</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-blog-2-architecting-zero-trust?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Blog Series - Blog 2: Architecting for Zero Trust]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking With Your Nemesis]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7861f75fcab4</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/hacking-with-your-nemesis-7861f75fcab4?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T20:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first post in this series, On (Structured) Data, we talked about the gap area of offensive structured data and ended with the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing the state machine: the true potential of web race conditions]]></title>
        <id>smashing-the-state-machine</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/smashing-the-state-machine"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For too long, web race condition attacks have focused on a tiny handful of scenarios. Their true potential has been masked thanks to tricky workflows, missing tooling, and simple network jitter hiding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SEC Cyber Rules Incentivize Proactive Security Measures]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/new-sec-cybersercurity-rules</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/new-sec-cybersercurity-rules"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently finalized a regulation that imposes increased transparency related to cybersecurity risk management, governance, and incidents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleep computer (remotely) from the command line]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575833</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/sleep-computer-remotely-from-the-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T15:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, you might want to send a computer into power-saving mode remotely or from the command line. The onboard utilities offer limited options for this, and PowerShell offers none at all. As alternatives, two free utilities from Microsoft's Sysinternals and NirSoft get the job done.
Sleep computer (remotely) from the command line first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advisory | NetModule Router Software Race Condition Leads to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://pentest.blog/?p=2687</id>
        <link href="https://pentest.blog/advisory-netmodule-router-software-race-condition-leads-to-remote-code-execution/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T12:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction NetModule Router Software (NRSW) is a Linux-based software solution developed by NetModule for managing data connections across various devices. It applies to a various devices, including stationary and mobile routers, gateways, and IoT devices. NRSW provides consistent configuration processes and functions across all NetModule devices. It includes security features and supports over-the-air updates. NetModule […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nuri Çilengir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use our suite of eBPF libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104838</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/09/use-our-suite-of-ebpf-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg Trail of Bits has developed a suite of open-source libraries designed to streamline the creation and deployment of eBPF applications. These libraries facilitate efficient process and network event monitoring, function tracing, kernel debug symbol parsing, and eBPF code generation. Previously, deploying portable, dependency-free eBPF applications posed significant challenges due to Linux kernel […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PNG Steganography from First Principles]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/png-steganography/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/png-steganography/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T10:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steganography is experiencing a revival as a wrapper for delivering payloads. In this post we'll go back to basics and show just how steganography can be applied to a PNG image using the common least significant bit (LSB) encoding technique. No magic... just raw information... and a little C++.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Citrix Workspace with SecureAuth’s Arculix: A New Standard in Passwordless Continuous Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=49115</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/enhancing-citrix-workspace-with-secureauths-arculix-a-new-standard-in-passwordless-continuous-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T10:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This was co-authored by Faranak Talebi, Integrations Engineer at SecureAuth. In the digital era, the seamless integration of various platforms is crucial for efficient and secure operations. SecureAuth’s Arculix, an award-winning platform in next-gen passwordless continuous authentication, is setting new standards in this domain. Today, we announce how Arculix enhances the capabilities of Citrix […]
The post Enhancing Citrix Workspace with SecureAuth’s Arculix: A New Standard in Passwordless Continuous Authentication appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Badge of Shame - Breaking Into Secure Facilities with OSDP]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/breaking-into-secure-facilities-with-osdp</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/breaking-into-secure-facilities-with-osdp"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about five exploitable vulnerabilities we've identified in OSDP and share what defenders can do about them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Petro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability disclosure in aviation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27409</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/vulnerability-disclosure-in-aviation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T05:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We joined Boeing and United Airlines on a panel recently at the RSA Conference to talk about vulnerability disclosure in the aviation world. The engagement we are now seeing between […]
Vulnerability disclosure in aviation first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Engineer Salary, Skills, and Career Path]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/network-engineer-salary-skills-and-career-path</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/network-engineer-salary-skills-and-career-path?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about a network engineer's salary, skills, and career path]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco call handler with Cisco Unity Connection messaging]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575699</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/cisco-call-handler-with-cisco-unity-connection-messaging/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T20:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many businesses rely on a caller attendant to manage or route phone calls for their business or call center. If you have ever called a business and received an automated greeting like "Press 1 for Sales, press 2 for Accounting," you have encountered a caller attendant. In a previous article, we looked at the components of the Cisco Unified Communication Manager System. In this article, we will dive deeper and look at how the caller handler is built using Cisco Unity Connection Server.
Cisco call handler with Cisco Unity Connection messaging first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The August 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64cc1aed8ada730e80dab699</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/8/8/the-august-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T17:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings from hacker summer camp! Black Hat and DEFCON start this week, but let’s kick everything off with Patch Tuesday and the latest security offerings from Adobe and Microsoft. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. If you’d rather watch the video recap, you can check it out here.
Adobe Patches for August 2023
For August, Adobe released four patches addressing 37 CVEs in Adobe Acrobat and Reader, Commerce, Dimension, and the Adobe XMP Toolkit SDK. A total of 28 of these CVEs came through the ZDI program. The update for Reader is the largest, clocking in with 30 CVEs. The most severe of these are rated Critical and would allow code execution when opening a specially crafted PDF. The update for Commerce fixe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BloodHound Community Edition: A New Era]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d64689806e90</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/bloodhound-community-edition-a-new-era-d64689806e90?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel BIOS Advisory – Memory Corruption in HID Drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32552</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/08/intel-bios-advisory-memory-corruption-in-hid-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T12:28:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I will be focusing on two additional BIOS vulnerabilities. The first bug impacts the Bluetooth keyboard driver (HidKbDxe in BluetoothPkg) and the second bug impacts a touch panel driver (I2cTouchPanelDxe in AlderLakePlatSamplePkg).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Boone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing BitSight Automation Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=15881</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/08/08/introducing-bitsight-automation-tool/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glossary Entity A part of an organization that can be assessed as a single figure. Subsidiary Same as an Entity on BitSight’s side. Group Cluster A complex. It can contain entities/subsidiaries, or Groups, or more Group Clusters. Group A structure that can contain Entities. Glossary Introduction In this blog post you will be introduced to … Continue reading Introducing BitSight Automation Tool →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantinos Papanagnou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne and the OWASP Top 10 for LLM: A Powerful Alliance for Secure AI]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/owasp-llm-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/owasp-llm-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is HackerOne’s perspective on the Top 10 list for LLM vulnerabilities and how organizations can prevent these critical security risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manjesh S.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resultant Set of Policy (RSoP), Group Policy Results, and Group Policy Modeling]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575444</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/resultant-set-of-policy-rsop-group-policy-results-and-group-policy-modeling/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T15:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Resultant Set of Policy (RSOP) snap-in of the Microsoft Management Console (MCC) helps troubleshoot Group Policy settings. Group Policy Results and Group Policy Modeling are the corresponding features of the Group Policy Management Console (GPMC).
Resultant Set of Policy (RSoP), Group Policy Results, and Group Policy Modeling first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comrades in Arms? | North Korea Compromises Sanctioned Russian Missile Engineering Company]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=83314</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/comrades-in-arms-north-korea-compromises-sanctioned-russian-missile-engineering-company/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean threat actors attempt to further missile program by compromising sanctioned Russian defense company with OpenCarrot backdoor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Role of Mentorship in Cyber Threat Intelligence (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-role-of-mentorship-in-cyber-threat-intelligence-part-2-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-role-of-mentorship-in-cyber-threat-intelligence-part-2-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we can all benefit from professional mentorship, mentoring needs will vary from person to person based largely on where they are in their career. In this blog series we introduced mentorship concepts, the role and responsibilities of mentors and mentees, and provided resources on areas to engage to find prospective mentors, both formally through organizational program and through industry specific events or initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis and Exploitation of CVE-2023-3519]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/analysis-exploitation-cve-2023-3519</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/analysis-exploitation-cve-2023-3519"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our latest blog offers additional analysis and exploitation of CVE-2023-3519, a critical remote code execution vulnerability in Citrix ADC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Gross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What To Expect When You’re “Expecting” — Purple Team Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c6879655fe1</id>
        <link href="https://cedowens.medium.com/what-to-expect-when-youre-expecting-purple-team-edition-c6879655fe1?source=rss-fd791048dac0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T20:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post describes how “expect” routines can be used to help make Purple Team exercises more efficient and repeatable. In particular…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Owens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Fall 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2153</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/08/04/public-mobile-exploitation-training-fall-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T16:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Exploitation Training We are pleased to announce that the researchers of Exodus Intelligence will be providing publicly available training in person on November 14 2023 in London, England. This 4 day course is designed to provide students with both an overview of the Android attack surface and an in-depth understanding of advanced vulnerability and exploitation topics. Attendees ... Read more Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Fall 2023
The post Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Fall 2023 appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Browser Exploitation Training – Fall 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2154</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/08/04/public-browser-exploitation-training-fall-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T16:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browser Exploitation Training We are pleased to announce that the researchers of Exodus Intelligence will be providing publicly available training in person on November 14 2023 in London, England. This 4 day course is designed to provide students with both an overview of the current state of the browser attack surface and an in-depth understanding of advanced vulnerability ... Read more Public Browser Exploitation Training – Fall 2023
The post Public Browser Exploitation Training – Fall 2023 appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find enabled local Group Policy settings with rsop.msc and PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575415</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-enabled-local-group-policy-settings-with-rsopmsc-and-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T15:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to GPO troubleshooting, you might want to find settings that are configured by local Group Policy. With rsop.msc, a graphical tool is available for this purpose. However, it is generally more efficient to generate a report using gpresult.exe and evaluate it with PowerShell.
Find enabled local Group Policy settings with rsop.msc and PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BloodHound Enterprise Learns Some New Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/26f0fa89e1d1</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/bloodhound-enterprise-learns-some-new-tricks-26f0fa89e1d1?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T18:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BloodHound code-convergence project brings some significant and long-desired feature enhancements to BloodHound Enterprise (BHE): BloodHound Enterprise customers will get access to these features…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Hinck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Inspector: AWS security monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575376</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/amazon-inspector-aws-security-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T14:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Amazon Inspector, an AWS security monitoring service that provides automated security scans for EC2 instances, AWS Lambda, and ECR container images.
Amazon Inspector: AWS security monitoring first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PTP at DEF CON 31 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27344</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/ptp-at-def-con-31-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T05:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come and see us at the Aerospace Village, at Caesars Forum. Aerospace Village Fri 11th to Sun 13th Activity Take off in an A320 with hacked engine performance calculator. Then try to […]
PTP at DEF CON 31 2023 first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Bursell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[n00b’s guide to DEF CON. Surviving the Matrix of the underground]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27302</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/n00bs-guide-to-def-con-surviving-the-matrix-of-the-underground/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T05:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, DEF CON. The world’s largest hacker convention. A beacon for the diverse spectrum of cyber security enthusiasts. From code-cracking challenges to the infamous Wall of Sheep, the event is […]
n00b’s guide to DEF CON. Surviving the Matrix of the underground first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Company Update]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ceo/company-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ceo/company-update"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T03:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Mårten Mickos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS DFIR Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-dfir-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-dfir-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS DFIR Summit 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges In Post-Exploitation Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2b3469810fe9</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/challenges-in-post-exploitation-workflows-2b3469810fe9?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our previous post, we talked about the problem of structured data in the post-exploitation community. We touched on the existing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MTE As Implemented, Part 3: The Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/mte-as-implemented-part-3-kernel.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/mte-as-implemented-part-3-kernel.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:30:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=4mNYFHt_IKFsPe52toizH6nwuZUPj2AFYBEz-aMyENVctA_KpTDBIb9wIwVqFCm-);.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-3>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-3}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-1.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-1 0}.lst-kix_8lngbvh6wilc-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_8lngbvh6wilc-4}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-0{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-2{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-2>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-2}.lst-kix_8lngbvh6wilc-5>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_8lngbvh6wilc-5}ol.lst-kix_cp4qttrp12lb-6.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_cp4qttrp12lb-6 0}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-1{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-4{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-3{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_8lngbvh6w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MTE As Implemented, Part 2: Mitigation Case Studies]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/mte-as-implemented-part-2-mitigation.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/mte-as-implemented-part-2-mitigation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:30:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=4mNYFHt_IKFsPe52toizH6nwuZUPj2AFYBEz-aMyENXbDjL3Cv1g7CpfdyRoONLEXShKQSnoFmUtAspFfwQKag);ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-8.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-8 0}.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-3>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-3}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-1.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-1 0}.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-8>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-8}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-0{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-2{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-2>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_46kwnuz47r-2}ol.lst-kix_cp4qttrp12lb-6.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_cp4qttrp12lb-6 0}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-1{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-4{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_46kwnuz47r-3{list-style-type:none}.ls…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MTE As Implemented, Part 1: Implementation Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/mte-as-implemented-part-1.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/mte-as-implemented-part-1.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:30:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=cGvuclDC_Z1vE_cnVEU6AbvdjsQquauI-GoInd1DzsRjfxSl7duaBsON8MRB32eGNP6BCxV-AQSEvP01Vpd9xT0e5qzIIUg9OvSRGeMDk3I);.lst-kix_exl34y7adtul-6>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_exl34y7adtul-6}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-4>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-6>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_w66ctsc8735u-5>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_w66ctsc8735u-5}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-3>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-7>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_7336pfhg38rf-8>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_7336pfhg38rf-8}ol.lst-kix_w66ctsc8735u-1.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_w66ctsc8735u-1 0}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-5>li:before{content:"-  "}ol.lst-kix_pmivlm2h8rwq-6.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_pmivlm2h8rwq-6 0}.lst-kix_cm1sbgja1sfy-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary: MTE As Implemented]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/summary-mte-as-implemented.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/08/summary-mte-as-implemented.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=DFQxm4rd7fRHgM9OTejWVT5Vho6BE7M80rHXEVKqXWdbV0WvE1cEyAoIq5yYZlSc);.lst-kix_exl34y7adtul-6>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_exl34y7adtul-6}.lst-kix_kzys3uxts4nk-6>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_kzys3uxts4nk-6,decimal) ". "}.lst-kix_kzys3uxts4nk-8>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_kzys3uxts4nk-8,lower-roman) ". "}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-4>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-6>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_kzys3uxts4nk-7>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_kzys3uxts4nk-7,lower-latin) ". "}.lst-kix_w66ctsc8735u-5>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_w66ctsc8735u-5}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-3>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_s8b3u49h11dr-7>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_7336pfhg38rf-8>li{counter-increment:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting a Flaw in Bitmap Handling in Windows User-Mode Printer Drivers]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64c962195d0bc15becbbc36d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/8/1/exploiting-a-flaw-in-bitmap-handling-in-windows-user-mode-printer-drivers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guest blog from researcher Marcin Wiązowski, he details CVE-2023-21822 – a Use-After-Free (UAF) in win32kfull that could lead to a privilege escalation. The bug was reported through the ZDI program and later patched by Microsoft. Marcin has graciously provided this detailed write-up of the vulnerability, examines how it could be exploited, and a look at the patch Microsoft released to address the bug.
In the Windows kernel, there are three APIs intended for general use by device drivers for the purpose of creating bitmaps: EngCreateBitmap, EngCreateDeviceBitmap and EngCreateDeviceSurface. Each of these APIs return a bitmap handle. If the caller wants to perform some drawing operations on the bitmap, the caller must first lock the bitmap by passing its handle to EngLockSurface. EngL…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Blogger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ConfigMap in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575354</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configmap-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, you learned about node selectors and node affinity in Kubernetes. In this post, we will discuss the ConfigMap resource that allows you to store data as a dictionary (using key–value pairs) outside of your containerization applications. It offers a means of storing configuration information, environment variables, command-line arguments, or other configuration data that Pods or other Kubernetes objects can use during their execution. This approach makes your applications more portable, flexible, and easier to maintain since the configuration settings are stored and maintained independently of specific Pods.
ConfigMap in Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Fortinet Firmware Encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/breaking-fortinet-firmware-encryption</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/breaking-fortinet-firmware-encryption"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out our latest research on Fortinet products hat breaks encryption on firmware images, leading to improved detection, fingerprinting, and exploit development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A mistake in the bulletproofs paper could have led to the theft of millions of dollars]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104826</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/02/a-mistake-in-the-bulletproofs-paper-could-have-led-to-the-theft-of-millions-of-dollars/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jim Miller We discovered a critical vulnerability in Incognito Chain that would allow an attacker to mint arbitrary tokens and drain user funds. Incognito offers confidential transactions through zero-knowledge proofs, so an attacker could have stolen millions of dollars of shielded funds without ever being detected or identified. The vulnerability stemmed from an insecure […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been compromised?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27282</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/have-you-been-compromised/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T05:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine the scenario… A nation state recruits an asset / spy at age 18. Their education and living expenses are fully funded, all with the aim of getting them a […]
Have you been compromised? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vladimir Panek-Noble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Zero Trust Architecture?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-zero-trust-architecture</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-zero-trust-architecture?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article outlines what Zero Trust is, how Zero Trust works, the five core principles of Zero Trust, and the stages of implementing Zero Trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Purple Team Can Use Continuous Adversary Emulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-purple-team-can-use-continuous-adversary-emulation</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-purple-team-can-use-continuous-adversary-emulation?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post series offers a primer on continuous adversary emulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Claude Data Exfiltration Vulnerability Fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/anthropic-fixes-claude-data-exfiltration-via-images/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/anthropic-fixes-claude-data-exfiltration-via-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T22:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common attack vector that LLM apps face is data exfiltration, in particular data exfiltration via Image Markdown Injection is a common vulnerability. Microsoft fixed the vulnerability in Bing Chat, ChatGPT is still vulnerable as Open AI “won’t fixed” the issue, and Anthropic just mitigated this vulnerability in Claude.
This post documents the Anthropic Claude data exfiltration vulnerability and the mitigation put in place.
The Vulnerability - Image Markdown Injection As a quick recap, imagine a large language model (LLM) returns the following text:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Terraform AWS provider example]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575322</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/a-terraform-aws-provider-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T15:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a beginner's guide to using the Terraform AWS provider? This guide will show you how to easily set up, operate, and manage your AWS infrastructure using HashiCorp’s Infrastructure as Code (IaC) solution. Plus, we'll walk you through a practical example that you can try out on your own AWS account. For this guide, I assume that you are familiar with AWS and that you already have an AWS account with the corresponding security credentials.
A Terraform AWS provider example first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Konstellation, for Kubernetes RBAC Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4752</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/konstellation-tool-for-kubernetes-rbac-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T13:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Praetorian is excited to announce the upcoming release of Konstellation, a new open-source tool that simplifies Kubernetes role-based access control (RBAC) data collection and security analysis. Join us August 10, 2023, at Black Hat Arsenal 2023 for a deeper dive on exactly what this tool can do for you. Kubernetes RBAC is a powerful tool […]
The post Introducing Konstellation, for Kubernetes RBAC Analysis appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Konstellation, for Kubernetes RBAC Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4752</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/introducing-konstellation-for-kubernetes-rbac-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T13:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Praetorian is excited to announce the upcoming release of Konstellation, a new open-source tool that simplifies Kubernetes role-based access control (RBAC) data collection and security analysis. Join us August 10, 2023, at Black Hat Arsenal 2023 for a deeper dive on exactly what this tool can do for you. Kubernetes RBAC is a powerful tool […]
The post Introducing Konstellation, for Kubernetes RBAC Analysis appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your new best friend: Introducing BloodHound Community Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cb908446e270</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/your-new-best-friend-introducing-bloodhound-community-edition-cb908446e270?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T12:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now featuring enterprise-grade deployment, usability, and UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Hinck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI will affect cybersecurity: What we told the CFTC]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104822</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/31/how-ai-will-affect-cybersecurity-what-we-told-the-cftc/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T11:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Guido, CEO The second meeting of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission’s Technology Advisory Committee (TAC) on July 18 focused on the effects of AI on the financial sector. During the meeting, I explained that AI has the potential to fundamentally change the balance between cyber offense and defense, and that we need security-focused benchmarks […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Guido</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TPM, PIN, Passwords, and SID: Managing BitLocker Key Protectors]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575306</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/tpm-pin-passwords-and-sid-managing-bitlocker-key-protectors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T08:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitLocker uses symmetric encryption methods to encrypt drives. The key used for this is protected by two encryption layers. On the top layer, different kinds of protectors grant access to the drive. However, not all are equally secure or suitable for all drives.
TPM, PIN, Passwords, and SID: Managing BitLocker Key Protectors first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the power of Red Teaming: An overview of trainings and certifications]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=14980</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/07/31/unlocking-the-power-of-red-teaming-an-overview-of-trainings-and-certifications/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO enjoys an excellent working relationship with SANS and has been involved as Instructors and Course Authors for a variety of their courses: As technology continues to evolve, so do the tactics and techniques used by cyber criminals. This means that staying up to date as a red team operator is crucial for protecting customers … Continue reading Unlocking the power of Red Teaming: An overview of trainings and certifications →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steffen Rogge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving Beyond Tech: The SEC’s New Cybersecurity Regulations and the Need for Comprehensive Training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/moving-beyond-tech-the-sec-s-new-cybersecurity-regulations-and-the-need-for-comprehensive-training</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/moving-beyond-tech-the-sec-s-new-cybersecurity-regulations-and-the-need-for-comprehensive-training?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These new regulations reinforce a crucial tenet that we at the SANS Institute have long embraced: effective cybersecurity starts with skilled people first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LDR553: Cyber Incident Management – Now 5 Days!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ldr553-cyber-incident-management-now-5-days</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ldr553-cyber-incident-management-now-5-days?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a blog about LDR553: Cyber Incident Management – Now 5 Days! by Steve Armstrong-Godwin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cloud Infrastructure?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cloud-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cloud-infrastructure?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a blog explaining "what is cloud infrastructure?" by Chris Edmundson]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Escaping the Google kCTF Container with a Data-Only Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://h0mbre.github.io/kCTF_Data_Only_Exploit/</id>
        <link href="https://h0mbre.github.io/kCTF_Data_Only_Exploit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction I’ve been doing some Linux kernel exploit development/study and vulnerability research off and on since last Fall and a few months ago I had some downtime on vacation to sit and challenge myself to write my first data-only exploit for a real bug that was exploited in kCTF. io_ring has been a popular target in the program’s history up to this point, so I thought I’d find an easy-to-reason-about bug there that had already been exploited as fertile ground for exploit development creativity. The bug I chose to work with was one which resulted in a struct file UAF where it was possible to hold an open file descriptor to the freed object. There have been quite a few write-ups on file UAF exploits, so I decided as a challenge that my exploit had to be data-only. The parameters of the self-imposed challenge were completely arbitrary, but I just wanted to try writing an exploit that didn’t rely on hijacking control flow. I have written quite a few Linux kernel exploits of real kCTF bugs at this point, probably 5-6 as practice, just starting with the vulnerability and going from there, but all of them have ended up in me using ROP, so this was my first try at data-only. I also had not seen a data-only exploit for a struct file UAF yet, which was encouraging as it seemed it was worthwile “research”. Also, before we get too far, please do not message me to tell me that someone already did xyz years prior. I’m very new to this type of thing and was just doing this as a personal challenge, if some aspects of the exploit are unoriginal, that is by coincidence. I will do my best to cite all my inspiration as we go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Human Machine Interface</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rancher Desktop: Kubernetes for your Windows, macOS, or Linux desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1575288</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/rancher-desktop-kubernetes-for-your-windows-macos-or-linux-desktop/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Rancher Desktop, a free, open-source solution for seamless Kubernetes and container management on your desktop, allowing you to run the Kubernetes version of your choice on a Windows, macOS, or Linux desktop.
Rancher Desktop: Kubernetes for your Windows, macOS, or Linux desktop first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of Clang-based tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104803</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/28/the-future-of-clang-based-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T11:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Peter Goodman Clang is a marvelous compiler; it’s a compiler’s compiler! But it isn’t a toolsmith’s compiler. As a toolsmith, my ideal compiler would be an open book, allowing me to get to everywhere from anywhere. The data on which my ideal compiler would operate (files, macros, tokens), their eventual interpretation (declarations, statements, types), […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes guide: Node selector and node affinity in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572779</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-guide-node-selector-and-node-affinity-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T17:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, you learned about taints and tolerations in Kubernetes, which enable you to reserve a certain node for specific workloads, but they don't guarantee that the workload will always be scheduled on the desired node. In this post, you will learn about the concepts of node selector and node affinity to ensure that your workloads are always scheduled on the desired nodes.
Kubernetes guide: Node selector and node affinity in Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strengthening the SDLC with Security Advisory Services (SAS)]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/security-advisory-services-sdlc</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/security-advisory-services-sdlc"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We see untapped potential in how customers use our HackerOne solutions every day, which inspired the creation of our latest offering: HackerOne Security Advisory Services (SAS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Chariot Managed Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4747</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/the-power-of-chariot-managed-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T13:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of cybersecurity is one of constant, rapid change, challenging organizations to keep pace with emerging threats. Organizations search for a tool or product that holistically enhances their cybersecurity program and gives them peace of mind – a silver bullet. Unfortunately, no single vendor offers silver bullets. With budgets tightening, cybersecurity leaders may face […]
The post The Power of Chariot Managed Service appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cloud Security Compliance?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cloud-security-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cloud-security-compliance?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a blog explaining "what is cloud security compliance?" by Chris Edmundson]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cloud Security Compliance?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cloud-security-compliance-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cloud-security-compliance-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a blog explaining "what is cloud security compliance?" by Chris Edmundson]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Impact on IAM Development and Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=48995</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/ai-impact-on-iam-development-and-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Background and Proliferation of AI Tools and Services:  Despite some misconceptions, AI and AI chatbots are not new technologies. The first AI chatbot was introduced in 1966 named Eliza by an MIT professor, and IBM Watson in 2010 (more info here). AI is changing the Identity and Access Management (IAM) code development landscape with a possibility […]
The post AI Impact on IAM Development and Productivity appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On (Structured) Data]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/707b7d9876c6</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-structured-data-707b7d9876c6?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T18:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactive Microsoft 365 monitoring with ENow]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572761</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/proactive-microsoft-365-monitoring-with-enow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T16:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional monitoring tools, designed primarily for on-premises systems, struggle to monitor Software as a Service (SaaS) applications effectively. Explore ENow Microsoft 365 Monitoring & Reporting, which leverages synthetic transactions to monitor cloud service accessibility that go beyond simple reachability checks. It also provides multiple checks of the Microsoft cloud, providing a visual map of service status for the regions your users are in. In addition, ENow's Microsoft 365 Monitoring & Reporting tool offers a variety of reports for license optimization, governance, and Teams call quality management.
Proactive Microsoft 365 monitoring with ENow first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Trail of Bits Testing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104793</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/26/announcing-the-trail-of-bits-testing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T11:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Maciej Domanski Trail of Bits is thrilled to announce the Testing Handbook, the shortest path for developers and security professionals to derive maximum value from the static and dynamic analysis tools we use at Trail of Bits. Why did we create the Testing Handbook? At Trail of Bits, we have spent countless hours studying, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Role of Mentorship in Cyber Threat Intelligence (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-role-of-mentorship-in-cyber-threat-intelligence-part-1-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-role-of-mentorship-in-cyber-threat-intelligence-part-1-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mentorship means different things to different people and is an area not often appreciated until a later point in one's career. Mentorship, however, is an easily accessible tool that new, junior or transitioning cyber security professionals can use to jumpstart their career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei Theme Manager Arbitrary Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/07/26/huawei-theme-arbitrary-code-exec.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/07/26/huawei-theme-arbitrary-code-exec.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2019, we were lucky enough to take part in the newly-launched Huawei mobile bug bounty. For that, we decided to research Huawei’s Themes.
The Themes Manager allows custom themes on EMUI devices to stylize preferences, and the customization of lock screens, wallpapers and icons. Processes capable of making these types of system-wide changes need to have elevated privileges, making them valuable targets for research as well as exploitation.
Background
When it comes to implementing a lockscreen on EMUI, there were three possible engines used:
com.ibimuyu.lockscreen
com.vlife.huawei.emuilock
com.huawei.ucdlockscreen
When installing a theme, the SystemUI.apk verifies the signature of the application attempting to make these changes against a hardcoded list of trusted ones. From what we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Exchange Online commands using Azure Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572743</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/run-exchange-online-commands-using-azure-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T19:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Microsoft has made multifactor authentication (MFA) mandatory for connecting to Exchange Online, running commands has become challenging. If you followed my previous article, you have all the building blocks needed to connect to Exchange Online with PowerShell using an app registration. In this post, you will learn how to leverage Azure Automation to schedule your Exchange Online scripts.
Run Exchange Online commands using Azure Automation first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoom and Salesforce: The Role of Hackers in Addressing Security Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/zoom-salesforce-ethical-hackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/zoom-salesforce-ethical-hackers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“You can’t find everything, and it’s crucial to leverage the best talent where you can find it,” says Michael Adams, Chief Information Security Officer at Zoom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurie Mercer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon's Security Researcher Collaboration: Highlights from H1-213]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/live-hacking-events/amazons-security-researcher-collaboration-highlights-h1-213</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/live-hacking-events/amazons-security-researcher-collaboration-highlights-h1-213"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“At Amazon, protecting our customers’ information is our top priority. Part of those efforts includes our bug bounty program through HackerOne, which allows participating researchers to submit findings directly to the company. We work with researchers across the security industry that reach out about potential issues that may impact our customers, and we take steps to investigate and fix them. Events like H1-213 provide our security teams with the unique opportunity to engage a diverse group of ethical, independent researchers.”
-	Travis Lee, Senior Manager, Offensive Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabeth@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS 2023 Security Awareness Report: Managing Human Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-2023-security-awareness-report-managing-human-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-2023-security-awareness-report-managing-human-risk?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the SANS 2023 Security Awareness Report which provides practical, actionable information to increase your security awareness team’s maturity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Intuition for Lattice-Based Signatures – Part 1: Trapdoor Signatures]]></title>
        <id>https://ncc-blog.pixelpreview.net/?p=26782</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/07/24/building-intuition-for-lattice-based-signatures-part-1-trapdoor-signatures/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Since the first lattice-based cryptography results in [Ajtai96], lattices have become a central building block in quantum-resistant cryptosystems. Based on solving systems of linear equations, lattice-based cryptography adds size constraints or error terms to linear systems of equations, turning them into quantum-computer resistant one-way or trapdoor functions. Since the first theoretical cryptosystems of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elenabakoslang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure BitLocker key with a PIN]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572710</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/secure-bitlocker-key-with-a-pin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T16:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, BitLocker is configured to release the volume master key (VMK) solely through the TPM. However, this might not adequately protect the VMK if a notebook falls into the wrong hands. Therefore, Microsoft recommends two-factor authentication using an additional PIN or startup key.
Secure BitLocker key with a PIN first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Custom Instructions: Persistent Data Exfiltration Demo]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-custom-instruction-post-exploitation-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-custom-instruction-post-exploitation-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T14:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT is vulnerable to data exfiltration via image markdown injections. This. is. pretty well known.
As more features are added to ChatGPT the exfiltration angle becomes more likely to be abused.
Recently OpenAI added Custom Instructions, which allow to have ChatGPT always automatically append instructions to every message exchange.
An adversary can abuse this feature to install a data exfiltration backdoor that depends on, and only works because of the image markdown injection vulnerability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The top 10 community-created BChecks, so far ...]]></title>
        <id>the-top-10-community-created-bchecks-so-far</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/the-top-10-community-created-bchecks-so-far"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T14:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently launched BChecks, scripted scan checks that allow you to create customized scans without the hassle of learning advanced programming. We've shortlisted the top ten BChecks (so far) that ha]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 Cloud Log Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/microsoft-365-cloud-log-extraction</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/microsoft-365-cloud-log-extraction?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we discussed the various methods of accessing and exporting the Unified Audit Log (UAL). If you need a way to perform a quick and targeted search, you can leverage the Purview Compliance Portal. If you want to retrieve a small part of the UAL and export to JSON format, PowerShell has the Search-UnifiedAuditLog cmdlet. For larger organizations or those who need to continuously poll the UAL, there is the Microsoft 365 Management API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix ADC Gateway RCE: CVE-2023-3519 is Exploitable, and 53% of Servers Are Unpatched]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/citrix-adc-gateway-rce-cve-2023-3519</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/citrix-adc-gateway-rce-cve-2023-3519"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T17:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bishop Fox developed an exploit for CVE-2023-3519, a stack overflow in Citrix ADC Gateway that allows remote code execution. There are 61,000 affected appliances exposed on the internet, and roughly 53% of them are currently unpatched.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Team X</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Git Bash on Windows with git command examples]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572693</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-git-bash-on-windows-with-git-command-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T16:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system used by developers to collaborate and manage changes in their applications. It was created for Linux and macOS. But what about Windows? This is where Git Bash for Windows comes in. This tutorial will explain how to install Git Bash on Windows and introduce a few Git Bash commands to interact with the Git repository.
Install Git Bash on Windows with git command examples first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Tic Tac Toe with 170mb of HTML - no JS or CSS]]></title>
        <id>tic-tac-toe-in-html</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/tic-tac-toe-in-html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it when Chrome releases a new feature, I especially like it when it is experimental. In this post I'm going to show you how I created Tic Tac Toe (Noughts and crosses) with HTML, using one of t]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzing on-chain contracts with Echidna]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104755</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/21/fuzzing-on-chain-contracts-with-echidna/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T11:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Guillermo Larregay and Elvis Skozdopolj With the release of version 2.1.0 of Echidna, our fuzzing tool for Ethereum smart contracts, we’ve introduced new features for direct retrieval of on-chain data, such as contract code and storage slot values. This data can be used to fuzz deployed contracts in their on-chain state or to test […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Media Exploitation Analyst (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-media-exploitation-analyst-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-media-exploitation-analyst-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[メディアエクスプロイテーションアナリストの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release: Cartographer]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31427</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/07/20/tool-release-cartographer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T21:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cartographer is a Ghidra plugin that creates a visual "map" of code coverage data, enabling researchers to easily see what parts of a program are executed. It has a wide range of uses, such as better understanding a program, honing in on target functionality, or even discovering unused content in video games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Peavy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Ansible on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572625</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-ansible-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T19:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible is an open-source configuration management platform from Red Hat. So isn't Ansible a Linux-only solution? While it is indeed primarily for Linux configuration management, you can, in fact, install Ansible on Windows.
Install Ansible on Windows first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shifting boundaries: Exploiting an Integer Overflow in Apple Safari]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2144</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/07/20/shifting-boundaries-exploiting-an-integer-overflow-in-apple-safari/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vignesh Rao Overview In this blog post, we describe a method to exploit an integer overflow in Apple WebKit due to a vulnerability resulting from incorrect range computations when optimizing Javascript code. This research was conducted along with Martin Saar in 2020. We show how to convert this integer overflow into a stable out-of-bounds ... Read more Shifting boundaries: Exploiting an Integer Overflow in Apple Safari
The post Shifting boundaries: Exploiting an Integer Overflow in Apple Safari appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-36934: Progress Software MOVEit Transfer SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64b84d887cb6720b78392146</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/7/19/cve-2023-36934-progress-software-moveit-transfer-sql-injection-remote-code-execution-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Guy Lederfein and Lucas Miller of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in Progress MOVEit Transfer. This bug was originally discovered by Trend Micro Vulnerability Researcher Guy Lederfein and is the same type of vulnerability being used by the Cl0p ransomware gang to exfiltrate data. A crafted request can trigger the execution of SQL queries composed from a user-supplied string. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the “moveitsvc” user. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2023-36934, with a few minimal modifications.
An SQL injection vulnerability has been reported for Progress MOVEit Tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing jsluice: A Technial Deep-Dive for JavaScript Gold (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-technical-deep-dive</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-technical-deep-dive"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for a technical deep-dive of jsluice, an open-source mining tool for JavaScript code and files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing jsluice: The Why Behind JavaScript Gold Mining (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-gold-mining</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-gold-mining"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use jsluice, an open-source, Go package and command-line tool used to extract information from JavaScript files and code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JumpCloud Intrusion | Attacker Infrastructure Links Compromise to North Korean APT Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=82769</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/jumpcloud-intrusion-attacker-infrastructure-links-compromise-to-north-korean-apt-activity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T10:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean state sponsored APT is behind a new supply chain attack on zero-trust directory platform JumpCloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SOC Toolbox: Analyzing AutoHotKey compiled executables]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=14236</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/07/20/the-soc-toolbox-analyzing-autohotkey-compiled-executables/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A quick post on how to extract AutoHotKey scripts from an AutoHotKey script compiled executable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Dhaeyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SecureAuth Identity Platform 23.07 Release Provides Streamlined Migration and Improved User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=48975</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/secureauth-identity-platform-23-07-release-provides-streamlined-migration-and-improved-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of the SecureAuth® Identity Platform version 23.07. The feature-rich release focuses on two major benefits: streamlined migration and improved user experience. Streamlined Migration / Upgrades  Since the creation of the Migration Tool, several customers have realized huge success in significantly reducing migration time and effort. Whether […]
The post SecureAuth Identity Platform 23.07 Release Provides Streamlined Migration and Improved User Experience appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect to Exchange Online with PowerShell and certificate-based authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572600</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/connect-to-exchange-online-with-powershell-and-certificate-based-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting to Exchange Online with PowerShell to automate tasks was made slightly more challenging when Microsoft discontinued basic authentication for Microsoft 365 tenants, making certificate-based authentication mandatory.
Connect to Exchange Online with PowerShell and certificate-based authentication first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cobalt Strike and Outflank Security Tooling: Friends in Evasive Places]]></title>
        <id>https://outflank.nl/?p=2948</id>
        <link href="https://outflank.nl/blog/2023/07/19/cobalt-strike-and-outflank-security-tooling-friends-in-evasive-places/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a joint blog written by the Cobalt Strike and Outflank teams. It is also available on the Cobalt Strike site.
Over the past few months there has been increasing collaboration and knowledge sharing internally between the Cobalt Strike and Outflank R&D teams. We are excited about the innovation opportunities made possible by this teamwork and have decided to align Cobalt Strike and Outflank Security Tooling (OST) closely going forward. Although we are actively collaborating, Cobalt Strike will continue to be the industry standard Command & Control (C2) framework, while OST will continue to offer a red team toolbox for all environments containing custom tradecraft that is OPSEC safe, evasive by design, and simple to use. Our vision is that Cobalt Strike and OST together will provide the best red team offering on the planet. 
Tags: announcements, c2, cobalt strike, developments, integrations, red team, yara
Read full post
The post Cobalt Strike and Outflank Security Tooling: Friends in Evasive Places appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pieter Ceelen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>