<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-12-06T00:38:06.434Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Confidential Space Security Review]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18326</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/12/06/public-report-confidential-space-security-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the summer of 2022, Google engaged NCC Group to conduct a security assessment of the Confidential Space product. The system provides a confidential computing environment that allows cloud customers to run workloads in the cloud that can be attested to run a specific payload with high assurances that the workload was not and cannot … Continue reading Public Report – Confidential Space Security Review →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viktor Gazdag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Prompt Injection Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18253</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/12/05/exploring-prompt-injection-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever heard about Prompt Injection Attacks[1]? Prompt Injection is a new vulnerability that is affecting some AI/ML models and, in particular, certain types of language models using prompt-based learning.  This vulnerability was initially reported to OpenAI by Jon Cefalu (May 2022)[2] but it was kept in a responsible disclosure status until it was … Continue reading Exploring Prompt Injection Attacks →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Selvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New features in VMware vSphere 8]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568952</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-features-in-vmware-vsphere-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vSphere 8 release includes many new features that are exposed in the new vCenter Server 8 and ESXi 8 releases. With the release of vSphere 8, many organizations will look at upgrading to the latest VMware vSphere.
New features in VMware vSphere 8 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extracting Certificates For Defender]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9703</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/05/extracting-certificates-for-defender/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A colleague asked me for help with extracting code signing certificates from malicious files, to add them to Defender’s block list. The procedure involves right-clicking the EXE in Windows Explorer, selecting properties to view the digital signature, and so on … But I don’t like procedures where one has to click on malware. So I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 SANS Summits Talks of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/top-sans-summits-talks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/top-sans-summits-talks-2022?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, SANS hosted 13 Summits with 246 talks. Here were the top-rated talks of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: python-per-line.py Version 0.0.9]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9713</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/04/update-python-per-line-py-version-0-0-9/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a small update to add the lineNumber variable. python-per-line_V0_0_9.zip (http)MD5: CD9FC344E4C5F649E4043BD703CDCA52SHA256: BD6713A7DF86AC75ADC2A6742A453919F56583D8CC5EB3B82B736608D2A52619]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using make_sc_hash_db.py to create API hashing DBs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8299</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/12/03/using-make_sc_hash_db-py-to-create-api-hashing-dbs/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever used shellcode_hashes IDA plugin from Mandiant, you probably have also used make_sc_hash_db.py before. But, if you haven’t, this post is for you. The focus of the article […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in November]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9698</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/03/overview-of-content-published-in-november-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T09:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in November: Blog posts: Quickpost: Testing A USB Fridge Update: pdf-parser.py Version 0.7.7 Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.71 Quickpost: Testing A USB Fridge (Update) Update: what-is-new.py Version 0.0.2 YouTube videos: Extracting Information From “logfmt” Files With CyberChef Extracting Information From “logfmt” Files With InteractiveSieve Videoblog posts: Extracting Information […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environment… is variable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8287</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/12/02/environment-is-variable/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T23:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love environmental variables. They are often post-worthy, and sometimes they are just simply cool. Yet, many are still not known. Many are still not described. Looking for ‘easy’ research […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT: Imagine you are a database server]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/chatgpt-imagine-you-are-a-database/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/chatgpt-imagine-you-are-a-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T16:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After reading this post about ChatGPT imitating Linux, I wanted it to be a database server.
Let’s try it out!
 Imagine you are a Microsoft SQL Server. I type commands, and you reply with the result, and no other information or descriptions. Just the result. Start with exec xp_cmdshell ‘whoami’;
 
Wow, this looks like a promising start.
And, it “thinks” that it is running as LOCAL SYSTEM - quite funny actually.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a custom Azure image]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568929</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-a-custom-vm-image-in-azure/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T13:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you to want to upload an on-premises Hyper-V VM to the cloud to create a custom Azure image containing all your business applications in a preconfigured state, this post will help you.
Create a custom Azure image first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can we block the addition of local Microsoft Defender Antivirus exclusions?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12954</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/12/02/can-we-block-the-addition-of-local-microsoft-defender-antivirus-exclusions/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction A few weeks ago, I got a question from a client to check how they could prevent administrators, including local administrators on their device, to add exclusions in Microsoft Defender Antivirus. I first thought it was going to be pretty easy by pushing some settings via Microsoft Endpoint Manager. However, after doing some research … Continue reading Can we block the addition of local Microsoft Defender Antivirus exclusions? →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillaume Bossiroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer advice for buying smart IoT devices this Christmas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26158</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/consumer-advice-for-buying-smart-iot-devices-this-christmas/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T06:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rightly or wrongly there’s plenty of fear, uncertainty, and downright doom associated with the IoT and devices. So, is it safe to buy these things as gifts or even as […]
Consumer advice for buying smart IoT devices this Christmas first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stalking inside of your Chromium Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/757848b67949</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/stalking-inside-of-your-chromium-browser-757848b67949?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T18:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, you got your favorite agent running on the target machine. You did a process listing, but nothing interesting popped out. You searched through every possible thing, even the trash bins to find…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kai Huang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambassador Spotlight: Emperor]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/ambassador-spotlight-emperor</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/ambassador-spotlight-emperor"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T15:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who are you?
My name is Raviraj; I'm from Gujarat, India. I go by the handle, Emperor. My handle came from an anime called "Kuruko no Basuke." It r]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Returns to Miami Beach for 2023]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6387cc73a344c24acf985796</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/11/30/pwn2own-returns-to-miami-beach-for-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T14:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[¡Bienvenidos de nuevo a Miami!
Even as we make our final preparations for our consumer-focused contest in Toronto, we’re already looking ahead to warmer climes and returning to the S4 Conference in Miami for our ICS/SCADA-themed event. Pwn2Own returns to South Beach on February 14-16, 2023, and for this year’s event, we’ve refined our target list to include the latest trends in the ICS world. As we did last year, we’ll have contestants both in person and around the world demonstrating the latest exploits on OPC Unified Architecture (OPC UA) Servers, OPC UA Clients, Data Gateways, and Edge systems.
Our inaugural Pwn2Own Miami was held back in January 2020 at the S4 Conference, and we had a fantastic time as we awarded over $280,000 USD in cash and prizes for 24 unique 0-day vulnerabilities.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mystery of Metador | Unpicking Mafalda’s Anti-Analysis Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=73728</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/the-mystery-of-metador-unpicking-mafaldas-anti-analysis-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T14:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the anti-analysis techniques of the Mafalda implant, a unique, feature-rich backdoor used by the Metador threat actor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | The Mystery of Metador]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=73910</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-the-mystery-of-metador/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T14:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An elusive APT is attacking telcos, ISPs and Universities with custom backdoors and attack chains designed to bypass native security solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FSLogix VHDX compaction: Resize virtual disks]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568907</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/fslogix-vhdx-compaction-resize-virtual-disks/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T12:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new FSLogix version, which was released in October, introduces a long-awaited feature: VHDX compaction. FSLogix is a standalone product acquired in late 2017 by Microsoft for profile management and application masking features. It is primarily used in virtual desktop or RDSH solutions to provide users with a persistent experience in nonpersistent environments.
FSLogix VHDX compaction: Resize virtual disks first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rankin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Split-brain DNS deployment using Windows Server DNS policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568889</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/split-brain-dns-deployment-using-windows-server-dns-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T14:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is common for organizations to host websites and other resources that may be accessible from external and internal clients on the LAN. Traditionally, organizations may have maintained two different DNS servers for this reason. Microsoft's split-brain DNS deployment using DNS policy helps consolidate these resources using Active Directory-integrated zones.
Split-brain DNS deployment using Windows Server DNS policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Burp challenge]]></title>
        <id>the-burp-challenge</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/the-burp-challenge"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T09:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently launched the Burp challenge, to give our customers a unique opportunity to demonstrate their skills with Burp Suite Professional. Not only that, but the challenges involved put your web vu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a CTF: The Success of Flag Hunt Bangladesh]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/creating-ctf-success-flag-hunt-bangladesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/creating-ctf-success-flag-hunt-bangladesh"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T02:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About the CTF 
Flag Hunt 2022 CTF was the first ever two-stage event in Bangladesh, where the qualification round took place online among 159 te]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CISO's Approach to Ransomware Playbooks]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cisos-approach-to-ransomware</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cisos-approach-to-ransomware"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a CISO's perspective on testing your security defenses against real-world ransomware playbooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating the Discovery of NTLM Authentication Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4284</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/automating-the-discovery-of-ntlm-authentication-endpoints/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T14:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I have been working on adding support for automated enumeration and discovery of NTLM authentication endpoints to Chariot, our external attack surface and continuous automated red teaming product. Our red team requested this feature as a way to identify NTLM authentication endpoints exposed over HTTP that they could potentially leverage for password spraying attacks […]
The post Automating the Discovery of NTLM Authentication Endpoints appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hijacking service workers via DOM Clobbering]]></title>
        <id>hijacking-service-workers-via-dom-clobbering</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/hijacking-service-workers-via-dom-clobbering"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we'll briefly review how service worker hijacking works, then introduce a variant that can be triggered via DOM clobbering thanks to a quirk in document.getElementById(). Understanding s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Specialized Zero-Knowledge Proof failures]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103253</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/11/29/specialized-zero-knowledge-proof-failures/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T12:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Opal Wright Zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs are useful cryptographic tools that have seen an explosion of interest in recent years, largely due to their applications to cryptocurrency. The fundamental idea of a ZK proof is that a person with a secret piece of information (a cryptographic key, for instance) can prove something about the secret […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block notifications in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568878</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/block-notifications-in-chrome-edge-and-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T11:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites ask users whether they want to receive notifications. In managed environments, this feature can be disabled via group policies. Both Chromium-based browsers and Firefox allow whitelisting and blacklisting of such websites.
Block notifications in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install the unified CloudWatch agent on Windows EC2 instances]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568862</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-the-unified-cloudwatch-agent-on-windows-ec2-instances/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T14:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This step-by-step guide explains how to install the unified CloudWatch agent on Windows on EC2 Windows instances. This allows you to monitor logs and guest OS metrics. In the example here, I will show you how we can monitor IIS with CloudWatch.
Install the unified CloudWatch agent on Windows EC2 instances first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sujith Rajendran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: From Workstation To Domain Controller With Havoc C2 and Microsoft EDR]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6b17018e32f6</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-from-workstation-to-domain-controller-with-havoc-c2-and-microsoft-edr-6b17018e32f6?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T13:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! In this blog entry we’ll be facing off with Microsoft’s Defender For Endpoint EDR once again to see if we can go from a low…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable TLS on SQL Server]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568830</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-tls-on-sql-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T11:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and Transport Layer Security (TLS, which builds on the now deprecated SSL protocol) allow you to encrypt Microsoft SQL Server network communication, which is essential for your security. In this post, you'll learn how to enable TLS on your SQL Server.
Enable TLS on SQL Server first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restricting registration to Azure AD MFA from trusted locations with Conditional Access policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568804</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/restricting-registration-to-azure-ad-mfa-from-trusted-locations-with-conditional-access-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T14:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may be familiar with the Conditional Access policy feature in Azure AD as a means to control access to your tenant. In addition to granting or blocking access to the tenant as a whole, it is possible to restrict certain user actions. One important action you should consider controlling is from where a user can enroll in multifactor authentication (MFA).
Restricting registration to Azure AD MFA from trusted locations with Conditional Access policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So long and thanks for all the 0day]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18144</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/11/23/so-long-and-thanks-for-all-the-0day/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T19:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After nearly four years into my role, I am stepping down as NCC Group’s SVP & Global Head of Research. In part just for myself, to reflect on a whirlwind few years, and in part as a thank you and celebration of all of the incredible researchers with whom I have had the privilege of … Continue reading So long and thanks for all the 0day →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-40300: SQL Injection in ManageEngine Privileged Access Management]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:637d484bbd6d15315428d647</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/11/22/cve-2022-40300-sql-injection-in-manageengine-privileged-access-management"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T15:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Justin Hung and Dusan Stevanovic of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched SQL injection vulnerability in Zoho ManageEngine products. The bug is due to improper validation of resource types in the AutoLogonHelperUtil class. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to arbitrary SQL code execution in the security context of the database service, which runs with SYSTEM privileges. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2022-3236, with a few minimal modifications.
ManageEngine recently patched a SQL injection vulnerability bug in their Password Manager Pro, PAM360, and Access Manager Plus products. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of resource …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An End to KASLR Bypasses?]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=495086</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/an-end-to-kaslr-bypasses/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=an-end-to-kaslr-bypasses"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T14:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[…]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNMP vs WMI for Windows monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568782</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/snmp-vs-wmi-for-windows-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T10:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two most common protocols for monitoring Microsoft products are Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) and Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI). They are both natively supported in Windows and Windows Server, and neither one requires you to install third-party add-ons to start monitoring. This article explains the difference between the two protocols and helps you choose the one that works better for your scenario.
SNMP vs WMI for Windows monitoring first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: what-is-new.py Version 0.0.2]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9694</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/23/update-what-is-new-py-version-0-0-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update of what-is-new-.py, my tool that reports what lines inside files are new (e.g., never seen before) has a new option: -a –action. It allows me to launch a command when something new is detected. I use this for example to be alerted via TelegraM; More details in an upcoming blog post. what-is-new_V0_0_2.zip (http)MD5: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mind the Gap]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/mind-the-gap.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/mind-the-gap.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=OPeqXG-QxW3ZD8BtmPikfA');.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-0>li:before{content:"\0025cf  "}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-6{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-7{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-4{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-5{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-2{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf  "}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-1{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0  "}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf  "}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb  "}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb  "}.lst-kix_9a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure AD MFA with number matching and temporary access passes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568773</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/azure-ad-mfa-with-number-matching-and-temporary-access-passes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T15:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft will enable the new number matching feature by default in February 2023. Number matching for Azure AD MFA is almost the reverse of the multi-factor authentication you know. With number matching, a number is displayed to a user when they sign in, and instead of entering this number on the device, they log in to confirm the number on the MFA device. Temporary Access Pass is another feature that allows you to help end users who are unable to meet sign-in criteria.
Azure AD MFA with number matching and temporary access passes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated Windows Forensic Analysis Poster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/updated-windows-forensic-analysis-poster</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/updated-windows-forensic-analysis-poster?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new version of the FOR500: Windows Forensics Poster was a nearly complete re-write of the poster with significant updates made to every section.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A jq255 Elliptic Curve Specification, and a Retrospective]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18107</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/11/21/a-jq255-elliptic-curve-specification-and-a-retrospective/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T16:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First things first: there is now a specification for the jq255e and jq255s elliptic curves; it is published on the C2SP initiative and is formally in (draft) version 0.0.1: https://github.com/C2SP/C2SP/blob/main/jq255.md The jq255e and jq255s groups are prime-order groups appropriate for building cryptographic protocols, and based on elliptic curves. These curves are from the large class … Continue reading A jq255 Elliptic Curve Specification, and a Retrospective →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Pornin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log HTTP Requests, Version 1.3.1, Advisory]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/log-http-requests-advisory</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/log-http-requests-advisory"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this medium risk advisory to learn details about CVE-2022-3402.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Etan Castro Aldrete</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Device Code Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/device-code-phishing/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/device-code-phishing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T14:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more organizations move to hardware tokens and password-less auth (e.g. Yubikeys, Windows Hello,…) attackers will look for other ways to to trick users to gain access to their data.
One novel phishing technique is by using the OAuth2 Device Authorization Grant.
This post describes how it works with Microsoft AAD as example.
Attacker initiates the phishing flow The attacker starts a Device Code flow by issuing a request to the device code token endpoint (e.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware vSphere 8: Editions, licensing, and pricing]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568747</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/vmware-vsphere-8-editions-licensing-and-pricing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T11:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware recently announced the licensing terms, editions, and pricing of vSphere 8. All components, including ESXi, vCenter, and vSAN, are still available via perpetual licenses. However, the vendor announced a switch to subscriptions, which will be made more attractive through a subscription upgrade program.
VMware vSphere 8: Editions, licensing, and pricing first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ropci deep-dive for Azure hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ropci-usage/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/ropci-usage/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Misconfigurations with MFA setups are not uncommon when using AAD, especially when federated setups or Pass Through Authentication is configured I have seen MFA bypass opportunities in multiple production tenants.
A common misconfiguration is that MFA is enforced at the federated identity provider, but AAD is forgotten and ROPC authentication still succeeds against AAD.
To learn more about ROPC, check out the previous post about the topic.
This post focuses on the ropci features that can be leveraged post-exploitation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cracking Zeppelin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8283</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/11/19/cracking-zeppelin/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T23:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago Brian Krebs published a piece about Zeppelin key cracking, so … since I was also involved in recovering files for some of the ransomware gang victims […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond good ol’ Run key, Part 139]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8278</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/11/19/beyond-good-ol-run-key-part-139/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T22:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This one is a curious one. I actually don’t know how to trigger it! Yet, I will document some bits and bobs, so that you may take these entry points […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find and remove duplicate files with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568739</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-and-remove-duplicate-files-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T05:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use PowerShell to find and remove duplicate files that are only wasting valuable storage. Once you identify duplicate files, you can move them to another location, or you might even want to permanently remove all duplicates.
Find and remove duplicate files with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Account Takeovers:  Believe the Unbelievable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15783</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/account-takeovers-believe-the-unbelievable/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T17:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nikhil Srivastava is a member of the Synack Red Team and co-founder of Bsides Ahmedabad. An Account Takeover (ATO) is an attack whereby attackers take ownership of online accounts using several methods. It is unfortunately more common than you’d think, despite all the warnings to create complex passwords, avoid phishing emails and use multi-factor authentication. […]
The post Account Takeovers:  Believe the Unbelievable appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SRT Community</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hive Ransomware is on the rise. How should you deal with it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26105</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/hive-ransomware-is-on-the-rise-how-should-you-deal-with-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T06:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Now? Hive is not a new problem. It first surfaced in 2021 but it’s becoming a much bigger issue now. This is due to a growing number of affiliates […]
Hive Ransomware is on the rise. How should you deal with it? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 compliance policy: Control access with compliant devices]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568724</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-365-compliance-policy-control-access-with-compliant-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T05:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the procedure described in this post, you can ensure that only devices with an assigned Microsoft 365 compliance policy are able to sign in. This way, you will significantly improve the security of your Microsoft 365 deployment.
Microsoft 365 compliance policy: Control access with compliant devices first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – NXP i.MX SDP_READ_DISABLE Fuse Bypass (CVE-2022-45163)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17848</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/11/17/cve-2022-45163/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T16:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary NXP System-on-a-Chip (SoC) fuse configurations with the SDP READ_REGISTER operation disabled (SDP_READ_DISABLE=1) but other serial download functionality still enabled (SDP_DISABLE=0) can be abused to read memory contents in warm and cold boot attack scenarios. In lieu of an enabled SDP READ_REGISTER operation, an attacker can use a series of timed SDP WRITE_DCD commands to … Continue reading Technical Advisory – NXP i.MX SDP_READ_DISABLE Fuse Bypass (CVE-2022-45163) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Szymaniak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Go from Active Duty to Civilian Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/how-to-civilian-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/how-to-civilian-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, learn how veterans bridge the career gap between active duty service and civilian cybersecurity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People Are People: Gender Equality at Praetorian]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4279</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/gender-equality-at-praetorian/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T14:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early this Summer, we shared our thoughts on the industry-wide shortage of cybersecurity talent to meet an ever-growing demand. One aspect of this phenomenon that we did not touch on in that post was the gender gap within the cybersecurity community, about which the World Bank hosted a Spring conference . While 50 percent of […]
The post People Are People: Gender Equality at Praetorian appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Demystifying Threats to Satellite Communications in Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=73463</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-demystifying-threats-to-satellite-communications-in-critical-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T14:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite communications are an integral part of many Industrial Control Systems, but their usage in critical infrastructure continues to be misunderstood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate file downloads with Windows FTP or curl]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568693</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/automate-file-downloads-with-windows-ftp-or-curl/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to download files regularly from an FTP server, Windows offers two onboard tools to automate this process. These are ftp.exe and curl, which was added just recently. For the latter, you only need one command; for FTP, you can use whole scripts.
Automate file downloads with Windows FTP or curl first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Program Levels: Hacker-friendly Practices that Improve Program Results]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/company-news/introducing-program-levels-hacker-friendly-practices-improve-program-results</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/company-news/introducing-program-levels-hacker-friendly-practices-improve-program-results"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ethical hacker community is one of the most powerful security resources available to any organization. We’ve worked with this community firsthand for the last decade and have witnessed their effectiveness and ingenuity. We’ve also learned a lot while helping organizations engage the world’s largest community of ethical hackers. 

Today, we’re pleased to announce a new tool to align your program with the state-of-the-art and signal your program maturity: Program Levels, a structured framework that lets programs level up by publicly committing to certain best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control Your Types or Get Pwned: Remote Code Execution in Exchange PowerShell Backend]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6372bce0c67b98581b79d19f</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/11/14/control-your-types-or-get-pwned-remote-code-execution-in-exchange-powershell-backend"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T16:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now you have likely already heard about the in-the-wild exploitation of Exchange Server, chaining CVE-2022-41040 and CVE-2022-41082. It was originally submitted to the ZDI program by the researcher known as “DA-0x43-Dx4-DA-Hx2-Tx2-TP-S-Q from GTSC”. After successful validation, it was immediately submitted to Microsoft. They patched both bugs along with several other Exchange vulnerabilities in the November Patch Tuesday release.
It is a beautiful chain, with an ingenious vector for gaining remote code execution. The tricky part is that it can be exploited in multiple ways, making both mitigation and detection harder. This blog post is divided into two main parts:
·       Part 1 – where we review details of the good old ProxyShell Path Confusion vulnerability (CVE-2021-34473), and we sh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Ahead of the Five Most Dangerous New Attack Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/get-ahead-of-the-five-most-dangerous-new-attack-techniques</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/get-ahead-of-the-five-most-dangerous-new-attack-techniques?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS experts give an update on the five attack techniques shared at RSA Conference 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Lateral Movement With Havoc C2 And Microsoft EDR]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/300b7389b1f7</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-lateral-movement-with-havoc-c2-and-microsoft-edr-300b7389b1f7?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T21:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lateral movement is extremely important for any red team engagement. Getting your initial shell is great, but if you can’t move off the box…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Wrong with Bug Bounty Programs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15767</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/whats-wrong-with-bug-bounty-programs/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T18:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bug Bounty Program?  The concept of bug bounty programs is simple. You allow a group of security researchers, also known as ethical hackers, to access your systems and applications so they can probe for security vulnerabilities – bugs in your code. And you pay them a bounty on the bugs they find. […]
The post What’s Wrong with Bug Bounty Programs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How OneWeb is Safeguarding its Assets with the Hacker Community]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/how-oneweb-safeguarding-its-assets-hacker-community</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/how-oneweb-safeguarding-its-assets-hacker-community"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne sat down with Wendy Ng, Principal Cloud Security Architect at OneWeb, to talk about their experience with their private HackerOne bug bounty program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Raffa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stealing passwords from infosec Mastodon - without bypassing CSP]]></title>
        <id>stealing-passwords-from-infosec-mastodon-without-bypassing-csp</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/stealing-passwords-from-infosec-mastodon-without-bypassing-csp"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T14:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of how I could steal credentials on Infosec Mastodon with a HTML injection vulnerability, without needing to bypass CSP. Everybody on our Twitter feed seemed to be jumping ship to the infose]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABI compatibility in Python: How hard could it be?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103173</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/11/15/python-wheels-abi-abi3audit/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR: Trail of Bits has developed abi3audit, a new Python tool for checking Python packages for CPython application binary interface (ABI) violations. We’ve used it to discover hundreds of inconsistently and incorrectly tagged package distributions, each of which is a potential source of crashes and exploitable memory corruption due to undetected ABI differences. It’s publicly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam Backup for Microsoft 365—Why you need to back up your M365 data]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568680</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/veeam-backup-for-microsoft-365why-you-need-to-back-up-your-m365-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T08:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are backups required for Microsoft 365? We look at the reasons you should back up your Microsoft 365 data and the new Veeam Backup for Microsoft 365 v6 features to protect your M365 data.
Veeam Backup for Microsoft 365—Why you need to back up your M365 data first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncovering Window Security Events]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ab72e1ec745c</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/uncovering-window-security-events-ab72e1ec745c?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re streamers now]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103134</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/11/14/livestream-workshop-fuzzing-echidna-slither/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T13:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, we’ve built many high-impact tools that we use for security reviews. You might know some of them, like Slither, Echidna, Amarna, Tealer, and test-fuzz. All of our tools are open source, and we love seeing the community benefit from them. But mastering our tools takes time and practice, and it’s easier if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PsInfo: Get disk space, installed applications, and other information about local and remote Windows systems]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568671</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/psinfo-get-disk-space-installed-applications-and-other-information-about-local-and-remote-windows-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T12:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PsInfo, a command-line tool that is part of the Sysinternals suite, gets key information about Windows systems, such as the type of installation, available disk space, installed applications, kernel build number, uptime, registered owner, and the number of processors.
PsInfo: Get disk space, installed applications, and other information about local and remote Windows systems first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Pen Test HackFest Summit 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-pen-test-hackfest-summit-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-pen-test-hackfest-summit-2022?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Pen Test HackFest Summit 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Go AWS SDK example]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568650</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/a-go-aws-sdk-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T02:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon provides three ways you can access and manage Amazon Web Services: AWS Management Console, AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI), and software development kits (SDKs). Our focus here will be on the software development kit using the Go programming language. We will look at what the SDK actually is and how to get up and running with installation and AWS account access. As an example, we will use the Go AWS SDK to create an S3 bucket.
A Go AWS SDK example first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Beer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Testing A USB Fridge (Update)]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9679</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/12/quickpost-testing-a-usb-fridge-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I performed some extra tests with my USB fridge (see Quickpost: Testing A USB Fridge). Here is how the temperature evolved when I put a can with cold water (around 12° C) in the USB fridge: The temperature increased around 2° C over a period of 12 hours (room temperature was around 17 °C). That […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When did users last change their password in Active Directory?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568638</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/when-did-users-last-change-their-password-in-active-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T05:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changing passwords regularly is no longer recommended, and the Security Baseline for Windows doesn't include a corresponding setting. Nevertheless, in certain situations, it can be important to know how old the user's passwords are. You can easily find this out with PowerShell.
When did users last change their password in Active Directory? first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.71]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9675</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/11/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-71/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new plugin and an updated plugin. Plugin plugin_dttm is a plugin for Word documents: it searches for Dop structures. They contain DTTM timestamps. And plugin plugin_metadata has been updated to parse digital signatures (option -s). oledump_V0_0_71.zip (http)MD5: BA1142136F28DB218BADEAA642EA0EA9SHA256: FA09766D138A1AA60523B487D947BF29222D409CF1FCE078DE61BF62768A5950]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypting Shellcode using SystemFunction032/033]]></title>
        <id>https://osandamalith.com/?p=4293</id>
        <link href="https://osandamalith.com/2022/11/10/encrypting-shellcode-using-systemfunction032-033/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T22:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a while, I’m publishing a blog post which made me interested. With the recent tweets about the uncodumented SystemFunction032 Win32 API function, I decided to quickly have a look at it. The first thing I noted after Googling this function was the source code from ReactOS. Seems like other SystemFunctions from 001 got other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Osanda Malith Jayathissa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release – Web3 Decoder Burp Suite Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17917</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/11/10/tool-release-web3-decoder-burp-suite-extension/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T19:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Decoder is a Burp Suite Extension that allows to decode “web3” JSON-RPC calls that interact with smart contracts in a EVM blockchain. As it is said that a picture is worth a thousand words, the following two screenshots shows a Raw JSON-RPC call, and its decoded function call: Background When auditing a DApp (Decentralized … Continue reading Tool Release – Web3 Decoder Burp Suite Extension →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimize Noise With Human-Led API Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15745</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/minimize-noise-with-human-led-api-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we released a new API Pentesting product that allows you to test your headless API endpoints through the Synack Platform. Before the release, we conducted more than 100 requests for headless API pentests, indicating a growing need from our customers. This new capability provides an opportunity to get human-led testing and proof-of-coverage on […]
The post Minimize Noise With Human-Led API Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Torio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Are Digital Technologies Eroding the Principle of Distinction in War?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=73009</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/are-digital-technologies-eroding-the-principle-of-distinction-in-war/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T14:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent conflicts, digital technology has become weaponized, eroding the traditional barriers that divide the roles of civilians and combatants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look out! Divergent representations are everywhere!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103122</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/11/10/divergent-representations-variable-overflows-c-compiler/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T12:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Andreas Kellas Trail of Bits recently published a blog post about a signed integer overflow in certain versions of SQLite that can enable arbitrary code execution and result in a denial of service. While working on proof-of-concept exploits for that vulnerability, we noticed that the compiler’s representation of an important integer variable is semantically […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tobgreg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use splatting and PSBoundParameters to pass parameters in PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568608</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/use-splatting-and-psboundparameters-to-pass-parameters-in-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T02:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The automatic variable PSBoundParameters stores the parameters that you explicitly passed to a function in a hash table. With the help of splatting, you can use this PowerShell feature to simplify passing of parameters to functions.
Use splatting and PSBoundParameters to pass parameters in PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffery Hicks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: pdf-parser.py Version 0.7.7]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9669</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/10/update-pdf-parser-py-version-0-7-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a small update: you can now select which hash algorithm to use for option -H by setting environment variable DSS_DEFAULT_HASH_ALGORITHMS. And the statistics options (-a) also display a list of objects with streams. pdf-parser_V0_7_7.zip (http)MD5: BCAE193F171184F979603DFB1380FF43SHA256: 576C429FA88CF0A7A110DAB25851D90670C88EC4CD7728329E754E06D8D26A70]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Certificates and Pwnage and Patches, Oh My!]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8ae0f4304c1d</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/certificates-and-pwnage-and-patches-oh-my-8ae0f4304c1d?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO EXCELS IN MITRE ATT&CK® MANAGED SERVICES EVALUATION]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12916</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/11/09/nviso-excels-in-mitre-attck-managed-services-evaluation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As one of the only EU-based Cyber Security companies, NVISO successfully participated in a first-of-its-kind, MITRE-led, evaluation of Managed Security Services (MSS). The inaugural MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK® Evaluations for Managed Security Services ran in June 2022 and its results have been published today. NVISO performed excellently in the evaluation, demonstrating services that are at or … Continue reading NVISO EXCELS IN MITRE ATT&CK® MANAGED SERVICES EVALUATION →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Tischer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting web message misconfigurations for cross-domain credential theft]]></title>
        <id>detecting-web-message-misconfigurations-for-cross-domain-credential-theft</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/detecting-web-message-misconfigurations-for-cross-domain-credential-theft"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We released a new version of Burp recently on the Early Adopter channel that updates DOM Invader to help find cross-domain secrets. In this post we are going to show you how to use DOM Invader to dete]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visualizing MISP Threat Intelligence in Power BI – An NVISO TI Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12719</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/11/09/visualizing-misp-threat-intelligence-in-power-bi-an-nviso-ti-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T13:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog we will explain how to use the functionality of Power BI to visualize your MISP data in a interactive and useful way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Nixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales of Windows detection opportunities for an implant framework]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=17946</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/11/09/tales-of-windows-detection-opportunities-for-an-implant-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T09:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slides from a fifteen minute lightening talk on detection opportunities for implant framework behaviour on Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Whitehouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud-based patch management with Action1]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568594</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/cloud-based-patch-management-with-action1/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T05:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Action1 cloud-native platform provides IT teams with powerful patch management features and is free for the first 100 endpoints.
Cloud-based patch management with Action1 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The November 2022 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6369b7f687c1821a09667d41</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/11/8/the-november-2022-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the penultimate Patch Tuesday of 2021. As expected, Adobe and Microsoft have released their latest security updates and fixes to the world. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security offerings.
Adobe Patches for November 2022
For November, Adobe released no patches at all. They’ve released as few as one in the past, but this is the first month in the last six years where they had no fixes at all. Perhaps the U.S. elections play a factor, as Patch Tuesday hasn’t fallen on Election Day since 2016. Whatever the cause, enjoy a month of no Adobe updates.
Microsoft Patches for November 2022
This month, Microsoft released 64 new patches addressing CVEs in Microsoft Windows and Windows Components; Azure and Azure R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inspector, or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Testing in Prod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4276</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/inspector-prod-testing-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T16:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Recently, I’ve shifted from primarily performing red team engagements to assisting in the development of Chariot, Praetorian’s attack surface management (ASM) and continuous automated red teaming (CART) product offering. Our Praetorian Labs team has developed multiple tools to support Chariot and our Services organization. One of these, a subsystem for the core asset enumeration […]
The post Inspector, or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Testing in Prod appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Can Be the Hero or Villain of Your Cybersecurity Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15732</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/reporting-can-be-the-hero-or-villain-of-your-cybersecurity-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T16:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting is a critical but often-overlooked component of cybersecurity testing The overall goals of nearly any technology can be summed up by the title of a song by the popular French music duo Daft Punk: “Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger.” New technologies are commonly judged against two or more of these characteristics. Applying this to cybersecurity […]
The post Reporting Can Be the Hero or Villain of Your Cybersecurity Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We sign code now]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103080</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/11/08/sigstore-code-signing-verification-software-supply-chain/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T12:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William Woodruff Sigstore announced the general availability of its free and ecosystem-agnostic software signing service two weeks ago, giving developers a way to sign, verify and protect their software projects and the dependencies they rely on. Trail of Bits is absolutely thrilled to be a part of the project, and we spoke about our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install, remove, list, and set default printer with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1568575</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-remove-list-and-set-default-printer-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T03:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With PowerShell, you can easily install a printer driver, add a printer to the repository, and then add a local or shared network printer to your Windows installation. In this post, I will also explain how you can list printers, add a printer port, set the default printer, and remove a printer with PowerShell.
Install, remove, list, and set default printer with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emanuel Halapciuc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocGholish Diversifies and Expands Its Malware Staging Infrastructure to Counter Defenders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=73094</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/socgholish-diversifies-and-expands-its-malware-staging-infrastructure-to-counter-defenders/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T13:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SocGholish operators continue to infect websites at a massive scale, and the threat actor is ramping up its infrastructure to match.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Testing A USB Fridge]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9650</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/11/06/quickpost-testing-a-usb-fridge/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T14:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple years ago, I received a USB fridge from NVISO’s Secret Santa. It uses a Peltier element with a fan. I did the following test: overnight, I let the fridge run for 12 hours. It contained an Aluminum can filled with water at room temperature (around 17° C). I used a power meter to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, No Case Studies—But . . .]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e7cf012af19807518fba2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/sorry-no-case-study"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend of the site recently suggested that we create a current-issue case 
study using our updated risk discovery approach. “It’s a great idea,” we 
replied and immediately started kicking around ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pointillism of Daily Events]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2c8f009baa12346d3711f</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/pointillism-daily-events"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Baker’s book Human Smoke brilliantly illustrates a unique approach 
to historical narrative. It also underscores the need to remember that 
every artist paints with intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ready for What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2aa91391dcb70804f9850</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/getting-ready-whats-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new age of giant monsters, advanced awareness of classical 
surprise—that one big tipping moment—no longer suffices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Your ‘Free Cells’ Mindfully]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62deb6110fd7f314e5696ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/manage-free-cells"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accommodate but don’t fight the limitations you can’t control, recognize 
those you can influence and leverage, and don't imagine you have more free 
cells than you actually do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popski’s Planning]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d81b5affdc983dd1f616f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/popskis-planning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British officer Vladimir Peniakoff’s approach to planning might sound a bit 
unorthodox at first, but it aligns nicely with Patton’s view of 
intelligence and speaks to an enduring need to understand front-line 
conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a New Game Board]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d5b6db0343fb487527fc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/time-for-a-new-game-board"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need a more flexible game board where players can explore hypergame 
strategies—in other words, a game board where the strategist can play the 
hero for a change. We’ve built it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survivors Exceeded the Minimum]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62cf11283f1bdb1191fcdf9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/survivors-exceeded-minimum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T18:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every surprise is a cunning thunderbolt. Some surprises creep up 
slowly, rusting away former resilience until a simple nudge reveals the 
rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>