<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-02-25T00:37:31.183Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Risk of AI Voice Cloning: Q&A With an AI Hacker]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/voice-cloning-qa</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/voice-cloning-qa"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne Senior Solutions Architect and AI Hacker Dane Sherrets demonstrates how bad actors are using AI voice cloning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dane Sherrets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install the new Teams client: bulk installer, policies, changes from the classic client, system prerequisites]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1580066</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-the-new-teams-client-bulk-installer-policies-changes-from-the-classic-client-system-prerequisites/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users will gradually receive the new Teams client depending on the license and update channel. Microsoft now offers a bulk installer for businesses looking to migrate to the new version. Subsequently, admins can enforce a specific client for users using a policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuously fuzzing Python C extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106536</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/23/continuously-fuzzing-python-c-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Matt Schwager Deserializing, decoding, and processing untrusted input are telltale signs that your project would benefit from fuzzing. Yes, even Python projects. Fuzzing helps reduce bugs in high-assurance software developed in all programming languages. Fortunately for the Python ecosystem, Google has released Atheris, a coverage-guided fuzzer for both pure Python code and Python C […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice for manufacturers on the coming PSTI regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28847</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/advice-for-manufacturers-on-the-coming-psti-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T06:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR PSTI: The UK Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure (Product Security) Act Regulations effective from 29 April 2024 Assess how, where, why, and when you may be affected Review supply […]
Advice for manufacturers on the coming PSTI regulation first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jo Dalton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini: Planting Instructions For Delayed Automatic Tool Invocation]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/llm-context-pollution-and-delayed-automated-tool-invocation/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/llm-context-pollution-and-delayed-automated-tool-invocation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T06:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last November, while testing Google Bard (now called Gemini) for vulnerabilities, I had a couple of interesting observations when it comes to automatic tool invocation.
Confused Deputy - Automatic Tool Invocation First, what do I mean by this… “automatic tool invocation”…
Consider the following scenario: An attacker sends a malicious email to a user containing instructions to call an external tool. Google named these tools Extensions.
When the user analyzes the email with an LLM, it interprets the instructions and calls the external tool, leading to a kind of request forgery or maybe better called automatic tool invocation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unmasking Lorenz Ransomware: A Dive into Recent Tactics, Techniques and Procedures]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34096</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/02/22/unmasking-lorenz-ransomware-a-dive-into-recent-tactics-techniques-and-procedures/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T16:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zaid Baksh In the ever-evolving landscape of cyber threats, ransomware remains a persistent menace, with groups like Lorenz actively exploiting vulnerabilities in small to medium businesses globally. Since early 2021, Lorenz has been employing double-extortion tactics, exfiltrating sensitive data before encrypting systems and threatening to sell or release it publicly unless a ransom is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Global Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Dev Drive in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1580086</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-dev-drive-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T13:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dev Drive is a new feature in Windows 11 23H2, also included in the preview of Windows Server 2025. It is a drive based on ReFS, specifically designed for the requirements of developers and IT professionals. It offers enhanced control over volume settings and file system filters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doppelgänger | Russia-Aligned Influence Operation Targets Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=92023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/doppelganger-russia-aligned-influence-operation-targets-germany/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T13:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doppelgänger, a sophisticated Russia-aligned operation, targets German public opinion with disinformation ahead of elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCCM Hierarchy Takeover with High Availability]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7dcbd3696b43</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/sccm-hierarchy-takeover-with-high-availability-7dcbd3696b43?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T20:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Garrett Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unmasking I-Soon | The Leak That Revealed China’s Cyber Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=91854</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/unmasking-i-soon-the-leak-that-revealed-chinas-cyber-operations/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaked over the weekend of Feb 16th, I-Soon, a contractor for PRC agencies, shows the maturing nature of China’s cyber espionage. Despite undetermined authenticity, leaks reveal targeting of 14 governments and NATO, highlighting a competitive hacker marketplace driven by government demands]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dakota Cary &amp; Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Windows 11 Start menu with Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579909</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configure-windows-11-start-menu-with-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T12:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most noticeable innovations of Windows 11 is the redesigned Start menu. This changes not only its appearance but also its technical foundations. However, the settings in the Group Policy have remained mainly the same, so it is unclear which ones still apply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No fix KrbRelay VMware style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28851</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/no-fix-krbrelay-vmware-style/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T06:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The VMware Enhanced Authentication plugin that is offered as part of VMware vSphere’s seamless login experience for the web console contains multiple vulnerabilities relating to Kerberos authentication relay. The […]
No fix KrbRelay VMware style first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's New in FOR500: Windows Forensic Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/whats-new-in-for500-windows-forensic-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/whats-new-in-for500-windows-forensic-analysis?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Course updates focus on testing and documenting significant changes across the Windows ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Chasing Shadows |  The Rise of a Prolific Espionage Actor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=91867</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-chasing-shadows-the-rise-of-a-prolific-espionage-actor/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T21:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris McConkey at LABSCon23 revealed the rise of a cyber espionage 'superpower,' impacting 35+ countries with sophisticated tools like ShadowPad. This actor's evolution signals a growing cyber threat landscape]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding the Characteristics of Modern Pentesting: Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/modern-pentesting-speed</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/modern-pentesting-speed"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T19:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne pentest experts explore the "Speed" factor of effective pentesting methods to see how each security testing alternative measures up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the shared key in threshold signature schemes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106469</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/20/breaking-the-shared-key-in-threshold-signature-schemes/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T14:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Fredrik Dahlgren Today we are disclosing a denial-of-service vulnerability that affects the Pedersen distributed key generation (DKG) phase of a number of threshold signature scheme implementations based on the Frost, DMZ21, GG20, and GG18 protocols. The vulnerability allows a single malicious participant to surreptitiously raise the threshold required to reconstruct the shared key, which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Miorcec</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade Python in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579951</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/upgrade-python-in-windows/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will explain the four ways to upgrade to a new version of Python on a Windows system: installer, Microsoft Store, Winget, and Chocolatey. You will also learn how to use different versions of Python on your system and how to uninstall an old version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AS-REP Roasting]]></title>
        <id>http://pentestlab.blog/?p=32547</id>
        <link href="https://pentestlab.blog/2024/02/20/as-rep-roasting/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T07:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory users that have the Kerberos pre-authentication enabled and require access to a resource initiate the Kerberos authentication process by sending an Authentication Server… 
Continue reading → AS-REP Roasting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Administrator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber security for Credit Unions 101]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28829</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/cyber-security-for-credit-unions-101/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T06:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American consumers have two clear yet vastly differing choices when it comes to banking. Many opt for a large-sized national or regional bank. Folks select this option for a variety […]
Cyber security for Credit Unions 101 first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Leonard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tale of the Three *ishings: Part 1 – What is Phishing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-tale-of-the-three-ishings-part-1-what-is-phishing</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-tale-of-the-three-ishings-part-1-what-is-phishing?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part one of a three-part blog series about the different types of phishing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial Control Systems Cyber Threats and the Gulf Region – ICS Blog Series: 2 of 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/industrial-control-systems-cyber-threats-and-the-gulf-region-ics-blog-series-2-of-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/industrial-control-systems-cyber-threats-and-the-gulf-region-ics-blog-series-2-of-3?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about industrial control systems cyber threats and the gulf region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 web hacking techniques of 2023]]></title>
        <id>top-10-web-hacking-techniques-of-2023</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/top-10-web-hacking-techniques-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T14:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Top 10 Web Hacking Techniques of 2023, the 17th edition of our annual community-powered effort to identify the most innovative must-read web security research published in the last year]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free access to an enhanced ChatGPT 4 for 4sysops members]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1580011</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/free-access-to-an-enhanced-chatgpt-4-for-4sysops-members/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T13:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members can now enjoy free access to 4sysops AI powered by ChatGPT 4 (GPT-4 Turbo). 4sysops AI is a continuously updated and does not have a cutoff date of April 2023 like ChatGPT. As you may be aware, the free version of ChatGPT only supports ChatGPT 3.5, while the paid membership of ChatGPT Plus, which costs $20 per month, provides access to ChatGPT 4 (GPT-4). 4sysops members can now access the Turbo version of ChatGPT 4 for free, which is faster than the standard ChatGPT 4 available with the Plus subscription.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzer Development: Sandboxing Syscalls]]></title>
        <id>https://h0mbre.github.io/Lucid_Context_Switching/</id>
        <link href="https://h0mbre.github.io/Lucid_Context_Switching/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction If you haven’t heard, we’re developing a fuzzer on the blog these days. I don’t even know if “fuzzer” is the right word for what we’re building, it’s almost more like an execution engine that will expose hooks? Anyways, if you missed the first episode you can catch up here. We are creating a fuzzer that loads a statically built Bochs emulator into itself, and executes Bochs logic while maintaining a sandbox for Bochs. You can think of it as, we were too lazy to implement our own x86_64 emulator from scratch so we’ve just literally taken a complete emulator and stuffed it into our own process to use it. The fuzzer is written in Rust and Bochs is a C++ codebase. Bochs is a full system emulator, so the devices and everything else is just simulated in software. This is great for us because we can simply snapshot and restore Bochs itself to achieve snapshot fuzzing of our target. So the fuzzer runs Bochs and Bochs runs our target. This allows us to snapshot fuzz arbitrarily complex targets: web browsers, kernels, network stacks, etc. This episode, we’ll delve into the concept of sandboxing Bochs from syscalls. We do not want Bochs to be capable of escaping its sandbox or retrieving any data from outside of our environment. So today we’ll get into the implementation details of my first stab at Bochs-to-fuzzer context switching to handle syscalls. In the future we will also need to implement context switching from fuzzer-to-Bochs as well, but for now let’s focus on syscalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Human Machine Interface</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Dangerous Entra Role You’ve (Probably) Never Heard Of]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e00ea08b8661</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/the-most-dangerous-entra-role-youve-probably-never-heard-of-e00ea08b8661?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T16:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entra ID has a built-in role called “Partner Tier2 Support” that enables escalation to Global Admin, but this role is hidden from view in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harmonizing Security and User Experience: A Modern Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=52385</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/harmonizing-security-and-user-experience-a-modern-approach/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inevitably, organizations get to a point where it becomes challenging to impose increased security measures on their end users because the advancements would have too large an impact on their daily convenience and usability. Orchestration capabilities for identity and access management (IAM) products have allowed security teams to enhance their security measures. It’s a service […]
The post Harmonizing Security and User Experience: A Modern Approach appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Swanson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Programa de Interns de Bishop Fox: Foxes de México Assemble!]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/el-programa-de-interns-de-bishop-fox-foxes-de-méxico-assemble</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/el-programa-de-interns-de-bishop-fox-foxes-de-m%C3%A9xico-assemble"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En Bishop Fox, siempre estamos buscando crear la próxima generación de Avengers de la seguridad ofensiva a través de nuestro innovador internship program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lesley Mugford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few notes on AWS Nitro Enclaves: Images and attestation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106380</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/16/a-few-notes-on-aws-nitro-enclaves-images-and-attestation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T14:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Paweł Płatek (GrosQuildu) AWS Nitro Enclaves are locked-down virtual machines with support for attestation. They are Trusted Execution Environments (TEEs), similar to Intel SGX, making them useful for running highly security-critical code. However, the AWS Nitro Enclaves platform lacks thorough documentation and mature tooling. So we decided to do some deep research into it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Windows 11 Copilot is not working]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579879</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/if-windows-11-copilot-is-not-working/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T13:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent blog article, we discussed enabling or disabling Windows Copilot in Windows and Edge. One of the most common problems reported by end users is the fact that Windows 11 Copilot is not available or not working. In this blog article, I will go through various issues you might face and explain how to solve them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Three-Slide Executive Presentation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/three-slide-executive-presentation</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/three-slide-executive-presentation?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn all about the newly updated Security Strategic Planning, Policy, and Leadership Course; LDR514.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How an Improper Access Control Vulnerability Led to Account Theft in One Click]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/improper-access-control-deep-dive</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/improper-access-control-deep-dive"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s look more closely at the improper access control vulnerability type — what it is, how it’s used, and how to remediate it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bishop Fox Internship Program: Mexico Foxes Assemble!]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/the-bishop-fox-internship-program-mexico-foxes-assemble</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/the-bishop-fox-internship-program-mexico-foxes-assemble"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about our internship program for Mexico-based penetration testers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lesley Mugford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNS Sender | Active Campaigns Unleash Messaging Spam Through the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=91745</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/sns-sender-active-campaigns-unleash-messaging-spam-through-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T13:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors leverage cloud services to conduct massive smishing campaign through AWS Simple Notification Service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edit JSON config files with free JSON editors or Notepad++]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579759</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/edit-json-config-files-with-free-json-editors-or-notepad/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T12:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) is gaining popularity as a format for configuration files. Unlike XML or the still-used INI format, editing JSON in a text editor can be tedious and error-prone. However, there are free JSON editors and plugins for Notepad++ that simplify this task.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QR Phishing. Fact or Fiction?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28801</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/qr-phishing-fact-or-fiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T06:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2023’s Cyber Security Awareness Month  led to a flurry of blog posts about a new attack called Quishing (QR Code phishing) and how new AI powered email gateways can […]
QR Phishing. Fact or Fiction? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Gee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADCS ESC13 Abuse Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/fda4272fbd53</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/adcs-esc13-abuse-technique-fda4272fbd53?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is possible to configure an Active Directory Certificate Services (ADCS) certificate template with an issuance policy having an OID…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bülow Knudsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud cryptography demystified: Amazon Web Services]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106337</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/14/cloud-cryptography-demystified-amazon-web-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T14:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Scott Arciszewski This post, part of a series on cryptography in the cloud, provides an overview of the cloud cryptography services offered within Amazon Web Services (AWS): when to use them, when not to use them, and important usage considerations. Stay tuned for future posts covering other cloud services. At Trail of Bits, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling Proper PCI Testing with External Penetration Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/enabling-proper-pci-testing-with-external-penetration-tests</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/enabling-proper-pci-testing-with-external-penetration-tests"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain actionable insights on how to maximize external penetration testing to develop comprehensive PCI security strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Rush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT: Lack of Isolation between Code Interpreter sessions of GPTs]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/lack-of-isolation-gpts-code-interpreter/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/lack-of-isolation-gpts-code-interpreter/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T11:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your Code Interpreter sandbox, also known as Advanced Data Analysis sessions, are shared between private and public GPTs. Yes, your actual compute container and its storage is shared. Each user gets their own isolated container, but if a user uses multiple GPTs and stores files in Code Interpreter all GPTs can access (and also overwrite) each others files.
This is true also for files uploaded/created with private GPTs and ChatGPT itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add Azure AD group to local administrators group]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579781</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/add-local-azure-ad-group-to-local-administrators-group/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T11:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will explore adding an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) group to the local administrator's group. This will enable Azure AD group members to perform tasks requiring administrator privileges on Windows 10 and Windows 11 computers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammed Kaif Joey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delegated NT DLL]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5373</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/02/13/delegated-nt-dll/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction redplait and Adam/Hexacorn already documented this in 2017 and 2018 respectively, so it’s not a new discovery. Officially available since RedStone 2 released in April 2017, redplait states it was introduced with insider build 15007 released in January 2017. … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Kubernetes through Operator Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5596</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/exploiting-kubernetes-through-operator-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T19:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro The Kubernetes documentation describes operators as “software extensions to Kubernetes that use custom resources to manage applications and their components.” These operators automate application resource deployment and management with custom controllers tied to one or more custom resource definitions. Custom controllers create bespoke attack surfaces that attackers can target when they can control custom resource data. […]
The post Exploiting Kubernetes through Operator Injection appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-23724:  Ghost CMS Stored XSS Leading to Owner Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25006</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/cve-2024-23724-ghost-cms-stored-xss/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CVE-2024-23724: 
 Ghost CMS Stored XSS Leading to Owner Takeover appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Ramsbey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing Windows Event Logs with Security Onion]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579667</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/analyzing-windows-event-logs-with-security-onion/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T10:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security Onion is an open-source platform for threat hunting, security monitoring, and log management. It aggregates free tools such as Kibana, Elastic Fleet, InfluxDB, CyberChef, and Suricata. The solution provides access to these tools via a web console. I'll demonstrate how it can be used for analyzing Windows logs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Content Providers 101]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28780</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/android-content-providers-101/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T06:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Android has a number of different types of components that a program or app can instantiate to interact with the user or other programs. Recently I’ve been looking at […]
Android Content Providers 101 first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Lodge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: ASCII Smuggling and Hidden Prompt Instructions]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/ascii-smuggling-and-hidden-prompt-instructions/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/ascii-smuggling-and-hidden-prompt-instructions/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T01:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of weeks ago hidden prompt injections were discovered and we covered it at the time.
This video explains it in more detail, and also highlights implications beyond hiding instructions, including what I call ASCII Smuggling. This is the usage of Unicode Tags Block characters to both craft and deciper hidden messages in plain sight.
   Using Unicode encoding to bypass security features or execute code (XSS, SSRF,.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Directory.ReadWrite.All Is Not As Powerful As You Might Think]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c5b09a8f78a8</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/directory-readwrite-all-is-not-as-powerful-as-you-might-think-c5b09a8f78a8?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Directory.ReadWrite.All is an MS Graph permission that is frequently cited as granting high amounts of privilege, even being equated to the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The February 2024 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:65ca3647c5a8bc4523376b05</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/2/13/the-february-2024-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T15:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second patch Tuesday of the year, and Adobe and Microsoft have released a fresh crop of security updates just in time to be our Valentine. Take a break from your other activities and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. For those interested in the Microsoft 0-day discovered by the ZDI Threat Hunting Team, you can watch this special edition of the Patch Report:
If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check out here:
Adobe Patches for February 2024
For February, Adobe released six patches addressing 29 CVEs in Adobe Acrobat and Reader, Commerce, Substance 3D Painter, FrameMaker Publishing Server, Audition, and Substance 3D Designer. A total of four of these bugs were reported through the ZDI program. If you need to prio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Windows can’t follow WSL symlinks]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106300</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/12/why-windows-cant-follow-wsl-symlinks/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T14:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Yarden Shafir Did you know that symbolic links (or symlinks) created through Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) can’t be followed by Windows? I recently encountered this rather frustrating issue as I’ve been using WSL for my everyday work over the last few months. No doubt others have noticed it as well, so I wanted […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Cyber Revenge | Why the PRC Fails to Back Its Claims of Western Espionage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=88775</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/chinas-cyber-revenge-why-the-prc-fails-to-back-its-claims-of-western-espionage/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T11:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's claims of hacks and espionage lack the rigorous technical detail seen in western threat intel. Why the asymmetry, and how does it benefit the PRC?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dakota Cary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Firefox proxy settings with Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579677</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configure-firefox-proxy-settings-with-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T10:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to centrally manage proxy settings for the Mozilla browser in a network, a Group Policy is available. Unlike Google Chrome or Microsoft Edge, Firefox cannot only inherit the proxy configuration from Windows but can also receive it directly via GPO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory Enumeration for Red Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3370</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2024/02/active-directory-enumeration-for-red-teams/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T09:49:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Directory Service is the heart and soul of many organisations, and whether its Active Directory, OpenLDAP or something more exotic, as a source of much knowledge it often acts...
The post Active Directory Enumeration for Red Teams appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving the Human Risk Problem: Engaging and Securing Your Workforce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/solving-the-human-risk-problem-engaging-and-securing-your-workforce</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/solving-the-human-risk-problem-engaging-and-securing-your-workforce?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about solving the human risk problem through leadership's management of human risk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An example of using PowerShell to manage system and user-assigned managed identities in Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579691</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/an-example-of-using-powershell-to-manage-system-and-user-assigned-managed-identities-in-azure/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T14:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managed identities provide secure authentication for resources accessing other resources in Azure without requiring sensitive information such as secrets, credentials, and certificates to be handled. Microsoft Entra ID manages these identities, enabling applications to obtain tokens for authentication. In this post, I will provide an example that illustrates how to use system and user-assigned managed identities with PowerShell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master fuzzing with our new Testing Handbook chapter]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106293</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/09/master-fuzzing-with-our-new-testing-handbook-chapter/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our latest addition to the Trail of Bits Testing Handbook is a comprehensive guide to fuzzing: an essential, effective, low-effort method to find bugs in software that involves repeatedly running a program with random inputs to cause unexpected results. At Trail of Bits, we don’t just rely on standard static analysis. We tailor our approach […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puckungfu 2: Another NETGEAR WAN Command Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33888</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/02/09/puckungfu-2-another-netgear-wan-command-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A story on finding a zero day attacking the NETGEAR WAN interface after a last minute patch for Pwn2Own 2022, involving a command injection, predicting random numbers, boot timing and voltage supply variations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>McCaulay Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sudo On Windows a Quick Rundown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2024/02/sudo-on-windows-quick-rundown.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2024/02/sudo-on-windows-quick-rundown.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background
The Windows Insider Preview build 26052 just shipped with a sudo command, I thought I'd just take a quick peek to see what it does and how it does it. This is only a short write up of my findings, I think this code is probably still in early stages so I wouldn't want it to be treated too harshly. You can see the official announcement here.

To run a command using sudo you can just type:

C:\> sudo powershell.exe

The first thing to note, if you know anything about the security model of Windows (maybe buy my book, hint hint), is that there's no equivalent to SUID binaries. The only way to run a process with a higher privilege level is to get an existing higher privileged process to start it for you or you have sufficient permissions yourself though say SeImpersonatePrivilege or S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyranid's Lair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Chapter Unfolds: SecureAuth Announces Acquisition of Cloudentity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=52358</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/a-new-chapter-unfolds-secureauth-announces-acquisition-of-cloudentity/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to share some groundbreaking news that marks a significant milestone in our journey: SecureAuth has officially acquired Cloudentity. This strategic move represents a powerful step forward in our commitment to innovation, growth, and delivering unparalleled value to our customers and stakeholders.  A Vision Fulfilled  At SecureAuth, our mission has been to redefine […]
The post A New Chapter Unfolds: SecureAuth Announces Acquisition of Cloudentity appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Swanson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden Prompt Injections with Anthropic Claude]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/claude-hidden-prompt-injection-ascii-smuggling/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/claude-hidden-prompt-injection-ascii-smuggling/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago while waiting at the airport lounge I was wondering how other Chatbots, besides ChatGPT, handle hidden Unicode Tags code points.
A quick reminder: Unicode Tags code points are invisible in UI elements, but ChatGPT was able to interpret them and follow hidden instructions. Riley Goodside discovered it.
What about Anthropic Claude? While waiting for a flight I figured to look at Anthropic Claude. Turns out it has the same issue as ChatGPT had.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Docker with VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579725</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-docker-with-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T09:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can manage Docker images and containers directly within Visual Studio Code (VS Code) with Microsoft's Docker extension. This article walks you through adding Docker files to a Workspace, creating a containerized application environment, and explains how to build and run Docker containers directly from the VS Code interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new with BChecks?]]></title>
        <id>whats-new-with-bchecks</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/whats-new-with-bchecks"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T09:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, we released BChecks, a powerful yet simple scripting language that allows you to quickly build and create custom scan checks for anything you want to secure or test. We've already h]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report: Aleo snarkOS Implementation and Consensus Mechanism Review]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34006</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/02/08/public-report-aleo-snarkos-implementation-and-consensus-mechanism-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2023, Aleo engaged NCC Group’s Cryptography Services team to perform a review of the consensus mechanism implemented by snarkOS: “a decentralized operating system for zero-knowledge applications [that] forms the backbone of Aleo network, which verifies transactions and stores the encrypted state applications in a publicly verifiable manner.” The consensus mechanism is based on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Henry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Webs — Unveiling Arachne for Web Shell C2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/26c40f570ea1</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/spinning-webs-unveiling-arachne-for-web-shell-c2-26c40f570ea1?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T16:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Shell Agent for Mythic C2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cody Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing AI Application Threat Models]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33981</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/02/07/analyzing-ai-application-threat-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T14:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract The following analysis explores the paradigm and security implications of machine learning integration into application architectures, with emphasis on Large Language Models (LLMs). Machine learning models occupy the positions of assets, controls, and threat actors within the threat model of these platforms, and this paper aims to analyze new threat vectors introduced by this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nccdavid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary type inference in Ghidra]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106242</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/07/binary-type-inference-in-ghidra/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Ian Smith Trail of Bits is releasing BTIGhidra, a Ghidra extension that helps reverse engineers by inferring type information from binaries. The analysis is inter-procedural, propagating and resolving type constraints between functions while consuming user input to recover additional type information. This refined type information produces more idiomatic decompilation, enhancing reverse engineering comprehension. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Must-Listen Top Cybersecurity Podcasts]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/must-listen-top-cybersecurity-podcasts</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/must-listen-top-cybersecurity-podcasts"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interested in finding new ways to learn about the cybersecurity industry? Check this list of our must-listen top podcasts to hear from industry leading experts!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create bootable ISO for Windows image (.wim)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579601</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-bootable-iso-for-windows-image-wim/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T08:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before deploying to clients, you should update a Windows image with the latest patches and customize it to meet their needs. Depending on the deployment method, you need to provide the WIM archive on a bootable ISO file. This can be created using the tools from the Windows Assessment and Deployment Kit (ADK).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ski & bike helmets protect your head, not location or voice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28796</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/ski-bike-helmets-protect-your-head-not-location-or-voice/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T06:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Livall smart ski and bike helmet app leaks the wearers real time position Group audio chat allows snooping on conversations Both issues are due to missing authorisation Bike app […]
Ski & bike helmets protect your head, not location or voice first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn and Joe Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Infrastructure Cyber Threats & The UK Region]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/critical-infrastructure-cyber-threats-the-uk-region</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/critical-infrastructure-cyber-threats-the-uk-region?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mature ICS facilities in the region realize and embrace the differences between IT and ICS/OT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use AI Prompting for Security Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/how-to-use-ai-prompting</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/how-to-use-ai-prompting"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zahra Putri Fitrianti explores the power of AI prompting for security vulnerabilities at HackerOne.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zahra Putri Fitrianti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-46263: Ivanti Avalanche Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:65c118b841f5744c57206991</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/2/5/cve-2023-46263-ivanti-avalanche-arbitrary-file-upload-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Lucas Miller and Dusan Stevanovic of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in the Ivanti Avalanche enterprise mobility management program. Other Ivanti products have recently been under active exploitation, and the mobile device management system is an attractive target. This bug was originally reported to the ZDI program by an anonymous researcher and was also discovered by Lucas Miller of Trend Micro Research. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an authenticated attacker to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2023-46263, with a few minimal modifications.
An arbitrary f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulating complex networks with GNS3]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579656</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/simulating-complex-networks-with-gns3/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T10:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The free Graphical Network Simulator-3 (GNS3) allows for the planning and practical simulation of networks and their topology. Thanks to Dynamips, it also supports integrating images of Cisco IOS. GNS3 can be integrated with physical hardware, enabling, for instance, the testing of monitoring solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Adding Icons To Windows Based Executables Compiled In Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2d5383b940d7</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-adding-icons-to-windows-based-executables-compiled-in-linux-2d5383b940d7?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T18:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all! So, today we’re going to go over something that I haven’t seen anywhere else. This isn’t some super secret task, but when I went to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a Secure, Random Password with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.hboeck.de/archives/907-guid.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.hboeck.de/archives/907-How-to-create-a-Secure,-Random-Password-with-JavaScript.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T14:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>nospam@example.com (Hanno Böck)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving the state of Cosmos fuzzing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106206</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/05/improving-the-state-of-cosmos-fuzzing/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T14:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Gustavo Grieco Cosmos is a platform enabling the creation of blockchains in Go (or other languages). Its reference implementation, Cosmos SDK, leverages strong fuzz testing extensively, following two approaches: smart fuzzing for low-level code, and dumb fuzzing for high-level simulation. In this blog post, we explain the differences between these approaches and show how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Zero Day – Threat Actors observed leveraging CVE-2021-42278 and CVE-2021-42287 for quick privilege escalation to Domain Admin]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33968</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/02/05/ivanti-zero-day-threat-actors-observed-leveraging-cve-2021-42278-and-cve-2021-42287-for-quick-privilege-escalation-to-domain-admin/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T13:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: David Brown and Mungomba Mulenga TL;dr NCC Group has observed what we believe to be the attempted exploitation of CVE-2021-42278 and CVE-2021-42287 as a means of privilege escalation, following the successful compromise of an Ivanti Secure Connect VPN using the following zero-day vulnerabilities reported by Volexity1 on 10/01/2024: By combining these vulnerabilities threat actors […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Global Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build your own ChatGPT app]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579625</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/build-your-own-chatgpt-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T09:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post on the OpenAI API, I introduced a simple chatbot that demonstrated how to interact with the API. In this post, I will take it a step further by showing you how to create your own ChatGPT app. You may be wondering why you need your own ChatGPT app when you can use the OpenAI web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persistence – Windows Setup Script]]></title>
        <id>http://pentestlab.blog/?p=32525</id>
        <link href="https://pentestlab.blog/2024/02/05/persistence-windows-setup-script/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T05:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Windows Operating system is installed via a clean installation or via an upgrade, the Windows Setup binary is executed. The Windows setup allows… 
Continue reading → Persistence – Windows Setup Script]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Administrator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Breach — How Can I See This In BloodHound?]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/33c92dca4c65</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/microsoft-breach-how-can-i-see-this-in-bloodhound-33c92dca4c65?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T21:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Attack Paths from Foreign Principals in BloodHound]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Hinck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Breach — What Happened? What Should Azure Admins Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/da2b7e674ebc</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/microsoft-breach-what-happened-what-should-azure-admins-do-da2b7e674ebc?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T21:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 25, 2024, Microsoft published a blog post that detailed their recent breach at the hands of “Midnight Blizzard”. In this blog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chaos Communication Congress (37C3) recap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/02/02/chaos-communication-congress-37c3-recap/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T14:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, two of our engineers attended the 37th Chaos Communication Congress (37C3) in Hamburg, joining thousands of hackers who gather each year to exchange the latest research and achievements in technology and security. Unlike other tech conferences, this annual gathering focuses on the interaction of technology and society, covering such topics as politics, entertainment, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing custom scan checks to Burp Suite Enterprise Edition]]></title>
        <id>introducing-custom-scan-checks-to-burp-suite-enterprise-edition</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/introducing-custom-scan-checks-to-burp-suite-enterprise-edition"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T11:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BChecks, in a nutshell, are easy to use custom-created scan checks that enable you to extend the capabilities of Burp Scanner in a quick and simple way. We recently released BChecks to Burp Suite Prof]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuning Ceph performance]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579592</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/tuning-ceph-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T09:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuning Ceph performance is crucial to ensure that your Ceph storage cluster operates efficiently and meets the specific requirements of your workload. As Ceph installations, both in software and hardware, are upgraded or as your workload changes, the default tunables that were optimal at one time may now be obsolete or counterproductive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evi Vanoost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unmanaged .NET Patching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=3662</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2024/02/01/unmanaged-dotnet-patching/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To execute .NET post-exploitation tools safely, operators may want to modify certain managed functions. For example, some C# tools use the .NET standard library to terminate their process after execution. This may not be an issue for fork&run implementations that spawn a sacrificial process, but executing in-process will terminate an implant. One could write a small .NET program that resolves and patches these functions, but we were interested in an unmanaged approach (i.e. a unmanaged implant executing managed code in-process). While our example targets System.Environment.Exit, a similar technique should work for any managed function.

In January 2022, I uploaded a functional example of this approach to my personal GitHub. However, the implementation was a part of a larger project, and I’ve received a few questions about the technique, so I created this standalone example and writeup.
Tags: dotnet
Read full post
The post Unmanaged .NET Patching appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Avery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add updates (.msu) offline into Windows images (.wim)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579517</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/add-updates-msu-offline-into-windows-images-wim/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T12:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before deployment, Microsoft ISO's install .wim or custom images should be updated. With the DISM module in PowerShell, you can add .msu updates, apps, and drivers to a Windows image offline without the need to boot it up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking Electronic Flight Bags. Airbus NAVBLUE Flysmart+ Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27909</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/hacking-electronic-flight-bags-airbus-navblue-flysmart-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T06:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been testing the security of a number of different electronic flight bag, or EFB, applications for a few years now. Here’s the latest on that now it has been […]
Hacking Electronic Flight Bags. Airbus NAVBLUE Flysmart+ Manager first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Cassidy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relution Remote Code Execution via Java Deserialization Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5532</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/relution-remote-code-execution-java-deserialization-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T03:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In this article we discuss a recent deserialization vulnerability we found in Relution (CVE-2023-48178), a mobile device management product that is popular among multinational German corporations. CVE-2023-48178 can potentially lead to remote code execution and complete compromise of the MDM application and clients managed by the solution. The deserialization vulnerability exists in a component […]
The post Relution Remote Code Execution via Java Deserialization Vulnerability appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’m Not A Pentester (And You Might Not Want To Be One Either) Part 2 : The Response]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ab838cca3519</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/im-not-a-pentester-and-you-might-not-want-to-be-one-either-part-2-the-response-ab838cca3519?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T18:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, so obviously this thing blew up. I really wasn’t expecting it to go this way but I figured I should probably do some kind of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing DIFFER, a new tool for testing and validating transformed programs]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106148</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/01/31/introducing-differ-a-new-tool-for-testing-and-validating-transformed-programs/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T14:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Michael Brown We recently released a new differential testing tool, called DIFFER, for finding bugs and soundness violations in transformed programs. DIFFER combines elements from differential, regression, and fuzz testing to help users find bugs in programs that have been altered by software rewriting, debloating, and hardening tools. We used DIFFER to evaluate 10 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect an Azure Function or Web App to a Key Vault to retrieve secrets with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579562</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/connect-an-azure-function-or-web-app-to-a-key-vault-to-retrieve-secrets-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T08:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions often require access to sensitive information. It is a security risk to store credentials in code or configuration files. Thus, protecting sensitive information like connection strings, API keys, or passwords is crucial. This is where Azure Key Vault comes in, offering secure and centralized storage for all your secrets. In this article, I will explain how to retrieve secrets from the Key Vault within an Azure Function using PowerShell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Purple Teaming: A Practical Approach for Strengthening Your Offensive Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/continuous-purple-teaming-practical-approach-strengthening-offensive-capabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/continuous-purple-teaming-practical-approach-strengthening-offensive-capabilities?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog on continuous purple teaming with CALDERA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOFHound: Session Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7b88b6f18423</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/bofhound-session-integration-7b88b6f18423?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T17:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manually Enumerating Non-LDAP Data for BloodHound]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Creel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why VDIs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=52267</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/why-vdis/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of companies have a system of virtual desktops that they use to make their business work. It could be a healthcare business, and the console follows the doctor around. Maybe it’s a bank and the tellers have to switch kiosks from time to time. Maybe it’s manufacturing, and there are a series of […]
The post Why VDIs? appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LM Studio: Run a local AI on your desktop or server]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579582</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/lm-studio-run-a-local-ai-on-your-desktop-or-server/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T11:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LM Studio is a free tool that allows you to run an AI on your desktop using locally installed open-source Large Language Models (LLMs). It features a browser to search and download LLMs from Hugging Face, an in-app Chat UI, and a runtime for a local server compatible with the OpenAI API. You can use this server to set up a development environment before deploying a more extensive LLM system or even run your ChatGPT clone without sharing your corporate data with third parties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evi Vanoost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSINT in 60 seconds. Mind reading on TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28663</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/osint-in-60-seconds-mind-reading-on-tv/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T06:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR We were asked to help with a Channel 5 consumer education series about online banking scams The presenter, Alexis Conran, was to ‘read’ the minds of members of the […]
OSINT in 60 seconds. Mind reading on TV first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Roberts &amp;#38; Tony Gee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting a System Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=526810</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/troubleshooting-a-system-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=troubleshooting-a-system-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T02:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[…]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing PoIEx - Points Of Intersection Explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/01/30/poiex-release.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/01/30/poiex-release.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are releasing a previously internal-only tool to improve Infrastructure as Code (IaC) analysis and enhance Visual Studio Code allowing real-time collaboration during manual code analysis activities. We’re excited to announce that PoIEx is now available on Github.



Nowadays, cloud-oriented solutions are no longer a buzzword, cloud providers offer ever more intelligent infrastructure services, handling features ranging from simple object storage to complex tasks such as user authentication and identity access management. With the growing complexity of cloud infrastructure, the interactions between application logic and infrastructure begin to play a critical role in ensuring application security.
With many recent high-profile incidents resulting from an insecure combination of web and c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debug with Docker in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1579548</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/debug-with-docker-in-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T10:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will guide you in debugging containerized apps running in Docker using Visual Studio (VS) Code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persistence – Disk Clean-up]]></title>
        <id>http://pentestlab.blog/?p=32478</id>
        <link href="https://pentestlab.blog/2024/01/29/persistence-disk-clean-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T05:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disk Clean-up is a utility which is part of Windows operating systems and can free up hard drive disk space by deleting mainly cache and… 
Continue reading → Persistence – Disk Clean-up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Administrator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS CTI Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cti-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cti-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS CTI Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Common Threats to Your Organization’s Data to be Aware of on Data Protection Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/three-common-threats-to-your-organization-s-data-to-be-aware-of-on-data-protection-day</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/three-common-threats-to-your-organization-s-data-to-be-aware-of-on-data-protection-day?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the need for robust data protection policies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failing Upwards: Put on your own mask before assisting others (Pt2)]]></title>
        <id>65b67aa28792421d3c226d61</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/failing-upwards-pt2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T16:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reflecting on my experiences with various leaders, managers, and bosses, I've gained insights into effective and ineffective leadership styles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failing Upwards (or not) (Pt1)]]></title>
        <id>65a9c46a8792421d3c226be9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/failing-upwards-pt1/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T16:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you find yourself on the path of leading a team, make sure you set critical baselines with your team. Always do what is best for your team and set them up for success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Google Bard's Data Visualization Feature (Code Interpreter)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/exploring-google-bard-vm/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/exploring-google-bard-vm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T09:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last November Google had an interesting update to Google Bard. This updated included the ability to solve math equations and draw charts based on data.
What does this mean and why is it interesting?
It means that Google Bard has access to a computer and can run more complex programs, including Python code that plots graphs!
Let’s explore this with a simple example.
Drawing Charts with Google Bard The following prompt will create a chart:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’m Not A Pentester (And You Might Not Want To Be One Either)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8b5701808dfc</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/im-not-a-pentester-and-you-might-not-want-to-be-one-either-8b5701808dfc?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T14:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all! So, this is going to be a different type of post. I’ve tried to stay a little off the radar personally with my blogs and Twitter account for a lot of reasons. It’s not hard to find out who I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing trust for SGX enclaves]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=106092</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/01/26/enhancing-trust-for-sgx-enclaves/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artur Cygan Creating reproducible builds for SGX enclaves used in privacy-oriented deployments is a difficult task that lacks a convenient and robust solution. We propose using Nix to achieve reproducible and transparent enclave builds so that anyone can audit whether the enclave is running the source code it claims, thereby enhancing the security of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>