<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-10-04T00:45:10.144Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP ModSecurity: Web Application Firewall (WAF) for IIS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587242</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/owasp-modsecurity-web-application-firewall-waf-for-iis/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T22:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP ModSecurity is an open-source Web Application Firewall (WAF) that protects web servers from common attacks. ModSecurity inspects all incoming requests to prevent attacks such as Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), SQL Injection, or Remote Code Execution. The software supports Apache, Nginx, and IIS on Windows Server. This guide demonstrates how to set up the firewall on a Windows Server 2025. You'll need to use version 2.9.7 since newer versions (3.x and above) are not yet available for Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Fuzzing: A Dav1d Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/10/effective-fuzzing-dav1d-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/10/effective-fuzzing-dav1d-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw);.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_5msm2gllocvg-8>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-0>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-2>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_mfum7ompb01z-1>li:before{content:"\0025cb   …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Pwn2Own Automotive: More Autel Maxicharger Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66fd98460cdf9c480a4f9050</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/10/2/from-pwn2own-automotive-more-autel-maxicharger-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post highlights two additional vulnerabilities in the Autel Maxicharger that were exploited at Pwn2Own Automotive 2024. Details of the patches are also included.
Autel has been informed and has deployed a firmware update (v1.35) to address both of these issues. If you want to read about other Autel bugs reported at Pwn2Own, you check out our earlier blog here.
The First Vulnerability: CVE-2024-23967 (ZDI-CAN-23230)
Researchers from Computest Sector 7 identified and exploited a stack-based buffer overflow in v1.32 of the Autel firmware. This vulnerability stems from the decoding of base64 encoded data that can be controlled by an attacker. The encoded data is decoded into a fixed-size stack buffer with no bounds checks, leading to a stack buffer overflow and remote code execution.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Guids to guide the ID of samples’ capabilities or unique (attributable) properties…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9496</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/10/02/using-guids-to-guide-the-id-of-samples-capabilities-or-unique-attributable-properties/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T23:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago Karsten asked me what tool did I use for GUID extraction. I replied that it was my own old tool written waaaay before yara’s birth. In this post I will elaborate on this bit a bit… … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restore classic context menu in Windows 11 Explorer using Group Policy or PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587175</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/restore-classic-context-menu-in-windows-11-explorer-using-group-policy-or-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alongside the revamped Start Menu, one of the most noticeable changes in Windows 11 is the redesigned context menu in File Explorer. However, these modifications are not merely aesthetic – they also restrict its functionality. You can deploy a registry key using Group Policy Preferences to restore the classic context.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All that JavaScript for… spear phishing?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18719</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/10/02/all-that-javascript-for-spear-phishing/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVISO employs several hunting rules in multiple Threat Intelligence Platforms and other sources, such as VirusTotal. As you can imagine, there is no lack of APT (Advanced Persistent Threat) campaigns, cybercriminals and their associated malware families and campaigns, phishing, and so on. But now and then, something slightly different and perhaps novel passes by. In … Continue reading All that JavaScript for… spear phishing? →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bart Parys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing the Gaps: How Attack Path Management Improves Vulnerability Management Programs]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/41177a557368</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/closing-the-gaps-how-attack-path-management-improves-vulnerability-management-programs-41177a557368?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In conversation: Pete McKernan & Luke Luckett]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in September]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10543</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/10/02/overview-of-content-published-in-september-8/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content: Here is an overview of content I published in September: SANS ISC Diary entries: Wireshark 4.4: Converting Display Filters to BPF Capture Filters Protected OOXML Text Documents Python & Notepad++ Password Cracking & Energy: More Dedails Wireshark 4.4’s IP Address Functions YARA 4.5.2 Release YARA-X’s Dump Command]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Pollution in Ruby: A Deep Dive into Exploiting Recursive Merges]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/10/02/class-pollution-ruby.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/10/02/class-pollution-ruby.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
In this post, we are going to explore a rarely discussed class of vulnerabilities in Ruby, known as class pollution. This concept is inspired by the idea of prototype pollution in JavaScript, where recursive merges are exploited to poison the prototype of objects, leading to unexpected behaviors. This idea was initially discussed in a blog post about prototype pollution in Python, in which the researcher used recursive merging to poison class variables and eventually global variables via the __globals__ attribute.
In Ruby, we can categorize class pollution into three main cases:
Merge on Hashes: In this scenario, class pollution isn’t possible because the merge operation is confined to the hash itself.
Merge on Attributes (Non-Recursive): Here, we can poison the instance varia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dotnet Source Generators in 2024 Part 1: Getting Started]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/76d619b633f5</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/dotnet-source-generators-in-2024-part-1-getting-started-76d619b633f5?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T18:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Owens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerToys Workspaces: Group Windows apps]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587120</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-powertoys-workspaces-group-windows-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest PowerToys update introduced Workspaces, enabling users to open a group of applications in predefined positions with just one click. This post will explain how to use the Workspaces feature and showcase its key features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing the software supply chain with the SLSA framework]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108366</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/10/01/securing-the-software-supply-chain-with-the-slsa-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Cliff Smith Software supply chain security has been a hot topic since the Solarwinds breach back in 2020. Thanks to the Supply-chain Levels for Software Artifacts (SLSA) framework, the software industry is now at the threshold of sustainably solving many of the biggest challenges in securely building and distributing open-source software. SLSA is a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airbus Navblue Flysmart LPC-NG issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29805</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/airbus-navblue-flysmart-lpc-ng-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T05:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LPC-NG or Less Paper Cockpit – Next Generation is an electronic flight bag (EFB) application offered by Navblue, a part of Airbus. It’s used for calculating engine thrust requirements (perf) on […]
Airbus Navblue Flysmart LPC-NG issues first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PTP Aviation Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing the Grid: Lessons from China's Cyberattacks on U.S. Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/securing-the-grid-lessons-from-chinas-cyberattacks-on-u-s-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/securing-the-grid-lessons-from-chinas-cyberattacks-on-u-s-providers?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revelations about "Salt Typhoon" highlight that cyber threats targeting essential services are not a future concern—they are here and happening now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Find Broken Access Control Vulnerabilities in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/community/find-broken-access-control-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/community/find-broken-access-control-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T18:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the ins and outs of broken access control vulnerabilities and how to find them in your security research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Stevens @hakluke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in the Windows 11 24H2 update: Download and install, AI features, sudo for Windows, checkpoint updates, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587165</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-the-windows-11-24h2-update-download-and-install-ai-features-sudo-for-windows-checkpoint-updates-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T14:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 24H2, the yearly feature update, is now available for high-end AI-capable devices, with a broader rollout to other PCs in the next few weeks. This article explores the features introduced in the update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can you protect your data, privacy, and finances if your phone gets lost or stolen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29775</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-can-you-protect-your-data-privacy-and-finances-if-your-phone-gets-lost-or-stolen/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T05:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steps to take when your device is lost or stolen TL;DR This is a guide to help prepare for a situation where your mobile device is lost or stolen, including […]
How can you protect your data, privacy, and finances if your phone gets lost or stolen? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambros Zannettos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS CloudSecNext Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS CloudSecNext Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIS2: Next Step Forward on EU Security Requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/public-policy/nis2-eu-security-requirements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/public-policy/nis2-eu-security-requirements"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T23:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about the next NIS2 Directive, what it means for you, and how to be compliant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server 2025 upgrade: Feature update versus clean install]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586886</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-server-2025-upgrade-feature-update-versus-clean-install/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T15:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft provides two primary options for migrating to Windows Server 2025: performing a clean install (fresh install, wipe and load) or a feature update (in-place upgrade). Although the upgrade is quicker and less complicated, it is irreversible and comes with a risk of failure. Windows Server 2025 adopts the same upgrade strategy as Windows 11, with Microsoft's recommended method being an in-place update. Terms like feature update, upgrade, and in-place update are used interchangeably.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Evidence Collection: DFIR's 2024 Mobile and Cloud Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/advanced-evidence-collection-dfir-s-2024-mobile-and-cloud-shift</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/advanced-evidence-collection-dfir-s-2024-mobile-and-cloud-shift?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about how the increasing use of mobile and cloud technologies affects digital forensics and incident response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 4 – No Argument Constructor]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66f4669df5bec45c78ea5ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/25/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-4-no-argument-constructor"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of 4 blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details.
In this final part, I ’am going to describe the PowerShell Remoting ConvertViaNoArgumentConstructor conversion mechanism, which I underestimated at the beginning of my research. It allowed me to find 3 more vulnerabilities, even after the Exchange PowerShell attack surface had been significantly hardened by switching to a strict allow list of types. The vulnerabilities I found were:  
•	CVE-2023-36050 – XXE (File Read)
•	CVE-2023-36039 – NTLM Relaying
•	CVE-2023-36035 – NTLM Relaying  
At least at that time, Microsoft was taking seriously NTLM relaying vulnerabilities in Exchange, because it could lead…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install the AWS Secrets Manager Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1587053</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-install-the-aws-secrets-manager-agent/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T14:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS has recently unveiled the open-source release of the Secrets Manager Agent. This local HTTP service is designed to be installed within various compute environments. Its purpose is to fetch secrets from Secrets Manager and cache them in memory for efficient application access. This approach offers a simplified and consistent method to consume secrets across diverse environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Direct Memory Access (DMA) attacks. Risks, techniques, and mitigations in hardware hacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29725</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/direct-memory-access-dma-attacks-risks-techniques-and-mitigations-in-hardware-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T05:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Direct Memory Access (DMA) attacks are a powerful class of attack that give read and write access to the memory of a target system, bypassing the main CPU to […]
Direct Memory Access (DMA) attacks. Risks, techniques, and mitigations in hardware hacking first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Rabin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Applications of GenAI in a SOC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/practical-applications-of-genai-in-a-soc</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/practical-applications-of-genai-in-a-soc?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few standout candidates for the application of GenAI with Data Loss Prevention (DLP) alerts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Subdomain Takeovers 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/community/guide-subdomain-takeovers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/community/guide-subdomain-takeovers"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by experienced security researcher EdOverflow, this blog provides an understanding of subdomain configurations with current resources and tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EdOverflow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set the default search engine in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox with Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586965</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/set-the-default-search-engine-in-chrome-edge-and-firefox-with-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T19:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All browser vendors configure a default search engine that handles queries entered into the address bar. Microsoft provides Bing, Google uses its own search engine, and Mozilla partners with Google. The default search engines can be changed through Group Policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Streamline Your SDLC With Hai]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/streamline-sdlc-with-hai</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/streamline-sdlc-with-hai"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T17:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hai streamlines the SDLC with the tools to maintain consistency, automate tasks, and improve overall efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office 2024 (LTSC): new features, pricing, and the stability tax]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586901</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-office-2024-ltsc-new-features-pricing-and-the-stabilty-tax/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has officially announced Office LTSC 2024, the newest iteration of its Long-Term Servicing Channel (LTSC) suite. This article examines the new features in Office 2024, compares the standard to the LTSC edition, and breaks down their respective pricing models. Finally, I’ll explain why Microsoft leverages the hefty LTSC price tag and the new AI feature to lure you toward a Microsoft 365 subscription.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broken Hill: A Productionized Greedy Coordinate Gradient Attack Tool for Use Against Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/brokenhill-attack-tool-largelanguagemodels-llm</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/brokenhill-attack-tool-largelanguagemodels-llm"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough the GCG attack at a high level and be introduced to Broken Hill – Bishop Fox’s newly-released tool that can perform the GCG attack against a variety of popular LLMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lincoln</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Pwn2Own Automotive for 2025]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66f1c5f7542ca37795298f1d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/23/announcing-pwn2own-automotive-for-2025"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here.
Earlier this year we held our inaugural Pwn2Own Automotive contest, and it was a rousing success. On our biggest-ever stage (literally), we awarded $1,323,750 over the three-day event as researchers from around the globe demonstrated 49 unique zero days. Today, we’re excited to announce that we will be returning to Tokyo and the Automotive World conference for Pwn2Own Automotive 2025. The event will be held on January 22-24, 2025, and we have some exciting challenges planned for our second year.
As always, we’re pleased to be working with our cohorts over at VicOne again. Their help was instrumental in the success we had at our first event, and we’re glad to be partnering with them once more. Tesla also returns as a sponsor. They …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backdooring Azure Automation Account Packages and Runtime Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25550</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/backdooring-azure-automation-account-packages-and-runtime-environments/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Automation Accounts can allow an attacker to persist in the associated packages that support runbooks. Learn how attackers can maintain access to an Automation Account. 
The post Backdooring Azure Automation Account Packages and Runtime Environments  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Fosaaen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few notes on AWS Nitro Enclaves: Attack surface]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108306</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/24/notes-on-aws-nitro-enclaves-attack-surface/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Paweł Płatek In the race to secure cloud applications, AWS Nitro Enclaves have emerged as a powerful tool for isolating sensitive workloads. But with great power comes great responsibility—and potential security pitfalls. As pioneers in confidential computing security, we at Trail of Bits have scrutinized the attack surface of AWS Nitro Enclaves, uncovering potential […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Security: The 6 biggest challenges AppSec teams face, and how to solve them.]]></title>
        <id>api-security-the-6-biggest-challenges-appsec-teams-face-and-how-to-solve-them</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/api-security-the-6-biggest-challenges-appsec-teams-face-and-how-to-solve-them"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T10:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AppSec teams face a wide range of challenges when securing their API estate against attack threats. In our recent webinar, which demonstrated the enhanced API scanning features in Burp Suite Enterpris]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v4.3: SSO, JSON Fields, and Reporting with BloodHound]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/976835a7edba</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-v4-3-sso-json-fields-and-reporting-with-bloodhound-976835a7edba?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T18:53:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Ghostwriter v4.3’s new features and how to integrate tools like BloodHound]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Maddalena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Docker Desktop 4.34: MSI installer, host networking, auto disk space reclamation, NVIDIA AI workbench, Compose Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586859</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-docker-desktop-434-msi-installer-for-windows-host-networking-auto-disk-space-reclamation-for-wsl2-nvidia-ai-workbench-integration-compose-bridge-and-improved-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, we discussed the new features in Docker Desktop 4.33. This post will cover what's new in Docker Desktop 4.34.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptina RaaS | From Unsellable Cast-Off to Enterprise Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=105715</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/kryptina-raas-from-unsellable-cast-off-to-enterprise-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptina's adoption by Mallox affiliates complicates malware tracking as ransomware operators blend different codebases into new variants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Business Risks of Ignoring ICS Security: Five Critical Takeaways from Industry Experts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-business-risks-of-ignoring-ics-security-five-critical-takeaways-from-industry-experts</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-business-risks-of-ignoring-ics-security-five-critical-takeaways-from-industry-experts?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog summarizing five takeaways from a discussion between four SANS industrial control systems (ICS) security experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32 goes to hell…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9481</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/21/rundll32-goes-to-hell/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T22:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parsing command line invocations is fun, because it’s impossible to do it right (all the time). Imagine a test DLL that exports a function called foobar. We place this DLL in c:\test directory and name it like this: test.dll, #666 … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dexray v2.34]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9479</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/20/dexray-v2-34/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T21:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have updated the code to fix a few bugs that Роман Д. pointed out. Thank you Роман! Download the latest version here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spyware Injection Into Your ChatGPT's Long-Term Memory (SpAIware)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-macos-app-persistent-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-macos-app-persistent-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explains an attack chain for the ChatGPT macOS application. Through prompt injection from untrusted data, attackers could insert long-term persistent spyware into ChatGPT’s memory. This led to continuous data exfiltration of any information the user typed or responses received by ChatGPT, including any future chat sessions.
 OpenAI released a fix for the macOS app last week. Ensure your app is updated to the latest version.
Let’s look at this spAIware in detail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Copilot responses with identical PDF and DOCX content: Causes and solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586793</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/different-copilot-responses-with-identical-pdf-and-docx-content-causes-and-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T15:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saving identical text as both a Word file and a PDF leads to different responses from Copilot because of the fragmented nature of PDF files. Here's why this occurs and how to modify your prompt for more consistent results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicki Borell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Accelerate Vulnerability Remediation with Hai]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/accelerate-vulnerability-remediation-with-hai</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/accelerate-vulnerability-remediation-with-hai"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T22:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hai, HackerOne's AI co-pilot, streamlines remediation efforts and accelerates the find-to-fix process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to change the SSH port on Ubuntu 24.04]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586630</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-change-the-ssh-port-on-ubuntu-2404/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changing the SSH port on Ubuntu 24.04 differs from that on Ubuntu 22.04 and older. Since Ubuntu 22.10, the SSH daemon (sshd) uses socket-based activation, which means that the traditional method of changing the port in /etc/ssh/sshd_config is no longer sufficient. In addition, you need to modify the socket configuration to specify the new port using the ListenStream directive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 3 – DLL Loading Chain for RCE]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66eb2241c9b27c27492158f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/18/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-3-dll-loading-chain-for-rce"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T18:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of 4 blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details. 
In this article, part 3 of the series, I describe a chain of 3 vulnerabilities that led to remote code execution:
·       CVE-2023-36744 – Arbitrary File Write vulnerability
·       CVE-2023-36777 – Arbitrary File Read vulnerability
·       CVE-2023-36745 – Local DLL Loading vulnerability
In the sections that follow, I’m going to describe each of these in detail and show how I chained them to eventually achieve RCE.
You can also watch the talk here: “Half Measures and Full Compromise: Exploiting Microsoft Exchange PowerShell Remoting”. This blog post covers the part from 21:00 to 26:25.
Introduction
I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Trail of Bits and Semgrep partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108295</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/19/announcing-the-trail-of-bits-and-semgrep-partnership/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T13:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Trail of Bits, we aim to share and develop tools and resources used in our security assessments with the broader security community. Many clients, we observed, don’t use Semgrep to its fullest potential or even at all. To bridge this gap and encourage broader adoption, our CEO, Dan Guido, initiated discussions with the Semgrep […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proroute H685 4G router vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29704</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/proroute-h685-4g-router-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Two vulnerabilities on the Proroute H685t-w 4G Router Authenticated command injection is possible through the admin interface Reflected Cross Site-Scripting is possible through the admin interface Patch any routers […]
Proroute H685 4G router vulnerabilities first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lovett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Security Engineering to Make Phishing Harder - A Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/09/19/phishing-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/09/19/phishing-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Recently Doyensec was hired by a client offering a “Communication Platform as a Service”. This platform allows their clients to craft a customer service experience and to communicate with their own customers via a plethora of channels: email, web chats, social media and more.
While undoubtedly valuable, such a service introduces a unique threat model. Our client’s users work with a vast amount of incoming correspondence from outside (often anonymous) users, on a daily basis. This makes them particularly vulnerable to phishing and other social engineering attacks.
While such threats cannot be fully eliminated, it is possible to minimize the possibilities for exploitation. Recognizing this, Doyensec was hired to performed a security review, specifically focused on social enginee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 Copilot: Wave 2]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586714</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-365-copilot-wave-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is maintaining a brisk pace with its AI strategy. Under the title "Microsoft Copilot Wave 2," Redmond unveiled a bundle of innovations and improvements surrounding the diverse Copilot portfolio. There are especially exciting updates in collaboration and Office integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Miedl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber threats to shipping explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29689</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/cyber-threats-to-shipping-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Modern vessels are becoming increasingly connected. While it is unlikely that hackers could fully control a container ship remotely, they may be able to disrupt systems such as the […]
Cyber threats to shipping explained first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Tierney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Biggest Update Ever to SEC510: Cloud Security Controls and Mitigations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/announcing-the-biggest-update-ever-to-sec510-cloud-security-controls-and-mitigations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/announcing-the-biggest-update-ever-to-sec510-cloud-security-controls-and-mitigations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the biggest update ever to SEC510: Cloud Security Controls and Mitigations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does OpenAI’s new model o1 solve the hallucination problem?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586674</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/does-openais-new-model-o1-solve-the-hallucination-problem/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T17:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has officially launched its long-awaited "reasoning" AI model, formerly referred to as "Strawberry" and Q* (Q-star), now named OpenAI o1. Launched as o1-preview and o1-mini, this new family of models promises to tackle complex problems more effectively than its predecessors, including GPT-4o. However, while initial reports are promising, key questions remain about its capabilities. What matters most to me is whether OpenAI resolves the hallucination problem, an issue that all large language models (LLMs) face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside DEF CON: Michael Brown on how AI/ML is revolutionizing cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108279</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/17/inside-def-con-michael-brown-on-how-ai-ml-is-revolutionizing-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At DEF CON, Michael Brown, Principal Security Engineer at Trail of Bits, sat down with Michael Novinson from Information Security Media Group (ISMG) to discuss four critical areas where AI/ML is revolutionizing security. Here’s what they covered: AI/ML techniques surpass the limits of traditional software analysis As Moore’s law slows down after 20 years of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emergency Accounts: Last Call!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18604</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/17/emergency-accounts-last-call/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T10:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update your emergency accounts before October 15th. Even if you have been out of office for the last couple of months, you should be aware that starting October 15th you will need to provide Multi Factor Authentication (MFA) to logon to Azure portal, Entra admin center and Intune admin center. This will be enforced to … Continue reading Emergency Accounts: Last Call! →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Turegano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing HackerOne Automations]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/introducing-hackerone-automations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/introducing-hackerone-automations"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Alyona Vysotska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Microsoft 365 from Active Directory Users and Computers (ADUC) with Easy365Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586601</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-microsoft-365-from-active-directory-users-and-computers-aduc-with-easy365manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T16:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many IT admins manage both on-premises Active Directory environments and hybrid setups like Microsoft 365. Constantly switching between on-premises management and Microsoft 365 can be challenging. Easy365Manager aims to simplify this process. Let's explore this tool and the features it offers for hybrid management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Mainframe Memory Made Easy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25510</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/mainframe-penetration-testing/mapping-mainframe-memory/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how NetSPI's own LPAR enhances pentesting efficiency through rapid tool prototyping and deployment.
The post Mapping Mainframe Memory Made Easy appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Windows on ARM64 / AArch64]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5258</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/09/16/windows_arm64/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T14:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Back in October 2018, I wanted to write ARM assembly on Windows. All I could acquire then was a Surface tablet running Windows RT that was released sometime in October 2012. Windows RT (now deprecated) was a version of … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating DORA Compliance: A Comprehensive Approach to Threat-Led Penetration Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/dora-compliance-penetration-testing</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/dora-compliance-penetration-testing"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how organizations can strategically prepare for and execute TLPT to meet DORA compliance while strengthening overall cybersecurity resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The delayed import-table phantomDLL opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9442</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/14/the-delayed-import-table-phantomdll-opportunities/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T21:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many native OS PE files still rely on delayed imports. When APIs imported this way are called for the first time, a so-called delay load helper function is executed first – it loads the actual delayed library, resolves the address … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expand the Copilot Language Model with external data sources using GraphRAG]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586541</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/expand-the-copilot-language-model-with-external-data-sources-using-graphrag/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the knowledge of a language model is insufficient to answer questions, integrating additional data sources comprehensively can be beneficial. Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) serves this purpose by connecting to data sources outside the trained language model. Microsoft 365 Copilot already works with RAG and is now expanding with GraphRAG to unlock even more extensive knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicki Borell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friends don’t let friends reuse nonces]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108229</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/13/friends-dont-let-friends-reuse-nonces/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Joe Doyle If you’ve encountered cryptography software, you’ve probably heard the advice to never use a nonce twice—in fact, that’s where the word nonce (number used once) comes from. Depending on the cryptography involved, a reused nonce can reveal encrypted messages, or even leak your secret key! But common knowledge may not cover every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA CUDA monopoly faces competition from AMD’s open-source alternative ROCm]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586521</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/nvidia-cuda-monopoly-faces-competition-from-amds-open-source-alternative-rocm/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA's quasi-monopoly in the AI GPU market is achieved through its CUDA platform's early development and widespread adoption. It serves as a moat by becoming the industry standard due to its superior performance and integration with key AI tools. While NVIDIA's dominance is bolstered by its proprietary advantages and developer lock-in, emerging competitors like AMD and innovations such as AMD's ROCm, OpenAI's Triton, and PyTorch 2.0 are beginning to challenge this stronghold by offering open-source alternatives and reducing reliance on CUDA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 2 - ApprovedApplicationCollection]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66e1d60259527a323d805e5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/11/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-2-approvedapplicationcollection"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of 4 blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details. You can read the first post in this series here.
In part 2, I describe the ApprovedApplicationCollection gadget, which was available for abuse because it did not appear on the deny list and could therefore be accessed via MultiValuedProperty. I am also presenting a path traversal in the Windows utility extrac32.exe, which allowed me to complete the chain for a full RCE in Exchange. For the moment, at least, Microsoft has made a decision not to fix this path traversal bug.
You can watch the full talk here: “Half Measures and Full Compromise: Exploiting Microsoft Exchange PowerShell Remoting”. This blog …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Burp Suite’s game-changing performance update ⚡🏎️]]></title>
        <id>introducing-burp-suites-game-changing-performance-update</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/introducing-burp-suites-game-changing-performance-update"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T11:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-on security testers need the best tools for the job. Tools you have faith in, and enjoy using all day long. Burp Suite has long been that tool, and now, it's faster than ever. We’ve listened to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Third-Party Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18459</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/12/introduction-to-third-party-risk-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s world, organizations are increasingly depending on their third-party vendors, suppliers, and partners to support their operations. This way of working, in addition to the digitalization era we’re in, can have great advantages such as being able to offer new services quickly while relying on other’s expertise or cutting costs on already existing processes. … Continue reading Introduction to Third-Party Risk Management →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fishel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living off the land, GPO style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29636</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/living-off-the-land-gpo-style/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T05:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The ability to edit  Group Policy Object (GPOs) from non-domain joined computers using the native Group Policy editor has been on my list for a long time.  This blog […]
Living off the land, GPO style first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32.exe bomb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9463</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/11/rundll32-exe-bomb/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T22:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a silly example of a basic mistake leading to a funny discovery… When I was experimenting with the imported phantom DLLs I accidentally placed a dummy 64-bit DLL in a place of a 32-bit phantom DLL called WDSUTIL.dll … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Bug Bounty Programs in S-1 Filings: A New Standard in Corporate Security]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-s-1-filings</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-s-1-filings"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T21:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why more organizations are including their bug bounty programs in S-1 filings and other corporate disclosures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jobert Abma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Large Language Models: Local LLM CTF & Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/large-language-models-llm-ctf-lab</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/large-language-models-llm-ctf-lab"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore research on isolating functional expectations for LLMs using a controller to manage access between privileged and quarantined LLMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Rush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Built-in data security in Microsoft 365: What Microsoft provides and what the customer is responsible for]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586366</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/built-in-data-security-in-microsoft-365-what-microsoft-provides-and-what-the-customer-is-responsible-for/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T14:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How secure is the data in Microsoft 365, and what basic measures does Microsoft offer for data protection and reliability? The company has integrated some safeguarding mechanisms to protect customers from data mishaps. There is also a new framework that outlines the responsibilities of both the provider and the customer. Here's an overview of tools and regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Miedl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADCS Attack Paths in BloodHound — Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/33efb00856ac</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/adcs-attack-paths-in-bloodhound-part-3-33efb00856ac?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T13:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will explore the new ESC6/ESC9/ESC10 edges we have introduced with ADCS support in BloodHound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bülow Knudsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Improvements to table sorting and Repeater]]></title>
        <id>performance-improvements-to-table-sorting-and-repeater</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/performance-improvements-to-table-sorting-and-repeater"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T06:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance is a critical factor in the usability and efficiency of any software, and Burp Suite is no exception. We've recently focused on enhancing Burp Suite's performance across several key areas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite Performance Improvements]]></title>
        <id>burp-suite-performance-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/burp-suite-performance-improvements"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T06:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance is a critical factor in the usability and efficiency of any software, and Burp Suite is no exception. We've recently focused on enhancing Burp Suite's performance across several key areas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The September 2024 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66e07f45c60a2e7a02fabeb6</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/10/the-september-2024-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T17:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve reached September and the pumpkin spice floats in the air. While they aren’t pumpkin-spiced, Microsoft and Adobe have released their latest spicy security patches – including some zesty 0-days. Take a break from your regular activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts.If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for September 2024
For September, Adobe released eight bulletins covering 28 CVEs in Adobe Acrobat and Reader, ColdFusion, Photoshop, Media Encoder, Audition, After Effects, Premier Pro, and Illustrator. A total of seven of these bugs came through the ZDI program. If you’re prioritizing, I would look at the ColdFusion patch first. It corrects a single code execution bug rat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Hai Plays: Personalize Your Playbook for Spot-On Security Advice]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/hai-plays</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/hai-plays"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T17:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to introduce Hai Plays, a powerful new feature for Hai, HackerOne’s AI co-pilot. Hai Plays is designed to make your interactions with Hai more efficient and tailored to your specific security needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack My Career: Harley Kimball’s Journey to DEFCON]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-harley-kimballs-journey-defcon</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-harley-kimballs-journey-defcon"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>mbriones@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Workstation Pro 17.6: Free for personal use, enhanced OS support, and improved performance]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586460</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/vmware-workstation-pro-176-free-for-personal-use-enhanced-os-support-and-improved-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Workstation Pro 17.6 introduces a couple of valuable changes. Notably, it is now available for free for personal use. The update enhances OS support, adding compatibility with systems like Windows Server 2025 and Ubuntu 24.04 as both hosts and guests. Additionally, new tools like the vmcli command-line utility streamline virtual machine management, while crucial bug fixes and security updates enhance the platform's reliability and efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hijacking SQL Server Credentials using Agent Jobs for Domain Privilege Escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25333</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/network-pentesting/hijacking-sql-server-credentials-with-agent-jobs-for-domain-privilege-escalation/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how threat actors can exploit SQL Server credential objects to escalate domain privileges and how you can detect it.
The post Hijacking SQL Server Credentials using Agent Jobs for Domain Privilege Escalation  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Sutherland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sanitize your C++ containers: ASan annotations step-by-step]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108139</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/10/sanitize-your-c-containers-asan-annotations-step-by-step/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Dominik Klemba and Dominik Czarnota AddressSanitizer (ASan) is a compiler plugin that helps detect memory errors like buffer overflows or use-after-frees. In this post, we explain how to equip your C++ code with ASan annotations to find more bugs. We also show our work on ASan in GCC and LLVM. In LLVM, Trail of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudGoat Official Walkthrough Series: ‘glue_privesc’]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25344</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/cloud-security/cloudgoat-walkthrough-glue_privesc/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CloudGoat Official Walkthrough Series: ‘glue_privesc’ appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John De Armas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart home security advice. Ring, SimpliSafe, Swann, and Yale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29600</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/smart-home-security-advice-ring-simplisafe-swann-and-yale/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T05:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This guide covers the security of smart home security products from Ring, Yale, Swann, and SimpliSafe. Whether you’re looking to monitor your property remotely, enhance your home’s security, or […]
Smart home security advice. Ring, SimpliSafe, Swann, and Yale first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Bromiley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance your Cyber Threat Intelligence with the Admiralty System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/enhance-your-cyber-threat-intelligence-with-the-admiralty-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/enhance-your-cyber-threat-intelligence-with-the-admiralty-system?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about using the Admiralty System for better cyber threat intelligence (CTI).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strengthen Your Supply Chain Security with Effective SBOM Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/strengthen-your-supply-chain-security-with-effective-sbom-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/strengthen-your-supply-chain-security-with-effective-sbom-management?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Master SBOM management to secure your software supply chain. Explore the SBOM lifecycle with our guide and enhance your compliance and security strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One Launches Public Bug Bounty Program with HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/capital-one-public-bug-bounty</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/capital-one-public-bug-bounty"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One has officially launched a public bug bounty program with HackerOne, partnering with ethical hackers to secure their assets and prevent security breaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block AI scrapers and other web parasites with Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586408</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/block-ai-scrapers-and-other-web-parasites-with-cloudflare/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T15:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post, I discussed three standard methods to block AI crawlers that have little prospect of being successful. Please also read it if you want to know why it is important to block AI scrapers. One way that works reliably for 4sysops is leveraging Cloudflare's Web Application Firewall (WAF). Cloudflare's free plan provides all the essential tools to safeguard your site against content theft by AI companies. However, I found that Cloudflare's new Block AI Scrapers and Crawlers feature is insufficient for the task. Fortunately, Cloudflare's WAF is sophisticated enough to reliably block all AI scrapers and other web parasites with a single, relatively simple rule. My proposed method serves as a way to enforce an opt-in approach, rather than relying on the non-binding opt-out recommendations in your robots.txt file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS AI Cybersecurity Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ai-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ai-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS AI Cybersecurity Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why ICS Is the Business: Essential Cybersecurity Strategies for Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/why-ics-is-the-business-essential-cybersecurity-strategies-for-critical-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/why-ics-is-the-business-essential-cybersecurity-strategies-for-critical-infrastructure?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog detailing strategies to protect industrial control systems (ICS) and critical infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This post is totally Iconic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9457</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/07/this-post-is-totally-iconic/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T22:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 6 years ago I decided to pursue yet another silly idea: extract all the unique .ico files from PE resources from as many samples as I can. This exercise yielded ~450K unique .ico files. If I remember correctly, the … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of underDLLoading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9440</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/06/the-art-of-underdlloading/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T22:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post I created a posh artisan .exe file ornamented with a large number of intricate system32 DLL imports. The process of building that file was painful – before I even managed to run the final executable I … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Prospect to Partner: Jon Stone Shares HackerOne Career Story]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/prospect-partner-jon-stone-shares-hackerone-career-story</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/prospect-partner-jon-stone-shares-hackerone-career-story"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T20:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recover data from corrupted BitLocker drives with repair-bde and key packages]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586344</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/recover-data-from-corrupted-bitlocker-drives-with-repair-bde-and-key-packages/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activating BitLocker encryption on a drive automatically generates a 48-digit numeric recovery password. This password is crucial if other unlocking methods fail and Windows prompts you with the BitLocker recovery console during startup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Unstripping” binaries: Restoring debugging information in GDB with Pwndbg]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108110</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/06/unstripping-binaries-restoring-debugging-information-in-gdb-with-pwndbg/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jason An GDB loses significant functionality when debugging binaries that lack debugging symbols (also known as “stripped binaries”). Function and variable names become meaningless addresses; setting breakpoints requires tracking down relevant function addresses from an external source; and printing out structured values involves staring at a memory dump trying to manually discern field boundaries. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunting Chromium Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=17131</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/06/hunting-chromium-notifications/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browser notifications provide social-engineering opportunities. In this post we'll cover the associated forensic artifacts, threat hunting possibilities and hardening recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Thiebaut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of overDLLoading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9430</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/05/the-art-of-overdlloading/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T23:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some time ago I came up with a silly idea: i’d like to build an executable that statically links to most of the c:\windows\system2 libraries. It’s a non-sensical programming exercise, but it’s also an interesting challenge. Forcing a static import … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical debt of C:\Windows\System path]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9423</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/05/technical-debt-of-cwindowssystem-path/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T21:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to @sixtyvividtails who corrected a mistake I made in the earlier version of the post Updated post One of a less known paths that is being searched when the libraries are loaded is C:\Windows\System. Anytime the search for a … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 1 - MultiValuedProperty]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66d8b6216c0b0917fc4e4ef7</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/4/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-1-multivaluedproperty"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of four blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details. For those who did not attend OffensiveCon, you can also watch the full talk here: “Half Measures and Full Compromise: Exploiting Microsoft Exchange PowerShell Remoting”. This blog post covers the part from 12:05 to 18:10.
In this article, part one of the series, I describe the MultiValuedProperty exploitation primitive, which became fundamental for my further exploitation of Exchange PowerShell. I also present a bypass for Microsoft’s first patch for this vulnerability, accomplished by chaining MultiValuedProperty with the Command class.  
Introduction
You might already be familiar with the Exchange…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How not to block AI crawlers: robots.txt, authentication, CAPTCHA]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586317</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-not-to-block-ai-crawlers-robotstxt-authentication-captcha/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The content wars are on. AI crawlers ignore robots.txt, scraping greedily any web content they can reach to train their models. If search engine traffic from Google and Bing is helpful for your website, you must block all AI scrapers. This post covers three standard but ineffective methods for blocking AI crawlers on your site: robots.txt, authentication, and CAPTCHAs. In my next post, I'll introduce a solution that effectively blocks AI crawlers and other web parasites: Cloudflare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon23 Replay | They Spilled Oil in My Health-Boosting Smoothie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=104518</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon23-replay-they-spilled-oil-in-my-health-boosting-smoothie/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zuzana Hromcová explores how Iran-aligned APT OilRig targets healthcare and local governments with a stream of updated and newly developed tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What would you do with that old GPU?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108089</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/05/what-would-you-do-with-that-old-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T13:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg and Peter Goodman (Would you get up and throw it away?) [sing to the tune of The Beatles – With A Little Help From My Friends] Here’s a riddle: when new GPUs are constantly being produced, product cycles are ~18-24 months long, and each cycle doubles GPU power (per Huang’s Law), what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validate your Windows Audit Policy Configuration with KQL]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=14001</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/05/validate-your-windows-audit-policy-configuration-with-kql/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We provide a KQL query that will help you validate your defined Windows audit security policy configuration. Defining a Windows audit policy is an important step in establishing a robust security posture. Ensuring that the audit policy is applied consistently across your environment is just as important as defining that policy and quality controls should be in place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stamatis Chatzimangou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve Taken a SANS Course – Now What?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/youve-taken-a-sans-course-now-what</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/youve-taken-a-sans-course-now-what?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog detailing what to do once you have completed a SANS Live Training course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantifying the Value of Bug Bounty Programs: ROI, ROM, or Both?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/quantifying-value-bug-bounty-programs-roi-rom-or-both</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/quantifying-value-bug-bounty-programs-roi-rom-or-both"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T21:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is ROI the right method to measure bug bounty value? Check out the cost-benefit analysis of ROI vs. ROM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32 and Phantom DLL lolbins, 32-bit version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9419</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/04/rundll32-and-phantom-dll-lolbins-32-bit-version/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I have shown in the last post, there exists a class of DLLs on Windows OS that load other libraries via import table, and sometimes these needed imported libraries do not exist. This creates an opportunity that we can … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Determine effective password policy for AD users with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586100</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/determine-effective-password-policy-for-ad-users-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T15:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the default domain password policy, administrators can assign different password rules to specific users or groups using fine-grained password policies. When multiple policies exist, it can become unclear which one is effective for a particular user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New website address and RSS Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34806</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/08/13/new-website-address-and-rss-feed/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that all of NCC Group’s latest research findings and articles are now hosted on our website at the following link: NCC Group Research Blog. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/) To stay up-to-date with our latest research, you can also subscribe to our RSS feed here: NCC Group Research Blog RSS Feed. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/feed/) Be sure to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>R.Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side-by-Side with HelloJackHunter: Unveiling the Mysteries of WinSxS]]></title>
        <id>65f5ceb78792421d3c2272e4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/hellojackhunter-exploring-winsxs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T09:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores Windows Side-by-Side (WinSxS) and DLL hijacking, deep-diving some tooling I've written and some of the fun along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>