<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-03T00:43:49.059Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe: JSX and JSXBIN files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8217</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/09/02/adobe-jsx-and-jsxbin-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T22:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote about older Adobe scripting before. I recently discovered that Adobe products support scripting using so-called ExtendScript language with code being stored either in a source-level JSX file, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: jpegdump.py Version 0.0.10]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9422</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/02/update-jpegdump-py-version-0-0-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T19:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update to jpegdump.py, my tool to analyze JPEG images, brings 2 small changes: Data between segments can be selected with suffix d. Like this: -s 10d This means: select the data between segments 9 and 10. And when option -E is used to add hash values, repeating hashes are marked with parentheses. jpegdump_V0_0_10.zip (http)MD5: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s Another Hole In Your SoC: Unisoc ROM Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16862</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/02/theres-another-hole-in-your-soc-unisoc-rom-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T18:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UNISOC (formerly Spreadtrum) is a rapidly growing semiconductor company that is nowadays focused on the Android entry-level smartphone market. While still a rare sight in the west, the company has nevertheless achieved impressive growth claiming 11% of the global smartphone application processor market, according to Counterpoint Research. Recently, it’s been making its way into some … Continue reading There’s Another Hole In Your SoC: Unisoc ROM Vulnerabilities →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilya Zhuravlev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up Remote Desktop Easy Print]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567514</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/setting-up-remote-desktop-easy-print/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T15:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One challenge with Remote Desktop printing is the issue of drivers. If users want to output documents on locally attached printers, for example, in work-from-home environments, organizations might have to deal with various printer models. Remote Desktop Easy Print offers a solution with a single driver.
Setting up Remote Desktop Easy Print first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When disclosure goes wrong. People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=24315</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/when-disclosure-goes-wrong-people/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T05:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My experience of vulnerability disclosure is that it is rarely as easy or simple as it could be. I had hoped that bug bounty programmes and vulnerability disclosure programmes (VDPs) […]
When disclosure goes wrong. People first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Standby Power Consumption Of My Bosch 18V Chargers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9410</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/02/quickpost-standby-power-consumption-of-my-bosch-18v-chargers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 2 Bosch 18V “power for all” chargers. A normal charger (AL 1830 CV) and a fast charger (AL 1880 CV). Measuring the power consumption of these 2 chargers in standby mode (plugged into a 230V outlet, but no battery connected) with a GPM-8310 powermeter, I obtained the following results: AL 1830 CV: 476,33 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Directory Services Restore Mode: DSRM password reset, recover Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567501</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/directory-services-restore-mode-dsrm-password-reset-recover-active-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T19:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever received the following error message when you tried to sign in on a domain controller? We can't sign you in with this credential because your domain isn't available. Scary, huh? With the help of Active Directory's Directory Services Restore Mode (DSRM), you can recover Active Directory by booting up in safe mode to restore a working configuration of your Active Directory. I hope you still know your DSRM password. If not, I show you how to reset the DSRSM password in this article.
Directory Services Restore Mode: DSRM password reset, recover Active Directory first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyPI Phishing Campaign | JuiceLedger Threat Actor Pivots From Fake Apps to Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=69799</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/pypi-phishing-campaign-juiceledger-threat-actor-pivots-from-fake-apps-to-supply-chain-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new threat actor is spreading infostealer malware through targeted attacks on developers and fraudulent cryptotrading applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitai Ben Shushan Ehrlich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in August]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9406</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/09/01/overview-of-content-published-in-august-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in August: Blog posts: Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.15 Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.16 YouTube videos: 1768.py’s Sanity Check Videoblog posts: 1768.py?s Sanity Check SANS ISC Diary entries: VBA Maldoc & UTF7 (APT-C-35) YARA 4.2.3 Released Sysinternals Updates: Sysmon v14.0 and ZoomIt v6.01 Dealing With False Positives when Scanning […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conference Talks – September/October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16685</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/01/conference-talks-september-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T15:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout September and October, members of NCC Group will be presenting their work at SANS CyberThreat, ResponderCon, BSides St John’s, ICMC, DevOps World, RootCon, and Hexacon. Ollie Whitehouse & Eric Shamper, “Enterprise IR:Live Free, live large” to be presented at Sans CyberThreat (September 12-13 2022) Balazs Bucsay, “Alternative way to detect mikatz” to be presented … Continue reading Conference Talks – September/October 2022 →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Fernick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whitebox Security Assessments: Doing More with More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4151</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/benefits-of-a-whitebox-approach/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T13:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deciding on what type of security assessment to get, an organization should consider how much information they are willing to share. Several types of assessments exist, and the key differentiator is how much access an organization grants the testers from the beginning. The terms blackbox, greybox, and whitebox refer to whether a client chooses […]
The post Whitebox Security Assessments: Doing More with More appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Hackability to uncover a Chrome infoleak]]></title>
        <id>using-hackability-to-uncover-a-chrome-infoleak</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/using-hackability-to-uncover-a-chrome-infoleak"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been hacking browsers for over 15 years and one of the challenges I set myself was to find a SOP bypass or info leak in every major browser. Chrome was the last browser standing…until now. This p]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SETTLERS OF NETLINK: Exploiting a limited UAF in nf_tables (CVE-2022-32250)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16956</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/09/01/settlers-of-netlink-exploiting-a-limited-uaf-in-nf_tables-cve-2022-32250/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T08:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction netlink and nf_tables Overview Sets Expressions Set Expressions Stateful Expressions Expressions of Interest nft_lookup nft_dynset nft_connlimit Vulnerability Discovery CVE-2022-32250 Analysis Set Creation Set Deactivation Initial Limited UAF Write Exploitation Building an Initial Plan Offsets We Can Write at Into the UAF Chunk Hunting for Replacement Objects What Pointer Do We Want to Arbitrary Free? … Continue reading SETTLERS OF NETLINK: Exploiting a limited UAF in nf_tables (CVE-2022-32250) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Halbronn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure Abuse Research — Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3e5bbe7a20c0</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/automating-azure-abuse-research-part-2-3e5bbe7a20c0?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, we looked at how to port functionality from the Azure GUI to PowerShell. Specifically, we looked at how to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing FreeBSD Kernel Modules in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16915</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/31/writing-freebsd-kernel-modules-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At present all major operating system kernels are written in C/C++, languages which provide no or minimal assistance in avoiding common security problems. Modern languages such as Rust provide better security guarantees by default and prevent many of the common classes of memory safety security bugs. In this post we will take a brief look … Continue reading Writing FreeBSD Kernel Modules in Rust →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find AD accounts with ChangePasswordAtLogon, set and enforce password change with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567476</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-ad-accounts-with-changepasswordatlogon-set-and-enforce-password-change-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Admins can prompt users to change their password at their next login. While it is easy to see the status of the corresponding attribute in AD Users and Computers, the procedure with PowerShell is a bit tricky. On the other hand, enforcing a password change with PowerShell is quite simple.
Find AD accounts with ChangePasswordAtLogon, set and enforce password change with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite price increases]]></title>
        <id>burp-suite-price-increases</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/burp-suite-price-increases"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T07:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are increasing prices for Burp Suite Professional and Burp Suite Enterprise Edition, due to a significant increase in costs caused by global inflation. The price of an annual Burp Suite Professiona]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free network speed test tools]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567468</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/free-network-speed-test-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running a simple network speed test is often a good start when troubleshooting or verifying network performance. Such a test may measure speeds between two computers or the Internet download speed from an ISP. Many free network performance test tools are readily available for testing network performance.
Free network speed test tools first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NTLMv1 vs NTLMv2: Digging into an NTLM Downgrade Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4180</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/ntlmv1-vs-ntlmv2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview During the summer, my colleague Derya Yavuz and I published an article on some of the different methods we’ve leveraged to elevate privileges within Active Directory environments. We discussed authentication coercion techniques such as PrinterBug, PetitPotam, and DFSCoerce. One of the techniques we mentioned in that article was performing an NTLM downgrade attack to […]
The post NTLMv1 vs NTLMv2: Digging into an NTLM Downgrade Attack appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-26113:  FortiClient Arbitrary File Write As SYSTEM]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=24617</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/cve-2022-26113-forticlient-arbitrary-file-write-as-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T12:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CVE-2022-26113:  FortiClient Arbitrary File Write As SYSTEM appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yesland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NCC Con Europe 2022 – Pwn2Own Austin Presentations]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16529</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/30/ncc-con-europe-2022-pwn2own-austin-presentations/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T10:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cedric Halbronn, Aaron Adams, Alex Plaskett and Catalin Visinescu presented two talks at NCC Con Europe 2022. NCC Con is NCC Group’s annual private internal conference for employees. We have decided to publish these 2 internal presentations as it is expected that the wider security community could benefit from understanding both the approach and methodology … Continue reading NCC Con Europe 2022 – Pwn2Own Austin Presentations →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Plaskett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootkitting Windows Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>https://secret.club/2022/08/29/bootkitting-windows-sandbox.html</id>
        <link href="https://secret.club/2022/08/29/bootkitting-windows-sandbox.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction &amp; Motivation Windows Sandbox is a feature that Microsoft added to Windows back in May 2019. As Microsoft puts it: Windows Sandbox provides a lightweight desktop environment to safely run applications in isolation. Software installed inside the Windows Sandbox environment remains “sandboxed” and runs separately from the host machine. The startup is usually very fast and the user experience is great. You can configure it with a .wsb file and then double click that file to start a clean VM. The sandbox can be useful for malware analysis and as we will show in this article, it can also be used for kernel research and driver development. We will take things a step further though and share how we can intercept the boot process and patch the kernel during startup with a bootkit. TLDR: Visit the SandboxBootkit repository to try out the bootkit for yourself. Windows Sandbox for driver development A few years back Jonas L tweeted about the undocumented command CmDiag. It turns out that it is almost trivial to enable test signing and kernel debugging in the sandbox (this part was copied straight from my StackOverflow answer). First you need to enable development mode (everything needs to be run from an Administrator command prompt): CmDiag DevelopmentMode -On Then enable network debugging (you can see additional options with CmDiag Debug): CmDiag Debug -On -Net This should give you the connection string: Debugging successfully enabled. Connection string: -k net:port=50100,key=cl.ea.rt.ext,target=&lt;ContainerHostIp&gt; -v Now start WinDbg and connect to 127.0.0.1: windbg.exe -k net:port=50100,key=cl.ea.rt.ext,target=127.0.0.1 -v Then you start Windows Sandbox and it should connect: Microsoft (R) Windows Debugger Version 10.0.22621.1 AMD64 Copyright (c) Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved. Using NET for debugging Opened WinSock 2.0 Using IPv4 only. Waiting to reconnect... Connected to target 127.0.0.1 on port 50100 on local IP &lt;xxx.xxx.xxx.xxx&gt;. You can get the target MAC address by running .kdtargetmac command. Connected to Windows 10 19041 x64 target at (Sun Aug 7 10:32:11.311 2022 (UTC + 2:00)), ptr64 TRUE Kernel Debugger connection established. Now in order to load your driver you have to copy it into the sandbox and you can use sc create and sc start to run it. Obviously most device drivers will not work/freeze the VM but this can certainly be helpful for research. The downside of course is that you need to do quite a bit of manual work and this is not exactly a smooth development experience. Likely you can improve it with the &lt;MappedFolder&gt; and &lt;LogonCommand&gt; options in your .wsb file. PatchGuard &amp; DSE Running Windows Sandbox with a debugger attached will disable PatchGuard and with test signing enabled you can run your own kernel code. Attaching a debugger every time is not ideal though. Startup times are increased by a lot and software might detect kernel debugging and refuse to run. Additionally it seems that the network connection is not necessarily stable across host reboots and you need to restart WinDbg every time to attach the debugger to the sandbox. Tooling similar to EfiGuard would be ideal for our purposes and in the rest of the post we will look at implementing our own bootkit with equivalent functionality. Windows Sandbox internals recap Back in March 2021 a great article called Playing in the (Windows) Sandbox came out. This article has a lot of information about the internals and a lot of the information below comes from there. Another good resource is Microsoft’s official Windows Sandbox architecture page. Windows Sandbox uses VHDx layering and NTFS magic to allow the VM to be extremely lightweight. Most of the system files are actually NTFS reparse points that point to the host file system. For our purposes the relevant file is BaseLayer.vhdx (more details in the references above). What the article did not mention is that there is a folder called BaseLayer pointing directly inside the mounted BaseLayer.vhdx at the following path on the host: C:\ProgramData\Microsoft\Windows\Containers\BaseImages\&lt;GUID&gt;\BaseLayer This is handy because it allows us to read/write to the Windows Sandbox file system without having to stop/restart CmService every time we want to try something. The only catch is that you need to run as TrustedInstaller and you need to enable development mode to modify files there. When you enable development mode there will also be an additional folder called DebugLayer in the same location. This folder exists on the host file system and allows us to overwrite certain files (BCD, registry hives) without having to modify the BaseLayer. The configuration for the DebugLayer appears to be in BaseLayer\Bindings\Debug, but no further time was spent investigating. The downside of enabling development mode is that snapshots are disabled and as a result startup times are significantly increased. After modifying something in the BaseLayer and disabling development mode you also need to delete the Snapshots folder and restart CmService to apply the changes. Getting code execution at boot time To understand how to get code execution at boot time you need some background on UEFI. We released Introduction to UEFI a few years back and there is also a very informative series called Geeking out with the UEFI boot manager that is useful for our purposes. In our case it is enough to know that the firmware will try to load EFI\Boot\bootx64.efi from the default boot device first. You can override this behavior by setting the BootOrder UEFI variable. To find out how Windows Sandbox boots you can run the following PowerShell commands: &gt; Set-ExecutionPolicy -ExecutionPolicy Unrestricted &gt; Install-Module UEFI &gt; Get-UEFIVariable -VariableName BootOrder -AsByteArray 0 0 &gt; Get-UEFIVariable -VariableName Boot0000 �VMBus File System�VMBus�\EFI\Microsoft\Boot\bootmgfw.efi� From this we can derive that Windows Sandbox first loads: \EFI\Microsoft\Boot\bootmgfw.efi As described in the previous section we can access this file on the host (as TrustedInstaller) via the following path: C:\ProgramData\Microsoft\Windows\Containers\BaseImages\&lt;GUID&gt;\BaseLayer\Files\EFI\Microsoft\Boot\bootmgfw.efi To verify our assumption we can rename the file and try to start Windows Sandbox. If you check in Process Monitor you will see vmwp.exe fails to open bootmgfw.efi and nothing happens after that. Perhaps it is possible to modify UEFI variables and change Boot0000 (Hyper-V Manager can do this for regular VMs so probably there is a way), but for now it will be easier to modify bootmgfw.efi directly. Bootkit overview To gain code execution we embed a copy of our payload inside bootmgfw and then we modify the entry point to our payload. Our EfiEntry does the following: Get the image base/size of the currently running module Relocate the image when necessary Hook the BootServices-&gt;OpenProtocol function Get the original AddressOfEntryPoint from the .bootkit section Execute the original entry point To simplify the injection of SandboxBootkit.efi into the .bootkit section we use the linker flags /FILEALIGN:0x1000 /ALIGN:0x1000. This sets the FileAlignment and SectionAlignment to PAGE_SIZE, which means the file on disk and in-memory are mapped one-to-one. Bootkit hooks Note: Many of the ideas presented here come from the DmaBackdoorHv project by Dmytro Oleksiuk, go check it out! The first issue you run into when modifying bootmgfw.efi on disk is that the self integrity checks will fail. The function responsible for this is called BmFwVerifySelfIntegrity and it directly reads the file from the device (e.g. it does not use the UEFI BootServices API). To bypass this there are two options: Hook BmFwVerifySelfIntegrity to return STATUS_SUCCESS Use bcdedit /set {bootmgr} nointegritychecks on to skip the integrity checks. Likely it is possible to inject this option dynamically by modifying the LoadOptions, but this was not explored further Initially we opted to use bcdedit, but this can be detected from within the sandbox so instead we patch BmFwVerifySelfIntegrity. We are able to hook into winload.efi by replacing the boot services OpenProtocol function pointer. This function gets called by EfiOpenProtocol, which gets executed as part of winload!BlInitializeLibrary. In the hook we walk from the return address to the ImageBase and check if the image exports BlImgLoadPEImageEx. The OpenProtocol hook is then restored and the BlImgLoadPEImageEx function is detoured. This function is nice because it allows us to modify ntoskrnl.exe right after it is loaded (and before the entry point is called). If we detect the loaded image is ntoskrnl.exe we call HookNtoskrnl where we disable PatchGuard and DSE. EfiGuard patches very similar locations so we will not go into much detail here, but here is a quick overview: Driver Signature Enforcement is disabled by patching the parameter to CiInitialize in the function SepInitializeCodeIntegrity PatchGuard is disabled by modifying the KeInitAmd64SpecificState initialization routine Bonus: Logging from Windows Sandbox To debug the bootkit on a regular Hyper-V VM there is a great guide by tansadat. Unfortunately there is no known way to enable serial port output for Windows Sandbox (please reach out if you know of one) and we have to find a different way of getting logs out. Luckily for us Process Monitor allows us to see sandbox file system accesses (filter for vmwp.exe), which allows for a neat trick: accessing a file called \EFI\my log string. As long as we keep the path length under 256 characters and exclude certain characters this works great! A more primitive way of debugging is to just kill the VM at certain points to test if code is executing as expected: void Die() { // At least one of these should kill the VM __fastfail(1); __int2c(); __ud2(); *(UINT8*)0xFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFull = 1; } Bonus: Getting started with UEFI The SandboxBootkit project only uses the headers of the EDK2 project. This might not be convenient when starting out (we had to implement our own EfiQueryDevicePath for instance) and it might be easier to get started with the VisualUefi project. Final words That is all for now. You should now be able to load a driver like TitanHide without having to worry about enabling test signing or disabling PatchGuard! With a bit of registry modifications you should also be able to load DTrace (or the more hackable implementation STrace) to monitor syscalls happening inside the sandbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>secret club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risk-Based Continuous Authentication a Huge Hit at Gartner IAM 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=44906</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/risk-based-continuous-authentication-a-huge-hit-at-gartner-iam-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T16:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a breath of fresh air, so to speak, to be able to sponsor a live event after the long covid era. And it was even more exciting to show off of our next- generation Arculix platform to many of the 1,500 attendees at the 2022 Gartner IAM event in Las Vegas We got great […]
The post Risk-Based Continuous Authentication a Huge Hit at Gartner IAM 2022 appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jendres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Defender exploit protection using PowerShell and Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567451</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configure-defender-exploit-protection-using-powershell-and-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T15:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the term exploit protection, Microsoft brings together several technologies intended to protect against malware attacks. Among them are well-known features such as DEP, which has been around for a long time. While most mechanisms are active by default at the system level, you should still tune the settings for individual apps.
Configure Defender exploit protection using PowerShell and Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Pwn2Own Toronto 2022 and Introducing the SOHO Smashup!]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63067620e4ef9327f0ded618</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/8/29/announcing-pwn2own-toronto-2022-and-introducing-the-soho-smashup"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T15:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here. 
Our Fall Pwn2Own event has become a bit of a nomad, having gone from Amsterdam to Tokyo to Austin. This year, we’re heading to Toronto to celebrate the 10th anniversary of the contest formerly known as Mobile Pwn2Own. Since 2012, we’ve expanded the contest to include devices beyond phones. This year is no different, with devices typically found on homes and home offices.
Pwn2Own Toronto will be held at our Toronto office on December 6-8, 2022. While this year’s contest isn’t being held in conjunction with a conference, we still want contestants to attend in person. In fact, we want them there so much that we’re going to put our money where our mouth is by reimbursing $3,000 for travel expenses for teams that participate in Toront…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Attack Series: Backdooring Pickle Files]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/machine-learning-attack-series-injecting-code-pickle-files/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2022/machine-learning-attack-series-injecting-code-pickle-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T03:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I read this excellent post by Evan Sultanik about exploiting pickle files on Trail of Bits. There was also a DefCon30 talk about backdooring pickle files by ColdwaterQ.
This got me curious to try out backdooring a pickle file myself.
Pickle files - the surprises Surprisingly Python pickle files are compiled programs running in a VM called the Pickle Machine (PM). Opcodes control the flow, and when there are opcodes there is often fun to be had.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.16]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9403</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/08/27/update-1768-py-version-0-0-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T09:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a bug fix version and also adds updated statistics. 1768_v0_0_16.zip (http)MD5: E72E66BE5A66DC2C6E1806DE82DF9B39SHA256: 008E15C617EE94D849A3325643497D216E559609602E97CF2EE41968CCA5D096]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join Server Core to an Active Directory (AD) domain]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567419</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/join-server-core-to-an-active-directory-ad-domain/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T17:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you install Windows Server Core in your environment, there is no GUI or desktop experience to manage it. Admins who switch to Server Core from the desktop experience often face a slight learning curve. In this article, I will show you how to join a Server Core machine to an Active Directory (AD) domain with SConfig, PowerShell, or the command prompt.
Join Server Core to an Active Directory (AD) domain first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living off the land, AD CS style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25633</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/living-off-the-land-ad-cs-style/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T05:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Unless you have been living under a rock for the last year or so,  Active Directory Certificate Services (AD CS) abuse continues to be a hot topic in offensive […]
Living off the land, AD CS style first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release – JWT-Reauth]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=13399</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/25/tool-release-jwt-reauth/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When testing APIs with short-lived authentication tokens, it can be frustrating to login every few minutes, taking up a consultant’s time with an unnecessary cut+paste task — As well as introducing the possibility for human error in copying across the token, which can further hinder testing. Today we are releasing JWT-Reauth, a plugin aims to … Continue reading Tool Release – JWT-Reauth →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Leonard (they/them)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Windows Fax Server in Windows Server 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567383</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-windows-fax-server-in-windows-server-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Fax Server has been around for quite some time and is still part of Windows Server 2022. So what does it take to install and configure Windows Fax Server in Windows Server 2022?
Install Windows Fax Server in Windows Server 2022 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing the Family]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4104</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/securing-the-family/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Culture of Excellence Praetorian’s culture is one of delivering excellence to others, whether securing a client or securing the family–each other and at home. This is only possible when each employee takes responsibility for their role in maximizing the utility of that delivery. Each of our company core values boils down to the “what” and […]
The post Securing the Family appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magnifier: An Experiment with Interactive Decompilation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102590</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/08/25/magnifier-an-experiment-with-interactive-decompilation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alan Chang Today, we are releasing Magnifier, an experimental reverse engineering user interface I developed during my internship. Magnifier asks, “What if, as an alternative to taking handwritten notes, reverse engineering researchers could interactively reshape a decompiled program to reflect what they would normally record?” With Magnifier, the decompiled C code isn’t the end—it’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth + Electrical switchgear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=19697</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/bluetooth-electrical-switchgear/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T05:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing rapid growth of Industrial IoT (IIoT) across all business sectors continues to bring to focus the discrepancies that exist between the approaches to safety and cyber-security on safety […]
Bluetooth + Electrical switchgear first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JP Milne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cloud Security Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog outlining the new SANS Institute Cloud Security Curriculum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Security Expertise - Where Should You Begin?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cyber-security-expertise--where-should-you-begin-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cyber-security-expertise--where-should-you-begin-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Determine which SANS cybersecurity course is right for you to help you build foundational cybersecurity skills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable two-factor authentication for SSH in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567359</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-two-factor-authentication-for-ssh-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to enable two-factor authentication for SSH in Linux. Secure Shell (or SSH) is primarily used by admins to securely access and manage remote computers, particularly those running Linux. It supports two very common forms of authentication: password authentication and public key authentication. It is always recommended to use public key authentication for SSH access since it is more secure. However, if you still depend on password authentication, it is highly recommended to enable two-factor authentication.
Enable two-factor authentication for SSH in Linux first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Audi MMI Maps and Speedcams Update 2022/2023]]></title>
        <id>6302adfa8180697158e68e12</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/myaudi-maps2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T10:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update Audi Maps and Speedcams for free; files and steps are included for Maps 2022/2023. All without the need for OBDeleven or VCDS. This process will work for other VAG cars too not just Audi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST CSF 2.0 Workshop Themes: Praetorian’s View]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4178</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/nist-csf-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T17:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On 17 August 2022, NIST conducted the first Workshop to organize the effort to update the NIST Cybersecurity Framework (CSF) to version 2.0. Praetorian originally submitted comments to the CSF 2.0 RFI in February 2022. This Workshop provided a forum for NIST to frame the discussion around the major topics that emerged from the RFI. […]
The post NIST CSF 2.0 Workshop Themes: Praetorian’s View appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[But You Told Me You Were Safe: Attacking the Mozilla Firefox Renderer (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63010ae2dbdc0770f5103847</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/8/23/but-you-told-me-you-were-safe-attacking-the-mozilla-firefox-renderer-part-2"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T16:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of this series, we reviewed how Pwn2Own contestant Manfred Paul was able to compromise the Mozilla Firefox renderer process via a prototype pollution vulnerability in the await implementation. In modern browser architecture design, compromising the renderer gets us just half the way there, since the sandbox prevents further damage. In this blog post, we discuss a second prototype pollution vulnerability that allowed the execution of attacker-controlled JavaScript in the privileged parent process, escaping the sandbox. This vulnerability is known as CVE-2022-1529 and is tracked as ZDI-22-798 on the Zero Day Initiative advisory page. Mozilla fixed this vulnerability along with the first one in Firefox 100.0.2 via Mozilla Foundation Security Advisory 2022-19.
Root Cause
As d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hossein Lotfi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Graph: A single (PowerShell) API for Microsoft’s cloud services]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567323</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-graph-a-single-powershell-api-for-microsofts-cloud-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Graph is an API for accessing data in various Microsoft services, including Azure Active Directory, Teams, and OneDrive. If you want to use it in PowerShell, you only need a single module instead of one for each cloud service. In scripts, it eliminates the need for separate authentication for each service.
Microsoft Graph: A single (PowerShell) API for Microsoft’s cloud services first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roland Eich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuration Items in Configuration Manager (SCCM, MECM)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567289</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configuration-items-in-configuration-manager-sccm-mecm/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T16:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Endpoint Configuration Manager (MECM), formerly System Center Configuration Manager (SCCM) is systems management software that comes with several compliance-related features, including the ability to deploy configuration baselines (CBs) and configuration items (CIs) to ensure that the endpoints in your environment remain compliant with your organization's security policies. In this guide, I will show you how to create CIs and BIs, run compliance reports, and, if applicable, remediation scripts.
Configuration Items in Configuration Manager (SCCM, MECM) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Pazik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Base-N Decoding for Text-Only Compression and Obfuscation]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5210</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2022/08/22/base_n_compression/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Concise Binary Object Representation (CBOR), the binary equivalent to JavaScript Object Notation (JSON), is ideal for storing a configuration to a shellcode/stager/loader. I’ve always wanted support for text-only compression to store API strings and URLs. CBOR currently doesn’t support … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to know, what to learn? What are useful skills for cyber in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8139</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/08/19/what-to-know-what-to-learn-what-are-useful-skills-for-cyber-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T23:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~12 years ago I felt I am on the top of the (blue side of cyber) world. I knew Windows forensics pretty well, Linux forensics far less, but with some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Password as a (Yara) Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8199</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/08/19/password-as-a-yara-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T21:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent Twitter exchange with Tim I mentioned my earlier post in which I described a practice of crypto code copypasting being quite prevalent. Such practice is problematic of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Defender Antivirus using Intune]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567252</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-defender-antivirus-using-intune/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T19:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defender Antivirus is Microsoft's built-in antivirus, available in Windows 10/11 and Windows Server. You can manage this security component using Group Policies, PowerShell, or the Settings app. However, reporting and monitoring capabilities are only provided via the subscription-based Defender for Endpoint. Alternatively, you can use Intune for this purpose.
Manage Defender Antivirus using Intune first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back in Black: Unlocking a LockBit 3.0 Ransomware Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16889</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/19/back-in-black-unlocking-a-lockbit-3-0-ransomware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T14:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores some of the TTPs employed by a threat actor who were observed deploying LockBit 3.0 ransomware during an incident response engagement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RIFT: Research and Intelligence Fusion Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase the Outlook attachment size limit]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567229</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-increase-the-attachment-size-limit-in-outlook/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you ever try to attach a file larger than 20 MB in Outlook? If so, you probably received this error message: The file you're attaching is bigger than the server allows. Try putting the file in a shared location and sending a link instead. In this post, you will learn how tot increase the Outlook attachment size limit.
Increase the Outlook attachment size limit first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Detection: Tactical to Functional]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/fef1e09d3174</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-detection-tactical-to-functional-fef1e09d3174?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 5: Expanding the Operation Graph]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intercept Flutter traffic on iOS and Android (HTTP/HTTPS/Dio Pinning)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12049</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/08/18/intercept-flutter-traffic-on-ios-and-android-http-https-dio-pinning/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some time ago I wrote some articles on how to Man-In-The-Middle Flutter on iOS, Android (ARM) and Android (ARM64). Those posts were quite popular and I often went back to copy those scripts myself. Last week, however, we received a Flutter application where the script wouldn’t work anymore. As we had the source code, it … Continue reading Intercept Flutter traffic on iOS and Android (HTTP/HTTPS/Dio Pinning) →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeroen Beckers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[But You Told Me You Were Safe: Attacking the Mozilla Firefox Renderer (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:62fd3fbdcea0b95fd2ab97ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/8/17/but-you-told-me-you-were-safe-attacking-the-mozilla-firefox-renderer-part-1"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerabilities and exploits in common targets like browsers are often associated with memory safety issues. Typically this involves either a direct error in memory management or a way to corrupt internal object state in the JavaScript engine. One way to eliminate such memory safety issues is to use a memory-safe language such as Rust or even JavaScript itself. At Pwn2Own Vancouver 2022, Manfred Paul compromised the Mozilla Firefox browser using a full chain exploit that broke the mold. Although his exploit used some memory corruptions, the vulnerable code was written in a memory-safe programming language: JavaScript! In fact, both vulnerabilities used in the chain were related to one rather notorious language aspect of JavaScript – prototypes. In this blog, we will look at the first vulne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hossein Lotfi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 3 – Trends in the Cybersecurity Talent Marketplace in the Face of Sustained Shortages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3910</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/marketplace-talent-shortage/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T13:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve written previously about how I believe a team’s expertise and talent are the most important factors in determining the success of a cybersecurity program. I’d like to elaborate a bit more on how I think that is affecting the marketplace for cybersecurity expertise and what it means for people operations. To summarize my previous […]
The post Part 3 – Trends in the Cybersecurity Talent Marketplace in the Face of Sustained Shortages appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.15]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9389</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/08/17/update-1768-py-version-0-0-15/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T22:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some new features that help with analyzing memory dumps. Here is the analysis of a VMware vmem file: There’s a new sanity check, determining if an extracted configuration is OK or not OK (NOK). A config passes the sanity check if it contains a valid payload type and a valid public key. Configurations that don’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using mutants to improve Slither]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102567</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/08/17/using-mutants-to-improve-slither/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T13:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alex Groce, Northern Arizona University Improving static analysis tools can be hard; once you’ve implemented a good tool based on a useful representation of a program and added a large number of rules to detect problems, how do you further enhance the tool’s bug-finding power? One (necessary) approach to coming up with new rules […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Google Chrome or Microsoft Edge with Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567211</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-google-chrome-or-microsoft-edge-with-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T12:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Google Chrome using Group Policy is not a new idea. Because Microsoft Edge, as you may know, is based on Chromium, you can update your Group Policies to manage Edge as well.
Manage Google Chrome or Microsoft Edge with Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing ICS/OT Engineering Cyber Defense Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/developing-ics-ot-engineering-cyber-defense-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/developing-ics-ot-engineering-cyber-defense-teams?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve seen increased threats including ransomware and tailored ICS-specific attacks against engineering control systems.  As such the shift has also changed the security job tasks, security roles, and knowledge required to now perform ICS security for the protection of these engineering processes in today’s threat landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wheel of Fortune Outcome Prediction – Taking the Luck out of Gambling]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16733</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/16/wheel-of-fortune-outcome-prediction-taking-the-luck-out-of-gambling/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T19:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authored by: Jesús Miguel Calderón Marín Introduction Two years ago I carried out research into online casino games specifically focusing on roulette. As a result, I composed a detailed guide with information on classification of online roulette, potential vulnerabilities and the ways to detect them[1]. Although this guideline was particularly well-received by the security community, … Continue reading Wheel of Fortune Outcome Prediction – Taking the Luck out of Gambling →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesús Calderón Marín</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Jenkins]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567192</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/getting-started-with-jenkins/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T18:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will get you started with Jenkins, an open-source automation tool written in Java. It's a popular choice when it comes to continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD ) tools. We will explore what Jenkins can be used for, its features, and the terms associated with a pipeline.
Getting started with Jenkins first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Beer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding a New Mitigation: Module Tampering Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=484181</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/understanding-a-new-mitigation-module-tampering-protection/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=understanding-a-new-mitigation-module-tampering-protection"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T16:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[…]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Detection: Tactical to Functional]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5ff667af633b</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-detection-tactical-to-functional-5ff667af633b?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T14:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 4: Compound Functions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure attack surface reduction in Microsoft Defender using Group Policy or PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567184</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configure-attack-surface-reduction-in-microsoft-defender-using-group-policy-or-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T12:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the virus scanner, Microsoft Defender offers other security functions. These include the reduction of the attack surface, which hardens applications such as Office, browsers, and Adobe Reader. The feature is not active by default and can be configured via group policies or PowerShell.
Configure attack surface reduction in Microsoft Defender using Group Policy or PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database Integrity Vulnerabilities in Boeing’s Onboard Performance Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25530</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/database-integrity-vulnerabilities-in-boeings-onboard-performance-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-13T03:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is released in a co-ordinated manner with Boeing. TL;DR: Security gaps in older, unprotected Windows desktop versions of Boeing’s Onboard Performance Tool (OPT) could make certain Electronic Flight […]
Database Integrity Vulnerabilities in Boeing’s Onboard Performance Tool first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Lomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Quarantine Policies in Microsoft 365]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567168</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configure-quarantine-policies-in-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T15:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email security is important for every Microsoft 365 tenant, and the configuration of quarantine policies is a critical part of this. Every Microsoft 365 administrator has to decide the manner in which their tenant will react to spam, phishing, and malicious content in emails. One possible action is to quarantine such emails. In this post, you will learn the technicalities of configuring quarantine policies in Microsoft 365.
Configure Quarantine Policies in Microsoft 365 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The road to the apprenticeship]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=102550</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/08/12/the-road-to-the-apprenticeship/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T13:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Josselin Feist, Principal Security Engineer Finding talent is hard, especially in the blockchain security industry. The space is new, so you won’t find engineers with decades of experience with smart contracts. Training is difficult, as the technology evolves constantly, and online content quickly becomes outdated. There are also a lot of misconceptions about blockchain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW DFIR COURSE DEVELPOMENT SURVEY | FOR478]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/new-dfir-course-develpoment-survey-for478</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/new-dfir-course-develpoment-survey-for478?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within this  survey, we would like to seek input on level of interest, topical coverage, and course duration with an emphasis on the underpinning elements of cyber threat analysis and analytic tradecraft]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Disclosure Timelines for Bugs Resulting from Incomplete Patches]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:62eaac22d55b06120db85e4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/8/11/new-disclosure-timelines-for-bugs-from-faulty-patches"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today at the Black Hat USA conference, we announced some new disclosure timelines. Our standard 120-day disclosure timeline for most vulnerabilities remains, but for bug reports that result from faulty or incomplete patches, we will use a shorter timeline. Moving forward, the ZDI will adopt a tiered approach based on the severity of the bug and the efficacy of the original fix. The first tier will be a 30-day timeframe for most Critical-rated cases where exploitation is detected or expected. The second level will be a 60-day interval for Critical- and High-severity bugs where the patch offers some protections. Finally, there will be a 90-day period for other severities where no imminent exploitation is expected. As with our normal timelines, extensions will be limited and granted on a case…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Windows Terminal as admin]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567153</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/run-windows-terminal-as-admin/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T15:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like with cmd.exe or PowerShell, you often have to run Windows Terminal as admin to execute commands that need elevated privileges. In Windows Terminal, you can configure the elevation of privileges for an individual shell or for all shells. However, you have to expect some inconsistencies and peculiarities.
Run Windows Terminal as admin first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting DNS implants: Old kitten, new tricks – A Saitama Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16708</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/11/detecting-dns-implants-old-kitten-new-tricks-a-saitama-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T15:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Groot & Ruud van Luijk TL;DR A recently uncovered malware sample dubbed ‘Saitama’ was uncovered by security firm Malwarebytes in a weaponized document, possibly targeted towards the Jordan government. This Saitama implant uses DNS as its sole Command and Control channel and utilizes long sleep times and (sub)domain randomization to evade detection. As no … Continue reading Detecting DNS implants: Old kitten, new tricks – A Saitama Case Study  →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Groot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The quantum state of Linux kernel garbage collection CVE-2021-0920 (Part I)]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/08/the-quantum-state-of-linux-kernel.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/08/the-quantum-state-of-linux-kernel.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T23:00:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=wJuDEFlUsDZt7lpAAPdLm9CoNqneSjGN6FUREF5POP9krml-9Eg4KzR8naUO0aF3kuG_eoWNft1SfWZjF8JeEg');.lst-kix_wm3dnufq67dx-7>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_wm3dnufq67dx-8>li:before{content:"-  "}ol.lst-kix_iptxq54yrrnf-3.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_iptxq54yrrnf-3 0}.lst-kix_u3opzkdcnklc-1>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_u3opzkdcnklc-1}.lst-kix_wm3dnufq67dx-1>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_iptxq54yrrnf-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_iptxq54yrrnf-4}ol.lst-kix_mfudkcwv2w89-7.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_mfudkcwv2w89-7 0}.lst-kix_wm3dnufq67dx-0>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_hk8k8itxmlfp-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_hk8k8itxmlfp-4}.lst-kix_8chkxhfzc2ds-3>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_8chkxhfzc2ds-5>li:before{content…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browser-Powered Desync Attacks: A New Frontier in HTTP Request Smuggling]]></title>
        <id>browser-powered-desync-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/browser-powered-desync-attacks"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent rise of HTTP Request Smuggling has seen a flood of critical findings enabling near-complete compromise of numerous major websites. However, the threat has been confined to attacker-accessib]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robocopy usage examples]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567140</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/robocopy-usage-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robocopy (Robust File Copy) is a command line folder and file replication tool available as a standard Windows feature since Windows Server 2008. The goal of this post is to give you a quick start guide by providing some Robocopy examples.
Robocopy usage examples first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EventSentry 5: SIEM & Monitoring with many new features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567125</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/eventsentry-5-siem-monitoring-with-many-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping an eye on activities and logs in the environment is a crucial aspect of cybersecurity and requires businesses to have the right tools to monitor network and system events. EventSentry is a networking monitoring tool that provides many capabilities for organizations looking to keep an eye on the environment. In addition, the recent release of version 5 offers many new features.
EventSentry 5: SIEM & Monitoring with many new features first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The August 2022 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:62ea9641816a3c749cba539d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/8/9/the-august-2022-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T17:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second Tuesday of the month, and the last second Tuesday before Black Hat and DEFCON, which means Microsoft and Adobe have released their latest security fixes. Take a break from packing (if you’re headed to hacker summer camp) or your normal activities and join us as we review the details of their latest patches and updates.
Adobe Patches for August 2022
For August, Adobe addressed 25 CVEs in five patches for Adobe Acrobat and Reader, Commerce, Illustrator, FrameMaker, and Adobe Premier Elements. A total of 13 of these bugs were reported through the ZDI program. The update for Acrobat and Reader addresses three Critical-rated and four Important-rated bugs. The critical vulnerabilities could allow code execution if an attacker could convince a user to open a specially crafted file…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Detection: Tactical to Functional]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/45e41fef7af4</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-detection-tactical-to-functional-45e41fef7af4?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 3: Expanding the Function Call Graph]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Outside the Mailbox: Modernized Phishing Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4132</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/modernized-phishing-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T13:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As defensive controls have advanced, so too have adversaries’ approaches to social engineering. Landing a phishing email in an inbox has become harder, and most campaigns that do make it to an inbox are quickly reported, quarantined, or triaged. So, adversaries have asked themselves why not skip the inbox all together or leverage a service […]
The post Thinking Outside the Mailbox: Modernized Phishing Techniques appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS DFIR Summit 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-dfir-summit-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-dfir-summit-2022?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS DFIR Summit 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving MBA Deobfuscation using Equality Saturation]]></title>
        <id>https://secret.club/2022/08/08/eqsat-oracle-synthesis.html</id>
        <link href="https://secret.club/2022/08/08/eqsat-oracle-synthesis.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post will first give a brief overview of obfuscation based on Mixed-Boolean-Arithmetic (MBA), how it has historically been attacked and what are the known limitations. The main focus will then shift to an extension of the oracle-based synthesis approach, detailing how combining program synthesis with the equality saturation technique produces significantly more simplification opportunities. Finally, a set of examples spanning from different MBA categories over unsolved limitations up to future work ideas will hopefully serve as food for thoughts to the reader. Across the post, references to existing research are provided to delve into additional details and deepen the understanding of the topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>secret club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing the Castryck-Decru SIDH Key Recovery Attack in SageMath]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=16638</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/08/08/implementing-the-castryck-decru-sidh-key-recovery-attack-in-sagemath/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T21:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Last weekend (July 30th) a truly incredible piece of mathematical/cryptanalysis research was put onto eprint. Wouter Castryck and Thomas Decru of KU Leuven published a paper “An efficient key recovery attack on SIDH (preliminary version)” describing a new attack on the Supersingular Isogeny Diffie-Hellman (SIDH) protocol together with a corresponding proof-of-concept implementation. SIDH is … Continue reading Implementing the Castryck-Decru SIDH Key Recovery Attack in SageMath →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giacomo Pope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exchange impersonation: Grant permissions to service accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567111</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/exchange-impersonation-grant-permissions-to-service-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T19:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations use software that needs access to users' mailboxes. In this case, it makes sense to assign the necessary permissions centrally. Exchange provides the impersonation role for this, which can act on behalf of the respective users.
Exchange impersonation: Grant permissions to service accounts first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roland Eich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corb3nik Introduces Caido!]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/corb3nik-introduces-caido</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/corb3nik-introduces-caido"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T03:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, who is Corb3nik?
My name is Ian, also known as Corb3nik on social media. I’m a long time CTF enthusiast and bug bounty hunter. Currentl]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesse@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week of Data Dumps, Part 7 – registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8195</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/08/06/week-of-data-dumps-part-7-registry/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T20:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This one is not a surprise, I hope. Most of forensic artifacts come from either file- or Registry- oriented artifacts. Of course, there is a macOS&OS/X world out there, there […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[H1-702 Las Vegas Day 3: Switching Up Scopes]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/community-blog/h1-702-las-vegas-day-3-switching-scopes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/community-blog/h1-702-las-vegas-day-3-switching-scopes"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T04:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a new day with new challenges. Scope has shifted for the next part of our LHE. Today, you can feel the focus. These hackers have been heads do]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesse@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week of Data Dumps, Part 6 – file names]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8189</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/08/05/week-of-data-dumps-part-6-file-names/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T20:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week is longer than I thought, so time to catch up… 🙂 This one is a mess, but sometimes a bit of a mess is not a bad thing. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hot Authentication Space Is Fueled Further by the Ping Identity Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=44856</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/hot-authentication-space-is-fueled-further-by-the-ping-identity-acquisition/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T18:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thoma Bravo’s investment in the IAM and authentication space continues with another massive ($2.8B) acquisition of Ping Identity on the heels of announcing that it intends to acquire SailPoint later this year. I believe it’s a great transaction for both sides. Shareholders of Ping get a nice exit after the stock was trading near its […]
The post Hot Authentication Space Is Fueled Further by the Ping Identity Acquisition appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get AD user group membership with Get-ADPrincipalGroupMembership]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567100</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/get-ad-user-group-membership-with-get-adprincipalgroupmembership/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T16:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Get-ADPrincipalGroupMembership PowerShell cmdlet enables you to query all the Active Directory group memberships of a user. In this tutorial, you'll learn to work with Get-ADPrincipalGroupMembership, and see how you can use this useful cmdlet to quickly and easily use a PowerShell one-liner to search and see whether a user is a member of a particular Active Directory group. Simply put, if your organization uses Active Directory security groups, the ability to use this cmdlet is an absolute must.
Get AD user group membership with Get-ADPrincipalGroupMembership first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Greenhaus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding hooks with windbg]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12164</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/08/05/finding-hooks-with-windbg/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T15:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blogpost we are going to look into hooks, how to find them, and how to restore the original functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Bachtik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maritime regulation. All Hands-on Deck!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=25437</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/maritime-regulation-all-hands-on-deck/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T05:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The regulation from the IMO has changed, you need to do more about cyber security. Key things to focus on:  Start asking questions of your supply chain, of your […]
Maritime regulation. All Hands-on Deck!  first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[H1-702 Las Vegas Day 2: Hacking with Zoom]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/community-blog/h1-702-las-vegas-day-2-hacking-zoom</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/community-blog/h1-702-las-vegas-day-2-hacking-zoom"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T04:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to our first day of in-person hacking! We had some lovely people greeting you today for your check-in. Again, we want all of our hacker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesse@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping SANS FOR578 Coverage to the Mandiant CTI Core Competencies Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/mapping-sans-for578-coverage-to-the-mandiant-cti-core-competencies-framework</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/mapping-sans-for578-coverage-to-the-mandiant-cti-core-competencies-framework?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Needs Macros? | Threat Actors Pivot to Abusing Explorer and Other LOLBins via Windows Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=69136</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/who-needs-macros-threat-actors-pivot-to-abusing-explorer-and-other-lolbins-via-windows-shortcuts/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T15:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crimeware vendors say 'macros are dead', but they have a new weapon to help threat actors successfully deploy malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Detection: Tactical to Functional]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/37ddcd75234b</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-detection-tactical-to-functional-37ddcd75234b?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T14:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2: Operations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of support for Office (2013, 2016, 2019):  No Microsoft 365 access, and outdated OS versions]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1567070</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/the-end-for-office-apps-office-2013-2016-2019-no-further-support-no-microsoft-365-access-and-outdated-os-versions/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T13:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditionally, the Office applications followed a lifecycle of five years each in mainstream and extended support. However, the situation is now more complicated because the apps are also limited in their use by being disconnected from the Microsoft 365 cloud services or when being run on an outdated Windows.
End of support for Office (2013, 2016, 2019):  No Microsoft 365 access, and outdated OS versions first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, No Case Studies—But . . .]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e7cf012af19807518fba2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/sorry-no-case-study"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend of the site recently suggested that we create a current-issue case 
study using our updated risk discovery approach. “It’s a great idea,” we 
replied and immediately started kicking around ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pointillism of Daily Events]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2c8f009baa12346d3711f</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/pointillism-daily-events"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Baker’s book Human Smoke brilliantly illustrates a unique approach 
to historical narrative. It also underscores the need to remember that 
every artist paints with intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ready for What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2aa91391dcb70804f9850</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/getting-ready-whats-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new age of giant monsters, advanced awareness of classical 
surprise—that one big tipping moment—no longer suffices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Your ‘Free Cells’ Mindfully]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62deb6110fd7f314e5696ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/manage-free-cells"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accommodate but don’t fight the limitations you can’t control, recognize 
those you can influence and leverage, and don't imagine you have more free 
cells than you actually do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popski’s Planning]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d81b5affdc983dd1f616f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/popskis-planning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British officer Vladimir Peniakoff’s approach to planning might sound a bit 
unorthodox at first, but it aligns nicely with Patton’s view of 
intelligence and speaks to an enduring need to understand front-line 
conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a New Game Board]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d5b6db0343fb487527fc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/time-for-a-new-game-board"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need a more flexible game board where players can explore hypergame 
strategies—in other words, a game board where the strategist can play the 
hero for a change. We’ve built it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survivors Exceeded the Minimum]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62cf11283f1bdb1191fcdf9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/survivors-exceeded-minimum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T18:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every surprise is a cunning thunderbolt. Some surprises creep up 
slowly, rusting away former resilience until a simple nudge reveals the 
rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>