<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-09-02T00:43:43.409Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: API Hashing with Block Ciphers (Maru4)]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5609</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/09/01/shellcode-api-hashing-with-block-ciphers-maru4/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T16:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Constructing your own hash algorithm is controversial because there will always be professionals in the field of cryptography and engineering that can expose vulnerabilities in the design. I’m not encouraging anyone to construct a cryptographic hash algorithm without extensive … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in August]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10541</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/09/01/overview-of-content-published-in-august-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T15:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in August: SANS ISC Diary entries: OOXML Spreadsheets Protected By Verifier Hashes Wireshark 4.4.0rc1’s Custom Columns Wireshark 4.4.0 is now available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: RSA (Data Masking 4)]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5595</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/08/31/masking4/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T15:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Malware like OceanLotus have used RSA-256 to hide strings. Darkhotel used RSA to hide code. For fun, some crackmes used RSA-32 or RSA-64 for simple keygen challenges. The RSA cryptosystem uses two exponents (or keys) and a modulus derived … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Pseudo-Random Involution (Data Masking 3)]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5569</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/08/30/shellcode-pris/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T18:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Not sure if the title is an accurate description, but when you apply a self-inverse permutation or involution twice, you get back the original data and that’s pretty much what the code shown in this post does. There’s a … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne’s Commitment to Learning and Development]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-commitment-learning-and-development</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-commitment-learning-and-development"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T16:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox 7.1: New features of the free  desktop virtualzation tool]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586171</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/virtualbox-71-new-features-of-the-free-desktop-virtualzation-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T15:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox, the popular open-source virtualization software from Oracle, has recently released its 7.1 Beta version, bringing exciting new features and improvements. The new update aims to improve the user experience and performance, ensuring that VirtualBox remains a viable option in the desktop virtualization market. This post focuses on the new features, thoroughly summarizing what users can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to enhance the security of your social media accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29545</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-to-enhance-the-security-of-your-social-media-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR  Strong passwords: Use a password manager. Multi-factor authentication (MFA): MFA requires multiple forms of identification, adding an extra layer of security. This makes it harder for unauthorised users to […]
How to enhance the security of your social media accounts first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentesting for iOS Mobile Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/ios-mobile-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/ios-mobile-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T21:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the different methodologies and best practices for pentesting for iOS applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul De Baldo V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SquaredUp Cloud: Comprehensive monitoring and dashboard solution for a wide range of on-prem and cloud services]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585869</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/squaredup-cloud-comprehensive-monitoring-and-dashboard-solution-for-a-wide-range-of-on-prem-and-cloud-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T18:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SquaredUp Cloud allows the creation of dashboards and visualizations of data as a SaaS solution with many sharing options, 70+ plugins, custom APIs, and on-prem integration for hybrid cloud monitoring. The dashboard solution is easy to set up and has many features and integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in July]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10539</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/08/29/overview-of-content-published-in-july-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in July: Blog posts: Update: hash.py Version 0.0.13 Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.77 Update: cut-bytes.py Version 0.0.17 SANS ISC Diary entries: 16-bit Hash Collisions in .xls Spreadsheets Wireshark 4.2.6 Released Protected OOXML Spreadsheets Create Your Own BSOD: NotMyFault Quickie: Password Cracking & Energy CrowdStrike Outage Themed Maldoc]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the VirusTotal Dataset | An Analyst’s Guide to Effective Threat Research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=104092</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/exploring-the-virustotal-dataset-an-analysts-guide-to-effective-threat-research/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T09:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We teamed up with VirusTotal to take a deep dive into the platform's extensive query capabilities through both the web and API interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski &amp; Jose Luis Sánchez Martínez (VirusTotal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big TIBER Encyclopedia]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18027</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/08/29/the-big-tiber-encyclopedia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of current TIBER implementations ahead of DORA’s TLPT requirements Introduction TIBER (Threat Intelligence-Based Ethical Red Teaming) is a framework introduced by the European Central Bank (ECB) in 2018 as a response to the increasing number of cyber threats faced by financial institutions. The framework provides a standardized methodology and guidelines for conducting controlled … Continue reading The Big TIBER Encyclopedia →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bauters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3CX Phone System Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3094</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/3cx-phone-system-local-privilege-escalation-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T22:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Recently, we decided to take a look at the 3CX Phone Management System with the goal of identifying an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability within […]
The post 3CX Phone System Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenneth King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Hai Facilitates Clear and Effective Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/hai-facilitates-effective-communication</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/hai-facilitates-effective-communication"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T21:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HackerOne's AI co-pilot, Hai, bridges communication gaps and streamlines collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythic 3.3 — Out of Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9979e82660c3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/mythic-3-3-out-of-beta-9979e82660c3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T19:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythic 3.3 was released in a Beta six weeks ago, and since then there has been a bunch of feedback, not just about new Mythic 3.3 features…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cody Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Purview AI Hub – Monitor and block AI applications]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586139</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-purview-ai-hub-monitor-and-block-ai-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T16:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Purview is a data governance and compliance solution tailored for Microsoft's ecosystem, predominantly used in Microsoft 365. Microsoft Purview AI Hub is a feature within the platform that secures and proactively monitors AI applications, such as Microsoft Copilot for Microsoft 365 and third-party large language models (LLMs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-37079: VMware vCenter Server Integer Underflow Code Execution Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66ce3dcb39b07158e559220d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/8/27/cve-2024-37079-vmware-vcenter-server-integer-underflow-code-execution-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Grigory Dorodnov and Guy Lederfein of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched code execution vulnerability in the VMware vCenter Server. This bug was originally discovered by Hao Zheng and Zibo Li from TianGong Team of Legendsec at Qi'anxin Group. Successfully exploiting this vulnerability could lead to a heap buffer overflow, which could result in the execution of arbitrary code in the context of the vulnerable service. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2024-37079, with a few minimal modifications.
An integer underflow vulnerability has been reported for VMware vCenter Server. The vulnerability is due to a lack of validation of the calculated response header size u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offensive Security Under the EU Digital Operational Resilience Act (DORA)]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/offensive-security-eu-dora</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/offensive-security-eu-dora"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the EU's new DORA regulation and how financial entities and their ICT vendors must promptly align their security frameworks with DORA's requirements to mitigate potential risks and ensure operational stability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harley Geiger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter ❤ Tool Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2dfbb952eb8a</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-tool-integration-2dfbb952eb8a?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incorporating new components into existing systems is such a pain, this process has been labeled “Integration Hell”. To ease tool…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Sou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Provisioning cloud infrastructure the wrong way, but faster]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108061</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/08/27/provisioning-cloud-infrastructure-the-wrong-way-but-faster/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg Today we’re going to provision some cloud infrastructure the Max Power way: by combining automation with unchecked AI output. Unfortunately, this method produces cloud infrastructure code that 1) works and 2) has terrible security properties. In a nutshell, AI-based tools like Claude and ChatGPT readily provide extremely bad cloud infrastructure provisioning code, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-37888 – CKEditor 4 Open Link plugin XSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25306</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/web-application-pentesting/cve-2024-37888-ckeditor-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NetSPI discovered CVE-2024-37888, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CKEditor 4 Open Link plugin. Read about the nature of the vulnerability and its implications.
The post CVE-2024-37888 – CKEditor 4 Open Link plugin XSS appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anurag Mondal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Maintenance Burden by Bending C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we look at how we were able to use new C features and GCC plugin additions to eliminate over a megabyte of changes from grsecurity patches without any change in functionality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Maintenance Burden by Bending C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we look at how we were able to use new C features and GCC plugin additions to eliminate over a megabyte of changes from grsecurity patches without any change in functionality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Copilot: From Prompt Injection to Exfiltration of Personal Information]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/m365-copilot-prompt-injection-tool-invocation-and-data-exfil-using-ascii-smuggling/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/m365-copilot-prompt-injection-tool-invocation-and-data-exfil-using-ascii-smuggling/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post describes vulnerability in Microsoft 365 Copilot that allowed the theft of a user’s emails and other personal information. This vulnerability warrants a deep dive, because it combines a variety of novel attack techniques that are not even two years old.

I initially disclosed parts of this exploit to Microsoft in January, and then the full exploit chain in February 2024. A few days ago I got the okay from MSRC to disclose this report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory auditing with ManageEngine ADAudit Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586073</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/active-directory-auditing-with-manageengine-adaudit-plus/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most organizations view Microsoft Active Directory as a "black box," lacking full visibility into its activities. ManageEngine ADAudit Plus aims to change that with its Active Directory auditing solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ring Around The Regex: Lessons learned from fuzzing regex libraries (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://secret.club/2024/08/23/ring-around-the-regex-2.html</id>
        <link href="https://secret.club/2024/08/23/ring-around-the-regex-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a little late (one whole month passed in a blink of an eye!). Let’s catch up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>secret club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Volume Email in Microsoft 365: Overcoming sending limits]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585881</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/high-volume-email-in-microsoft-365-overcoming-sending-limits/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T15:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sending a high number of emails in Microsoft 365 without hitting the throttling limits has always been an issue. Microsoft has introduced a new feature called High Volume Email to address this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Try it for yourself: the latest PortSwigger Research from Black Hat USA]]></title>
        <id>try-it-for-yourself-the-latest-portswigger-research-from-black-hat-usa</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/try-it-for-yourself-the-latest-portswigger-research-from-black-hat-usa"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T07:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The modern web is constantly developing, with new potential vulnerabilities emerging all the time. Ensuring your web applications are secure in the face of this evolving threat is a constant challenge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to root an Android device for analysis and vulnerability assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29465</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-to-root-an-android-device-for-analysis-and-vulnerability-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T05:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Rooting is useful for Android assessments The process is relatively simple It will wipe all user data from the device and void any warranty Introduction For mobile testing, be […]
How to root an Android device for analysis and vulnerability assessment first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lovett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Pwn2Own Automotive: Taking Over the Autel Maxicharger]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66c778414d92b844416f5702</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/8/22/from-pwn2own-automotive-taking-over-the-autel-maxicharger"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T17:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog highlights two vulnerabilities that were disclosed by researchers from Synacktiv in the Autel Maxicharger firmware at the Pwn2Own Automotive 2024 event and how Autel responded to and patched these in their latest firmware release.
At the Pwn2Own event,  the Synacktiv researchers demonstrated two unique remote attacks on the Autel Maxicharger running firmware v1.32 that demonstrated RCE.  Autel was later informed of these issues and they responded with firmware update v1.35 before ZDI publicly disclosed the research to the public. The first vulnerability we discuss in this blog was addressed in ZDI-24-851, while the second is covered by ZDI-24-852. In this blog, we describe the reverse engineering process used to find the vulnerabilities in the original firmware and how ZDI observ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thanos Kaliyanakis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zed vs. VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585995</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/zed-vs-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T15:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its debut in 2015, Visual Studio Code (VS Code) has become the preferred code editor for most developers. A 2023 Stack Overflow survey revealed that 73% of users favored VS Code. It is free and packed with features and extensions. So why did I switch to Zed?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Beer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google AI Studio: LLM-Powered Data Exfiltration Hits Again! Quickly Fixed.]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-ai-studio-data-exfiltration-now-fixed/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-ai-studio-data-exfiltration-now-fixed/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T02:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I found what appeared to be a regression or bypass that again allowed data exfiltration via image rendering during prompt injection. See the previous post here for reference.
Data Exfiltration via Rendering HTML Image Tags During re-testing, I had sporadic success with markdown rendering tricks, but eventually, I was able to drastically simplify the exploit by asking directly for an HTML image tag.
This behavior might actually have existed all along, as Google AI Studio hadn’t yet implemented any kind of Content Security Policy to prevent communication with arbitrary domains using images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS DFIR Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-dfir-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-dfir-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS DFIR Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life at SpecterOps: The Red Team Dream]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/0713b1c59ae1</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/life-at-specterops-the-red-team-dream-0713b1c59ae1?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T16:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come work with us!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Duane Michael</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon23 Replay | Black Magic – Influence Operations in the Open and At-Scale in Hungary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=103772</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon23-replay-black-magic-influence-operations-in-the-open-and-at-scale-in-hungary/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T16:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As electorates across the US and Europe go to the polls in 2024, this must-see talk on large-scale state influence operations could hardly be more timely or relevant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Send email notifications about expiring Active Directory passwords with a PowerShell script]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585957</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/send-users-email-notifications-about-expiring-active-directory-passwords-with-a-powershell-script/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T15:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enforcing a policy for regular password changes is no longer recommended, as it can result in more helpdesk requests due to expired passwords, especially for VPN users, and may actually undermine security. However, timely notifications can help mitigate issues when password changes are necessary. Learn how to notify users with Group Policy or a PowerShell script.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teach a Man to Phish]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/43528846e382</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/teach-a-man-to-phish-43528846e382?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T14:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Decade of Distilled Phishing Wisdom]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction to GCPwn – Parts 2 and  3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25186</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/introduction-to-gcpwn-parts-2-and-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Example exploit path using GCPwn covering enumeration, brute forcing secrets manager versions, and downloading data from cloud storage both through default enum_buckets and with HMAC keys.
The post An Introduction to GCPwn – Parts 2 and  3 appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“YOLO” is not a valid hash construction]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107981</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/08/21/yolo-is-not-a-valid-hash-construction/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Opal Wright Among the cryptographic missteps we see at Trail of Bits, “let’s build our own tool out of a hash function” is one of the most common. Clients have a problem along the lines of “we need to hash a bunch of different values together” or “we need a MAC” or “we need […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Hacking Tools and Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ethical-hacker/100-hacking-tools-and-resources</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ethical-hacker/100-hacking-tools-and-resources"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve just started hacking or are a real pro, we’ve created the ultimate list of 100 hacking tools for your toolkit!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shlomie Liberow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Microsoft 365 Backup?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585931</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/what-is-microsoft-365-backup/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T16:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 Backup is a new solution for recovering and restoring data in case of malicious or accidental deletion. It provides coverage for critical data by backing up SharePoint sites, OneDrive accounts, and Exchange mailboxes. Third-party backup solutions for Microsoft 365 typically provide more comprehensive features, granular control, and cross-platform capabilities for organizations with complex needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail Under Attack: 6 Learnings from a Retail Customer]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/retail-under-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/retail-under-attack"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T16:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss sportswear brand On provides insights into the threats to the retail industry and how human-powered security addresses them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Fleming</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the Uncharted: A Framework for Attack Path Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c5a0a020a144</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/navigating-the-uncharted-a-framework-for-attack-path-discovery-c5a0a020a144?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T14:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second post in a series on Identity-Driven Offensive Tradecraft, which is also the focus of the new course we will launch in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elad Shamir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Browser Stored Credentials]]></title>
        <id>http://pentestlab.blog/?p=34081</id>
        <link href="https://pentestlab.blog/2024/08/20/web-browser-stored-credentials/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft introduced Data Protection Application Programming Interface (DPAPI) in Windows environments as a method to encrypt and decrypt sensitive data such as credentials using the… 
Continue reading → Web Browser Stored Credentials]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Administrator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Teams client on Windows Server Session Hosts: system requirements and installation]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585716</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-teams-client-on-windows-server-session-hosts-system-requirements-and-installation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T16:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new Teams client, Microsoft has imposed a challenging migration to unfinished software for its users. The hasty transition is especially problematic in Remote Desktop Services (RDS) environments, where the prerequisites and installation process for terminal servers are not fully documented and require significant manual intervention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xeon Sender | SMS Spam Shipping Multi-Tool Targeting SaaS Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=103621</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/xeon-sender-sms-spam-shipping-multi-tool-targeting-saas-credentials/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T09:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud attack tool has been repurposed by multiple threat actors to push SMS spam and smishing campaigns through major SaaS providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Zero Trust Privileged Access Management: A Fireside Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/exploring-zero-trust-privileged-access-management-a-fireside-chat</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/exploring-zero-trust-privileged-access-management-a-fireside-chat?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog summarizing an in-depth discussion about Zero Trust privileged access management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack My Career: Meet Bertijn Eldering]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-bertijn-eldering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-bertijn-eldering"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T17:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEF CON 32 Recap: Insights and Experiences from The NetSPI Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25230</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/netspi-agent-updates/defcon32-insights-and-experiences-from-the-netspi-agents/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the highlights of DEF CON 32 through the eyes of The NetSPI Agents. Discover key takeaways, expert insights, and firsthand experiences from this year's premier hacker conference. 
The post DEF CON 32 Recap: Insights and Experiences from The NetSPI Agents  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The NetSPI Agents</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is model fine-tuning? An OpenAI GPT example]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585847</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/what-is-model-fine-tuning-an-openai-gpt-example/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Model fine-tuning involves adjusting the weights (parameters) between the nodes, providing additional training to the model. This process allows the model to learn relevant information to your organization. This post's example demonstrates how to fine-tune an OpenAI GPT model. After reading this article, you will able to fine-tune models and understand how an LLM learns additional information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insights and highlights from DEF CON 32]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29436</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/insights-and-highlights-from-def-con-32/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T05:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL; DR Event Dates: August 8-11, 2024, in Las Vegas. PTP Presentations: Windows Hello: Our Ceri Coburn (with Outsider Security’s Dirk-Jan Mollema) revealed vulnerabilities in biometric authentication. Maritime Security: Paul […]
Insights and highlights from DEF CON 32 first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices for Securing Your Network with Zero Trust Network Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/best-practices-for-securing-your-network-with-zero-trust-network-access</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/best-practices-for-securing-your-network-with-zero-trust-network-access?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about best practices for securing networks with Zero Trust network access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Takeaways from the Dismissal of the Government’s Case Against the SolarWinds CISO]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/public-policy/solarwinds-case-dismissal</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/public-policy/solarwinds-case-dismissal"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T21:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government’s case against the SolarWinds CISO has been dismissed. What does this development mean?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Remote Desktop for Mac not working after upgrade (errors 0x3000064 and 0x3000066)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585801</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-remote-desktop-for-mac-not-working-after-upgrade-errors-0x3000064-and-0x3000066/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T16:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple users have reported that the Microsoft Remote Desktop for Mac and iPhone is not working when connecting to a remote desktop session, particularly when using a Remote Desktop Gateway on Windows Server 2022. The issue is associated with two error codes: 0x3000064 and 0x3000066.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-38213: Copy2Pwn Exploit Evades Windows Web Protections]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66bd050aa73b4d0286447585</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/8/14/cve-2024-38213-copy2pwn-exploit-evades-windows-web-protections"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T15:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Day Initiative threat researchers discovered CVE-2024-38213, a simple and effective way to bypass Windows mark-of-the-web protections leading to remote code execution.
In March 2024, Trend Micro’s Zero Day Initiative Threat Hunting team started analyzing samples connected to the activity carried out by DarkGate operators to infect users through copy-and-paste operations. This DarkGate campaign was an update from a previous campaign  in which the DarkGate operators were exploiting a zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2024-21412, which we disclosed to Microsoft earlier this year. 
The investigation into this campaign directly influenced further vulnerability research into Windows Defender SmartScreen and how files originating from WebDAV shares are handled during copy-and-paste operations. As …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Girnus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We wrote the code, and the code won]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108024</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/08/15/we-wrote-the-code-and-the-code-won/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T11:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Tjaden Hess Earlier this week, NIST officially announced three standards specifying FIPS-approved algorithms for post-quantum cryptography. The Stateless Hash-Based Digital Signature Algorithm (SLH-DSA) is one of these standardized algorithms. The Trail of Bits cryptography team has been anticipating this announcement, and we are excited to share an announcement of our own: we built an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Guido</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Content Security: A New Frontier in Safeguarding Unstructured Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-content-security-a-new-frontier-in-safeguarding-unstructured-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-content-security-a-new-frontier-in-safeguarding-unstructured-data?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the convergence of Zero Trust and content security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s new Fix problems using Windows Update tool]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585724</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsofts-new-fix-problems-using-windows-update-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T15:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, I discussed various ways of repairing a Windows machine that will not boot up correctly after a faulty update. If you can log into your system but still find it broken, you can use Microsoft's Fix problems using Windows Update tool to attempt a repair. This article explores Microsoft's new tool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating Zero Trust in the Hybrid Workforce: Insights from Industry Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/navigating-zero-trust-in-the-hybrid-workforce-insights-from-industry-leaders</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/navigating-zero-trust-in-the-hybrid-workforce-insights-from-industry-leaders?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the convergence of Zero Trust and Hybrid Workforces]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Cyber Risk and Compliance Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-a-cyber-risk-and-compliance-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-a-cyber-risk-and-compliance-analyst?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about how to become a Risk and Compliance Analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enter Sandbox 29: The subtle art of reversing persuasion – pushing samples to run…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9370</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/08/13/enter-sandbox-29-the-subtle-art-of-reversing-persuasion-pushing-samples-to-run/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T23:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while you will run into samples that themselves do not run. Some use anti- techniques, some require command line arguments, command line input, others require configuration and/or data files, and then some fail if the specific … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions to Assess Your Organization’s Bug Bounty Readiness]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-readiness-questions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-readiness-questions"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T20:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your organization ready for a bug bounty program? These 5 questions will help assess your security program's bug bounty readiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Jacobson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack My Career: Meet Alek Relyea]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-alek-relyea</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-alek-relyea"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T18:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The August 2024 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66bb9076d375993f4d82ad59</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/8/13/the-august-2024-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T18:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have successfully survived Summer Hacker Camp, and I hope you have too. And we return just in time for Patch Tuesday and a new crop of 0-days as Microsoft and Adobe have released their regularly scheduled updates. Take a break from your regular activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts. If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for August 2024
For August, Adobe released 11 security bulletins addressing 71 CVEs in Adobe Illustrator. Dimension, Photoshop, InDesign, Acrobat and Reader, Bridge, Substance 3D Stager, Commerce, InCopy. Substance 3D Sampler, and Substance 3D Designer. A total of 14 of these bugs came through the ZDI program. The largest of these updates is for Adobe Comme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New website address and RSS Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34806</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/08/13/new-website-address-and-rss-feed/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that all of NCC Group’s latest research findings and articles are now hosted on our website at the following link: NCC Group Research Blog. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/) To stay up-to-date with our latest research, you can also subscribe to our RSS feed here: NCC Group Research Blog RSS Feed. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/feed/) Be sure to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>R.Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manipulating the Mind: The Strategy and Practice of Social Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/manipulating-mind-strategy-practice-social-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/manipulating-mind-strategy-practice-social-engineering"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the intricacies of social engineering, explore its various forms, and describe how adversaries set, define, and achieve objectives leveraging social engineering tactics and strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alethe Denis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleeping With the Phishes]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7d9e4dd88054</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/sleeping-with-the-phishes-7d9e4dd88054?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiding C2 With Stealthy Callback Channels]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the real #GrimResource please stand up? – Abusing the MSC file format]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=4099</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2024/08/13/will-the-real-grimresource-please-stand-up-abusing-the-msc-file-format/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post we describe how the MSC file format can be leveraged to execute arbitrary code via MMC (Microsoft Management Console) for initial access or lateral movement purposes. A sample payload that implements this technique was publicly shared recently. This sample was generated using our Outflank Security Tooling (OST) offering and hence we decided to publish additional details on this method and its discovery.

Context of this blog post
Recently, Elastic released details on a new initial access vector technique leveraging MSC files, which they dubbed “GrimResource”. These files can be used to execute code within MMC (Microsoft Management Console). This technique was researched and developed by Outflank as part of the Outflank Security Tooling (OST) toolkit. The analyzed sample was a payload generated using our In-Phase Builder,

Read full post
The post Will the real #GrimResource please stand up? – Abusing the MSC file format appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Van Bockhaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unifying endpoint management and security: An overview of ManageEngine Endpoint Central]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585658</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/unifying-endpoint-management-and-security-an-overview-of-manageengine-endpoint-central/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ManageEngine Endpoint Central is an all-in-one solution for advanced endpoint management and security designed to help enterprises efficiently manage and secure their digital assets in today's complex, interconnected landscape. This unified platform addresses the diverse needs of modern IT environments, streamlining operations across various devices and operating systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Up and Running with Siftgrab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/up-and-running-with-siftgrab</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/up-and-running-with-siftgrab?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog on installing Siftgrab for increased Windows forensics analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits Advances to AIxCC Finals]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107966</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/08/12/trail-of-bits-advances-to-aixcc-finals/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T23:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits has qualified for the final round of DARPA’s AI Cyber Challenge (AIxCC)! Our Cyber Reasoning System, Buttercup, placed in the top 7 out of 39 teams competing in the semifinal round held at DEF CON 2024. Competition Overview The AIxCC semifinal featured a series of challenges based on real-world software, including nginx, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Guido</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock BitLocker drive from Windows PE with a PowerSell script]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585665</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/unlock-bitlocker-drive-from-windows-pe-with-a-powershell-script/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitLocker can pose a significant challenge when multiple PCs need to be booted from an external drive for troubleshooting. The helpdesk must manually enter the 48-digit recovery password each time. However, this process can be automated by exporting the keys and using a script.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living off the land with Bluetooth PAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29423</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/living-off-the-land-with-bluetooth-pan/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL:DR Bluetooth is enabled by default on the majority of Windows laptops Bluetooth PAN can be used to bridge connections locally between a client laptop and attacking device Attackers can […]
Living off the land with Bluetooth PAN first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Thomas-Litman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is AGI (Artificial General Intelligence)?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585634</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/what-is-agi/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T15:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an Ars Technica article, De Kraker's skepticism was sparked regarding the upcoming "AGI" timeline. I can't help but share my perspective on "AGI," albeit in general terms. Concepts like "AGI" have intrigued me since I wrote my master's thesis about 30 years ago on language processing in neural networks. Despite the recent impressive advancements in the field, my viewpoint on the term remains unchanged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits’ Buttercup heads to DARPA’s AIxCC]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107920</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/08/09/trail-of-bits-buttercup-heads-to-darpas-aixcc/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T13:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With DARPA’s AI Cyber Challenge (AIxCC) semifinal starting today at DEF CON 2024, we want to introduce Buttercup, our AIxCC submission. Buttercup is a Cyber Reasoning System (CRS) that combines conventional cybersecurity techniques like fuzzing and static analysis with AI and machine learning to find and fix software vulnerabilities. The system is designed to operate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the Scoop on FrostyGoop: The Latest ICS Malware and ICS Controls Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/whats-the-scoop-on-frostygoop-the-latest-ics-malware-and-ics-controls-considerations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/whats-the-scoop-on-frostygoop-the-latest-ics-malware-and-ics-controls-considerations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the latest ICS malware, FrostyGoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gotta cache 'em all: bending the rules of web cache exploitation]]></title>
        <id>gotta-cache-em-all</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/gotta-cache-em-all"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T22:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the years, we have seen many attacks exploiting web caches to hijack sensitive information or store malicious payloads. However, as CDNs became more popular, new discrepancies between propriet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Hai’s Report Summarization Turns Complex Data Into Actionable Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/hai-report-summarization</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/hai-report-summarization"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T21:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Hai, HackerOne's AI Co-pilot, summarizes reports, provides remediation advice, and creates content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create an Assistant with Vector Store using the OpenAI API and curl]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585586</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-an-assistant-with-vector-store-using-the-openai-api-and-curl/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post, I detailed the steps of creating an Assistant and an OpenAI Vector Store in the Playground. I showed how to upload a text file to the Vector Store and send a prompt utilizing its embeddings. Today, we will perform the same exercise programmatically using curl and the OpenAI API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Expands Their Model Safety Bug Bounty Program]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/anthropic-expands-bug-bounty-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/anthropic-expands-bug-bounty-program"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic is expanding its private program on HackerOne!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximizing Vendor Risk Assessments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/maximizing-vendor-risk-assessments</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/maximizing-vendor-risk-assessments?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to maximize vendor risk assessments with advanced strategies and a detailed security assessment matrix. Explore various assessment types and process enhancements to minimize risks and strengthen vendor relationships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the Future: The Power of a Global Workforce in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3040</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/embracing-the-future-the-power-of-a-global-workforce-in-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T22:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era of rapid technological advancement and an ever-evolving threat landscape, the traditional work and talent management paradigms are being redefined. The world has never been more connected, while data, information, and wealth derived from both data and information have never been more compromised.  At Praetorian, we recognize that the future of work is […]
The post Embracing the Future: The Power of a Global Workforce in Cybersecurity appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenneth King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the API arguments…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9351</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/08/07/counting-the-api-arguments/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T21:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Matt posted a half-joking twit about the acceptable number of arguments that can be passed to a function… I took the challenge VERY SERIOUSLY and decided to investigate. In my old post I shared my collections of API prototypes … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Splitting the email atom: exploiting parsers to bypass access controls]]></title>
        <id>splitting-the-email-atom</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/splitting-the-email-atom"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T21:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some websites parse email addresses to extract the domain and infer which organisation the owner belongs to. This pattern makes email-address parser discrepancies critical. Predicting which domain an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Outflank C2 with Implant Support for Windows, macOS, and Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=4371</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2024/08/07/introducing-outflank-c2-with-implant-support-for-windows-macos-and-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T20:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have rebranded our commercial C2 framework from Stage1 to Outflank C2 to reflect its continued growth and functionality, including native implant support for Windows, macOS, and Linux.

The Evolution of Stage1
Since the origin of our red team tooling offering, Outflank Security Tooling (OST), Stage1 C2 has been a core component. Stage1 began as a minimal framework, with its sole focus being an initial access implant with some nifty OPSEC and C2 characteristics. It was ideal for initial reconnaissance, modifying C2 channels if needed, and OPSEC safe techniques for loading another C2 framework once you required stage-2 capabilities.
As more red teams adopted OST, Stage1 quickly proved to be an unexpectedly popular framework, with users providing consistently positive feedback and requests for more features.

Read full post
The post Introducing Outflank C2 with Implant Support for Windows, macOS, and Linux appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Smeets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Listen to the whispers: web timing attacks that actually work]]></title>
        <id>listen-to-the-whispers-web-timing-attacks-that-actually-work</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/listen-to-the-whispers-web-timing-attacks-that-actually-work"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T18:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Websites are riddled with timing oracles eager to divulge their innermost secrets. It's time we started listening to them. In this paper, I'll unleash novel attack concepts to coax out server secrets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Guide to Bug Bounty Success]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/application-security/visual-guide-bug-bounty-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/application-security/visual-guide-bug-bounty-success"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've created a visual guide to planning, operating, and evaluating your bug bounty program for success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Microsoft 365 Copilot data with Microsoft Purview retention policies]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585534</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/managing-microsoft-365-copilot-data-with-microsoft-purview-retention-policies/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T14:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing the data stored in Copilot for Microsoft 365 is essential for meeting organizational compliance requirements. This article explains how to use retention policies to handle users' Copilot data. It will discuss creating retention policies for Copilot data, various retention strategies, and the functionality of these policies within Copilot for Microsoft 365.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key safe security, or the lack of it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29374</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/key-safe-security-or-the-lack-of-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years back we put a key safe into our office. Previously, we had used a very simple locked cabinet to ensure keys were returned, as before that, keys […]
Key safe security, or the lack of it first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Kitchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Leadership in the Age of AI and Zero Trust: Insights from Industry Experts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/security-leadership-in-the-age-of-ai-and-zero-trust-insights-from-industry-experts</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/security-leadership-in-the-age-of-ai-and-zero-trust-insights-from-industry-experts?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about security leadership in the age of AI and Zero Trust]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Lambda Functions for Fun and Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3035</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/exploiting-lambda-functions-for-fun-and-profit/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T22:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Praetorian recently performed an assessment of a platform responsible for downloading and building untrusted, user-supplied code. The client was concerned about the possibility of attackers leveraging this process to compromise the client’s AWS environment or gain access to sensitive data belonging to other users. Their solution to sandboxing untrusted code builds was to perform […]
The post Exploiting Lambda Functions for Fun and Profit appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenneth King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BloodHound Operator — Dog Whispering Reloaded]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/156020b7c5e9</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/bloodhound-operator-dog-whispering-reloaded-156020b7c5e9?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T18:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s summer 2024 and we are back! Actually, we are SO back, so I decided that this return required a little blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SadProcessor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Desktop 4.33: Build checks, docker debug, and configuration integrity checker 2]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585554</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/docker-desktop-433-build-checks-docker-debug-and-configuration-integrity-checker-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T16:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Desktop 4.33 introduces several new features that enhance container management through its GUI. Key updates include Docker Build Checks, which optimize and secure Dockerfile creation, and Docker Debug, offering robust troubleshooting for containers without built-in shells. Another significant improvement is Configuration Integrity Checker 2.0 on macOS, providing less intrusive alerts and proactive handling of misconfigurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vestaboard: Exploring Broken Access Controls and Privilege Escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25291</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/vestaboard-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Vestaboard: Exploring Broken Access Controls and Privilege Escalation appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Ramsbey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Cloud Security Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-a-cloud-security-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-a-cloud-security-engineer?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the role of a Cloud Security Engineer, including essential skills, daily activities, career growth, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Vendor Integrations Gone Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-vendor-integrations-gone-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-vendor-integrations-gone-wrong?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about properly securing cloud vendor integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips for Parents Working from Home from HackerOne Employees]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/tips-parents-working-home-hackerone-employees</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/tips-parents-working-home-hackerone-employees"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T21:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing RAG with the OpenAI Vector Store]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585499</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/testing-rag-with-the-openai-vector-store/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T15:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my recent posts, I discussed the concept of embeddings and introduced their use with vector databases in Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG). Since April, OpenAI has offered its own vector index, known as the Vector Store. In this article, I will explain how to use the Vector Store in the OpenAI Playground. In my next post, I will provide code examples to demonstrate how to access the Vector Store via the OpenAI API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extracting Managed Identity Certificates from the Azure Arc Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25067</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/extracting-managed-identity-certificates-from-azure-arc-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Arc service is handy for bringing on-prem systems to the cloud, but it includes features that could lead to pivots from on-prem into your Azure environment.
The post Extracting Managed Identity Certificates from the Azure Arc Service  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Fosaaen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Vanguard Awards]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66abf12457679472a60f991b</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/8/1/introducing-the-vanguard-awards"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year at Black Hat USA, Trend Micro’s Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) will award our inaugural Vanguard Awards recognizing some of the best researchers and vendors we have dealt with over the last year. We plan on these being annual awards, with the categories changing to keep with the latest changes in the threat landscape – or if there’s someone or something we really want to highlight. Our goal is simply to highlight the good work in the community that may go unnoticed. We also want to stay positive with these awards. While it certainly may be fun to point out errors that occur, we think it’s more important to highlight the good work being done that would otherwise go unnoticed.
For the Researcher Awards, there are five categories for 2024:
1.         Best use of the RF enclosure 
During …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud cryptography demystified: Google Cloud Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107890</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/08/05/cloud-cryptography-demystified-google-cloud-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Scott Arciszewski This post, the second in our series on cryptography in the cloud, provides an overview of the cloud cryptography services offered within Google Cloud Platform (GCP): when to use them, when not to use them, and important usage considerations. Stay tuned for future posts covering other cloud services. At Trail of Bits, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzy matching with Ghidra BSim, a guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29334</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/fuzzy-matching-with-ghidra-bsim-a-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T05:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR BSim, Ghidra’s new built-in plugin is a game-changer for reversing firmware and other stripped binaries. Rapidly identify and annotate functions from known libraries. Fuzzy matching works with unknowns, like […]
Fuzzy matching with Ghidra BSim, a guide first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Bromiley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side-by-Side with HelloJackHunter: Unveiling the Mysteries of WinSxS]]></title>
        <id>65f5ceb78792421d3c2272e4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/hellojackhunter-exploring-winsxs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T09:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores Windows Side-by-Side (WinSxS) and DLL hijacking, deep-diving some tooling I've written and some of the fun along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>