<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-05-05T00:38:31.828Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of artifact collection and hoarding for the sake of forensic exclusivity… – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9178</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/05/03/the-art-of-artifact-collection-and-hoarding-for-the-sake-of-forensic-exclusivity-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T23:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part I had promised that I would demonstrate that the piracy is good! (sometimes) I kinda lied back there, but I am not going to lie today: I will tell you all about it in the part … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deregister an AMI and delete attached EBS snapshots in AWS with a script]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1580997</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/deregister-an-ami-and-delete-attached-ebs-snapshots-in-aws-with-a-script/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T15:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, I shared a bash script that enables you to effortlessly create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from an EC2 instance in AWS.
The bash script introduced in today's post allows you deregister an AMI and delete all associated snapshots in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerabilities that (mostly) aren’t: LUCKY13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29035</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/vulnerabilities-that-mostly-arent-lucky13/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR LUCKY13 is more an attack than a vulnerability LUCKY13 was patched over a decade ago … so it’s really unlikely that your server is vulnerable now It’s an implementation […]
Vulnerabilities that (mostly) aren’t: LUCKY13 first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Lodge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI and ML are Changing Mobile Device Forensics Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-ai-and-ml-are-changing-mobile-device-forensics-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-ai-and-ml-are-changing-mobile-device-forensics-investigations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about how AI and ML are changing mobile device forensics investigations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne’s Spring Day of Service]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-spring-day-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-spring-day-service"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Kernel Research with LiveCloudKd]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=531305</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/secure-kernel-research-with-livecloudkd/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=secure-kernel-research-with-livecloudkd"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[…]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delegate permission to unlock Active Directory accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1582083</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/delegate-permission-to-unlock-active-directory-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When organizations implement a lockout policy, it is common for users to lock themselves out and require assistance from the helpdesk. In such cases, helpdesk personnel without administrator rights require permission to unlock user accounts. This can be achieved through delegation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-2887: A Pwn2Own Winning Bug in Google Chrome]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6633b93d81f8ef5916e65fcf</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/5/2/cve-2024-2887-a-pwn2own-winning-bug-in-google-chrome"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guest blog from Master of Pwn winner Manfred Paul, he details CVE-2024-2887 – a type confusion bug that occurs in both Google Chrome and Microsoft Edge (Chromium). He used this bug as a part of his winning exploit that led to code execution in the renderer of both browsers. This bug was quickly patched by both Google and Microsoft. Manfred has graciously provided this detailed write-up of the vulnerability and how he exploited it at the contest.
In this blog, I describe a means of exploiting the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine to gain execution of arbitrary shellcode inside the renderer process. This includes a bypass of the V8 memory sandbox (Ubercage), though code execution is still constrained by the process isolation-based browser sandbox. For demonstration purposes, this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Blogger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CREST and Pentesting: What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/crest-pentesting</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/crest-pentesting"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the importance of using a CREST-certified and approved security partner for your pentest engagements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne Pentest Delivery Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manual LDAP Querying: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8a65099e12e3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/manual-ldap-querying-part-2-8a65099e12e3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is a follow-up to my previous post on manual LDAP querying. I would highly recommend reading that post prior to reading this one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hope Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The life and times of an Abstract Syntax Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107179</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/05/02/the-life-and-times-of-an-abstract-syntax-tree/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Francesco Bertolaccini You’ve reached computer programming nirvana. Your journey has led you down many paths, including believing that God wrote the universe in LISP, but now the truth is clear in your mind: every problem can be solved by writing one more compiler. It’s true. Even our soon-to-be artificially intelligent overlords are nothing but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of artifact collection and hoarding for the sake of forensic exclusivity…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9172</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/05/02/the-art-of-artifact-collection-and-hoarding-for-the-sake-of-forensic-exclusivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T00:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is going to blow your mind – I am going to demonstrate that the piracy is good! (sometimes) I like to challenge the forensic processes du jour. At least in my head. Today we often use this forensic … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the 2024 SANS | GIAC Cyber Workforce Research Report: Building and Sustaining Mid-Level Cybersecurity Roles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/unveiling-the-2024-sans-giac-cyber-workforce-research-report-building-and-sustaining-mid-level-cybersecurity-roles</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/unveiling-the-2024-sans-giac-cyber-workforce-research-report-building-and-sustaining-mid-level-cybersecurity-roles?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the key findings from the 2024 SANS | GIAC Cyber Workforce Research Report on cybersecurity workforce management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Security Audits vs. Bug Bounty]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/05/02/products-security-audit-vs-bugbounty.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/05/02/products-security-audit-vs-bugbounty.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every so often we see people discussing whether they still need to have product security audits (commonly referred to as pentests) because they have a bug bounty program. While the answer to this seems clear to us, it nonetheless is a recurring topic of discussion, particularly in the information security corners of social media. We’ve decided to publish our thoughts on this topic to clarify it for those who might still be unsure.



Defining the approaches
Product Security Audit
What we refer to as a product security audit is a time-bound project, where one or more engineers focus on a particular application exclusively. The testing is performed by employees of an application security firm. This work is usually scoped ahead of time and billed at flat hourly/daily rates, with the total cos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install a Proxmox high-availability cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1582217</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-install-a-proxmox-high-availability-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are virtualizing critical workloads, you want to ensure they do not fail if a host goes offline. All common platforms offer the capability to operate VMs in a high-availability cluster. Proxmox allows you to install a cluster even in the free version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne and Zoom Select EverythingALS as the Latest Charity For #Hackforgood]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/zoom-als-hackforgood</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/zoom-als-hackforgood"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne has partnered with Zoom to select EverythingALS as the Hack For Good donation option for ALS Awareness Month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADCS Attack Paths in BloodHound — Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ac7f925d1547</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/adcs-attack-paths-in-bloodhound-part-2-ac7f925d1547?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will cover how we have incorporated the Golden Certificates and the ADCS ESC3 abuse technique in BloodHound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bülow Knudsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne’s Next Stage of Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerones-next-stage-growth</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerones-next-stage-growth"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T11:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am retiring from HackerOne and have started the search for my successor as CEO of this awesome company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marten Mickos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing MFA on Microsoft Azure Entra ID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29023</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/bypassing-mfa-on-microsoft-azure-entra-id/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T05:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Even though MFA is effective it is one security control amongst many Even if MFA is in use, check its configuration Consider unexpected patterns of use, such as people […]
Bypassing MFA on Microsoft Azure Entra ID first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Barradell-Johns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Star Wars Character Fits Your Cybersecurity Style?]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/which-star-wars-character-fits-your-cybersecurity-style</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/which-star-wars-character-fits-your-cybersecurity-style"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leader in offensive security, providing continuous pen testing, red teaming, attack surface management, and traditional security assessments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bishopfox.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon23 Replay | From Vulkan to Ryazan – Investigative Reporting from the Frontlines of Infosec]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=96818</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon23-replay-from-vulkan-to-ryazan-investigative-reporting-from-the-frontlines-of-infosec/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T16:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Covering investigations into Turla, Magna Bear and REvil, this talks offers a fascinating insight into how researchers unmask threat actor identities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curvance: Invariants unleashed]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107141</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/04/30/curvance-invariants-unleashed/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T13:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Nat Chin Welcome to our deep dive into the world of invariant development with Curvance. We’ve been building invariants as part of regular code review assessments for more than 6 years now, but our work with Curvance marks our very first official invariant development project, in which developing and testing invariants is all we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New features in Proxmox 8.2]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1582298</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-features-in-proxmox-82/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T13:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox Virtual Environment (VE) 8.2 includes new functionalities such as an automated installation tool for more straightforward setup on bare-metal servers, a migration wizard for VMware ESXi virtual machines, and a switch to an nftables-based firewall for enhanced security. It also introduces LXC device passthrough for containerized workloads and advanced backup settings to optimize resource utilization during backups. These updates are part of a broader release that updates core technologies and system components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relaying Kerberos Authentication from DCOM OXID Resolving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2024/04/relaying-kerberos-authentication-from.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2024/04/relaying-kerberos-authentication-from.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, there's been some good research into further exploiting DCOM authentication that I initially reported to Microsoft almost 10 years ago. By inducing authentication through DCOM it can be relayed to a network service, such as Active Directory Certificate Services (ADCS) to elevated privileges and in some cases get domain administrator access.
The important difference with this new research is taking the abuse of DCOM authentication from local access (in the case of the many Potatoes) to fully remote by abusing security configuration changes or over granting group access. For more information I'd recommend reading the slides from Tianze Ding Blackhat ASIA 2024 presentation, or reading about SilverPotato by Andrea Pierini.
This short blog post is directly based on slide 36 of Tianze …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyranid's Lair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Multi Factor Authentication – The What, How, and Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/deploying-multi-factor-authentication-the-what-how-and-why</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/deploying-multi-factor-authentication-the-what-how-and-why?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about deploying multi factor authentication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partition Windows drive in WinPE using PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581798</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/partition-windows-drive-in-winpe-using-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An essential step towards automating the Windows setup process is replacing the system drive's interactive partitioning with a script. Microsoft's examples for this purpose rely on batch files and Diskpart. However, installing PowerShell in Windows PE allows for a much more elegant solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OST Release Blog: EDR Tradecraft, Presets, PowerShell Tradecraft, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.outflank.nl/?p=3979</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2024/04/29/ost-release-blog-edr-tradecraft-presets-powershell-tradecraft-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T16:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors continuously deploy new or improved techniques. Red teams must maintain an equally rapid pace of development of their tooling arsenal to remain effective at testing evolving defensive measure and preparing organizations for advanced threats. With the dedicated research and development efforts from the Outflank team, OST is constantly evolving, with additions of new, leading-edge tools unique to the market as well as regular enhancements to our existing tools. 
In this quarterly release blog, we’ll summarize some of the latest updates we’ve made over the past few months.  
EDR Tradecraft
Over the last few years we have clearly seen the big EDR names in the market up their game. Generally, we can say that they are doing a great job and that EDR-bypasses are becoming harder. However, EDRs can’t be expected to do magic,
Tags: EDR, OST, powershell, tradecraft
Read full post
The post OST Release Blog: EDR Tradecraft, Presets, PowerShell Tradecraft, and More  appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Smeets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Prompt Injection Vulnerability Led to Data Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/prompt-injection-deep-dive</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/prompt-injection-deep-dive"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the use of GenAI and LLMs has ramped up, so have the vulnerabilities that come with them, and one of the worst is prompt injection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Data Masking 2]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5405</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/04/29/shellcode-data-masking-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T08:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This is a quick follow up post to Data Masking that discussed how one might use the Fisher-Yates shuffle and a DRBG to mask shellcode. There’s a lot of ways to mask data that don’t involve using an XOR … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insane Incident Incursion Recursion: Mastering Incident Response Reporting Regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/insane-incident-incursion-recursion-mastering-incident-response-reporting-regulations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/insane-incident-incursion-recursion-mastering-incident-response-reporting-regulations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about industrial control system incident response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A license (metadata) to kill (for)…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9164</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/04/26/a-license-metadata-to-kill-for/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T23:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many forensic artifacts can be looked at from many different angles. A few years ago I proposed a concept of filighting that tried to solve a problem of finding unusual, orphaned and potentially malicious files dropped inside directories that contain … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons Learned from Over a Decade of On-Call]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering/on-call-lessons</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering/on-call-lessons"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T23:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shubhi Gupta shares tips and lessons from 12 years of being an on-call engineer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubhi Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in Ant Media Server (CVE-2024-32656)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5703</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/local-privilege-escalation-vulnerability-ant-media-server-cve202432656/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Recently, we decided to take a look at Ant Media Server with the goal of identifying any vulnerabilities within the application. We performed testing against […]
The post Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in Ant Media Server (CVE-2024-32656) appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes — A Journey Has Just Begun]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering/kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering/kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T16:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exhausted but hopeful and longing for new horizons, the Infrastructure Team embarked on the "Container Journey."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantinos Stavropoulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Writing Well as a Software Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering/writing-tips-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering/writing-tips-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T16:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Kroon discusses tips for good writing to make you a better and more impactful engineer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlie Kroon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing two new LMS libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107130</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/04/26/announcing-two-new-lms-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Will Song The Trail of Bits cryptography team is pleased to announce the open-sourcing of our pure Rust and Go implementations of Leighton-Micali Hash-Based Signatures (LMS), a well-studied NIST-standardized post-quantum digital signature algorithm. If you or your organization are looking to transition to post-quantum support for digital signatures, both of these implementations have been […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to RBAC application impersonation in Exchange Online]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1582127</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/alternatives-to-rbac-application-impersonation-in-exchange-online/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft will retire the Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) application impersonation role in Exchange Online in May 2024. Applications widely use this role in Exchange Online as it enables them to impersonate users in the tenant to perform actions on behalf of the users. You must migrate all your applications from using this role to other options. This article will explore Microsoft's reasoning behind this move and the current alternatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring 2024 Update: Explore the Latest Enhancements to SANS FOR585: Smartphone Forensic Analysis In-Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/Spring-2024-Update-Explore-the-Latest-Enhancements</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/Spring-2024-Update-Explore-the-Latest-Enhancements?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the latest update to the SANS Institute's FOR585: Smartphone Forensic Analysis In-Depth!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excelling at Excel, Part 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9153</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/04/25/excelling-at-excel-part-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T23:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excel is the emperor of automation. Not the SOAR type, but the local one – yours. Why? Its formulas and VBA capabilities can turn many awfully mundane tasks into plenty of automation opportunities… For instance… certain programming tasks. The case/switch … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues Resolving Symbols on Windows 11 on ARM64]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2024/04/issues-resolving-symbols-on-windows-11.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.tiraniddo.dev/2024/04/issues-resolving-symbols-on-windows-11.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a short blog post about an issue I encountered during some development work on my OleViewDotNet tool and how I resolved it. It might help others if they come across a similar problem, although I'm not sure if I took the best approach.
OleViewDotNet has the ability to parse the internal COM structures in a process and show important information such as the list of current IPIDs exported by the process and the access security descriptor. 
PS C:\> $p = Get-ComProcess -ProcessId $pid
PS C:\> $p.Ipids
IPID                                 Interface Name  PID    Process Name
----                                 --------------  ---    ------------
00008800-4bd8-0000-c3f9-170a9f197e11 IRundown        19416  powershell.exe
00009401-4bd8-ffff-45b0-a43d5764a731 IRundown        19416  powershel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyranid's Lair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nemesis 1.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8c6b745dc7c5</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/nemesis-1-0-0-8c6b745dc7c5?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In August of last year, @tifkin_, @0xdab0, and I released Nemesis, our offensive data enrichment platform. After lots of feedback…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Schroeder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate Find-to-Fix Cycles With Hai]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/accelerate-find-to-fix-hai</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/accelerate-find-to-fix-hai"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now streamline and enhance your vulnerability management process with HackerOne’s in-platform GenAI copilot, Hai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-21111 – Local Privilege Escalation in Oracle VirtualBox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3464</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2024/04/cve-2024-21111-local-privilege-escalation-in-oracle-virtualbox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T13:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox is a popular open source, cross-platform, virtualization software developed by Oracle Corporation. Earlier this year we identified an arbitrary file move vulnerability in the VirtualBox system service service that...
The post CVE-2024-21111 – Local Privilege Escalation in Oracle VirtualBox appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate VMware VMs to Proxmox with the new import wizard]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1582192</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/migrate-vmware-vms-to-proxmox-with-the-new-import-wizard/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T11:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With all the changes in VMware’s offerings, sysadmins and businesses are looking for alternatives to reduce expenditure or have more control over their infrastructure. Proxmox is a free enterprise-ready alternative to VMware ESXi with optional commercial hypervisor and backup support. Many organizations have refrained from migrating from VMware to Proxmox due to the high costs associated with migration. The new Proxmox import wizard simplifies the migration process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sifting through the spines: identifying (potential) Cactus ransomware victims]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34446</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/04/25/sifting-through-the-spines-identifying-potential-cactus-ransomware-victims/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authored by Willem Zeeman and Yun Zheng Hu This blog is part of a series written by various Dutch cyber security firms that have collaborated on the Cactus ransomware group, which exploits Qlik Sense servers for initial access. To view all of them please check the central blog by Dutch special interest group Cyberveilig Nederland […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yun Zheng Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack My Career: Meet Frances H]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-frances-h</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-frances-h"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T19:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOC 2 and Pentesting: What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/soc-2-pentesting</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/soc-2-pentesting"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the importance of SOC 2 Type II compliance and how to address it with methodology-driven pentesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne Pentest Delivery Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allow end users to execute code on the Windows logon screen with administrator privileges]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581997</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/allow-end-users-to-execute-code-on-the-windows-logon-screen-with-administrator-privileges/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The instructions in this post outline how to execute arbitrary code with administrator privileges on the Windows logon screen before the user signs in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Welf Alberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human-Powered Security: The Value of Ethical Hackers & Bug Bounty]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/human-powered-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/human-powered-security"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T16:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who is an ethical hacker, what is a bug bounty program, and why is human-powered security the best method for strengthening your security posture?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-2389: Command Injection Vulnerability  In Progress Flowmon]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25168</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/cve-2024-2389-in-progress-flowmon/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CVE-2024-2389: 
Command Injection Vulnerability 
 In Progress Flowmon appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yesland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon23 Replay | Meet the Iranian Company Powering Russia’s Drone War on Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=96672</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon23-replay-meet-the-iranian-company-powering-russias-drone-war-on-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T12:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a unique look inside Iran's drone and missile program as Adam Rawnsley charts the rise of Mado, a key IRGC drone company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New features in Podman 5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581938</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-features-in-podman-50/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T12:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, I covered Podman Desktop, an alternative to Docker Desktop. Today, I will look into Podman 5.0, the latest iteration of Red Hat's free open-source container engine. The new release brings significant enhancements, including revamped container engine code for Windows and macOS, native Apple Hypervisor support, and streamlined image building for Podman farms. Let's explore the new Podman 5.0 features and improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ripple Effect: NIS2's Impact on Cybersecurity Practices Across the EU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-ripple-effect-nis2-impact-on-cybersecurity-practices-across-the-eu</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-ripple-effect-nis2-impact-on-cybersecurity-practices-across-the-eu?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about NIS2 compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One Teams Up With Top-Tier Ethical Hackers at H1-305]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/lhe/capital-one-h1-305</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/lhe/capital-one-h1-305"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T16:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One and 52 highly skilled global ethical hackers came together for the organization's second live hacking event with HackerOne.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New mitigations for CVE-2023-24932 (BlackLotus) in the April update, not yet enabled by default]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1582061</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-mitigations-for-cve-2023-24932-blacklotus-in-the-april-update-not-yet-enabled-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T12:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The remediation of CVE-2023-24932, discovered in May 2023, is taking longer than Microsoft's initial timeline. This flaw allows attackers to bypass Secure Boot and disable security features like BitLocker. The April 2024 update introduces a new fix that admins should thoroughly test because it has significant ramifications and will be automatically activated in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PAN-OS CVE-2024-3400: Patch Your Palo Alto Firewalls]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/pan-os-cve-2024-3400-patch-your-palo-alto-firewalls</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/pan-os-cve-2024-3400-patch-your-palo-alto-firewalls"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bishop Fox shares limited details about mitigation bypasses for PAN-OS CVE-2024-3400 in an effort to be maximally useful for defenders, while minimally useful for opportunistic attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to enable Azure App Service Automatic Scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581695</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-enable-azure-app-service-automatic-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T13:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service Automatic Scaling is a new feature that intelligently manages the number of instances of a web application. It analyzes real-time HTTP traffic and scales out (adds instances) or scales in (removes instances) to match demand. The most significant advantage of Automatic Scaling is that it simplifies web application management, offering a less complex approach than services like Azure Virtual Machine Scale Sets (VMSS) or Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), which often require detailed rule definitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shall we say… Good bye, phishing queue? Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9143</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/04/19/shall-we-say-good-bye-phishing-queue-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T00:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[this post is work in progress; it will be updated when the script finishes its processing] In my older piece I argued that we should stop caring about phishing alerts. Of course, it was a bit of a parabole… Still, … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Following the Trail of Threat Actors in Google Workspace Audit Logs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/following-trail-threat-actors-google-workspace-audit-logs</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/following-trail-threat-actors-google-workspace-audit-logs?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When approaching incident response in an environment you may not be very familiar with, the biggest challenge is often knowing what to look for. This is especially true when you’re facing dozens of data sources with hundreds of event types. As an incident responder, it’s your job to determine what is legitimate and what is not among a sea of activity, which is easier said than done. This blog post and its accompanying cheat sheet provide guidance on some key events of interest that can be a starting point for reviewing Google Workspace activity in the scope of an incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Reviews, Small Moments, Big Impacts]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering/code-review-impact</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering/code-review-impact"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T17:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rafael de Carvalho shares tips for code reviews, how to optimize delivery, and providing effective feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael de Carvalho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Interaction Hacks: Tips and Tricks for Crafting Effective Prompts]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering/ai-prompting-tips</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering/ai-prompting-tips"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI prompting is more of an art than a science. Zahra Putri Fitrianti shares tips and tricks for creating effective prompts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zahra Putri Fitrianti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FAQ: Everything Hackers Need to Know About the 2024 Ambassador World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/awc-faq</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/awc-faq"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Answer all your questions about how to get involved in HackerOne's Ambassador World Cup!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariel Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Registry Adventure #2: A brief history of the feature]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/04/the-windows-registry-adventure-2.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/04/the-windows-registry-adventure-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw);ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-8{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-7{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-6{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-5{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-4{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-2{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-1{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_qqcc7cub1y3f-1>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}ul.lst-kix_isoepzyy3bf4-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_qqcc7cub1y3f-0>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_qqcc7cub1y3f-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_qqcc7cub1y3f-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_qqcc7cub1y3f-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_qqcc7c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Registry Adventure #1: Introduction and research results]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/04/the-windows-registry-adventure-1.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/04/the-windows-registry-adventure-1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ul.lst-kix_c4pdvykpeuss-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_c4pdvykpeuss-2{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_c4pdvykpeuss-1{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_c4pdvykpeuss-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_2wnifzn4nxg9-1>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}ul.lst-kix_5uedwcx8bazf-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_5uedwcx8bazf-4{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_2wnifzn4nxg9-0>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_2wnifzn4nxg9-2>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_4m34njm6c6og-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}ul.lst-kix_5uedwcx8bazf-5{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_5uedwcx8bazf-6{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_2wnifzn4nxg9-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_4m34njm6c6og-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}ul.lst-kix_5uedwcx8bazf-7{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_5uedwcx8bazf-8{list-style-type:none}…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started on Personal Development]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering/personal-development</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering/personal-development"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself feeling stuck? Rafael de Carvalho shares critical steps toward moving in the right direction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael de Carvalho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing DAST scanning in the Cloud, with Burp Suite Enterprise Edition]]></title>
        <id>introducing-dast-scanning-in-the-cloud-with-burp-suite-enterprise-edition</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/introducing-dast-scanning-in-the-cloud-with-burp-suite-enterprise-edition"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that Burp Suite Enterprise Edition is now available in PortSwigger’s secure cloud. You can now free up testing time with scalable, automated DAST scanning, without the burden]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combining password policies for Active Directory and Entra ID (Azure AD)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581892</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/combining-password-policies-for-active-directory-and-entra-id-azure-ad/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T12:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory and Entra ID (formerly known as Azure AD) have their own password policies to prevent users from using weak and insecure passwords. While these policies can be combined, the level of protection achieved through this approach is still limited.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LSA Whisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/20874277ea3b</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/lsa-whisperer-20874277ea3b?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T15:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to SpecterOps for supporting this research, to Elad for helping draft this blog, and to Sarah, Daniel, and Adam for proofreading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan McBroom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-20697: Windows Libarchive Remote Code Execution Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:661988d3adb56256669d3ecf</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/4/17/cve-2024-20697-windows-libarchive-remote-code-execution-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Guy Lederfein and Jason McFadyen of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in Microsoft Windows. This bug was originally discovered by the Microsoft Offensive Research & Security Engineering team. Successful exploitation could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the application using the vulnerable library. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2024-20697, with a few minimal modifications.
An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the Libarchive library included in Microsoft Windows. The vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checks on the block length of a RARVM filter used for Intel E8 preprocessing, include…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to the Microsoft 365 search-mailbox command]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581877</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/alternatives-to-the-microsoft-365-search-mailbox-command/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T12:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 has deprecated the search-mailbox cmdlet, a decision that has faced considerable resistance from numerous Exchange Online administrators. In this post, I aim to examine the consequences of this cmdlet's removal and discuss viable alternatives and potential solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semgrep Rules for iOS Application Security (Swift)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mindedsecurity.com/2024/04/semgrep-rules-for-ios-application.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mindedsecurity.com/2024/04/semgrep-rules-for-ios-application.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T11:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, millions of people rely on iOS mobile applications for almost everything. As a result iOS devices manage a significant amount of data including sensitive ones, such as: credentials, health data, payment data and so on. 

For these reasons ensuring the security of iOS applications is more critical than ever when developing iOS applications. Securely handling sensitive data and minimizing vulnerabilities are essential core concepts for developers when coding iOS applications, using Swift and Objective-C languages.


Swift is an open-source object-oriented language mostly used on Apple platforms, which  allows to write software for various environments and devices such as: phones, tablets, desktops, servers, etc.
To harden the attack surface of the iOS applications it is crucial to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IMQ Minded Security Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Your Cyber Defense: Comparing Simulations and Tabletop Exercises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/enhancing-your-cyber-defense-comparing-simulations-and-tabletop-exercises</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/enhancing-your-cyber-defense-comparing-simulations-and-tabletop-exercises?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the importance of simulations and tabletop exercises]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-Pentest Checklist Part 2: Essential Questions to Answer Before Your Next Pentest]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/pre-pentest-checklist-part2</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/pre-pentest-checklist-part2"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 of our pre-pentest checklist answers 9 questions about the "when," "who," and "how" of pentest preparation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-2448:  Authenticated Command Injection  In Progress Kemp LoadMaster]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25153</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/cve-2024-2448-kemp-loadmaster/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CVE-2024-2448: 
 Authenticated Command Injection 
 In Progress Kemp LoadMaster appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yesland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy GitHub Pages with custom GitHub Actions workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581722</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/deploy-github-pages-with-custom-github-actions-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T10:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions workflows for GitHub Pages just became generally available. GitHub Pages is a service that lets you host static websites on GitHub directly from your repositories. GitHub Actions is a continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) platform provided by GitHub that allows users to automate their build, test, and deployment pipelines. This article takes you through using custom workflows to deploy static websites to GitHub Pages with GitHub Actions workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aviata Cloud Solo Flight Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/aviata-solo-flight-challenge-cloud-security-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/aviata-solo-flight-challenge-cloud-security-workshops/?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Master cloud security by tackling this free series of workshops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense of the Sisense News]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/sisense-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/sisense-breach"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T16:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA issued a warning to CISOs that it was investigating a breach of Sisense. Let's make sense of this breach and what it means for organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blake Entrekin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bobby Tables but with LLM Apps - Google NotebookML Data Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-notebook-ml-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-notebook-ml-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T15:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s NotebookML is an experimental project that was released last year. It allows users to upload files and analyze them with a large language model (LLM).
However, it is vulnerable to Prompt Injection, meaning that uploaded files can manipulate the chat conversation and control what the user sees in responses.
There is currently no known solution to these kinds of attacks, so users can’t implicitly trust responses from large language model applications when untrusted data is involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 reasons to strive for better disclosure processes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107053</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/04/15/5-reasons-to-strive-for-better-disclosure-processes/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Max Ammann This blog showcases five examples of real-world vulnerabilities that we’ve disclosed in the past year (but have not publicly disclosed before). We also share the frustrations we faced in disclosing them to illustrate the need for effective disclosure processes. Here are the five bugs: Undefined behavior in the borsh-rs Rust library Denial-of-service […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTofu example (Terraform fork): Create an EC2 instance in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581785</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/opentofu-example-terraform-fork-create-an-ec2-instance-in-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T08:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp changed Terraform's license from open source to Business-Source License (BSL). Soon after, the open-source fork OpenTofu became available. OpenTofu is an infrastructure-as-code (IaC) tool that allows you to define and manage your infrastructure in configuration files. In this post, I demonstrate with a practical example how to create an EC2 instance in AWS with OpenTofu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Compliance: Leveraging NIS2 for Enhanced Cyber Resilience and Leadership Accountability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/beyond-compliance-leveraging-nis2-for-enhanced-cyber-resilience-and-leadership-accountability</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/beyond-compliance-leveraging-nis2-for-enhanced-cyber-resilience-and-leadership-accountability?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about NIS2 compliance and leadership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in March]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10237</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/04/14/overview-of-content-published-in-march-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-14T10:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in March: Blog posts: Update: metatool.py Version 0.0.4 SANS ISC Diary entries: Obfuscated Hexadecimal Payload 1768.py’s Experimental Mode Wireshark 4.2.4 Released Checking CSV Files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackSpaceCon 2024: Short Trip Report, Slides and Rocket Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/hackspacecon-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/hackspacecon-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-14T01:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week was HackSpaceCon 2024. It was the first time I attended and it was fantastic.
The conference was at the Kennedy Space Center! Yes, right there and the swag and talks matched the world class location.
The keynote “Buckle up! Let’s make the world a safer place” was by Dave Kennedy, who provided great insights on attacker strategies of the past and present, the importance of active threat hunting and challenges ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Confidential Mode for Hyperdisk – DEK Protection Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34401</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/04/12/public-report-confidential-mode-for-hyperdisk-dek-protection-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the spring of 2024, Google engaged NCC Group to conduct a design review of Confidential Mode for Hyperdisk (CHD) architecture in order to analyze how the Data Encryption Key (DEK) that encrypts data-at-rest is protected. The project was 10 person days and the goal is to validate that the following two properties are enforced: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Catalin Visinescu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne Company Values Matter: Default to Disclosure]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerone-company-values-matter-default-disclosure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerone-company-values-matter-default-disclosure"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T17:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Deterministic Nature of Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34407</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/04/12/non-deterministic-nature-of-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T15:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we explained in a previous blogpost, exploiting a prompt injection attack is conceptually easy to understand: There are previous instructions in the prompt, and we include additional instructions within the user input, which is merged together with the legitimate instructions in a way that the underlying model cannot distinguish between them. Just like what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Selvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Assessment Course – Summer 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2266</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2024/04/12/vulnerability-assessment-course-summer-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T14:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This course introduces vulnerability analysis and research with a focus on Ndays. We start with understanding security risks and discuss industry-standard metrics such as CVSS, CWE, and Mitre Attack. Next, we explore the outcome of what a detailed analysis of a CVE contains including vulnerability types, attack vectors, source and binary code analysis, exploitation, and ... Read more Vulnerability Assessment Course – Summer 2024
The post Vulnerability Assessment Course – Summer 2024 appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Summer 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2264</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2024/04/12/public-mobile-exploitation-training-summer-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This 4 day course is designed to provide students with both an overview of the Android attack surface and an in-depth understanding of advanced vulnerability and exploitation topics. Attendees will be immersed in hands-on exercises that impart valuable skills including static and dynamic reverse engineering, zero-day vulnerability discovery, binary instrumentation, and advanced exploitation of widely ... Read more Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Summer 2024
The post Public Mobile Exploitation Training – Summer 2024 appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Browser Exploitation Training – Summer 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2265</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2024/04/12/public-browser-exploitation-training-summer-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This 4 day course is designed to provide students with both an overview of the current state of the browser attack surface and an in-depth understanding of advanced vulnerability and exploitation topics. Attendees will be immersed in hands-on exercises that impart valuable skills including static and dynamic reverse engineering, zero-day vulnerability discovery, and advanced exploitation ... Read more Public Browser Exploitation Training – Summer 2024
The post Public Browser Exploitation Training – Summer 2024 appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exodusintel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Power Automate with the PowerApps V2 Trigger]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581355</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/using-power-automate-with-the-powerapps-v2-trigger/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T10:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PowerApps is a low-code platform from Microsoft that enables businesses and individuals to quickly build custom applications for web and mobile, connecting to various data sources without extensive coding experience. I'm new to PowerApps and initially relied on guides on the internet to build my first app. The app was simple: collect user input and send it to Power Automate for processing. However, online guides can sometimes be outdated, and I ran into trouble with a deprecated Power Automate trigger called 'Ask in PowerApps.' The recommended solution is to use the newer PowerApps V2 trigger; this guide will show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can ships be hacked?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28997</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/can-ships-be-hacked/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T05:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: David Adams, MV Dali and the Francis Scott Key Bridge collapse – 240326-A-SE916-6662, A layer has been added showing a character and a speech bubble, CC0 1.0 TL;DR Ships […]
Can ships be hacked? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Tierney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Race Condition Vulnerability Could Cast Multiple Votes]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/sherrets-race-condition</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/sherrets-race-condition"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T16:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker and Senior Solutions Architect Dane Sherrets tells the story of how a race condition vulnerability could cast multiple votes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dane Sherrets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rooting out Risky SCCM Configs with Misconfiguration Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/0beecaab1af3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/rooting-out-risky-sccm-configs-with-misconfiguration-manager-0beecaab1af3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T15:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tl;dr: I wrote a script to identify every TAKEOVER and ELEVATE attack in Misconfiguration Manager.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create, use, and manage Windows Passkeys]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581191</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-use-and-manage-windows-passkeys/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T12:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Passkeys, introduced with Windows 11 23H2, is a passwordless sign-in solution that uses your Windows Hello credentials (face, PIN, or linked device) for secure and convenient authentication to websites and apps. This guide will teach you how to create, use, and manage a passkey using Windows Hello.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to get the most out of your One-on-Ones]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering-blog/guide-get-most-out-your-one-ones</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering-blog/guide-get-most-out-your-one-ones"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T21:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>cweiner@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use unattend.xml to skip Out-of-Box Experience (OOBE) when installing Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581566</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/use-unattendxml-to-skip-out-of-box-experience-oobe-when-installing-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows setup goes through several phases, with the last one being the Out-of-Box Experience (OOBE). It presents users with multiple dialogs for system configuration. Some settings are security-related, while others may be unclear to many users. Using an answer file, they can be automatically customized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne Celebrates Global Work from Home Day]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerone-celebrates-global-work-home-day</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerone-celebrates-global-work-home-day"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T07:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The April 2024 Security Updates Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66157e7f2eda2f1607e47653</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/4/9/the-april-2024-security-updates-review"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T17:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second Tuesday of the month, and Adobe and Microsoft have released a fresh crop of security updates. Take a break from your other activities and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for April 2024
For April, Adobe released nine patches addressing 24 CVEs in Adobe After Effects, Photoshop, Commerce, InDesign, Experience Manager, Media Encoder, Bridge, Illustrator, and Adobe Animate. The largest of these updates is for Experience Manager, however, all of the bugs being patched are simple Cross-site Scripting (XSS) bugs. Still, if exploited, these Important-severity bugs could lead to code execution if exploited. The only other patches that address …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding the Characteristics of Modern Pentesting: Value]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/modern-pentesting-value</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/modern-pentesting-value"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's explore the "Value" factor of different pentesting methodologies and see how each one measures up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne Company Values Matter: Lead with Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerone-company-values-matter-lead-integrity</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerone-company-values-matter-lead-integrity"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox backup with NAKIVO Backup and Replication v10.11]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581466</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/proxmox-backup-with-nakivo-backup-and-replication-v1011/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T14:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore NAKIVO Backup & Replication v10.11's new features, including Proxmox backup support, enhanced IT monitoring, Oracle RMAN on Linux, and more for efficient data protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quest to Summit | SANS ICS Security Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-quest-to-summit-sans-ics-security-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-quest-to-summit-sans-ics-security-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Register for the ICS Security Summit to be able to participate in The Quest to Summit and win big prizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne’s Digital First Workplace]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-digital-first-workplace</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-digital-first-workplace"/>
        <updated>2024-04-08T21:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Ollama DNS Rebinding Attack (CVE-2024-28224)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34251</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/04/08/technical-advisory-ollama-dns-rebinding-attack-cve-2024-28224/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ollama is an open-source system for running and managing large language models (LLMs).

NCC Group identified a DNS rebinding vulnerability in Ollama that permits attackers to access its API without authorization, and perform various malicious activities, such as exfiltrating sensitive file data from vulnerable systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gérald Doussot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Windows performance with Microsoft PC Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1581274</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/improve-windows-performance-with-microsoft-pc-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-08T10:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PC Manager is a new Microsoft tool that helps improve Windows performance with features such as disk cleanup and startup program management. Additionally, it integrates with Microsoft Defender to provide security insights, ensuring that users have a comprehensive tool for both system optimization and protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google AI Studio Data Exfiltration via Prompt Injection - Possible Regression and Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-aistudio-mass-data-exfil/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-aistudio-mass-data-exfil/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T23:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I like about the rapid advancements and excitement about AI over the last few years is that we see a resurgence of the testing discipline!
Software testing is hard, and adding AI to the mix does not make it easier at all!
Google AI Studio - Initially not vulnerable to data leakage via image rendering When Google released AI Studio last year I checked for the common image markdown data exfiltration vulnerability and it was not vulnerable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of cutting corners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9133</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/04/05/the-art-of-cutting-corners/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T23:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love ROI-driven solutions and this post is about one of them. My personal cybersecurity consulting practice exposed me to many different types of ‘IT security’ jobs over last 13 years and today I will describe one of them… Nearly … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v4.1: The Custom Fields Update]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/fe07f7dda293</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-v4-1-the-custom-fields-update-fe07f7dda293?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T17:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the awesome changes in the latest Ghostwriter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Maddalena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Credential Rotations: Best Practices for Security and Data Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/engineering/credentials-rotation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/engineering/credentials-rotation"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T16:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the importance of credential rotations and best practices for managing them effectively from HackerOne's experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martzen Haagsma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Credential Rotations: Best Practices for Security and Data Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/credentials-rotation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/credentials-rotation"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T16:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the importance of credential rotations and best practices for managing them effectively from HackerOne's experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martzen Haagsma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>