<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-27T00:34:21.151Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long Live the Pwn Request: Hacking Microsoft GitHub Repositories and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5175</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/pwn-request-hacking-microsoft-github-repositories-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T13:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software supply chain attacks have been increasing both in frequency and severity in recent months. In response to these attacks, the CISA has even released a cybersecurity information sheet (CSI) on how organizations can secure their CI/CD pipelines. The introduction to the CSI states: “(The) CSI explains how to integrate security best practices into typical […]
The post Long Live the Pwn Request: Hacking Microsoft GitHub Repositories and More appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which WSUS products to select for Windows 11?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576534</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/which-wsus-products-to-select-for-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T09:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to distribute updates for Windows 11 via WSUS, there are several products to choose from. The ones you need depends on the editions you are using and on how you install feature updates. Most products are needed for in-place upgrades.
Which WSUS products to select for Windows 11? first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCCM Hierarchy Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/41929c61e087</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/sccm-hierarchy-takeover-41929c61e087?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T14:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Site to Rule Them All]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOM Invader and the case of direct eval vs indirect eval]]></title>
        <id>dom-invader-and-the-case-of-direct-eval-vs-indirect-eval</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/dom-invader-and-the-case-of-direct-eval-vs-indirect-eval"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is DOM Invader? DOM Invader is a browser extension that makes it easy to find DOM based XSS by instrumenting various JavaScript functions. You can find out more about DOM Invader here: Introducin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pitfalls of relying on eBPF for security monitoring (and some solutions)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105140</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/09/25/pitfalls-of-relying-on-ebpf-for-security-monitoring-and-some-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T11:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg eBPF (extended Berkeley Packet Filter) has emerged as the de facto Linux standard for security monitoring and endpoint observability. It is used by technologies such as BPFTrace, Cilium, Pixie, Sysdig, and Falco due to its low overhead and its versatility. There is, however, a dark (but open) secret: eBPF was never intended […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Miorcec</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes logs: Pod logs, container logs, Docker logs, kubelet logs, and master node logs]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576523</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-logs-pod-logs-container-logs-docker-logs-kubelet-logs-and-master-node-logs/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T09:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to view Kubernetes logs is essential when it comes to troubleshooting. Whereas the worker nodes store the Pod logs, container logs, and kubelet logs, the master node stores the API server logs, controller manager logs, and the scheduler log. If your entire Kubernetes cluster is in trouble, the cluster events can help you track down the issue.
Kubernetes logs: Pod logs, container logs, Docker logs, kubelet logs, and master node logs first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of the New SEC Rules and Regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/summary-of-the-new-sec-rules-and-regulations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/summary-of-the-new-sec-rules-and-regulations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the new Security and Exchange Commission mandates]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-side JavaScript Instrumentation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/09/25/clientside-javascript-instrumentation.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/09/25/clientside-javascript-instrumentation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a ton of code that is not worth your time and brain power. Binary
reverse engineers commonly skip straight to the important code by using ltrace,
strace, or frida. You can do the same for client side JavaScript using only
common browser features. This will save time, make testing more fun and help
keep your attention span available for the code that deserves your focus.
This blog introduces my thinking processes and practical methods for
instrumenting client side JavaScript. This processes have helped me to find
deeply embedded bugs in complicated codebases with relative ease. I have been
using many of these tricks for so long that I implemented them in a web
extension called Eval
Villain. While I
will introduce you to some of Eval Villain’s brand new features, I will also show ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hidden side of 24/7/365 – The dreadful APAC shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8745</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/09/23/the-hidden-side-of-24-7-365-the-dreadful-apac-shift/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-23T22:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to say ‘we follow the Sun’ or ‘we deliver that 24/7/365 service’. The story doesn’t end there though – the delivery part of this promise has a different story to tell. The one that is rarely talked about, … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using OSINT skills for your own protection…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8613</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/09/22/using-osint-skills-for-your-own-protection/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T22:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is probably the most unusual blog post I have ever written here… Oh, well… — TL;DR; My wife and I recently stayed at a pretty expensive hotel. I won’t name and shame, but it’s fair to say they didn’t … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macros Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=31071</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/web-application-penetration-testing/macros-demystified/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T14:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These tutorials on Burp Suite's Macros will level up your skills in the basics of Macros, gathering dynamic values, and using Macros for complex situations. Plus, you can practice those skills on a custom lab that we’ve built to accompany these tutorials.
The post Macros Demystified appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoubleQlik: Bypassing the Fix for CVE-2023-41265 to Achieve Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4846</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/doubleqlik-bypassing-the-original-fix-for-cve-2023-41265/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T13:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview On August 29th, 2023, Qlik issued a patch for two vulnerabilities we identified in Qlik Sense Enterprise, CVE-2023-41265 and CVE-2023-41266. These vulnerabilities allowed for unauthenticated remote code execution via path traversal and HTTP request tunneling. As part of our standard operating procedure, we performed a diff of the issued patch to identify potential bypasses […]
The post DoubleQlik: Bypassing the Fix for CVE-2023-41265 to Achieve Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Azure PowerShell global settings]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576498</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-azure-powershell-global-settings/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T09:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the lesser-known but very useful features of Azure PowerShell is the ability to manage Azure PowerShell global settings using the PowerShell cmdlets Get-AzConfig, Update-AzConfig, Export-AzConfig, Import-AzConfig, and Clear-AzConfig.
Manage Azure PowerShell global settings first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baki Onur Okutucu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability in the Wake of Linux XLTS Sunsetting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/stability_in_the_wake_of_linux_xlts_sunsetting.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/stability_in_the_wake_of_linux_xlts_sunsetting.php"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog covers the news of the sunsetting of Linux's 6-year eXtended Long Term Support (XLTS) offering, how this move won't affect grsecurity or its customers, and why businesses can continue to rely on grsecurity's stable offerings for a longer period than future two-year upstream LTS releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability in the Wake of Linux XLTS Sunsetting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/stability_in_the_wake_of_linux_xlts_sunsetting.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/stability_in_the_wake_of_linux_xlts_sunsetting.php"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog covers the news of the sunsetting of Linux's 6-year eXtended Long Term Support (XLTS) offering, how this move won't affect grsecurity or its customers, and why businesses can continue to rely on grsecurity's stable offerings for a longer period than future two-year upstream LTS releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS OSINT Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-osint-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-osint-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cyber Defense Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS OSINT Summit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building the Human Risk Dream Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/building-the-human-risk-dream-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/building-the-human-risk-dream-team?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing human risk is a team effort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Documenting the undocumented – Excel’s SaveAs method…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8739</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/09/21/documenting-the-undocumented-excels-saveas-method/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T22:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago kernelv0id asked about an undocumented Excel format that he observed being used by one of the payloads he was analysing. He saw a malicious .xlsb file dropping a file that was being saved with a file … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Moment In Cybersecurity Needs Hackers To Protect All Software]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ceo/why-moment-cybersecurity-needs-hackers-protect-all-software</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ceo/why-moment-cybersecurity-needs-hackers-protect-all-software"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>alice@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helpdesk Telephone Attack: How to Close Process and Technology Gaps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5159</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/helpdesk-telephone-attack/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T20:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction As we have witnessed in recent weeks with the MGM and Caesars Entertainment breaches, helpdesks are prime attack surfaces that are seeing a surge in exploitation. Although much of the press surrounding these most recent events alludes to helpdesk operators’ roles in the exploits, this type of vulnerability actually is a technology and process […]
The post Helpdesk Telephone Attack: How to Close Process and Technology Gaps appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandman APT | A Mystery Group Targeting Telcos with a LuaJIT Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=84531</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/sandman-apt-a-mystery-group-targeting-telcos-with-a-luajit-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T19:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sophisticated threat actor deploys high-end malware utilizing the LuaJIT platform to backdoor telcos in Europe, Middle East and South Asia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Soft Power | China’s Continental Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=84572</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/cyber-soft-power-chinas-continental-takeover/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China-aligned threat actors are increasingly involved in strategic intrusions in Africa, aiming to extend the PRC's influence across the continent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Deserialization Bugs in the SolarWind Platform]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:650c63a48dee587e9e1587c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/9/21/finding-deserialization-bugs-in-the-solarwind-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T16:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a while since I have written a blog post, please accept my sincerest apologies. This is because a lot of fun stuff that I’ve recently done is going to be presented during conferences.
Please treat this post as a small introduction to my upcoming Hexacon 2023 talk titled “Exploiting Hardened .NET Deserialization: New Exploitation Ideas and Abuse of Insecure Serialization”. The entire talk and research was inspired by two small research projects, one of which focused on issues in SolarWinds deserialization.
In this blog post, I would like to present four old vulnerabilities that were fixed within the last year:
— CVE-2022-38108
— CVE-2022-36957
— CVE-2022-36958
— CVE-2022-36964
A small part of the Hexacon talk will show how I have bypassed patches to some of these vulnerabilities. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passing the OSEP Exam Using Sliver]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/passing-the-osep-exam-using-sliver</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/passing-the-osep-exam-using-sliver"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Bishop Fox senior security expert, Jon Guild, passed the OSEP exam using Sliver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Guild</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Nginx Proxy Manager with Docker on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576480</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-nginx-proxy-manager-with-docker-on-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T10:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nginx Proxy Manager (NPM) is an open-source reverse proxy management system that runs as a Docker container. It is easy to set up and requires no expertise to work with Nginx servers or SSL certificates. All you need to do is install a Docker and Docker Compose on each server.
Install Nginx Proxy Manager with Docker on Ubuntu first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Must-Read Malware Analysis Blogs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/latest-must-read-malware-analysis-blogs</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/latest-must-read-malware-analysis-blogs?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this brief post, we present a selection of recent malware analysis write-ups. Our goal is to highlight the contributions of individuals who share their passion for malware analysis with the community. These dedicated analysts work tirelessly to document their approach to reverse engineering malware, publish code, and educate others on effective malware analysis tools and techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Engineer Salary, Skills, and Career Path]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-engineer-salary-skills-and-career-path</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-engineer-salary-skills-and-career-path?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the skills, education, and career path of a Cloud Engineer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter v4: 2FA, RBAC, and Logging, Oh My!]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1f47e9aade7c</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-v4-2fa-rbac-and-logging-oh-my-1f47e9aade7c?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T17:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Maddalena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t overextend your Oblivious Transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105120</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/09/20/dont-overextend-your-oblivious-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Joop van de Pol We found a vulnerability in a threshold signature scheme that allows an attacker to recover the signing key of threshold ECDSA implementations that are based on Oblivious Transfer (OT). A malicious participant of the threshold signing protocols could perform selective abort attacks during the OT extension subprotocol, recover the secret […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activate BitLocker with manage-bde, PowerShell, or WMI]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576461</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/activate-bitlocker-with-manage-bde-powershell-or-wmi/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T09:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can configure various settings for BitLocker using group policies, but this doesn't initiate encryption. Similarly, it doesn't create the configured protectors that are necessary for activating BitLocker. Manage-bde, PowerShell, or the WMI class Win32_EncryptableVolume serve this purpose.
Activate BitLocker with manage-bde, PowerShell, or WMI first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3yrs of CAA ASSURE assessments. What we’ve learned]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27820</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/3yrs-of-caa-assure-assessments-what-weve-learned/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T05:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction We’re now in our third year of CREST CAA ASSURE auditing and we’ve learned a lot. The Cyber Assessment Framework (CAF) is big, there’s no denying that. It’s not […]
3yrs of CAA ASSURE assessments. What we’ve learned first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaria Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reactive Progress and Tradecraft Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b616f85b6c0a</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/reactive-progress-and-tradecraft-innovation-b616f85b6c0a?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T16:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Detection as Prediction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Barclay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing a Modern In-the-wild Android Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/09/analyzing-modern-in-wild-android-exploit.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/09/analyzing-modern-in-wild-android-exploit.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Seth Jenkins, Project Zero

Introduction

In December 2022, Google’s Threat Analysis Group (TAG) discovered an in-the-wild exploit chain targeting Samsung Android devices. TAG’s blog post covers the targeting and the actor behind the campaign. This is a technical analysis of the final stage of one of the exploit chains, specifically CVE-2023-0266 (a 0-day in the ALSA compatibility layer) and CVE-2023-26083 (a 0-day in the Mali GPU driver) as well as the techniques used by the attacker to gain kernel arbitrary read/write access.

Notably, all of the previous stages of the exploit chain used n-day vulnerabilities:


CVE-2022-4262, a vulnerability patched in Chrome that was unpatched in the Samsung browser (i.e. a "Chrome n-day"), was used to achieve RCE.


CVE-2022-3038, another Chrome n-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Services: 2023 Insights From the Ponemon Institute]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/financial-services-2023-insights-ponemon-institute</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/financial-services-2023-insights-ponemon-institute"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a sneak peek into why FinServ organizations are at the forefront of offensive security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not So Pleasant Password Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3292</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2023/09/the-not-so-pleasant-password-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview During a recent adversary simulation, the MDSec ActiveBreach red team were asked to investigate the organisation’s Password Manager solution, with the key objective of compromising stored credentials, ideally from...
The post The Not So Pleasant Password Manager appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect Linux to Active Directory using SSSD]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576452</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/connect-linux-to-active-directory-using-sssd/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T09:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will show you how to connect Linux to Active Directory using the modern System Security Services Daemon (SSSD) and allow authentication against trusted Active Directory domains.
Connect Linux to Active Directory using SSSD first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evi Vanoost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juplink RX4-1500 Hard-coded Credential Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2166</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/09/18/juplink-rx4-1500-hard-coded-credential-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-6a41336a Hard coded credentials exists in Juplink RX4-1500, a WiFi router. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to log into the web interface or telnet service as the ‘user’ user. Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-6a41336a MITRE: CVE-2023-41030 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:A/AC:L/Au:N/C:P/I:P/A:P CVSSv2 Score: 5.8 Vendor References The affected product is end-of-life and no patches are available. ... Read more Juplink RX4-1500 Hard-coded Credential Vulnerability
The post Juplink RX4-1500 Hard-coded Credential Vulnerability appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juplink RX4-1500 Command Injection Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2165</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/09/18/juplink-rx4-1500-command-injection-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-9f56ea7e A command injection exists in Juplink RX4-1500, a WiFi router. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to achieve code execution as root. Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-9f56ea7e MITRE: CVE-2023-41029 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:A/AC:L/Au:S/C:C/I:C/A:C CVSSv2 Score: 7.7 Vendor References The affected product is end-of-life and no patches are available. Discovery Credit Exodus Intelligence Disclosure Timeline Vendor ... Read more Juplink RX4-1500 Command Injection Vulnerability
The post Juplink RX4-1500 Command Injection Vulnerability appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juplink RX4-1500 homemng Command Injection Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2167</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/09/18/juplink-rx4-1500-homemng-command-injection-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-57838768 A command injection vulnerability exists in Juplink RX4-1500, a WiFi router. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to achieve code execution as root. Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-57838768 MITRE: CVE-2023-41031 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:A/AC:L/Au:S/C:C/I:C/A:C CVSSv2 Score: 7.7 Vendor References The affected product is end-of-life and no patches are available. Discovery Credit Exodus Intelligence Disclosure Timeline ... Read more Juplink RX4-1500 homemng Command Injection Vulnerability
The post Juplink RX4-1500 homemng Command Injection Vulnerability appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juplink RX4-1500 Credential Disclosure Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2164</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/09/18/juplink-rx4-1500-credential-disclosure-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-3fd79566 A credential disclosure vulnerability exists in Juplink RX4-1500, a WiFi router. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to achieve code execution as root. Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-3fd79566 MITRE: CVE-2023-41027 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:A/AC:L/Au:S/C:C/I:C/A:C CVSSv2 Score: 7.7 Vendor References The affected product is end-of-life and no patches are available. Discovery Credit Exodus Intelligence Disclosure Timeline Vendor ... Read more Juplink RX4-1500 Credential Disclosure Vulnerability
The post Juplink RX4-1500 Credential Disclosure Vulnerability appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Multiplications with Unsaturated Limbs]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32604</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/09/18/on-multiplications-with-unsaturated-limbs/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is about a rather technical coding strategy choice that arises when implementing cryptographic algorithms on some elliptic curves, namely how to represent elements of the base field. We will be discussing Curve25519 implementations, in particular as part of Ed25519 signatures, as specified in RFC 8032. The most widely used Rust implementation of these […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Pornin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CapraTube | Transparent Tribe’s CapraRAT Mimics YouTube to Hijack Android Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=84390</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/capratube-transparent-tribes-caprarat-mimics-youtube-to-hijack-android-phones/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan-aligned threat actor weaponizes fake YouTube apps on the Android platform to deliver mobile remote access trojan spyware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security flaws in an SSO plugin for Caddy]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105094</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/09/18/security-flaws-in-an-sso-plugin-for-caddy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Maciej Domanski, Travis Peters, and David Pokora We identified 10 security vulnerabilities within the caddy-security plugin for the Caddy web server that could enable a variety of high-severity attacks in web applications, including client-side code execution, OAuth replay attacks, and unauthorized access to resources. During our evaluation, Caddy was deployed as a reverse proxy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HITCON CMT 2023 - LLM Security Presentation and Trip Report]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/hitcon-llm-security-presentation-and-trip-report/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/hitcon-llm-security-presentation-and-trip-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T10:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month I had the opportunity to attend HITCON in Taiwan for the first time. It’s an annual event hosted by the Hackers in Taiwan organization and CMT stands for the community version.

There is a second event for enterprises later this year also - think of it like Blackhat vs Defcon in a way.
Conference, Location and Registration HITCON CMT 2023 was a two day event hosted in the east side of Taipei at Academia Sinica.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create your first Grafana dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576440</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-your-first-grafana-dashboard/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T09:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grafana, an open-source platform, has emerged as a powerful tool for creating interactive and visually appealing dashboards. Whether you're a data analyst, developer, or IT professional, mastering the art of crafting a dashboard in Grafana can provide a significant edge in making data-driven decisions. In this tutorial, I will walk you through creating your first dashboard in Grafana.
Create your first Grafana dashboard first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysing NSRL data set for fun and because… curious, Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8715</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/09/16/analysing-nsrl-data-set-for-fun-and-because-curious-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T22:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly two years ago I published a quick summary of my analysis of NSRL data. I believe I was the first one to publicly evaluate this data set, and I still stand by the harsh conclusions I reached back then, … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLM Apps: Don't Get Stuck in an Infinite Loop! 💵💰]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/llm-cost-and-dos-threat/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/llm-cost-and-dos-threat/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens if an attacker calls an LLM tool or plugin recursively during an Indirect Prompt Injection? Could this be an issue and drive up costs, or DoS a system?
I tried it with ChatGPT, and it indeed works and the Chatbot enters a loop! 😊

However, for ChatGPT users this isn’t really a threat, because:
 It’s subscription based, so OpenAI would pay the bill. There seems to be a call limit of 10 times in a single conversation turn (I tried a few times).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes resource requests, resource limits, and LimitRanges]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576389</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-resource-requests-resource-limits-and-limitranges/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T12:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we explore the concepts of resource requests, resource limits, and limit ranges (LimitRanges) in Kubernetes. I will discuss how these concepts are used to manage resources, such as CPU, memory, and storage, in a Kubernetes cluster and provide examples that you can try in your test environment.
Kubernetes resource requests, resource limits, and LimitRanges first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Strong Foundations: Exploring IaC for Cloud IAM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-security-iam-iac</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-security-iam-iac?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go on a journey to explore the synergy between Identity and Access Management (IAM) and Infrastruture as Code (IaC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move VirtualBox VM to other hosts]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576365</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/move-virtualbox-vm-to-other-hosts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T15:48:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're running VirtualBox on multiple PCs, you may occasionally need to move virtual machines to another host. There are two methods for this task. First, you can copy the VM files to the new host and register them there. Alternatively, you can export the VM as an appliance and import it on the target PC.
Move VirtualBox VM to other hosts first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tier Zero — Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6e1d14fddcaf</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/what-is-tier-zero-part-2-6e1d14fddcaf?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T15:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bülow Knudsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PCI v4 is coming. Are you ready?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27655</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/pci-v4-is-coming-are-you-ready/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T05:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve landed here the chances are you are considering PCI compliance. At present the scheme is running against v3.2.1. In March 2022, the PCI Council released the long-anticipated v4.0. […]
PCI v4 is coming. Are you ready? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamaria Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cyber Academy Awards 108 Students Scholarships to Launch Careers in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cyber-academy-awards-108-students-scholarships-to-launch-careers-in-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cyber-academy-awards-108-students-scholarships-to-launch-careers-in-cybersecurity?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS continues its push toward diversity of the cyber workforce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker logs tail: Troubleshoot Docker containers with real-time logging]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576382</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/docker-logs-tail-troubleshoot-docker-containers-with-real-time-logging/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T16:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to view low-level Docker container logging, tail log output, view log timestamps, find logs since a specific or relative time, display logs until a specific timestamp, display only a specific number of Docker log entries, use Docker logs for troubleshooting, use Docker logs with grep, and debug the Docker daemon.
Docker logs tail: Troubleshoot Docker containers with real-time logging first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New learning paths, from the Web Security Academy]]></title>
        <id>new-learning-paths-from-the-web-security-academy</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/new-learning-paths-from-the-web-security-academy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're starting out in the world of web security, it can be overwhelming trying to work out where to begin. There are dozens of vulnerability classes, and numerous exploit techniques to learn abo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The September 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64ff56cff38054698ff63682</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/9/12/the-september-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to another patch Tuesday in what continues to be a hot 0-day summer, with new exploits being identified by Apple, Cisco, and Microsoft. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of the latest advisories from Adobe, Microsoft, and more. If you’d rather watch the video recap, you can check it out here.
Apple Patches for September 2023
Apple kicked off the September patch release by patching two bugs in macOS Ventura, iPad and iOS, and watchOS to address active exploits. The first vulnerability is tracked as CVE-2023-41064 and represents a buffer overflow in Image I/O. The other bug, CVE-2023-41061, represents a validation issue that can be exploited used malicious attachments. According to Citizen Lab researchers, these bugs …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethical Hacking: Unveiling the Power of Hacking for Good in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/thought-leadership/aws-podcast-ethical-hacking-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/thought-leadership/aws-podcast-ethical-hacking-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne CEO Marten Mickos joins the Amazon Web Services podcast, Conversations With Leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marten Mickos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join Azure Active Directory with Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576355</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/join-azure-active-directory-with-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T10:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most companies' PCs are usually joined to Azure AD ("Entra ID") through a hybrid join, where the on-premises Active Directory (AD) is synchronized with Azure AD. However, if organizations have largely migrated their IT infrastructure to the cloud, PCs can directly join Azure AD. Like on-prem, there are several options for doing so.
Join Azure Active Directory with Windows 11 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST’s SP800-50r1 – Building a Cybersecurity and Privacy Learning Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/nists-sp800-50r1-building-a-cybersecurity-and-privacy-learning-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/nists-sp800-50r1-building-a-cybersecurity-and-privacy-learning-program?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overall, this document is really about defining and meeting training requirements, rather than managing human risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing a Node.js application with NGINX, Let’s Encrypt, and Docker Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576341</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/dockerizing-a-nodejs-application-with-nginx-lets-encrypt-and-docker-compose/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T13:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this step-by-step guide, I will walk you through the process of dockerizing a Node.js application with NGINX, Let's Encrypt, and Docker Compose.
Dockerizing a Node.js application with NGINX, Let’s Encrypt, and Docker Compose first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holy Macroni! A recipe for progressive language enhancement]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105038</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/09/11/holy-macroni-a-recipe-for-progressive-language-enhancement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T12:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Brent Pappas Despite its use for refactoring and static analysis tooling, Clang has a massive shortcoming: the Clang AST does not provide provenance information about which CPP macro expansions a given AST node is expanded from; nor does it lower macro expansions down to LLVM Intermediate Representation (IR) code. This makes the construction of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From ERMAC to Hook: Investigating the technical differences between two Android malware variants]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32890</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/09/11/from-ermac-to-hook-investigating-the-technical-differences-between-two-android-malware-variants/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T09:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authored by Joshua Kamp (main author) and Alberto Segura. Summary Hook and ERMAC are Android based malware families that are both advertised by the actor named “DukeEugene”. Hook is the latest variant to be released by this actor and was first announced at the start of 2023. In this announcement, the actor claims that Hook […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Global Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lolbins for connoisseurs… Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8701</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/09/09/lolbins-for-connoisseurs-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T00:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may sound a bit counterintuitive, but some very known lolbins often make it to places that no one ever thought would be possible… Continuing the topic I started a few days earlier, today I will explore a few more … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruling the rules]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32641</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/09/08/ruling-the-rules/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T14:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mathew Vermeer is a doctoral candidate at the Organisation Governance department of the faculty of Technology, Policy and Management of Delft University of Technology. At the same university, he has received both a BSc degree in Computer Science and Engineering, as well as a MSc degree in Computer Science with a specialization in cyber security. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ruud-fox-it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage enhanced security mode in Microsoft Edge using Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576325</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-enhanced-security-mode-in-microsoft-edge-using-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced security mode (ESM) introduced with Edge 111 is designed to protect the browser against attacks that manipulate data in the application's memory to inject executable code. ESM primarily aims to thwart attempts by malicious websites to exploit unresolved vulnerabilities in the browser.
Manage enhanced security mode in Microsoft Edge using Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR509 – Always Evolving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/for509-always-evolving</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/for509-always-evolving?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the significant amount of new content and labs in this release, it’s by far our most major update since the release of the 6-day version of the course last year. We will continue to have regular updates to the course to ensure our students can leave the class feeling prepared to implement the knowledge and skills learned in the real-world. You can find a flyer covering many of the latest updates here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hacker Perspective on Generative AI and Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/thought-leadership/generative-ai-cybersecurity-hacker-perspective</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/thought-leadership/generative-ai-cybersecurity-hacker-perspective"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T17:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne spoken with several experienced hackers in the space to get their perspectives on the most important considerations for Generative AI and cybersecurity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network monitoring with the open-source tool Observium]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576313</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/network-monitoring-with-the-open-source-tool-observium/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observium is a network monitoring tool based on Python and MySQL available for free as a Community Edition. It provides real-time information about detected devices, including their health and traffic through selected ports. Observium can utilize SNMP, WMI, or agents for monitoring devices.
Network monitoring with the open-source tool Observium first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking at the ChargePoint Home Flex Threat Landscape]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64f9f26fe91e62552664e865</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/9/7/looking-at-the-chargepoint-home-flex-threat-landscape"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently announced the rules and targets for the upcoming Pwn2Own Automotive competition. As we look forward to the event, we thought we would review the attack surface on some of the targets. We begin with the ChargePoint Home Flex – a 240-volt Level 2 home charger that delivers up to 50 amps of power. 
The ChargePoint Home Flex is a level 2 electric vehicle charge station designed for use by end-users in their homes. The device has a minimal user interface in its hardware. The device employs mobile applications for both the installation and the regular operation of the equipment by the consumer.
ChargePoint Home Flex Attack Surface Summary
Broadly speaking, the attack surface of the device can be broken down into three categories.
1.     ChargePoint Mobile Applications
The ServicePro …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Manning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Information disclosure through insecure design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27607</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/information-disclosure-through-insecure-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T05:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Insecure design can lead to many issues. The Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) should contain steps to evaluate and consider security throughout the process. Several recent web application and […]
Information disclosure through insecure design first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Tams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Sprocket Security's offensive security testing with BChecks, from Burp Suite]]></title>
        <id>supporting-sprocket-securitys-offensive-security-testing-with-bchecks-from-burp-suite</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/supporting-sprocket-securitys-offensive-security-testing-with-bchecks-from-burp-suite"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US-based organization Sprocket Security provides continuous penetration testing services to customers by monitoring clients’ attack surfaces and searching for new and novel exploitation techniques]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes DaemonSets]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576300</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-daemonsets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A DaemonSet is a Kubernetes object that ensures that a copy of a Pod is always available on all (or selected) nodes in the cluster. The Pod can run background processes that provide services, such as logging, monitoring, networking, or usuage on every node in a Kubernetes cluster.
Kubernetes DaemonSets first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to the 90s: Fujitsu “IP series”  Real-time Video Transmission Gear Hard Coded Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4841</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/fujitsu-ip-series-hard-coded-credentials/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Exposed embedded devices are a particular area of concern because they typically do not have host-based security controls such as EDR or Antivirus, but still […]
The post Back to the 90s: Fujitsu “IP series”  Real-time Video Transmission Gear Hard Coded Credentials appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shadow Wizard Registry Gang: Structured Registry Querying]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9a2fab62a26f</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/shadow-wizard-registry-gang-structured-registry-querying-9a2fab62a26f?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T16:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love casting spells]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Harley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dark Side of Convenience: Understanding the Dangers of Digital Supply Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/understanding-dangers-digital-supply-chain</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/understanding-dangers-digital-supply-chain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into this blog for an offensive security perspective on the dangers of the digital supply chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find compromised passwords in Active Directory with Have I Been Pwned]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576285</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-compromised-passwords-in-active-directory-with-have-i-been-pwned/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T13:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given that Active Directory logins still primarily rely on usernames and passwords, it's crucial to use secure passwords. However, many passwords have been compromised due to hacking attacks and should be avoided. To determine whether a user is utilizing compromised credentials, you can query HaveIBeenPwned.com.
Find compromised passwords in Active Directory with Have I Been Pwned first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.28]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10149</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/09/05/update-zipdump-py-version-0-0-28/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T07:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an update linked to option -f l to find PKZIP records. When option -E all is used, field externalattributes is parsed now: zipdump_v0_0_28.zip (http)MD5: 288DBCFACB42E6563F417E46BD6081BCSHA256: 4C3AD3A49FCFC1B5A680EAE80CE129A67912BCC03402EC9F46D08F902BC512A1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes errors: ImagePullBackOff, CrashLoopBackOff, CreateContainerConfigError, Kubernetes connection failed]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576272</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-troubleshooting-imagepullbackoff-crashloopbackoff-createcontainerconfigerror-and-kubernetes-service-connection-failed/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T17:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes can be challenging to use when errors are encountered. In this guide, we will explore some of the most frequently occurring Kubernetes errors and offer practical solutions to troubleshoot and resolve them effectively.
Kubernetes errors: ImagePullBackOff, CrashLoopBackOff, CreateContainerConfigError, Kubernetes connection failed first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolution of Cloud Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/evolution-of-cloud-tactics-techniques-and-procedures</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/evolution-of-cloud-tactics-techniques-and-procedures?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post discussed techniques implemented across the kill chain, from initial access to lateral movement to impact. One of the goals of FOR509 is to teach responders how to look into all these different aspects of cloud attacks, including investigating IAM logs, analyzing service-specific actions being taken, and understanding resource-level activity in logs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The secret of 961c151d2e87f2686a955a9be24d316f1362bf21]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8703</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/09/03/the-secret-of-961c151d2e87f2686a955a9be24d316f1362bf21/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T18:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across a malware sample that included the following, mysterious string: There are a few versions of this strings out there (extracted from a few malware samples downloaded in 2023): 961c151d2e87f2686a955a9be24d316f1362bf21 2.1.1 961c151d2e87f2686a955a9be24d316f1362bf21 3.5.0 961c151d2e87f2686a955a9be24d316f1362bf21 3.6.1 961c151d2e87f2686a955a9be24d316f1362bf21 3.9.1 … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Generation FOR508]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/next-generation-for508</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/next-generation-for508?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce a significant update to the SANS FOR508 Advanced Incident Response, Threat Hunting and Digital Forensics class.  It represents a major upgrade to the courseware with a complete replacement of every hands-on exercise in the course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in August]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10147</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/09/02/overview-of-content-published-in-august-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in August: Blog posts: Update: sortcanon.py Version 0.0.3 Update: emldump.py Version 0.0.12 Quickpost: Analysis of PDF/ActiveMime Polyglot Maldocs Quickpost: PDF/ActiveMime Maldocs YARA Rule SANS ISC Diary entries: PDFiD: False Positives Revisited Analysis of RAR Exploit Files (CVE-2023-38831)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: The Offensive Clipboard Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c66f336f2c11</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-the-offensive-clipboard-revisited-c66f336f2c11?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn’t going to be a long post, but I think it’s a really cool concept that I have wanted to implement for a while. This isn’t a new…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Static Pods in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576258</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/static-pods-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article of this Kubernetes tutorial, you learned how to encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest. In today's post, I will introduce you to Static Pods, a special type of Pod in Kubernetes that is not managed by the Kubernetes control plane. Instead, Static Pods are directly managed by kubelet on a specific node.
Static Pods in Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You're Doing Pentesting Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging the power of the pentester community and the efficiency of a Pentest as a Service (PTaaS) platform, pentesting can add real value to your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Chin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You're Doing Pentesting Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/youre-doing-pentesting-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging the power of the pentester community and the efficiency of a Pentest as a Service (PTaaS) platform, pentesting can add real value to your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Chin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging VSCode Extensions for Initial Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3259</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2023/08/leveraging-vscode-extensions-for-initial-access/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction On a recent red team engagement, MDSec were tasked with crafting a phishing campaign for initial access. The catch was that the in-scope phishing targets were developers with technical...
The post Leveraging VSCode Extensions for Initial Access appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dsregcmd: Troubleshoot and manage Azure Active Directory (Microsoft Entra ID) joined devices]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576240</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/dsregcmd-troubleshoot-and-manage-azure-active-directory-microsoft-entra-id-joined-devices/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use dsregcmd to manage Azure Active Directory-joined devices. This post covers examples of getting device state, including status, device details, tenant details, user state, SSO state, joining and unjoining, displaying debug information for verbose output, and listing and deleting Windows Account Manager accounts. Notice that Microsoft rebranded Azure Active Directory to Microsoft Entra ID. In this post I will use both brand names interchangeably.
dsregcmd: Troubleshoot and manage Azure Active Directory (Microsoft Entra ID) joined devices first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZeroQlik: Achieving Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via HTTP Request Tunneling and Path Traversal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4806</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/qlik-sense-technical-exploit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations.  Recently, we decided to take a look at Qlik Sense Enterprise, a data analytics solution similar to Tableau. The recent exploitation of vulnerabilities in the […]
The post ZeroQlik: Achieving Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via HTTP Request Tunneling and Path Traversal appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HITB Phuket 2023 – Exploiting the Lexmark PostScript Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32844</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/31/hitb-phuket-2023-exploiting-the-lexmark-postscript-stack/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Adams presented this talk at HITB Phuket on the 24th August 2023. The talk detailed how NCC Exploit Development Group (EDG) in Pwn2Own 2022 Toronto was able to exploit two different PostScript vulnerabilities in Lexmark printers. The presentation is a good primer for those interested in further researching the Lexmark PostScript stack, and also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Session Hijacking Visual Exploitation (SHVE): An Innovative Open-Source Tool for XSS Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/31/introducing-session-hijacking-visual-exploitation.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/08/31/introducing-session-hijacking-visual-exploitation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings, folks! Today, we’re thrilled to introduce you to our latest tool: Session Hijacking Visual Exploitation, or SHVE. This open-source tool, now available on our GitHub, offers a novel way to hijack a victim’s browser sessions, utilizing them as a visual proxy after hooking via an XSS or a malicious webpage. While some exploitation frameworks, such as BeEF, do provide hooking features, they don’t allow remote visual interactions.
SHVE’s interaction with a victim’s browser in the security context of the user relies on a comprehensive design incorporating multiple elements. These components, each fulfilling a specific function, form a complex, interconnected system that allows a precise and controlled session hijacking. Let’s take a closer look at each of them:
VictimServer: This comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybercrime-intelligence-FOR589</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybercrime-intelligence-FOR589?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence course will teach you how to effectively anticipate, prevent, and mitigate potential cybercrime threats, while also helping law enforcement agencies and governments to combat cybercrime and prosecute cybercriminals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career Development for Security Awareness, Behavior, and Culture Professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/career-development-for-security-awareness-behavior-and-culture-professionals</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/career-development-for-security-awareness-behavior-and-culture-professionals?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute offers these key courses to help security awareness and culture professionals develop in their careers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Into OSINT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-get-into-osint</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-get-into-osint?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn various methods to find OSINT resources and communities, figure out how to practice techniques and build your skillset, and learn how you can get a job in OSINT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC568: Approaching the Software Supply Chain like Jack Byrnes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sec568-approaching-the-software-supply-chain-like-jack-byrnes</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sec568-approaching-the-software-supply-chain-like-jack-byrnes?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about product security testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Entropy/Rust Cryptography Review]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32756</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/30/public-report-entropy-rust-cryptography-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the summer of 2023, Entropy Cryptography Inc engaged NCC Group’s Cryptography Services team to perform a cryptography and implementation review of several Rust-based libraries implementing constant-time big integer arithmetic, prime generation, and secp256k1 (k256) elliptic curve functionality. Two consultants performed the review within 40 person-days of effort, which included retesting and report generation. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible yum module: Install RHEL/CentOS packages]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576221</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/ansible-yum-module-install-the-rhelcentos-packages/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T15:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible yum module manages packages using the yum package manager on CentOS and RPM-based Linux distributions, such as RHEL, CentOS, Fedora, and Rocky Linux. The Ansible yum module allows you to interact with the yum package manager and perform all basic package management tasks, such as installing, removing, and updating the packages.
Ansible yum module: Install RHEL/CentOS packages first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending Against Ransomware in Industrial Control Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/defending-against-ransomware-industrial-control-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/defending-against-ransomware-industrial-control-systems?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging ICS612 and the SANS Five Critical Cybersecurity Controls]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolution of Cybercriminal Operations in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/evolution-of-cybercriminal-operations-in-2023-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/evolution-of-cybercriminal-operations-in-2023-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SANS FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence course authors examined the latest key findings from the CrowdStrike 2023 threat hunting report and highlighted the top cybercriminal trends that defenders should pay attention to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: PDF/ActiveMime Maldocs YARA Rule]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10141</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/29/quickpost-pdf-activemime-maldocs-yara-rule/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a YARA rule I developed to detect PDF/ActiveMime maldocs I wrote about in “Quickpost: Analysis of PDF/ActiveMime Polyglot Maldocs“. It looks for files that start with %PDF- (this header can be obfuscated) and contain string QWN0aXZlTWlt (string ActiveMim in BASE64), possibly obfuscated with whitespace characters. The regex used to detect characters QWN0aXZlTWlt interspersed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix “The WinRM client cannot process the request”]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576203</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/fix-the-winrm-client-cannot-process-the-request/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T16:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work on Windows, one of the common errors you might encounter is when the WinRM client cannot process a request. Windows Remote Management (WinRM) is a Windows built-in remote management protocol that helps exchange information between different systems. For instance, you can spot it being used in Exchange, WSUS, and Microsoft Teams, especially when you're running PowerShell scripts and other third-party tools.
Fix “The WinRM client cannot process the request” first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealing the Targets and Rules for the First Pwn2Own Automotive]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64ecedcf9c27c149ad0a75b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/8/28/revealing-the-targets-and-rules-for-the-first-pwn2own-automotive"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T15:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here.
 
Earlier this year, I announced the ZDI, along with our cohorts at VicOne, will host a new Pwn2Own contest focused on automotive systems – Pwn2Own Automotive – at the upcoming Automotive World conference in Tokyo, Japan, held on January 24th – 26th, 2024. Today, we are releasing the targets and payouts for this inaugural event. As a reminder, we have three primary goals in hosting this event:
1.     Provide an avenue to encourage automotive research. We want to offer a place where researchers can submit and be financially rewarded for reports targeting various products and platforms.
2.     Incentivize vendors to participate in the security research community. We want to connect our global community of security researchers with a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloated Binaries | How to Detect and Analyze Large macOS Malware Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=83921</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/bloated-binaries-how-to-detect-and-analyze-large-macos-malware-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T13:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Massive malware binaries are becoming more common on macOS and can cause problems for detection and analysis. Here's how we can successfully deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Stokes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advisory: Qlik Sense Enterprise for Windows Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4803</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/advisory-qlik-sense/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T13:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advisory: Qlik Sense Enterprise Remote Code Execution In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities in applications that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Recently, we discovered two vulnerabilities which can be chained together to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution on […]
The post Advisory: Qlik Sense Enterprise for Windows Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Hak5 Gear In 2023 With Microsoft Defender For Endpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2ca386bf09d3</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-hak5-gear-in-2023-with-microsoft-defender-for-endpoint-2ca386bf09d3?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T12:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! Today we’ll take a look at some of the tools out there by Hak5. If you’re not familiar with Hak5, they are a company that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Apollo GraphQL server with Semgrep]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104947</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/08/29/secure-your-apollo-graphql-server-with-semgrep/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T12:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vasco Franco tl;dr: Our publicly available Semgrep ruleset has nine new rules to detect misconfigurations of versions 3 and 4 of the Apollo GraphQL server. Try them out with semgrep --config p/trailofbits! When auditing several of our clients’ Apollo GraphQL servers, I kept finding the same issues over and over: cross-site request forgery (CSRF) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickpost: Analysis of PDF/ActiveMime Polyglot Maldocs]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10122</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/29/quickpost-analysis-of-pdf-activemime-polyglot-maldocs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T10:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jpcert reported a new type of maldoc: “MalDoc in PDF – Detection bypass by embedding a malicious Word file into a PDF file –“. These maldocs are PDF files that embed a Word document (ActiveMime) in MIME format. ActiveMime documents can be analyzed by combining my emldump.py tool and oledump.py. ActiveMime documents were heavily obfuscated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: emldump.py Version 0.0.12]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10116</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/08/29/update-emldump-py-version-0-0-12/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T10:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update to emldump.py adds a new feature to fix (-F) some obfuscations. For the moment, only one obfuscation method is fixed (many are already ignored with option -f –filter), used in polyglot PDF/Word files. emldump_V0_0_12.zip (http)MD5: 3847B92460C0485E1238C47C29EF9DE1SHA256: AFDFB8E78AE7DE56F50EA73D69705B6DACB425FFBD40D6997D64C7C75E3D8A0D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIAM AG23: Algebraic Geometry with Friends]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32720</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/08/29/siam-ag23-algebraic-geometry-with-friends/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently returned from Eindhoven, where I had the pleasure of giving a talk on some recent progress in isogeny-based cryptography at the SIAM Conference on Applied Algebraic Geometry (SIAM AG23).…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giacomo Pope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Instance Metadata Services (IMDS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-instance-metadata-services-imds-</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-instance-metadata-services-imds-?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A misunderstood but deeply important feature to lock down when deploying workloads in cloud. Learn about Cloud Instance Metadata Services (IMDS) in this blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Data Exfiltration Vulnerabilities in LLM apps (Bing Chat, ChatGPT, Claude)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/video-data-exfiltration-vulns-in-llm-applictions/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/video-data-exfiltration-vulns-in-llm-applictions/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This video highlights the various data exfiltration vulnerabilities I discovered and responsibly disclosed to Microsoft, Anthropic, ChatGPT and Plugin Developers.
It also briefly discusses mitigations various vendors put in place (and triage decisions).
   Thanks to MSRC, Anthropic and Zapier for addressing vulnerabilities to help protect their users.
Let’s hope it inspires OpenAI to mitigate the image markdown injection issue finally as well. It’s rated as a CVSS High scored vulnerability basically and was first reported to them on April, 9th 2023 - the triage decision was “won’t fix”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VDPs Are Good For the Government — and Good For Business]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/congress-legislation-federal-contractors-vdp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/congress-legislation-federal-contractors-vdp"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress recently introduced the Federal Cybersecurity Vulnerability Reduction Act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576188</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/encrypt-kubernetes-secrets-at-rest/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T15:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, you learned that Kubernetes Secrets are not really secure by default; that is, they are stored in an etcd datastore in plaintext. etcd is a central key–value store where Kubernetes stores all cluster information in an unencrypted form. If security is a concern in your environment, you need to follow some manual steps to encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest.
Encrypt Kubernetes Secrets at rest first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>