<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-21T00:35:40.288Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer interns 2023 recap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105537</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/12/20/summer-associates-2023-recap/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past summer at Trail of Bits was a season of inspiration, innovation, and growth thanks to the incredible contributions of our talented interns, who took on a diverse range of technical projects under the mentorship of Trail of Bits engineers. We’d like to delve into their accomplishments, from enhancing the efficiency of fuzzing tools […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEGA and SIX Group: The Value of VDP and Bug Bounty]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/sega-six-group</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/sega-six-group"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T13:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEGA Europe and SIX Group discuss the power of bug bounty and vulnerability disclosure programs (VDPs) with HackerOne.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Begins Tackling ChatGPT Data Leak Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/openai-data-exfiltration-first-mitigations-implemented/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/openai-data-exfiltration-first-mitigations-implemented/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI seems to have implemented some mitigation steps for a well-known data exfiltration vulnerability in ChatGPT. Attackers can use image markdown rendering during prompt injection attacks to send data to third party servers without the users' consent.
The fix is not perfect, but a step into the right direction. In this post I share what I figured out so far about the fix after looking at it briefly this morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic and static Ansible inventory examples]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578628</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/dynamic-and-static-ansible-inventory-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T09:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible inventory is an essential element that defines the hosts and groups of hosts where Ansible operations are executed. There are two types of inventories: static and dynamic. In this post, I will provide examples to explain how you can work with both types of inventories.
Dynamic and static Ansible inventory examples first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Trust in AI: The Ethical Hacker's Approach to AI Red Teaming]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/ethical-hackers-ai-red-teaming</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/ethical-hackers-ai-red-teaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T17:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne offers robust AI Red Teaming services that help organizations bolster the security, fairness, and reliability of their AI deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retro Gaming Vulnerability Research: Warcraft 2]]></title>
        <id>https://ncc-blog.pixelpreview.net/?p=25991</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/19/retro-gaming-vulnerability-research-warcraft-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post is part one in a short series on learning some basic game hacking techniques. I’ve chosen Warcraft 2 for a variety of reasons: With those things in mind, most older RTS games work in a similar manner, and you should be able to apply these techniques to other games, though maybe not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Watt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server 2025 Hyper-V: GPU partitioning, deduplication for VHDs, AD-less live migration]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578711</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-server-2025-hyper-v-gpu-partitioning-deduplication-for-vhds-ad-less-live-migration/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The upcoming LTSC release of Windows Server introduces several enhancements to Hyper-V and new storage functions, which primarily benefit the operation of virtual machines. This includes GPU virtualization, a new deduplication feature for ReFS, and live migration of VMs on clusters that are not members of an AD domain.
Windows Server 2025 Hyper-V: GPU partitioning, deduplication for VHDs, AD-less live migration first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copyright banners – re-visited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8953</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/12/19/copyright-banners-re-visited/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:52:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a decade ago I posted some random copyright banner stats from my (relatively small by today’s standards) malware repo. I really liked these stats back then and I still like them today. Why? These banners are great ‘low hanging … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GWT: Unpatched, Unauthenticated Java Deserialization]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/gwt-unpatched-unauthenticated-java-deserialization-vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/gwt-unpatched-unauthenticated-java-deserialization-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, learn about an eight year old unpatched and unauthenticated Java deserialization vulnerability in GWT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lincoln</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A trail of flipping bits]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105490</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/12/18/a-trail-of-flipping-bits/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T13:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Joop van de Pol Trusted execution environments (TEE) such as secure enclaves are becoming more popular to secure assets in the cloud. Their promise is enticing because when enclaves are properly used, even the operator of the enclave or the cloud service should not be able to access those assets. However, this leads to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notepad++: Search and replace with regex und plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578600</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/notepad-search-and-replace-with-regex-und-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T11:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The free and widely-used editor for Windows supports not only basic search and replace functions but also regular expressions. A helpful plugin assists in formulating regex, providing real-time expression validation. However, for many tasks you don't need regex; built-in functions and plugins often offer simpler solutions.
Notepad++: Search and replace with regex und plugins first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Cybersecurity Predictions for 2024 in EMEA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/top-3-cybersecurity-predictions-for-2024-in-emea</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/top-3-cybersecurity-predictions-for-2024-in-emea?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get MFA, network segmentation, immutable backups, patch management on external attack surface, the principle of least privileges done NOW.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Predictions for ICS & OT Security in 2024 in EMEA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/top-3-predictions-for-ics-ot-security-in-2024-in-emea</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/top-3-predictions-for-ics-ot-security-in-2024-in-emea?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what we have to start to prepare for in ICS/OT Security while there is still time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diego Mendoza: Completing the SANS Operational Cybersecurity Executive Triad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/diego-mendoza-completing-the-sans-operational-cybersecurity-executive-triad</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/diego-mendoza-completing-the-sans-operational-cybersecurity-executive-triad?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diego shares his experience with this special achievement in cybersecurity leadership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 15 SANS Summit Talks of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/top-sans-summits-talks-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/top-sans-summits-talks-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, SANS hosted 16 Summits with 209 talks. Here were the top-rated talks of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Minikube on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578609</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-minikube-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T12:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minikube is an ideal solution for setting up a Kubernetes cluster for a test or development environment. It only requires a single node, optionally as a virtual machine. To install Minikube on Windows, several preparations are required, including the installation of Docker.
Install Minikube on Windows first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instructor Spotlight: Ryan Nicholson, Cloud Security Author]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/instructor-spotlight-ryan-nicholson-sec488-author</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/instructor-spotlight-ryan-nicholson-sec488-author?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Nicholson is a Certified Instructor for SANS Institute and the author of the new SEC488: Cloud Security Essentials course from SANS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 Ambassador World Cup Final: Results, Impact, and Looking Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/lhe/awc-finals-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/lhe/awc-finals-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T19:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final round of the 2023 Ambassador World Cup was an immense success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariel Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleepy — Python Tooling for Sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7a96d9d650ee</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/sleepy-python-tooling-for-sleep-7a96d9d650ee?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to SpecterOps for supporting this research and to Sarah, Cody, and Daniel for proofreading and editing! Crossposted on the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan McBroom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Virtual to Physical Adresses Using Superfetch]]></title>
        <id>https://outflank.nl/?p=3225</id>
        <link href="https://www.outflank.nl/blog/2023/12/14/mapping-virtual-to-physical-adresses-using-superfetch/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver (BYOVD) technique popping up in Red Teaming arsenals, we have seen additional capabilities being added like the ability to kill (EDR) processes or read protected memory (LSASS), all being performed by leveraging drivers operating in kernel land.
Sooner or later during BYOVD tooling development, you will run into the issue of needing to resolve virtual to physical memory addresses. Some drivers may expose routines that allow control over physical address ranges. While this is a powerful capability, how do we make the mapping between virtual and physical addresses? Mistakes can be costly and result in BSODs. That’s what we’re exploring in this blog post. We will document a technique that relies on a Windows feature referred to as “Superfetch”.

Within our Outflank Security Tooling (OST) toolkit,

Read full post
The post Mapping Virtual to Physical Adresses Using Superfetch appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Van Bockhaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Security Review of RSA Blind Signatures with Public Metadata]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33789</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/14/public-report-security-review-of-rsa-blind-signatures-with-public-metadata/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the Autumn of 2023, Google engaged NCC Group to conduct a security assessment of the white paper entitled “RSA Blind Signatures with Public Metadata”, along with the corresponding IETF draft for “Partially Blind RSA Signatures”. The work is inspired by the growing importance of anonymous tokens for the privacy of real-world applications. In particular, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Pornin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DARPA’s AI Cyber Challenge: We’re In!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105545</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/12/14/darpas-ai-cyber-challenge-were-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to announce that Trail of Bits will be competing in DARPA’s upcoming AI Cyber Challenge (AIxCC)! DARPA is challenging competitors to develop novel, fully automated AI-driven systems capable of securing the critical software that underpins the modern world. We’ve formed a team of world class software security and AI/ML experts, bringing together researchers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza Cybergang | Unified Front Targeting Hamas Opposition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=87124</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/gaza-cybergang-unified-front-targeting-hamas-opposition/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T13:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster of threat groups continues on trajectory to consolidate with shared victims, TTPs and evolving malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of Bambdas]]></title>
        <id>the-future-of-bambdas</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/the-future-of-bambdas"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T10:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bambdas, a unique new way to customize Burp Suite on the fly with small snippets of code, were first introduced in the form of a custom filter for the Proxy HTTP history. This is just the first of man]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a free lab for Microsoft 365 and Intune]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578576</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-a-free-lab-for-microsoft-365-and-intune/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T08:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking to delve into Microsoft 365 management, there are a few options available. Some components offer free, time-limited trial versions, and in the case of Azure AD, there's a stripped-down free edition. Alternatively, Microsoft provides a developer license with a fully-featured subscription to M365 E5.
Create a free lab for Microsoft 365 and Intune first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse, Reveal, Recover: Windows Defender Quarantine Forensics]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33535</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/14/reverse-reveal-recover-windows-defender-quarantine-forensics/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T05:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Groot and Erik Schamper TL;DR Introduction During incident response engagements we often encounter antivirus applications that have rightfully triggered on malicious software that was deployed by threat actors. Most commonly we encounter this for Windows Defender, the antivirus solution that is shipped by default with Microsoft Windows. Windows Defender places malicious files in quarantine […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Schamper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom Install Path & portability issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8945</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/12/14/custom-install-path-portability-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been reading my blog for a while now you will know that I love to challenge my threat hunting game with a lot of err…. banalities. And not the banalities I can ignore, but a lot of these … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Your Bug Bounty Budget Efficiently]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-budget-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-budget-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations of all sizes and budgets experience some of the same challenges when managing their bug bounty budgets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Hazen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Aleo snarkVM Implementation Review]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33754</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/13/public-report-aleo-snarkvm-implementation-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T14:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During late summer 2023, Aleo Systems Inc. engaged NCC Group’s Cryptography Services team to conduct an implementation review of several components of snarkVM, a virtual machine for zero-knowledge proofs. The snarkVM platform allows users to write and execute smart contracts in an efficient, yet privacy-preserving manner by leveraging zero-knowledge succinct non-interactive arguments of knowledge (zk-SNARKs). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Bottinelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes ReplicaSets by example]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578519</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/understanding-kubernetes-replicasets-by-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T13:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReplicaSet is a type of Kubernetes controller that is responsible for maintaining a specified number of Pods running at any given time. A controller in Kubernetes is a software loop that watches the shared state of the cluster through the API server and makes changes attempting to move the current state towards the desired state.
Understanding Kubernetes ReplicaSets by example first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Multiple Vulnerabilities in Nagios XI]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33224</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/13/technical-advisory-multiple-vulnerabilities-in-nagios-xi/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T13:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This is the second Technical Advisory post in a series wherein I audit the security of popular Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) tools. (First: Multiple Vulnerabilities in Faronics Insight). I was joined in this security research by Colin Brum, Principal Security Consultant at NCC Group. In this post I describe the 16 vulnerabilities which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Brooks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling your threat hunting operations with CrowdStrike and PSFalcon]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=16798</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/12/13/scaling-your-threat-hunting-operations-with-crowdstrike-and-psfalcon/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Most modern day EDRs have some sort of feature which allows blue teamers to remotely connect to hosts with an EDR agent/sensor installed, to aid in their investigation of incidents. In CrowdStrike, this is called Real Time Response, and it provides a wide range of capabilities, from executing built-in commands like ipconfig and netstat … Continue reading Scaling your threat hunting operations with CrowdStrike and PSFalcon →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dimitris Binichakis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious ChatGPT Agents: How GPTs Can Quietly Grab Your Data (Demo)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/openai-custom-malware-gpt/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/openai-custom-malware-gpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T02:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When OpenAI released GPTs last month I had plans for an interesting GPT.
Malicious ChatGPT Agents The idea was to create a kind of malware GPT that forwards users' chat messages to a third party server. It also asks users for personal information like emails and passwords.
Why would this be possible end to end? ChatGPT cannot guarantee to keep your conversation private or confidential, because it loads images from any website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Impact of the new Apache Struts File Upload Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5479</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/cve-2023-50164-apache-struts-file-upload-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T21:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Recently researcher Steven Seeley discovered a way to abuse the popular Apache Struts frameworks’ file upload functionality to achieve remote code execution. This bug, known as CVE-2023-50164, has been assigned a 9.8 CVSS score. No doubt this is causing some security practitioners to have flashbacks of the “good times” that a serious Struts bug […]
The post Understanding the Impact of the new Apache Struts File Upload Vulnerability appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sportsman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The December 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:65787527fd07e018bb3f0c6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/12/12/the-december-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T18:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the final patch Tuesday of 2023, and Apple, Adobe, and Microsoft have released their latest security offerings. Take a break from your holiday hustle and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. If you’d rather watch the video recap, you can check it out here:
Apple Patches for December 2023
Apple kicked off the December release cycle with patches for iOS and iPadOS with eight CVEs. Two of these CVEs in Webkit are reported as being under active attack on iOS versions 16.7.1 and older. If you’re using an older iPhone or iPad, you should definitely update your device immediately. If you’re using a device running iOS 17 and later, you should still update when possible. 
Adobe Patches for December 2023
For December, Adobe released nine patches covering a whopping 212 C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career Growth: Insights from Tiffany Jones, VP of Go to Market Operations and Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/career-growth-insights-tiffany-jones-vp-go-market-operations-and-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/career-growth-insights-tiffany-jones-vp-go-market-operations-and-strategy"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpret the 2023 GigaOm PTaaS Radar Report with HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/hackerone-named-leader-penetration-testing-service-ptaas-gigaom-radar-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/hackerone-named-leader-penetration-testing-service-ptaas-gigaom-radar-report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne has been named a "Leader" and a "Fast Mover" in the 2023 GigaOm PTaaS Radar Report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silverpeas App: Multiple CVEs leading to File Read on Server]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=24946</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/silverpeas-file-read-cves/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Silverpeas App: Multiple CVEs leading to File Read on Server appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Ramsbey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding that one weird endpoint, with Bambdas]]></title>
        <id>finding-that-one-weird-endpoint-with-bambdas</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/finding-that-one-weird-endpoint-with-bambdas"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security research involves a lot of failure. It's a perpetual balancing act between taking small steps with a predictable but boring outcome, and trying out wild concepts that are so crazy they might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Swagger Jacker: Auditing OpenAPI Definition Files]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/swagger-jacker-auditing-openapi-definition-files</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/swagger-jacker-auditing-openapi-definition-files"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Download Swagger Jacker, an open-source tool made for penetration testers that enables better auditing of OpenAPI definition files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony West</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EventSentry 5.1: New network security monitoring and compliance features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578551</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/eventsentry-51-new-network-security-monitoring-and-compliance-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T09:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the new features in EventSentry 5.1, including anomaly detection, NTFS permissions inventory, and new compliance dashboards.
EventSentry 5.1: New network security monitoring and compliance features first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intercepting MFA. Phishing and Adversary in The Middle attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28349</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/intercepting-mfa-phishing-and-attackers-in-the-middle/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T06:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3 of my last 5 business email compromise investigations have involved an Adversary in The Middle (AiTM) attack. Even the more security-aware people with bolstered Microsoft 365 (M365) configurations are […]
Intercepting MFA. Phishing and Adversary in The Middle attacks first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Harwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helping CTI Analysts Approach and Report on Emerging Technology Threats and Trends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/helping-cti-analysts-approach-and-report-on-emerging-technology-threats-and-trends</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/helping-cti-analysts-approach-and-report-on-emerging-technology-threats-and-trends?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there is no magic bullet solution on how to answer a question about emerging technologies and threat trends, this first blog post hopefully provided some insights and perhaps starting points on the various dimensions to consider when starting your research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Attacks: What’s Old is New – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-attacks-what-s-old-is-new-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-attacks-what-s-old-is-new-part-1?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about similar cloud and on-prem attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari, Hold Still for NaN Minutes!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2193</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/12/11/safari-hold-still-for-nan-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vignesh Rao and Javier Jimenez Introduction In October 2023 Vignesh and Javier presented the discovery of a few bugs affecting JavaScriptCore, the JavaScript engine of Safari. The presentation revolved around the idea that browser research is a dynamic area; we presented a story of finding and exploiting three vulnerabilities that led to gaining code execution within Safari’s renderer. This ... Read more Safari, Hold Still for NaN Minutes!
The post Safari, Hold Still for NaN Minutes! appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NCC Group’s 2022 & 2023 Research Report]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33749</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/11/ncc-groups-2022-2023-research-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T20:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past two years, our global cybersecurity research has been characterized by unparalleled depth, diversity, and dedication to safeguarding the digital realm. The highlights of our work not only signify our commitment to pushing the boundaries of cybersecurity research but also underscore the tangible impacts and positive change we bring to the technological landscape. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Know Ethical Hackers Can Be Trusted?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/clear-and-gateway</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/clear-and-gateway"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne has rolled out new updates that make our human-powered security program the most trusted in the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandman APT | China-Based Adversaries Embrace Lua]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=87029</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/sandman-apt-china-based-adversaries-embrace-lua/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T13:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SentinelLabs, Microsoft, and PwC threat intelligence researchers provide attribution-relevant information on the Sandman APT cluster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say hello to the next chapter of the Testing Handbook!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105486</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/12/11/say-hello-to-the-next-chapter-of-the-testing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T13:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Fredrik Dahlgren Today we are announcing the latest addition to the Trail of Bits Testing Handbook: a brand new chapter on CodeQL! CodeQL is a powerful and versatile static analysis tool, and at Trail of Bits, we regularly use CodeQL on client engagements to find common vulnerabilities and to perform variant analysis for already […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSL: Start Linux apps in Windows and Windows apps in Linux, access ext4 and NTFS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578397</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/wsl-start-linux-apps-in-windows-and-windows-apps-in-linux-access-ext4-and-ntfs/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T11:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) aims to seamlessly integrate the open-source operating system with Windows, blurring the boundaries between the two worlds for users. This integration includes the ability to access the file system of one operating system from the other and run applications from either system.
WSL: Start Linux apps in Windows and Windows apps in Linux, access ext4 and NTFS first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at the SANS Sponsorship Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-look-at-the-sans-sponsorship-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-look-at-the-sans-sponsorship-program?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reach the right audience, at the right time, with the right message with the SANS Sponsorship Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevating Linux Security: Why Linux is Essential in Mitigating Critical Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/elevating-linux-security-why-linux-is-essential-in-mitigating-critical-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/elevating-linux-security-why-linux-is-essential-in-mitigating-critical-risks?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most security professionals enter the field with more experience on Windows than they do on Linux.  As a result, there is a gap in their understanding of how to mitigate risks on Linux. Many individuals are self-taught in Linux security practices and only have fragmented understanding of how to secure systems effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RBAC in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578357</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/rbac-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post in this Kubernetes guide, you learned about deploying stateful applications with Kubernetes StatefulSets. Today, we will discuss role-based access control (RBAC) in Kubernetes, which controls who can access Kubernetes cluster resources. It uses roles and role bindings to grant permissions to subjects, such as users, groups, or service accounts.
RBAC in Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RPC or Not, Here We Log: Preventing Exploitation and Abuse with RPC Firewall]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=15577</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/12/08/rpc-or-not-here-we-log-preventing-exploitation-and-abuse-with-rpc-firewall/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, readers, to the first installment of our blog series “Preventing Exploitation and Abuse with the RPC Firewall”.In this post, we’ll delve into how to create rules for the RPC firewall and how to deploy them onto our servers.In the year 2024, we’ll release the second part of this series, where we’ll explore detection possibilities … Continue reading RPC or Not, Here We Log: Preventing Exploitation and Abuse with RPC Firewall →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steffen Rogge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Live Hacking Events]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/lhe/2024-lhe-invitations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/lhe/2024-lhe-invitations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 HackerOne Live Hacking Events are here and better than ever!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall WXA – Authentication Bypass and Remote Code Execution Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5439</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/sonicwall-wxa-authentication-bypass-and-rce-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Recently, we were looking at the list of available OVA appliances from SonicWall and identified the WXA appliance image was available for download. We decided […]
The post SonicWall WXA – Authentication Bypass and Remote Code Execution Vulnerability appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate Microsoft Entra Connect (Azure AD Connect) to a new server]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578297</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/migrate-microsoft-entra-connect-azure-ad-connect-to-a-new-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T08:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Entra Connect, formerly named Azure AD Connect, is an on-premises application used to synchronize your local Active Directory objects to Microsoft Entra ID, also known as Azure AD. This post will guide you through the process of migrating Microsoft Entra Connect to a new server.
Migrate Microsoft Entra Connect (Azure AD Connect) to a new server first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigate FDA 524b to get your medical cyber device to market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28404</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/navigate-fda-524b-to-get-your-medical-cyber-device-to-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T06:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With amendment 524b officially enacted, medical devices across the United States (and the globe) are living under some new rules and procedures. You’re not alone if you are finding these […]
Navigate FDA 524b to get your medical cyber device to market first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Leonard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Blog Series - Blog 4: Operating for Zero Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-blog-4-operating-for-zero-trust</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/zero-trust-blog-4-operating-for-zero-trust?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the fourth in a 4-part series of blogs covering the end-to-end aspects of zero trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) to Manage Human Risk: Part 6 – Analyzing Documents, Charts, and Spreadsheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-6-analyzing-documents-charts-and-spreadsheets</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-6-analyzing-documents-charts-and-spreadsheets?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about AI's ability to analyze many forms of data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Purple Teaming: Validating Cybersecurity Investments and Enhancing Efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/purple-teaming-validating-cybersecurity-investments-enhancing-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/purple-teaming-validating-cybersecurity-investments-enhancing-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Purple Teaming brings together offensive and defensive strategies for a more comprehensive and impactful cybersecurity approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Basden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publishing Trail of Bits’ CodeQL queries]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105418</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/12/06/publishing-trail-of-bits-codeql-queries/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Paweł Płatek We are publishing a set of custom CodeQL queries for Go and C. We have used them to find critical issues that the standard CodeQL queries would have missed. This new release of a continuously updated repository of CodeQL queries joins our public Semgrep rules and Automated Testing Handbook in an effort […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | The Cyber Arm of China’s Soft Power: Reshaping a Continent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=87025</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-the-cyber-arm-of-chinas-soft-power-reshaping-a-continent/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Hegel explores China's influence in Africa and highlights an opportunity for broader understanding of global cyber threat landscapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Playbook examples]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1578276</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/ansible-playbook-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T09:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Ansible playbook is a YAML file that contains a set of instructions and configurations for automating tasks on one or more remote machines using the Ansible automation tool. In this post in our Ansible beginner's series, I will explain how to use an Ansible Playbook by example.
Ansible Playbook examples first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Connector Health Monitoring on Microsoft Sentinel]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=15521</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/12/06/data-connector-health-monitoring-on-microsoft-sentinel/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Security information and event management (SIEM) tooling allows security teams to collect and analyse logs from a wide variety of sources. In turn this is used to detect and handle incidents. Evidently it is important to ensure that the log ingestion is complete and uninterrupted. Luckily SIEMs offer out-of-the-box solutions and/or capabilities to create … Continue reading Data Connector Health Monitoring on Microsoft Sentinel →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederik Meutermans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining the Intelligence Edge in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ceo/maintaining-intelligence-edge-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ceo/maintaining-intelligence-edge-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T18:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A message from HackerOne's CEO about the power of both artificial and human intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marten Mickos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attack Surface of the Ubiquiti Connect EV Station]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:656f549b970f832921366d20</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/12/5/attack-surface-of-the-ubiquiti-connect-ev-station"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T17:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, we looked at the attack surface of the ChargePoint Home Flex EV charger – one of the targets in the upcoming Pwn2Own Automotive contest. In this post, we look at the attack surface of another EV Charger. The Ubiquiti Connect EV Station is a weatherproof Level 2 electric vehicle charging station designed for organizations. We cover the most obvious areas a threat actor would explore when attempting to compromise the device.
The Ubiquiti Connect EV Station is a Level 2 charging station for electric vehicles. The EV Station is meant to be managed by a Ubiquiti management platform running the UniFi OS Console, such as the Ubiquiti Dream Machine or Cloud Gateway. Users can also use the iOS or Android UniFi Connect mobile apps to configure the EV Station.
Attack Surface Summary
The U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Manning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blind CSS Exfiltration: exfiltrate unknown web pages]]></title>
        <id>blind-css-exfiltration</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/blind-css-exfiltration"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T15:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a gif of the exfiltration process (We've increased the speed so you're not waiting around for 1 minute). Read on to discover how this works... Why would we want to do blind CSS exfiltration? I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Vulnerabilities In Extreme Networks ExtremeXOS]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=24839</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/research/extreme-networks-extremexos-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Multiple Vulnerabilities In Extreme Networks ExtremeXOS appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yesland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing the SonicWall Custom Grub LUKS Encryption Modifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5421</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/sonicwall-custom-grub-luks-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T14:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Recently, we decided to perform some reverse engineering of the SonicWall NSv appliance to identify any potential remote code execution vulnerabilities within the appliance. During our initial analysis of a virtual machine image for the application, we discovered a customized LUKS encryption mechanism meant to hinder reverse engineering of the application. We were able […]
The post Analyzing the SonicWall Custom Grub LUKS Encryption Modifications appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SystoLOCK in review: Logging in to Active Directory with multi-factor authentication without passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577987</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/systolock-in-review-logging-in-to-active-directory-with-multi-factor-authentication-without-passwords/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T13:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SystoLOCK offers a robust solution for enhancing security through multi-factor authentication (MFA) without passwords in an Active Directory environment. Unlike other methods, SystoLOCK does not rely on cloud services. The solution introduces the convenience similar to smartcard-based authentication, eliminating the need for complex password management. Moreover, SystoLOCK allows users to log in securely via VPN connections and supports offline login functionality.
SystoLOCK in review: Logging in to Active Directory with multi-factor authentication without passwords first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSINT. What can you find from a domain or company name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28358</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/osint-what-can-you-find-from-a-domain-or-company-name/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T06:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We carry out lots of attack surface assessments, parts of which involve investigating information that has been unintentionally disclosed. To help OPSEC people I thought it might be useful to […]
OSINT. What can you find from a domain or company name first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Gee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ldr521-security-culture-leaders-challenge-coin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ldr521-security-culture-leaders-challenge-coin</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ldr521-security-culture-leaders-challenge-coin?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about the new SANS Challenge Coin for LDR521: Security Culture for Leaders, the transformational triad, and the transformational triad coin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack My Career: Meet Kayla Underkoffler]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-kayla-underkoffler</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-kayla-underkoffler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T17:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne's Kayla Underkoffler shares her career journey and how she arrived at her current role.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes CoreDNS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577733</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-coredns/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T10:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post in this Kubernetes guide, you learned about deploying stateful applications with Kubernetes StatefulSets. Today's post will discuss Kubernetes CoreDNS. Earlier versions of Kubernetes used kube-dns to provide service discovery and name resolution within the cluster, which was based on dnsmasq and SkyDNS. The kube-dns had many problems, such as security vulnerabilities, scalability concerns, and higher latency, so starting with Kubernetes version 1.13, CoreDNS became the default cluster DNS server.
Kubernetes CoreDNS first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory: Sonos Era 100 Secure Boot Bypass Through Unchecked setenv() call]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33714</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/04/technical-advisory-sonos-era-100-secure-boot-bypass-through-unchecked-setenv-call/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T10:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vendor: Sonos Vendor URL: https://www.sonos.com/ Versions affected: * Confirmed 73.0-42060 Systems Affected: Sonos Era 100 Author: Ilya Zhuravlev Advisory URL: Not provided by Sonos. Sonos state an update was released on 2023-11-15 which remediated the issue. CVE Identifier: N/A Risk: High Summary Sonos Era 100 is a smart speaker released in 2023. A vulnerability exists […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Plaskett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shooting Yourself in the .flags – Jailbreaking the Sonos Era 100]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33724</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/12/04/shooting-yourself-in-the-flags-jailbreaking-the-sonos-era-100/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T10:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research performed by Ilya Zhuravlev supporting the Exploit Development Group (EDG). The Era 100 is Sonos’s flagship device, released on March 28th 2023 and is a notable step up from the Sonos One. It was also one of the target devices for Pwn2Own Toronto 2023. NCC found multiple security weaknesses within the bootloader of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Plaskett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE’s Updated ATT&CK Framework: What Cloud Defenders Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/mitres-updated-attck-framework-what-cloud-defenders-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/mitres-updated-attck-framework-what-cloud-defenders-need-to-know?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the MITRE ATT&CK framework version 14 cloud security updates]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in November]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10224</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/12/02/overview-of-content-published-in-november-9/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T08:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in November: Blog posts: Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.20 SANS ISC Diary entries: Quick Tip For Artificially Inflated PE Files Wireshark 4.2.0 Released OVA Files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of life…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8897</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/12/02/proof-of-life/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T00:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Blade Runner’ – the cult classic movie – teaches us that the (non-)human traits/behaviors can be detected with a so-called Voight-Kampff test. This post is about discussing (not designing yet) a similar test for our threat hunting purposes… The key … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A git merge example]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577706</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/a-git-merge-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T11:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article in this series, we looked at how to  merge branches on GitHub as a way to incorporate the changes from one branch into another. This article will demonstrate how to merge branches on the command line using Git.
A git merge example first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting XPath Injection Weaknesses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=31500</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/web-application-penetration-testing/exploiting-xpath-injection-weaknesses/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defend your web applications from XPath Injection: Explore the intricacies of this critical threat, understand its impact, and learn effective mitigation strategies.
The post Exploiting XPath Injection Weaknesses appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayur Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your ENow AppGov Score? Free Microsoft Entra ID app security assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577684</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/whats-your-enow-appgov-score-free-microsoft-entra-id-app-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations are behind the curve in understanding their SaaS applications and governance. In fact, for many IT admins, SaaS applications and SaaS app governance can be very challenging in terms of visibility and control. ENow has introduced a free assessment tool called AppGov Score that quantifies the governance state of Microsoft Entra ID apps and gives admins visibility into SaaS apps in the Microsoft cloud.
What’s your ENow AppGov Score? Free Microsoft Entra ID app security assessment first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPSEC failures when threat hunting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28323</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/opsec-failures-when-threat-hunting/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T06:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years I’ve carried out a lot of phishing, and have some interesting observations on how organisations respond. However, the purpose of this blog is to highlight […]
OPSEC failures when threat hunting first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Gee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Detailed Look at Pwn2Own Automotive EV Charger Hardware]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:65666188a332be611d44ba34</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/11/28/a-detailed-look-at-pwn2own-automotive-ev-charger-hardware"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous blog, we took a look at the ChargePoint Home Flex EV charger – one of the targets in the upcoming Pwn2Own Automotive contest. In this post, dive in with even greater detail on all of the EV Chargers targeted in the upcoming Pwn2Own Automotive competition. This isn’t meant to be a detailed exploitation guide. However, we hope these high-resolution images will inspire some of the research we hope to see on display in Tokyo.
This post provides detailed imagery of the target EV chargers we are including in the upcoming Pwn2Own Automotive contest. Our intention is to help contestants understand the component hardware included in the EV chargers for the competition. But first, a safety reminder: 
EV Chargers contain high voltages. Use extreme caution when working with them.  Never …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Manning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythic v3.2 Highlights: Interactive Tasking, Push C2, and Dynamic File Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7035065e2b3d</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/mythic-v3-2-highlights-interactive-tasking-push-c2-and-dynamic-file-browser-7035065e2b3d?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T14:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New UI and quality of life updates!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cody Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whitelist a domain in Microsoft 365]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577662</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/whitelist-a-domain-in-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T12:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defender for Office 365 and Exchange Online Protection monitor all emails hitting your domain and block harmful messages and spam. However, emails from legitimate sources can sometimes also be blocked for various reasons. In this scenario, as an admin, you want to whitelist the sender or the domain. In this post, you will learn how to whitelist a domain in Microsoft 365 and the necessary precautions you must take while doing so.
Whitelist a domain in Microsoft 365 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ekoparty Talk - Prompt Injections in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/ekoparty-prompt-injection-talk/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/ekoparty-prompt-injection-talk/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T00:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month I had the opportunity to present at Ekoparty 2023 about Prompt Injections in the Wild, and the video of the talk was just posted to YouTube. Check it out.
  It starts with a basic overview of LLMs and then dives deep into exploits and mitigations across various LLM applications and chatbots, including (but not limited) to demos of exploits with Bing Chat, ChatGPT, Anthropic Claude, Azure AI, GCP Vertex AI and Google Bard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercado Libre’s Journey to a Public Bug Bounty Program]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/mercado-libre-public-bug-bounty</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/mercado-libre-public-bug-bounty"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne is delighted to announce the launch of Mercado Libre’s Public Bug Bounty Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding the Past, Securing the Future | Enhancing Cyber Defense with Historical Threat Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=86799</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/decoding-the-past-securing-the-future-enhancing-cyber-defense-with-historical-threat-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T14:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how revisiting past cyber incidents can empower defenders and help to anticipate future threats more effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Azure B2C ROPC Custom Flows Are Inherently Insecure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5400</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/why-azure-b2c-ropc-custom-flows-are-inherently-insecure/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T14:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Azure Active Directory B2C service allows cloud administrators to define custom policies, which orchestrates trust between principals using standard authentication protocols. One such custom policy that B2C defines by default is the Resource Owner Password Credentials (ROPC) flow, which implements the OAuth standard authentication flow of the same name and allows users to simply […]
The post Why Azure B2C ROPC Custom Flows Are Inherently Insecure appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthcare: 2023 Insights from the Ponemon Institute]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/healthcare-2023-ponemon-institute-insights</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/healthcare-2023-ponemon-institute-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get insights into offensive security trends in the healthcare sector with data from the Ponemon Institute’s 2023 State of Offensive Security Report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock Linux Unified Key Setup (LUKS) encrypted partitions with TPM 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577641</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/unlock-linux-unified-key-setup-luks-encrypted-partitions-with-tpm-20/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging TPM 2.0 to unlock Linux Unified Key Setup (LUKS) encrypted partitions ensures an added layer of protection, utilizing hardware-backed security measures to safeguard critical data while automating the unlocking of encrypted drives at boot time.
Unlock Linux Unified Key Setup (LUKS) encrypted partitions with TPM 2.0 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evi Vanoost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Newsletter about Climate Change and Industrial Decarbonization]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.hboeck.de/archives/905-guid.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.hboeck.de/archives/905-A-Newsletter-about-Climate-Change-and-Industrial-Decarbonization.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>nospam@example.com (Hanno Böck)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ray, Versions 2.6.3, 2.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/ray-versions-2-6-3-2-8-0</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/ray-versions-2-6-3-2-8-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Bishop Fox advisory highlights three critical severity vulnerabilities in the RAY application versions 2.6.3 and 2.8.0.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Berenice Flores Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update container images with Copa]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577625</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/update-container-images-with-copa/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copa, an open-source container image security tool from Microsoft, addresses the need to update container images. It lets you immediately patch container image vulnerabilities without relying on developers or maintainers.
Update container images with Copa first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Vehicle to Grid spikes coming?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28285</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/are-vehicle-to-grid-spikes-coming/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T06:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you didn’t already know, I’m a massive fan of electric vehicles. One of the aspects that intrigues me is Vehicle to Grid (V2G), the potential for our car batteries […]
Are Vehicle to Grid spikes coming? first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KASLR Leaks Restriction]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=520214</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/kaslr-leaks-restriction/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=kaslr-leaks-restriction"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[…]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File System artifacts for known security software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8901</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/11/26/file-system-artifacts-for-known-security-software/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Phill Moore’s new project called Ruler, I combed my collection of all old HijackThis logs (that I web scraped a long time ago) looking for paths that may be associated with security software. Unlike Phill’s, the resulting data … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Incident Response - A Guide to syslog-ng]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/linux-incident-response-a-guide-to-syslog-ng</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/linux-incident-response-a-guide-to-syslog-ng?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Syslog-ng stands out as an essential log management tool in Linux environments. Its advanced functionalities, coupled with extensive configurational options and robust integration capabilities with SIEM systems, make it an indispensable asset in effective log management and cybersecurity operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.20]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10213</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/11/25/update-1768-py-version-0-0-20/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T10:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update to 1768.py, my Cobalt Strike beacon analysis tool, adds “runtime configuration” extraction. Although 1768.py could already search for beacon configurations inside process memory dumps, the dump was just processed as a raw file. With this update, 1768.py will also search for the runtime configuration inside a process memory dump. The runtime configuration, is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the randomness in the most non-AI/ML way…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8867</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/11/25/looking-for-the-randomness-in-the-most-non-ai-ml-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T00:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s an old-school file name-based research… it is not game changing, it won’t bring any immediate solution, but it’s still worth doing today… The software we install (focus here is on Windows, as usual) creates a loooot of files, and … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in October]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10211</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/11/24/overview-of-content-published-in-october-9/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T16:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in October: Blog posts: Update: simple_listener.py Version 0.1.3 Update: xor-kpa.py Version 0.0.8 Update: pecheck.py Version 0.7.16 Update: myjson-filter.py Version 0.0.5 Update: python-per-line.py Version 0.0.11 Update: simple_listener.py Version 0.1.4 Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.19 Update: format-bytes.py Version 0.0.15 SANS ISC Diary entries: Analyzing MIME Files: a Quick Tip Friendly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If the print spooler stops—how to fix common print spooler errors]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577604</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/if-the-print-spooler-stopshow-to-fix-common-print-spooler-errors/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T09:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you wondering why your printer spooler stopped? This article addresses common Windows print spooler errors and various methods for fixing them.
If the print spooler stops—how to fix common print spooler errors first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-spam policies in Microsoft 365 (Office 365)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577582</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/anti-spam-policies-in-microsoft-365-office-365/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T14:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is astonishing that over 200 billion spam emails are sent out every single day. One way to tackle this problem in Microsoft 365, formerly Office 365, is to use anti-spam policies.
Anti-spam policies in Microsoft 365 (Office 365) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cap Dev. Better red teaming with continuous Capability Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28264</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/cap-dev-better-red-teaming-with-continuous-capability-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T06:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR What Capability Development (Cap Dev) is in this context The big Cap Dev benefits for red teaming Operations and Development, sharing and improving Improvements to TTPs, hardware, and developing […]
Cap Dev. Better red teaming with continuous Capability Development first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world of partially downloaded files…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8883</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/11/22/the-world-of-partially-downloaded-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T23:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anytime you download a file via a browser, instant messenger, or other apps… it is first saved to a temporary file… These temporary files are saved with some particular extensions: For Browsers: For email clients: For Instant Messengers: Are there … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETW internals for security research and forensics]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105338</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/11/22/etw-internals-for-security-research-and-forensics/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T12:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Yarden Shafir Why has Event Tracing for Windows (ETW) become so pivotal for endpoint detection and response (EDR) solutions in Windows 10 and 11? The answer lies in the value of the intelligence it provides to security tools through secure ETW channels, which are now also a target for offensive researchers looking to bypass […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Secure Boot in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577557</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-secure-boot-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of Secure Boot technology has significantly changed the security landscape and gradually gained traction in operating systems, including Linux, offering an additional layer of protection against various forms of malware and unauthorized system alterations.
Install Secure Boot in Linux first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evi Vanoost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Incident Response - Using ss for Network Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/linux-incident-response-using-ss-for-network-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/linux-incident-response-using-ss-for-network-analysis?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ss command is a versatile and powerful tool for incident responders. Its ability to provide detailed socket information, coupled with advanced filtering and process association capabilities, makes it essential for modern network traffic analysis and incident investigation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Incident Response - Introduction to Rootkits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/linux-incident-response-introduction-to-rootkits</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/linux-incident-response-introduction-to-rootkits?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rootkits are an ongoing problem in cybersecurity, particularly within the Linux ecosystem. These surreptitious entities pose a considerable threat by affording unauthorised access and perpetuating control over compromised systems. In this comprehensive exploration, we will delve into the intricacies of Linux rootkits, unravelling their nature, the diverse types they encompass, their intricate construction techniques, and their historical evolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inaugural Glass Firewall Conference Invites Women to Learn About Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/community/glass-firewall-conference</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/community/glass-firewall-conference"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The inaugural Glass Firewall Conference: Breaking Bytes and Barriers was sponsored by Capital One, GitHub, and HackerOne.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passwordless Authentication: Going Beyond Passkeys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=51728</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/passwordless-authentication-going-beyond-passkeys/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T15:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction To overcome the shortcomings of password-based authentication, organizations are exploring innovative mechanisms for signing in. In this blog, we’ll delve into various mechanisms and technologies that address the limitations of passwords and highlight the pros and cons of these solutions. Mechanisms to Replace Passwords Authenticators are means to prove a user’s identity in the […]
The post Passwordless Authentication: Going Beyond Passkeys appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>