<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-17T00:39:51.166Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove an old Windows certificate authority]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569629</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/remove-an-old-windows-certificate-authority/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T13:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's look at the general steps required to remove an old Windows certificate authority without affecting previously issued certificates.
Remove an old Windows certificate authority first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restoring Dyld Memory Loading]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.xpnsec.com/restoring-dyld-memory-loading/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.xpnsec.com/restoring-dyld-memory-loading/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-14T12:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up until recently, we've enjoyed in-memory loading of Mach-O bundles courtesy of dyld and its NSCreateObjectFileImageFromMemory/NSLinkModule API methods. And while these methods still exist today, there is a key difference.. memory modules are now persisted to disk. So in this post we'll take a look at just what was changed in dyld, and see what we can do to restore this functionality... hopefully keeping our warez in memory for a little longer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XPN InfoSec Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypting SHell Compiled (SHC) ELF files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8374</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/01/13/decrypting-shell-compiled-shc-elf-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T23:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its recent blog post AhnLab described a campaign that relies on SHell Compiled (SHC) ELF files. I wanted to see if I can replicate their reverse engineering work and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudLinux LVE kernel module (kmod-lve) Reference Counter Overflow]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2045</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/01/13/cloudlinux-lve-kernel-module-kmod-lve-reference-counter-overflow/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cloudlinux-lve-kernel-module-kmod-lve-reference-counter-overflow"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T22:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-ad32d249 A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the CloudLinux Lightweight Virtualized Environment (LVE) kernel module due to an overflow of a reference counter. Successful exploitation allows an authenticated local user to escalate their privileges to root, whereas an unsuccessful exploit may cause a kernel panic.  Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-ad32d249 MITRE: CVE-2022-0492 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 ... Read more CloudLinux LVE kernel module (kmod-lve) Reference Counter Overflow
The post CloudLinux LVE kernel module (kmod-lve) Reference Counter Overflow appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[H1 Hackers Walk the Streets of Barcelona at H1-3493!]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/h1-hackers-walk-streets-barcelona-h1-3493</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/h1-hackers-walk-streets-barcelona-h1-3493"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T17:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing a stable release of sigstore-python]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103734</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/01/13/sigstore-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T15:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William Woodruff Read the official announcement on the Sigstore blog as well! Trail of Bits is thrilled to announce the first stable release of sigstore-python, a client implementation of Sigstore that we’ve been developing for nearly a year! This work has been graciously funded by Google’s Open Source Security Team (GOSST), who we’ve also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Windows VM in Proxmox VE]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569581</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-a-windows-vm-in-proxmox-ve/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T12:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post, you learned how to get started with Proxmox VE as an alternative to VMware and Hyper-V. In that post, I covered how to run your first Linux VM in Proxmox. Today, I will show you how to create a Windows VM in Proxmox. This may sound like a straightforward task, but there are certain settings in Proxmox VE that are worth checking out to make sure you get better performance in Windows. If you install Windows with the default Proxmox settings, you will likely experience poor performance.
Create a Windows VM in Proxmox VE first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall SMA 500v and SMA 100 Series Firmware Heap Buffer Overflow]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2048</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/01/12/sonicwall-sma-500v-and-sma-100-series-firmware-heap-buffer-overflow/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sonicwall-sma-500v-and-sma-100-series-firmware-heap-buffer-overflow"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T20:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-6a6472ab A remote code execution vulnerability exists in SonicWall SMA 100 Series and SMA 500v Series due to a heap buffer overflow in the ‘extensionsetting’ endpoint. A remote, authenticated attacker can send crafted HTTP POST requests to execute code on vulnerable targets as the ‘nobody’ user. Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-6a6472ab MITRE: CVE-2022-2915 Vulnerability Metrics ... Read more SonicWall SMA 500v and SMA 100 Series Firmware Heap Buffer Overflow
The post SonicWall SMA 500v and SMA 100 Series Firmware Heap Buffer Overflow appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schneider Electric SoMachine HVAC ActiveX Control Information Disclosure Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2047</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/01/12/schneider-electric-somachine-hvac-activex-control-information-disclosure-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=schneider-electric-somachine-hvac-activex-control-information-disclosure-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T20:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-50a1e402 An information disclosure vulnerability exists in Schneider Electric SoMachine HVAC due to a method in the ‘AxEditGrid3.ocx’ ActiveX control leaking a heap address of an ActiveX object. An attacker can entice a user to open a specially crafted web page to leak Internet Explorer process memory information. Vulnerability Identifiers Exodus Intelligence: EIP-50a1e402 MITRE: CVE-2022-2988 ... Read more Schneider Electric SoMachine HVAC ActiveX Control Information Disclosure Vulnerability
The post Schneider Electric SoMachine HVAC ActiveX Control Information Disclosure Vulnerability appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Installing NetHunter On A Nexus 5 (Like It’s 2013).]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/29c0951eba0</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-installing-nethunter-on-a-nexus-5-like-its-2013-29c0951eba0?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T20:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I already know what you’re thinking. What year is it? It’s 2023 and the price of a Raspberry Pi is $150 for a top tier model. A Raspberry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DER Entitlements: The (Brief) Return of the Psychic Paper]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/01/der-entitlements-brief-return-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/01/der-entitlements-brief-return-of.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T16:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=pYEwJuzr3ZMDX2Y1syVbvx06if6osnyAslCuLPPf50A');ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-4{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-5{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-2{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-8{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-6{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_o4b5kflpgafe-7>li:before{content:"-  "}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-7{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_5nbkgo2blvl3-0{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_5nbkgo2blvl3-1{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-0{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_5nbkgo2blvl3-4{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_o4b5kflpgafe-8>li:before{content:"-  "}ul.lst-kix_h97ui6n3g8c8-1{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_5nbkgo2blvl3-5{list…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuration Manager upgrade: New features and installation]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569552</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configuration-manager-upgrade-new-features-and-installation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T16:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Endpoint Configuration Manager 2211 production version was released on December 6, 2022, in the early update ring. In this post, we will go through the new features in version 2211, followed by a step-by-step guide to upgrade the Configuration Manager.
Configuration Manager upgrade: New features and installation first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karthick Jokirathinam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Pwn2Own Vancouver for 2023]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63bf1e75dbbc35368c081d37</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/1/11/announcing-pwn2own-vancouver-for-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T14:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jump to the contest rules
Last year, we celebrated the 15th anniversary of Pwn2Own with a spectacular contest. We awarded more than $1,000,000 USD for the amazing research demonstrated. That makes us even more excited to return to Vancouver for the 2023 edition of Pwn2Own. Similar to last year, we’ll be holding a hybrid conference with most of us in person at the Sheraton Wall Center in Vancouver for the CanSecWest conference on March 22-24, 2023. The other part of the hybrid event means that we also allow remote participation. If you have either travel restrictions or travel safety concerns, you can opt to compete remotely. 
We’re also excited to have Tesla return as a partner. They always innovate, and we’ve updated our target list to keep up. We’ve added a Steam VM Escape category with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCCM Site Takeover via Automatic Client Push Installation]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f567ec80d5b1</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/sccm-site-takeover-via-automatic-client-push-installation-f567ec80d5b1?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T13:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping the wolves out of wolfSSL]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103636</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/01/12/wolfssl-vulnerabilities-tlspuffin-fuzzing-ssh/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Max Ammann Trail of Bits is publicly disclosing four vulnerabilities that affect wolfSSL: CVE-2022-38152, CVE-2022-38153, CVE-2022-39173, and CVE-2022-42905. The four issues, which have CVSS scores ranging from medium to critical, can all result in a denial of service (DoS). These vulnerabilities have been discovered automatically using the novel protocol fuzzer tlspuffin. This blog post […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tobgreg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NoName057(16) – The Pro-Russian Hacktivist Group Targeting NATO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=75365</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/noname05716-the-pro-russian-hacktivist-group-targeting-nato/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T10:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the name of Russia's war in Ukraine, NoName057(16) abuses GitHub and Telegram in an ongoing campaign to disrupt NATO's critical infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Blasting Event-Driven Cornucopia: WMI-based User-Space Attacks Blind SIEMs and EDRs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=75386</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-blasting-event-driven-cornucopia-wmi-based-user-space-attacks-blind-siems-and-edrs/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T14:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WMI-based attacks impact all versions of Windows and can severely impact EDRs. Claudiu Teodorescu explores how they work and how they can be detected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate a SQL Server Database to Azure SQL Database]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569524</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/migrate-a-sql-server-database-to-azure-sql-database/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T14:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to assess and migrate your on-prem SQL Server databases to Azure SQL Database by using Microsoft's Data Migration Assistant and Azure Migrate products.
Migrate a SQL Server Database to Azure SQL Database first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The January 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63b86f0864ff2d30bc75a07d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/1/10/the-january-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first patch Tuesday of the new year. As expected, Adobe and Microsoft have released their latest fixes and updates. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security offerings.
Adobe Patches for January 2023
For January, Adobe released four patches addressing 29 CVEs in Adobe Acrobat and Reader, InDesign, InCopy, and Adobe Dimension. A total of 22 of these bugs were submitted through the ZDI program. The update for Reader fixes 15 bugs with eight of these being ranked Critical in severity. The most severe of these would allow arbitrary code execution if an affected system opened a specially crafted file. The patch for InDesign fixes six bug, four of which are rated Critical. Similar to the Reader patch, openin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDB Tricks: Tricking the Application into Generating Test Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/gdb-tricks--tricking-the-application-into-generating-test-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/gdb-tricks--tricking-the-application-into-generating-test-data"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While reverse engineering a Linux binary, I ran into a fairly common situation: I wanted to understand how a decompression function works, but I didn’t have compressed data to test with. In this blog, I’ll look at how to we can manipulate the instruction pointer in the GNU debugger (gdb) to trick the software into generating test data for us! I posted this on Mastodon awhile back, but I cleaned it up and expanded it a bit to make it a full blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkullSecurity Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Penetration: Not Your Typical Internal Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/not-your-typical-internal-testing</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/not-your-typical-internal-testing"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what it is like to be a cloud penetration tester from our expert, Seth Art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Art</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another prolific year of open-source contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103612</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/01/10/open-source-contributions-2022/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Samuel Moelius This time last year, we wrote about the more than 190 Trail of Bits-authored pull requests that were merged into non-Trail of Bits repositories in 2021. In 2022, we continued that trend by having more than 400 pull requests merged into non-Trail of Bits repositories! Why is this significant? While we take […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install vCenter 8 in VMware Workstation]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569503</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-vcenter-8-in-vmware-workstation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T12:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people use VMware Workstation to set up lab environments. The first step in getting vSphere 8 with a vSphere cluster running is to install the vCenter Server Appliance (vCSA). Let's see how we can deploy vCenter Server 8 in VMware Workstation.
Install vCenter 8 in VMware Workstation first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malware-based attacks on ATMs – A summary]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=13292</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/01/10/malware-based-attacks-on-atms-a-summary/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today we will take a first look at malware-based attacks on ATMs in general, while future articles will go into more detail on the individual subtopics. ATMs have been robbed by criminal gangs around the world for decades. A successful approach since ~ 20 years is the use of highly flammable gas, which is … Continue reading Malware-based attacks on ATMs – A summary →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Poth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Human Security Testing Helps the U.S. Government’s Zero Trust Mandate]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/how-human-security-testing-helps-us-governments-zero-trust-mandate</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/how-human-security-testing-helps-us-governments-zero-trust-mandate"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One major reason for the progress is a May 2021 Executive Order that pushes federal agencies to speedily embrace the “never trust; always verify”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAP Chief Trust Office Thinks Outside the Box on Fostering Talent with SANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sap-chief-trust-office-thinks-outside-the-box-on-fostering-talent-with-sans</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sap-chief-trust-office-thinks-outside-the-box-on-fostering-talent-with-sans?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAP gets creative to develop early cyber talent at the collegiate level, with the SANS Institute’s cyber range portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brand Ambassador Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/brand-ambassador-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/brand-ambassador-announcement"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T16:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 just came to an end. We hope you found plenty of bugs, collected a lot in bounties, and are ready to set goals for this new year. As we turn th]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find the source of AD account lockouts]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569454</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-the-source-of-account-lockouts-in-ad/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, we discussed how to quickly unlock AD accounts with PowerShell. However, the main problem admins tend to face is identifying the source computer or service that is causing the account to lock out in the first place.
Find the source of AD account lockouts first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK gov website being used to redirect to porn sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26414</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/uk-gov-website-being-used-to-redirect-to-porn-sites/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T13:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR UK Government Environment Agency web site had an open redirect that was actively being used to redirect to various porn sites, including OnlyFans clone sites. Disclosure should have been […]
UK gov website being used to redirect to porn sites first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Bromiley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK gov website being used to phish porn site creds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26414</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/uk-gov-website-being-used-to-phish-porn-site-creds/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T13:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR UK Government Environment Agency web site had an open redirect that was actively being used to redirect to various porn sites, including OnlyFans clone sites. Disclosure should have been […]
UK gov website being used to phish porn site creds first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Bromiley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excelling at Excel, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8359</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/01/08/excelling-at-excel-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-08T00:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I will talk about automated query-building using Excel. Working as a detection engineering and/or threat hunting specialist we often need to create a lot of queries including a lot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Holiday Hack Challange 2022: Writeup]]></title>
        <id>https://zeta-two.com/ctf/2023/01/07/sans-holidayhack-2022.html</id>
        <link href="https://zeta-two.com/ctf/2023/01/07/sans-holidayhack-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my write-up for the SANS Holiday Hack Challenge 2022.
Main Objectives
The first part of the objective is an introduction where you are told about how your badge work, how the terminal works and a tutorial on setting up your wallet. It also establishes the backstory and sends you down in the underground tunnels. After this is completed there are five main objective chapters, each containing a few challenges.
Recover the Tolkien Ring
The first chapter is to recover the Tolkien Ring. This chapter revolves around DFIR.
Wireshark Practice
The first challenge is a terminal where you get a PCAP and need to answer a few questions about the traffic.
To answer the first question, we look at the traffic, see that there is a lot of HTTP traffic and then go to File -> Export objects -> HTTP to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zeta-Two.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excelling at Excel, Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8338</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/01/07/excelling-at-excel-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T00:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my old article I have demonstrated an atypical approach one may take to browse through similarly-looking security artifacts while analyzing a gazillion of similarly looking URls in Excel. I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploits Explained: Second Order XXE Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=15895</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/exploits-explained-second-order-xxe-exploitation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T15:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kuldeep Pandya is a member of the Synack Red Team. You can find him on Twitter or his blog. This writeup is about my recent discovery of a Second Order XXE that allowed me to read files stored on the web server. One morning, a fresh target was onboarded and I hopped onto it as […]
The post Exploits Explained: Second Order XXE Exploitation appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SRT Community</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot for the Windows systems administrator]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569434</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/github-copilot-for-the-windows-systems-administrator/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T12:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the AI-powered GitHub Copilot pair programming engine can accelerate your Windows administration work by providing intelligent suggestions while you type.
GitHub Copilot for the Windows systems administrator first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute proudly welcomes professor Ciaran Martin, founder of the UK National Cyber Security Centre, to its ranks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-welcomes-professor-ciaran-martin</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-welcomes-professor-ciaran-martin?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute is thrilled to announce that per January 1st 2023, Professor Ciaran Martin joins our organisation as Director of the global SANS CISO Network and Summits EMEA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking Back at the Bugs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:63b608117391a5180da5502c</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/1/4/looking-back-at-the-bugs-of-2022"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T16:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve successfully orbited our star once more and are full throttle into the new year. We’ve just completed our largest Pwn2Own ever in Toronto and are only six weeks away from Pwn2Own Miami, but before we go too far into 2023, now is a good time to look at some of the numbers and highlights of the past year.
These are a Few of My Favorite Bugs
It’s always great to see the huge number of amazing bugs submitted by independent researchers around the globe, but some really stood out. We’re super thankful for our global community of independent researchers, and we congratulate the 23 researchers to achieve reward levels in 2022. We had five people reach Platinum status, five reach Gold, seven Silver, and six Bronze. The work and submissions from our community of independent researchers are key…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes to Disclosure Assistance]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/changes-disclosure-assistance</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/changes-disclosure-assistance"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne is excited to announce the revamp of our Disclosure Assistance program! Our goal is to reset expectations and realign with the hacker comm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Draft: Containerize apps for Azure Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569413</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/draft-containerize-apps-for-azure-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T14:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Draft is an open-source project that helps developers go from a noncontainerized application to running on Kubernetes with ease. As a developer with Draft, you don't have to go through an extensive ramp of containers, container registries, Kubernetes, and deployment methods to get your app running as a container on Azure Kubernetes.
Draft: Containerize apps for Azure Kubernetes Service first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Buchanan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cloud Security Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog outlining the SANS Cloud Security Curriculum offerings and resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protected: Investigating Filter Communication Ports]]></title>
        <id>https://windows-internals.com/?p=503075</id>
        <link href="https://windows-internals.com/investigating-filter-communication-ports/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=investigating-filter-communication-ports"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T18:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no excerpt because this is a protected post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yarden Shafir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Offensive Security Resolutions from the Fox Den]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/2023-security-resolutions</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/2023-security-resolutions"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get familiar with Bishop Fox's most important offensive security resolutions for 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypting TLS browser traffic with Wireshark]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/decrypt-wireshark-traffic-https-netsh/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/decrypt-wireshark-traffic-https-netsh/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T14:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a combination of lesser known tools and techniques to capture and later decrypt SSL/TLS network traffic on Windows. This technique is neat because it does not require the installation of additional driver/software when capturing the traffic.
Technique, Tools and Steps It is quite straight forward and consists of:
 Setting the SSLKEYLOGFILE environment variable to capture TLS session keys on target host Use netsh trace start to capture traffic (no need to install additional driver/software!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 web hacking techniques of 2022 - nominations open]]></title>
        <id>top-10-web-hacking-techniques-of-2022-nominations-open</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/top-10-web-hacking-techniques-of-2022-nominations-open"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T13:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nominations are now open for the top 10 new web hacking techniques of 2022! Every year, security researchers share their latest findings with the community in a firehose of presentations, whitepapers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | InkySquid: The Missing Arsenal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=75127</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-inkysquid-the-missing-arsenal/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T13:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Rascagneres explores a macOS port of the Windows RokRAT malware and how it bypasses Apple security protections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock AD accounts with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569378</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/unlock-ad-accounts-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T12:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT admins or helpdesk teams often use graphical tools, such as Active Directory Users and Computers (ADUC), to unlock AD accounts. However, it is usually easier to unlock multiple AD accounts with PowerShell.
Unlock AD accounts with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeTT&CT: Automate your detection coverage with dettectinator]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=13726</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/01/04/dettct-automate-your-detection-coverage-with-dettectinator/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T08:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Last year, I published an article on mapping detection to the MITRE ATT&CK framework using DeTT&CT. In the article, we introduced DeTT&CT and explored its features and usage. If you missed it, you can find the article here. Although, after writing that article, I encountered some challenges. For instance, I considered using DeTT&CT in … Continue reading DeTT&CT: Automate your detection coverage with dettectinator →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Renaud Frere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Scanning for Vulnerability Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-scanning-vulnerability-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-scanning-vulnerability-discovery?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we'll look at the step-by-step process of scanning a cloud provider's network for target enumeration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy: Disable cloud-based spell checker in Google Chrome and Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569362</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/privacy-disable-cloud-based-spell-checker-in-google-chrome-and-microsoft-edge/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T14:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the simple, purely local spell checker, the two Chromium-based web browsers, Google Chrome and Microsoft Edge, also offer an advanced spell checker that sends texts entered in web applications to the cloud. This can be turned off interactively or by group policy.
Privacy: Disable cloud-based spell checker in Google Chrome and Microsoft Edge first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABAC in Lambda]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4349</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/abac-in-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T14:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During August 2022 we published a blog discussing AWS Security Trends of 2022 , one of which was ABAC in Lambda. AWS allows administrators to use tags to designate attributes for both IAM and AWS resources. Attribute Based Access Control, or ABAC, is a strategy to allow permissions assignment based on the value of such […]
The post ABAC in Lambda appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting ELF on the shelf…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8329</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/01/03/putting-elf-on-the-shelf/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post I referred to something what I call “putting elf on the shelf”. The idea is simple — Windows is a very rich environment when it comes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PsLoggedOn: View logged-on users in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569348</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/psloggedon-view-logged-on-users-in-windows/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T12:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PsLoggedOn, a command line tool that is part of the Sysinternals suite, gets information about users logged on to Windows. Unfortunately, not everything works as it should.
PsLoggedOn: View logged-on users in Windows first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9874</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/01/02/overview-of-content-published-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in 2022: Blog posts: Update: jpegdump.py Version 0.0.9 Windows Explorer: Improper Exif Data Removal Beta: smtp-honeypot.py Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.63 Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.12 Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.64 New Tool: xlsbdump.py spring4shell Capture File Power Consumption Of A Philips Hue lamp In Off State .ISO Files With […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in December]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9872</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/01/01/overview-of-content-published-in-december-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T09:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in December: Blog posts: Update: python-per-line.py Version 0.0.9 Extracting Certificates For Defender Update: count.py Version 0.3.1 Update: hash.py Version 0.0.9 Update: virustotal-search.py Version 0.1.8 Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.23 New tool: teeplus.py Update: filescanner Version 0.0.0.8 Update: InteractiveSieve Version 0.9.2.0 Update: nsrl.py Version 0.0.4 Update: file-magic.py Version 0.0.5 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A bunch of OLD-School RCE tricks…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=7564</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/01/01/a-bunch-of-old-school-rce-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T00:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while I come across questions from RCE analysts who are asking how to analyze samples when either existing tools don’t work, or when they (analysts) get […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dJulkalender 2022: Write-up]]></title>
        <id>https://zeta-two.com/ctf/2023/01/01/djulkalendern-2022-writeup.html</id>
        <link href="https://zeta-two.com/ctf/2023/01/01/djulkalendern-2022-writeup.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The computer science chapter at my alma mater, KTH, arranges an advent calendar called “dJulkalendern”.
It is a CTF-like puzzle with challenges (almost) every day until christmas and also a competition.
The puzzles are not really security focused like regular CTF but more broader IT related puzzles.
This year, there were a puzzle every weekday and I will go through and explain them all.
To prevent this post from being too long, I will be pretty brief in my explanations. If you have any questions or solved something in a different way, please comment below.
Day -1: Ready?
The first window is simply a warm-up and encourages you to read the lore page to get the backstory and create some hype before the challenges begin.
It also introduces how the password system works by giving you the passwo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zeta-Two.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combining zipdump, file-magic And myjson-filter]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9761</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/31/combining-zipdump-file-magic-and-myjson-filter/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T09:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I show how you can combine my tools zipdump.py, file-magic.py and myjson-filter.py to select and analyze files of a particular type. I start with a daily batch of malware files published by Malware Bazaar. I let it produce JSON output using option –jsonoutput, that can be consumed by some of my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond good ol’ Run key, Part 140]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8321</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2022/12/30/beyond-good-ol-run-key-part-140/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T23:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a real oldie, but still worth a mention… Java gives us a lot of persistence possibilities and one of them are environment variables; when set, they will be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Download and install ADMX templates for Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569331</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/download-and-install-admx-templates-for-microsoft-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T12:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you take a look at the group policy settings in Windows 11 or the separately available ADMX files, you will find settings for Microsoft Edge there. However, they do not affect the Chromium-based browser. For this version, you have to download and install the administrative templates separately.
Download and install ADMX templates for Microsoft Edge first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox VE vs. VMware ESXi vs. Hyper-V]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569311</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/proxmox-ve-vs-vmware-esxi-vs-hyper-v/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T14:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point, admins need to pick a suitable virtualization solution that best aligns with their existing server infrastructure. This post will focus on comparing three hypervisors: Proxmox VE, VMware ESXi, and Hyper-V.
Proxmox VE vs. VMware ESXi vs. Hyper-V first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Breaking Firmware Trust From The Other Side: Exploiting Early Boot Phases (Pre-Efi)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=74649</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-breaking-firmware-trust-from-the-other-side-exploiting-early-boot-phases-pre-efi/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T12:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first public discussion of changes in the UEFI firmware security runtime from an offensive security perspective with Alex Matrosov.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.24]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/29/update-zipdump-py-version-0-0-24/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small update to option -W of zipdump.py. Next to value vir, you can now also specify values hash and hashvir. hash: write each file with name equal to the SHA256 of the content of the file. hashvir: write each file with name equal to the SHA256 of the content of the file plus extension […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work in Microsoft Azure with Visual Studio Code (VS Code)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569297</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/work-in-microsoft-azure-with-visual-studio-code-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T13:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the many ways you can make your Microsoft Azure work easier by integrating with Visual Studio Code (VS Code), Microsoft's free, open-source, cross-platform code editor.
Work in Microsoft Azure with Visual Studio Code (VS Code) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerstrip With Neon Lamp Switch]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9759</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/28/powerstrip-with-neon-lamp-switch/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are powerstrips with a switch that lights up when the switch is turned on. Like this one: These switches (certainly older models) often use a neon lamp as light source. I measured the electric energy consumption of a powerstrip with switch on and neon lamp burning (without anything plugged into the powerstrip’s outlets). It […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Favorite Tools of the Year: 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/favorite-tools-of-2022</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/favorite-tools-of-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out out favorite pen testing tools that we loved using in 2022!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Britt Kemp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install ESXi in a VirtualBox VM]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569284</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-esxi-in-a-virtualbox-vm/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T14:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox provides an effective and free solution for running ESXi in a lab environment. However, at this point, the support for nested virtualization doesn't allow the installation of current versions of VMware's hypervisor. As with Hyper-V VMs, a nested configuration is limited to ESXi 6.x. If you need to enable Microsoft's hypervisor on a Windows PC, VirtualBox can run on top of it.
Install ESXi in a VirtualBox VM first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combining dns-pydivert And dnsresolver]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9793</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/27/combining-dns-pydivert-and-dnsresolver/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use my tools dns-pydivert and dnsresolver.py for dynamic analysis of software (malware and benign software). On the virtual machine where I’m doing dynamic analysis, I disable IPv6 support. I install dnslib and run dnsresolver.py with a command like this, for example: The first command is a resolve command: DNS A queries for example.com will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terminate Windows processes with PsKill]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569257</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/terminate-windows-processes-with-pskill/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-26T16:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PsKill is a command-line tool that is part of the Sysinternals suite. As the name suggests, it allows you to terminate (kill) Windows processes on local or remote Windows systems.
Terminate Windows processes with PsKill first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tool: dns-pydivert.py]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9763</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/26/new-tool-dns-pydivert-py/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dns-pydivert is a tool that uses WinDivert, a “user-mode packet capture-and-divert package for Windows” to divert IPv4 DNS packets to and from the machine it is running on. This tool requires admin rights. When started, it listens for IPv4 UDP packets with source and/or destination port equal to 53.When this tools processes its first UDP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: dnsresolver.py Version 0.0.2]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9727</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/25/update-dnsresolver-py-version-0-0-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update to dnsresolver.py, my custom DNS server, adds a command to forward DNS request. With this forward command, all requests that are not handled by other commands, are forwarded to the provided DNS server. dnsresolver_V0_0_2.zip (http)MD5: D96EA9517E106C4C9E3668AB6799B150SHA256: 611C1540FE7FA2016E38689A153681428BBF3EAFC927A62342310A93022B3EC4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: myjson-filter.py Version 0.0.3]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9754</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/24/update-myjson-filter-py-version-0-0-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update of myjson-filter.py adds an option (-t) to filter on the magic field added by file-magic.py. To be explained in an upcoming blog post. myjson-filter_V0_0_3.zip (http)MD5: AB8AF505B120D02AD1A9846A72A340B5SHA256: AB73314ACCD65EC765D6DDA629AF273FF882D293F11F6A2EA8FC633B019E5836]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LTR102 - Published Finally!]]></title>
        <id>6396fefa31bc853bb2be6e53</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/ltr102-published-finally/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T18:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Everyone, 
This a short blog post to announce I have finally published my second book after several years of work. I have spent nearly five writing it; like my first one, it follows the path of getting into and progressing in the industry, while LTR101 was focused on bug]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SecureAuth Wins 2022 CISO Choice Award for Identity and Access Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=46733</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/secureauth-wins-2022-ciso-choice-award-for-identity-and-access-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T14:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contemporary customers expect every organization to deliver seamless customer registration and authentication—keeping that experience safe and convenient is challenging. Organizations shouldn’t have to compromise their user experience for strong security. With Arculix by SecureAuth platform, you can have both. SecureAuth is thrilled to be awarded the 2022 CISO Choice Award Identity and Access Management category […]
The post SecureAuth Wins 2022 CISO Choice Award for Identity and Access Management appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Microsoft apps with Intune]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569245</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-microsoft-apps-with-intune/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T12:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can install Microsoft apps with Intune and receive updates whenever a new version is released. Intune can also automatically update Microsoft apps. The Microsoft Store supports UWP apps, desktop applications packaged as .msix, and Win32 apps packaged as .exe or .msi installers. You can browse the apps in Intune and install or uninstall them.
Install Microsoft apps with Intune first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karthick Jokirathinam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: file-magic.py Version 0.0.5]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9751</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/23/update-file-magic-py-version-0-0-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update of file-magic.py brings option –jsonoutput to augment json input data with a magic field. To be explained in an upcoming blog post after myjson-filter.py update is released. file-magic_V0_0_5.zip (http)MD5: 5B4CB4EE75E1CAC7705E33CCE4809E10SHA256: 876F9AC31E1EC395EB93922AA2A7EFA027534F7343500648FE0A036021C7F1B9]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to share what you’ve learned from our audits]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103585</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/12/22/curl-security-audit-threat-model/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T20:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Nick Selby Trail of Bits recently completed a security review of cURL, which is an amazing and ubiquitous tool for transferring data. We were really thrilled to see cURL founder and lead developer Daniel Stenberg write a blog post about the engagement and the report, and wanted to highlight some important things he pointed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom-Branded Ransomware: The Vice Society Group and the Threat of Outsourced Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=74629</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/custom-branded-ransomware-the-vice-society-group-and-the-threat-of-outsourced-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T13:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New PolyVice ransomware is likely in use by multiple threat actors building re-branded payloads with the same custom encryption scheme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Cocomazzi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlled folder access: Configure ransomware protection with Group Policy and PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569225</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/controlled-folder-access-configure-ransomware-protection-with-group-policy-and-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T13:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Controlled folder access prevents suspicious programs from modifying or creating files in protected directories, such as Documents, Pictures, Favorites, or Desktop. The feature can be configured centrally via group policies, for example, to allow access to additional apps.
Controlled folder access: Configure ransomware protection with Group Policy and PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast and accurate syntax searching for C and C++]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103559</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/12/22/syntax-searching-c-c-clang-ast/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T13:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Mate Kukri The naive approach to searching for patterns in source code is to use regular expressions; a better way is to parse the code with a custom parser, but both of these approaches have limitations. During my internship, I prototyped an internal tool called Syntex that does searching on Clang ASTs to avoid […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puckungfu: A NETGEAR WAN Command Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18482</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/12/22/puckungfu-a-netgear-wan-command-injection/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T11:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Vulnerability Details Overview Execution Flow /bin/pucfu /usr/lib/libfwcheck.so get_check_fw fw_check_api curl_post /lib/libpu_util.so SetFileValue pegaPopen Check Firmware HTTPS Normal Request & Response Exploitation Command Injection Response Root Shell Final Notes Patch Pwn2Own Note Summary This blog post describes a command injection vulnerability found and exploited in November 2022 by NCC Group in the Netgear RAX30 router’s … Continue reading Puckungfu: A NETGEAR WAN Command Injection →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>McCaulay Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: nsrl.py Version 0.0.4]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9748</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/22/update-nsrl-py-version-0-0-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a bug fix version for my nsrl.py script, a tool to check hashes with the NSRL list. nsrl_V0_0_4.zip (http)MD5: 6F72B03493C73E88CB3771C860BC76D0SHA256: D68039B8654C1D52CD1C12670C7E885E462B72BF23892E86BE86E6381C95B669]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visualizing Live Hacking Events: Hackers Break Records at H1-702]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/visualizing-live-hacking-events-hackers-break-records-h1-702</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/visualizing-live-hacking-events-hackers-break-records-h1-702"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T22:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checkout this infographic for a more detailed look at stats, hacker perspectives, and highlights of our event. Be sure to checkout all of our H@ckti]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passwordless Persistence and Privilege Escalation in Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/98a01310be3f</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/passwordless-persistence-and-privilege-escalation-in-azure-98a01310be3f?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T16:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Problems ChatGPT Can Solve For Reverse Engineers and Malware Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=74592</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/11-problems-chatgpt-can-solve-for-reverse-engineers-and-malware-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT has captured the imagination of many across infosec. Here's how it can superpower the efforts of reversers and malware analysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-service password reset with ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569211</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/self-service-password-reset-with-manageengine-adselfservice-plus/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T14:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus is a fully featured solution to easily implement self-service password reset, SSO, password synchronization, MFA, and an employee directory while enforcing strong password policies.
Self-service password reset with ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: InteractiveSieve Version 0.9.2.0]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9743</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/21/update-interactivesieve-version-0-9-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New features: InteractiveSieve_V_0_9_2_0.zip (http)MD5: 74A4019A36199C5057207184341FB639SHA256: D9481C99F44FCEA0729F526B70E307881E2128FB1EB23DF135790EDB4392CB4A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A From SANS Special Broadcast: What You Need to Know About OpenAI's New ChatGPT Bot - and How it Affects Your Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/openai-chatgpt-special-broadcast-qa</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/openai-chatgpt-special-broadcast-qa?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We had an influx of questions come in during our ChatGPT Special Broadcast on Wednesday, December 21. Here were those questions — and our responses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrate Those Making a Difference in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/celebrate-those-making-a-difference-in-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/celebrate-those-making-a-difference-in-cybersecurity?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the 2022 SANS Difference Makers Award winners and how they are influencing the cybersecurity industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: Let’s Make Some Malware In C: Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/223b7e81133e</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-lets-make-some-malware-in-c-part-3-223b7e81133e?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to part 3 of our series! That last one was crazy long. This one is going to be pretty short because we’re not really going to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Hacker Holiday Gift Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/hacker-holiday-gift-guide</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/hacker-holiday-gift-guide"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need gift ideas for your favorite hackers? We've got you covered with our Hacker Holiday Gift Guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shanni Prutchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing the Work: How to Architect a Systematic Security Program, Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4334</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/prioritize-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T14:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a security program from the ground up is a complicated, complex undertaking that can pay massive dividends down the road. We firmly believe that “the devil is in the details,” in that the more thought an organization invests in organizing their framework (see Part 1 of this series) and planning how to measure against […]
The post Doing the Work: How to Architect a Systematic Security Program, Part 3 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What child is this?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=103522</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2022/12/20/process-reparenting-microsoft-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer on Process Reparenting in Windows By Yarden Shafir Process reparenting is a technique used in Microsoft Windows to create a child process under a different parent process than the one making the call to CreateProcess. Malicious actors can use this technique to evade security products or break process ancestry ties, making detection more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox VE: Virtualization alternative to VMware ESXi and Hyper-V]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569192</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/proxmox-ve-virtualization-alternative-to-vmware-esxi-and-hyper-v/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T12:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for a virtualization alternative to Microsoft Hyper-V and VMware ESXi? Proxmox VE is a Debian-based opensource alternative virtualization solution with a custom Linux kernel that you can use to virtualize bare-metal servers in your enterprise. It uses kernel-based virtual machine (KVM) virtualization technology for virtual machines and Linux Containers (LXC) for containers, allowing you to create and manage VMs, containers, storage, virtualized networks, clusters, and much more. This post shows how you can install the Proxmox Virtualization Environment (VE).
Proxmox VE: Virtualization alternative to VMware ESXi and Hyper-V first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: filescanner Version 0.0.0.8]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9737</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/20/update-filescanner-version-0-0-0-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new version brings extra statistics with option -f (fullread): counter for unique bytes, control bytes, printable bytes, high bytes. And lengths of the longest ASCII string, ASCII hexadecimal string and ASCII base64 string. Remark that no check is made for hex string length being a multiple of 2 and base64 string length being a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find Active Directory accounts configured for DES and RC4 Kerberos encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1569149</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-active-directory-accounts-configured-for-des-and-rc4-kerberos-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T17:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While DES has long been considered insecure, CVE-2022-37966 accelerates the departure of RC4 for the encryption of Kerberos tickets. If you have not explicitly assigned an algorithm to accounts, then AES will be used in the future. You can use PowerShell to determine which accounts are vulnerable to weak encryption.
Find Active Directory accounts configured for DES and RC4 Kerberos encryption first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Kernel: Exploiting a Netfilter Use-after-Free in kmalloc-cg]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2018</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2022/12/19/linux-kernel-exploiting-a-netfilter-use-after-free-in-kmalloc-cg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=linux-kernel-exploiting-a-netfilter-use-after-free-in-kmalloc-cg"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T15:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Sergi Martinez Overview It’s been a while since our last technical blogpost, so here’s one right on time for the Christmas holidays. We describe a method to exploit a use-after-free in the Linux kernel when objects are allocated in a specific slab cache, namely the kmalloc-cg series of SLUB caches used for cgroups. This ... Read more Linux Kernel: Exploiting a Netfilter Use-after-Free in kmalloc-cg
The post Linux Kernel: Exploiting a Netfilter Use-after-Free in kmalloc-cg appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MeshyJSON: A TP-Link tdpServer JSON Stack Overflow]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=18444</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2022/12/19/meshyjson-a-tp-link-tdpserver-json-stack-overflow/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T11:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Target Binary tdpServer Architecture & Mitigations Forks Understanding The Vulnerability Reaching The Vulnerable Function Broadcast Fork Flow Server Fork Flow JSON Array Stack Overflow Triggering The Bug Broadcast Fork Response Server Fork Request Vulnerability Constraints Storing Arbitrary Content In Memory cJSON Summarized cJSON Struct cJSON Data cJSON Heap Memory Single cJSON cJSON structure and … Continue reading MeshyJSON: A TP-Link tdpServer JSON Stack Overflow →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>McCaulay Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beauty of Being a Cybersecurity Project Manager for NVISO NITRO MDR]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=13274</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2022/12/19/the-beauty-of-being-a-cybersecurity-project-manager-for-nviso-nitro-mdr/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Project Managers might agree with this: working as a Project Manager is exciting as no two days are ever the same. Just like a conductor of an orchestra leads all musicians to bring harmonic masterpieces to life, so does the cybersecurity Project Manager leading and coordinating the different stakeholders to bring a project to … Continue reading The Beauty of Being a Cybersecurity Project Manager for NVISO NITRO MDR →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Rita Milanese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New tool: teeplus.py]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=9757</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2022/12/19/new-tool-teeplus-py/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new tool, teeplus.py, is an extension of the tee command. The tools takes (binary) data from stdin, and sends it to stdout, while also writing the data to a file on disk. While the tee command requires a filename as argument, teeplus.py takes no arguments (only options). By default, teeplus.py will write the data […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, No Case Studies—But . . .]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e7cf012af19807518fba2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/sorry-no-case-study"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend of the site recently suggested that we create a current-issue case 
study using our updated risk discovery approach. “It’s a great idea,” we 
replied and immediately started kicking around ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pointillism of Daily Events]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2c8f009baa12346d3711f</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/pointillism-daily-events"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Baker’s book Human Smoke brilliantly illustrates a unique approach 
to historical narrative. It also underscores the need to remember that 
every artist paints with intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ready for What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2aa91391dcb70804f9850</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/getting-ready-whats-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new age of giant monsters, advanced awareness of classical 
surprise—that one big tipping moment—no longer suffices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Your ‘Free Cells’ Mindfully]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62deb6110fd7f314e5696ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/manage-free-cells"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accommodate but don’t fight the limitations you can’t control, recognize 
those you can influence and leverage, and don't imagine you have more free 
cells than you actually do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popski’s Planning]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d81b5affdc983dd1f616f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/popskis-planning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British officer Vladimir Peniakoff’s approach to planning might sound a bit 
unorthodox at first, but it aligns nicely with Patton’s view of 
intelligence and speaks to an enduring need to understand front-line 
conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a New Game Board]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d5b6db0343fb487527fc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/time-for-a-new-game-board"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need a more flexible game board where players can explore hypergame 
strategies—in other words, a game board where the strategist can play the 
hero for a change. We’ve built it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survivors Exceeded the Minimum]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62cf11283f1bdb1191fcdf9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/survivors-exceeded-minimum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T18:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every surprise is a cunning thunderbolt. Some surprises creep up 
slowly, rusting away former resilience until a simple nudge reveals the 
rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>