<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-30T00:40:17.995Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes Persistent Volumes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571817</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/understanding-kubernetes-persistent-volumes/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T16:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Persistent volumes allow administrators to configure persistent data locations for stateful applications. They allow containerized applications to store data beyond the lifecycle of individual containers or pods. This makes it possible to retain data even after a pod restart or update. With Kubernetes, persistent volumes are storage locations provisioned by an administrator or dynamically created using StorageClasses.
Understanding Kubernetes Persistent Volumes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XSS in WordPress via open embed auto discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://research.securitum.com/?p=1966</id>
        <link href="https://research.securitum.com/xss-in-wordpress-via-open-embed-auto-discovery/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T10:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Users often assume that known software is free of security flaws because it has been checked by a sufficient number of tools and security testers. However, this is not an assumption that a pentester or bug hunter can afford to make. Vulnerabilities may lurk in various places, and finding an interesting bug often requires ...
The post XSS in WordPress via open embed auto discovery appeared first on research.securitum.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miwn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plugin Exploit Explained: From Prompt Injection to Accessing Private Data]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-cross-plugin-request-forgery-and-prompt-injection./</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-cross-plugin-request-forgery-and-prompt-injection./"/>
        <updated>2023-05-28T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are building ChatGPT plugins, LLM agents, tools or integrations this is a must read. This post explains how the first exploitable Cross Plugin Request Forgery was found in the wild and the fix which was applied.
Indirect Prompt Injections Are Now A Reality With plugins Indirect Prompt Injections are now a reality in the ChatGPT ecosystem.
The real-world examples and demos provided by others and myself to raise awarness about this increasing problem have been mostly amusing and harmless, like making Bing Chat speak like a pirate, make ChatGPT add jokes at the end or having it do a Rickroll when reading YouTube transcripts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BalenaEtcher (alias Etcher): Burn OS image to a USB drive]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571830</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/balenaetcher-alias-etcher-burn-os-image-to-a-usb-drive/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Etcher, also known as BalenaEtcher, is a tool for copying operating systems and burning the OS image onto removable external media, such as USB drives or SD cards. Etcher is an open-source, free tool. Etcher supports Windows (version 7 and above), macOS (Yosemite and above), and all major Linux distributions.
BalenaEtcher (alias Etcher): Burn OS image to a USB drive first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Massimo Maggioni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release: Code Query (cq)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30198</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/26/tool-release-code-query-cq/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code Query is a new, open source universal code security scanning tool. CQ scans code for security vulnerabilities and other items of interest to security-focussed code reviewers. It outputs text files containing references to issues found, into an output directory. These output files can then be reviewed, filtered by unix command line tools such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chrisanley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Technical Director (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-technical-director-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-technical-director-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[テクニカルディレクターの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cockpit: GUI administration for Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571808</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/cockpit-gui-administration-for-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T19:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cockpit is a Linux tool that allows you to perform system administration tasks via a graphical user interface (GUI), namely, a web browser. Traditionally, Linux administration was done using the command line, and a good sysadmin was characterized by the number of commands he knew well. Cockpit as a GUI tool aims to lower the barrier of entry for new sysadmins on Linux while making it easier for everyone with a friendly, clickable interface. In this article, I'll take a look at Cockpit, its features, advantages, limitations, and disadvantages.
Cockpit: GUI administration for Linux first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Virtual Machine Internals – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=30210</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/blockchain-penetration-testing/ethereum-virtual-machine-internals-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T19:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 of the EVM Internals series, exploring how data structures are persisted between contract calls.
The post Ethereum Virtual Machine Internals – Part 2  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NetSPI Distributed Ledger Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CowCloud]]></title>
        <id>https://ncc-blog.pixelpreview.net/?p=24778</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/25/cowcloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T17:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common challenge technical teams (e.g. penetration testers) face is centralized deployment and pipelining execution of security tools. It is possible that at some point you have thought about customising several tools, buying their commercial licenses, and allowing a number of people to run the tools from AWS. The problem is that this means you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nccricardomr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting the Sonos One Speaker Three Different Ways: A Pwn2Own Toronto Highlight]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:646e57de67cf777db719ba9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/5/24/exploiting-the-sonos-one-speaker-three-different-ways-a-pwn2own-toronto-highlight"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T15:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Pwn2Own Toronto 2022, three different teams successfully exploited the Sonos One Speaker. In total, $105,000 was awarded to the three teams, with the team of Toan Pham and Tri Dang from Qrious Secure winning $60,000 since their entry was first on the schedule. Part of Pwn2Own competitions involves a random drawing for order. Not only does the team selected first get the full award if they are successful, but the subsequent entries are also more likely to have bug collisions. That means if three teams show up with the same exploit, only the first one randomly selected will get full credit. That’s not exactly what happened during the event, but some bug collisions did occur. In fact, there were four unique bugs used by the three different teams. Let’s take a look at the vulnerabilitie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZDI Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power Up Your Pen Tests: Creating Burp Suite Extensions with the New Montoya API]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/power-pen-tests-with-montoya-api</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/power-pen-tests-with-montoya-api"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to power up your pen tests by using the new Montoya API to create Burp Suite extensions from scratch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Cerne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operation Magalenha | Long-Running Campaign Pursues Portuguese Credentials and PII]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=80903</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/operation-magalenha-long-running-campaign-pursues-portuguese-credentials-and-pii/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T10:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Brazilian threat actor is targeting users of over 30 Portuguese financial institutions with custom backdoors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cybersecurity-leadership-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cybersecurity-leadership-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Summit 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUEST BLOG: Governments Across The World Are Mandating Vulnerability Disclosure So Why Are Companies Sitting On Their Hands?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/guest-blog-governments-across-world-are-mandating-vulnerability-disclosure-so-why-are-companies</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/guest-blog-governments-across-world-are-mandating-vulnerability-disclosure-so-why-are-companies"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>alice@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change Windows network profiles between public and private]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571789</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/change-windows-network-profiles-between-public-and-private/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T16:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows has three types of network profiles: domain, private, and public. The former is automatically assigned to all computers that are members of an AD domain, and this cannot be changed. On the other hand, you can switch between private and public to activate the associated security settings.
Change Windows network profiles between public and private first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Procedures: Digging into the Function Call Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/88c082aeb573</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/beyond-procedures-digging-into-the-function-call-stack-88c082aeb573?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T15:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan D.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enforce Zero Trust in Microsoft 365 – Part 3: Introduction to Conditional Access]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=10403</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/05/24/enforce-zero-trust-in-microsoft-365-part-3-introduction-to-conditional-access/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post is the third blog post of a series dedicated to Zero Trust security in Microsoft 365. In the first two blog posts, we set the basics by going over the free features of Azure AD that can be implemented in an organization that starts its Zero Trust journey in Microsoft 365. We … Continue reading Enforce Zero Trust in Microsoft 365 – Part 3: Introduction to Conditional Access →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillaume Bossiroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EFB vulnerability in Lufthansa’s Lido eRouteManual]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26536</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/efb-vulnerability-in-lufthansas-lido-eroutemanual/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T05:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost all commercial airlines now use electronic flight bags (EFBs) to drive efficiency and safety in their operations. We’ve been testing the security of EFBs and their apps, here’s our […]
EFB vulnerability in Lufthansa’s Lido eRouteManual first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Lomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeXRAY, DFIR, and the art of ambulance chasing…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8548</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/23/dexray-dfir-and-the-art-of-ambulance-chasing/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T22:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty much all of my DeXRAY posts ever published been focusing on new versions of this tool being released. Today I will talk about the ‘making of the sausages’ part […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOSS BloodHound 4.3.1 release]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7606f87786f6</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/foss-bloodhound-4-3-1-release-7606f87786f6?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T17:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bülow Knudsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll: How reliable are chatGPT and Bing Chat?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571851</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/poll-how-reliable-are-chatgpt-and-bing-chat/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T17:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no denying that Google has been the most crucial resource for IT professionals for the past two decades. Most IT professionals are adept problem solvers, and there are only a handful of IT issues that cannot be resolved by the vast resources of the internet. As AI-powered search engines continue to emerge, a question arises: will Google be replaced by GPT-4-based chatbots and search engines like chatGPT and Bing Chat?
Poll: How reliable are chatGPT and Bing Chat? first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content Discovery: Understanding Your Web Attack Surface]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4642</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/content-discovery-understanding-your-web-attack-surface/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T13:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attack Surface Management (ASM) tools find quite a lot of vulnerabilities on the Web. This really isn’t surprising, given that HTTP/S is by far the most common and broadest of all the services comprising the Internet. In fact, Web-based issues represent the majority of the findings about which our Managed Service Providers (MSPs) inform our […]
The post Content Discovery: Understanding Your Web Attack Surface appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OffensiveCon 2023 – Exploit Engineering – Attacking the Linux Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30772</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/23/offensivecon-2023-exploit-engineering-attacking-the-linux-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T12:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cedric Halbronn and Alex Plaskett presented at OffensiveCon on the 19th of May 2023 on Exploit Engineering – Attacking the Linux kernel. Slides The slides for the talk can be downloaded below: libslub libslub can be downloaded from here. Abstract The abstract for the talk was as follows: Over the last year the Exploit Development […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Plaskett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kimsuky | Ongoing Campaign Using Tailored Reconnaissance Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=80904</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/kimsuky-ongoing-campaign-using-tailored-reconnaissance-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T11:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean APT group focuses on file reconnaissance and information exfiltration with latest variant of RandomQuery malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trusted publishing: a new benchmark for packaging security]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104441</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/05/23/trusted-publishing-a-new-benchmark-for-packaging-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T11:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the official announcement on the PyPI blog as well! For the past year, we’ve worked with the Python Package Index to add a new, more secure authentication method called “trusted publishing.” Trusted publishing eliminates the need for long-lived API tokens and passwords, reducing the risk of supply chain attacks and credential leaks while also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Woodruff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release: Code Credential Scanner (ccs)]]></title>
        <id>https://ncc-blog.pixelpreview.net/?p=26783</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/23/tool-release-code-credential-scanner-ccs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code Credential Scanner is a new open source tool designed to detect hardcoded credentials, or credentials present in configuration files within a repository. These represent a serious security issue, and can be extremely hard to detect and manage. The tool is intended to be used directly by dev teams in a CI/CD pipeline, to manage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chrisanley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Reasons to Attend SANS Blue Team Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/top-5-reasons-to-attend-sans-blue-team-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/top-5-reasons-to-attend-sans-blue-team-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Blue Team Summit 2023 is virtual, completely free, and is full of actionable talks from world-class blue team experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Overfitting Risks in Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30352</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/22/exploring-overfitting-risks-in-large-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T21:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the following blog post, we explore how overfitting can affect Large Language Models (LLMs) in particular, since this technology is used in the most promising AI technologies we see today (chatGPT, LLaMa, Bard, etc). Furthermore, by exploring the likelihood of inferring data from the dataset, we will determine how much we can trust these […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Selvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Brief: Chariot Alignment with FDA Section 524B.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4655</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/in-brief-chariot-and-section-524b-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T14:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chariot is more than a product; it’s a partnership that combines automated monitoring and human analysis to identify externally-accessible security risks. In light of the FDA’s latest requirements for in-market device security (summarized in Section 524B), Praetorian’s customers are having success leveraging the Chariot Managed Service as a cost-effective and scalable approach to satisfying Section […]
The post In Brief: Chariot Alignment with FDA Section 524B.1 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Evil WMI Event Consumers with Disk Forensics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/finding-evil-wmi-event-consumers-with-disk-forensics</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/finding-evil-wmi-event-consumers-with-disk-forensics?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WMI event consumers will continue to be abused in the wild as long as organizations fail to discover and remediate them. While live collection and analysis is preferable to scale efforts across a network, this post covered disk-based artifacts and tools available for use during deeper forensic investigations. A KAPE target exists to collect the required files for offline analysis, making it an easy check to perform during incident response forensic investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what-is-CVSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cvss</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cvss?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVSS stands for the Common Vulnerability Scoring System and is explained in this blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUEST BLOG: Vulnerability Disclosure Adoption In The Consumer IoT space Is Lagging, But What About Elsewhere?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-disclosure/guest-blog-vulnerability-disclosure-adoption-consumer-iot-space-lagging</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-disclosure/guest-blog-vulnerability-disclosure-adoption-consumer-iot-space-lagging"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>alice@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxmox Backup Server: Install and configure]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571771</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/proxmox-backup-server-install-and-configure/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T16:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, I discussed built-in snapshots and backup features in Proxmox VE. Today, I will have a look at Proxmox Backup Server. Proxmox Backup Server is an enterprise-ready backup and recovery solution for VMs, containers, and physical servers. It supports deduplicated and incremental backups to reduce network load and increase storage efficiency.
Proxmox Backup Server: Install and configure first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Paillier Cryptosystem with Applications to Threshold ECDSA]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30179</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/19/the-paillier-cryptosystem-with-applications-to-threshold-ecdsa/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard of RSA (b. 1977), but have you heard of its cousin, Paillier (b. 1999)? In this post, we provide a close look at the Paillier homomorphic encryption scheme [Paillier1999], what it offers, how it’s used in complex protocols, and how to implement it securely. Contents RSA Encryption Refresher and Notation We’ll […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marie-Sarah Lacharite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Windows 10 S mode? How does Windows 11 S mode differ?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571720</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/what-is-windows-10-s-mode-how-does-windows-11-s-mode-differ/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 S mode builds on its predecessor, Windows 10 S mode. It is a streamlined version of Windows 11, designed to provide a secure, fast, and easy-to-use computing experience. In this article, we will explore the key features and benefits of Windows 11 S mode and compare them to Windows 10 S mode. In addition, you will learn how to disable Windows 11 S mode.
What is Windows 10 S mode? How does Windows 11 S mode differ? first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Distilled: Building a First-Principles Approach to Understanding Security]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cc9cd093a318</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/security-distilled-building-a-first-principles-approach-to-understanding-security-cc9cd093a318?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T13:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan D.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All your building are belong to us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26892</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/all-your-building-are-belong-to-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T05:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Building Management Systems (BMS) bring new risks to businesses that haven’t had previous experience of  securing Operational Technology (OT) While there might not be direct financial gain from hacking […]
All your building are belong to us first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Thom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: OSINT investigator/Analyst (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-osint-investigator-analyst-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-osint-investigator-analyst-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OSINT調査員/アナリストの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-20869/20870: Exploiting VMware Workstation at Pwn2Own Vancouver]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64652c822dcf0d009e347fe0</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/5/17/cve-2023-2086920870-exploiting-vmware-workstation-at-pwn2own-vancouver"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T15:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post covers an exploit chain demonstrated by Nguyễn Hoàng Thạch (@hi_im_d4rkn3ss) of STAR Labs SG Pte. Ltd. during the Pwn2Own Vancouver event in 2023. During the contest, he used an uninitialized variable bug and a stack-based buffer overflow in VMware to escalate from a guest OS to execute code on the underlying hypervisor. His successful demonstration earned him $80,000 and 8 points towards Master of Pwn. All Pwn2Own entries are accompanied by a full whitepaper describing the vulnerabilities being used and how they were exploited. The following blog is an excerpt from that whitepaper detailing CVE-2023-20869 and CVE-2023-20870 with minimal modifications.
Prior to being patched by VMware, a pair of vulnerabilities existed within the implementation of the virtual Bluetooth USB device…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZDI Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulseway 9.2: Remote monitoring with workflow automation]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571710</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/pulseway-92-remote-monitoring-with-workflow-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T15:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the Pulseway 9.2 update, offering enhanced IT management features, such as policy redesign, workflow automation improvements, remote control enhancements, and more.
Pulseway 9.2: Remote monitoring with workflow automation first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Does This Look Infected 2 (APT41)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=80809</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-does-this-look-infected-2-apt41/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T13:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mandiant researchers Van Ta and Rufus Brown take us on a journey of discovery into the compromise of multiple U.S. Government networks by APT41.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rigging the Vote: Uniqueness in Verifiable Random Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://ncc-blog.pixelpreview.net/?p=26731</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/18/rigging-the-vote-uniqueness-in-verifiable-random-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post presents a whirlwind overview of Verifiable Random Functions (VRFs) as used by several leading-edge blockchains, and shows how a very interesting and recently found implementation oversight causes the VRF’s assurance of uniqueness to fall apart. As VRFs are commonly used for selecting blockchain consensus voting committees, this can result in a rigged […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blue teaming – it’s DATa complicated…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8513</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/17/blue-teaming-its-data-complicated/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T22:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade ago blue teaming was … easy (this is a really bad joke, I know!). In fairness, we had less targets, less programming languages to deal with, less platforms, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medical Devices: A Hardware Security Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30557</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/17/medical-devices-a-hardware-security-perspective/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T17:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medical device security is gaining more attention for several reasons. The conversation often gets connected to device safety, that is, the degree to which the risk of patient harm is limited by preventing or controlling for device malfunction. Device security expands the scope of safety by supposing a malicious attacker is causing or exploiting the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameson Hyde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bug bounties are broken – the story of “i915” bug, ChromeOS + Intel bounty programs, and beyond]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.pi3.com.pl/?p=931</id>
        <link href="http://blog.pi3.com.pl/?p=931"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T15:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At first, I didn’t plan to write an article about the problems with bug bounty programs. This was supposed to be a standard technical blogpost describing an interesting bug in the Linux Kernel i915 driver allowing for a linear Out-Of-Bound read and write access (CVE-2023-28410). Moreover, I’m not even into bug bounty programs, mostly because […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pi3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A More Complete Exploit for Fortinet CVE-2022-42475]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/exploit-cve-2022-42475</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/exploit-cve-2022-42475"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about our unique research focused on CVE-2022-42475 and how an exploit can be built to target a single specific FortiGate appliance running a single specific version of FortiOSbug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Livitt, Jon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to map a network drive with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571690</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-map-a-network-drive-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T08:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to assign a drive letter to file shares via the command line, you can use PowerShell instead of net.exe. The SmbShare module's cmdlets can display, connect, and disconnect shared drives. PowerShell also supports newer SMB features, such as QUIC and Compression.
How to map a network drive with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome V8 ArrayShift Race Condition Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2120</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/05/16/google-chrome-v8-arrayshift-race-condition-remote-code-execution/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T22:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Javier Jimenez Overview This post describes a method of exploiting a race condition in the V8 JavaScript engine, version 9.1.269.33. The vulnerability affects the following versions of Chrome and Edge: Google Chrome versions between 90.0.4430.0 and 91.0.4472.100. Microsoft Edge versions between 90.0.818.39 and 91.0.864.41. The vulnerability occurs when one of the TurboFan jobs generates a ... Read more Google Chrome V8 ArrayShift Race Condition Remote Code Execution
The post Google Chrome V8 ArrayShift Race Condition Remote Code Execution appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From DA to EA with ESC5]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f9f045aa105c</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/from-da-to-ea-with-esc5-f9f045aa105c?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T18:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a new, practical way to escalate from Domain Admin to Enterprise Admin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Robbins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding the HackerOne Code of Conduct]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/decoding-hackerone-code-conduct</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/decoding-hackerone-code-conduct"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the industry continues to rapidly evolve, it is on HackerOne to try to ensure that we align with the industry norms of Code of Conduct management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ENow Active Directory Monitoring & Reporting]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571679</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enow-active-directory-monitoring-reporting/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T15:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ENow Active Directory Monitoring & Reporting provides quick, granular visibility into your Active Directory environment so IT pros can proactively mitigate issues before they escalate into major problems for your organization.
ENow Active Directory Monitoring & Reporting first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plugins: Data Exfiltration via Images & Cross Plugin Request Forgery]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-webpilot-data-exfil-via-markdown-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-webpilot-data-exfil-via-markdown-injection/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T14:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post shows how a malicious website can take control of a ChatGPT chat session and exfiltrate the history of the conversation.
Plugins, Tools and Integrations With plugins, data exfiltration can happen by sending too much data into the plugin in the first place. More security controls and insights on what is being sent to the plugin are required to empower users.
However, this post is not about sending too much data to a plugin, but about a malicious actor who controls the data a plugin retrieves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Choose Exodus Intelligence for Enhanced Vulnerability Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2130</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/05/16/why-choose-exodus-intelligence-for-enhanced-vulnerability-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the contemporary digital landscape, vulnerability management teams and analysts are overwhelmed by countless alerts, data streams, and patch recommendations. The sheer volume of information is daunting and frequently misleading. Ideally, the systems generating these alerts should streamline and prioritize the information. While AI systems and products are not yet mature enough to effectively filter ... Read more Why Choose Exodus Intelligence for Enhanced Vulnerability Management? 
The post <strong>Why Choose Exodus Intelligence for Enhanced Vulnerability Management? </strong> appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real World Crypto 2023 Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104415</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/05/16/real-world-crypto-2023-recap/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T13:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, hundreds of cryptographers descended upon Tokyo for the first Real World Crypto Conference in Asia. As in previous years, we dispatched a handful of our researchers and engineers to present and attend the conference. What sets RWC apart from other conferences is that it strongly emphasizes research, collaborations, and advancements in cryptography that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Malshare: 10 Years of Running a Public Malware Repository]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=80742</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-malshare-10-years-of-running-a-public-malware-repository/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T13:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Silas Cutler, founder of MalShare, explores some of the challenges and rewards of developing and maintaining a free malware repository for researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s always DNS, here’s why…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26931</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/its-always-dns-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T05:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction There’s an old adage in network and Internet support: When something breaks in any network “it was DNS”. Sadly it’s usually true. …or at least it is when you […]
It’s always DNS, here’s why… first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Lodge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Docker with NAS and NFS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571663</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/using-docker-with-nas-and-nfs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To access remote storage from Docker containers, you must understand how Docker works with network-attached storage (NAS) and the Network File System (NFS) protocol. In this guide, I will explore the benefits of using Docker with NAS and NFS, and then I will explain how to set up an NFS share to access it from a Docker container. For demonstration, I will use TrueNAS with NFSv4.
Using Docker with NAS and NFS first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Windows Notification Facility’s (WNF) Code Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104354</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/05/15/introducing-windows-notification-facilitys-wnf-code-integrity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T11:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Yarden Shafir, Senior Security Engineer WNF (Windows Notification Facility) is an undocumented notification mechanism that allows communication inside processes, between processes, or between user mode processes and kernel drivers. Similar to other notification mechanisms like ETW (Event Tracing for Windows) and ALPC (Advanced Local Procedure Call), WNF communication happens over different “channels,” each representing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NETGEAR Routers: A Playground for Hackers?]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30224</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/15/netgear-routers-a-playground-for-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T09:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed analysis on multiple vulnerabilities which were identified on the NETGEAR Nighthawk WiFi 6 Router (RAX AX2400) and may exist on other NETGEAR router models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>McCaulay Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CS2BR pt. I – How we enabled Brute Ratel Badgers to run Cobalt Strike BOFs]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=13966</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/05/15/introducing-cs2br-pt-i-how-we-enabled-brute-ratel-badgers-to-run-cobalt-strike-bofs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you know all about CS, BRC4 and BOFs you might want to skip this introduction and get right into the problem statement. You can also jump right to the solution. Introduction When we conduct Red Team assessments at NVISO, we employ a wide variety of proprietary and open source tools. One central component in … Continue reading Introducing CS2BR pt. I – How we enabled Brute Ratel Badgers to run Cobalt Strike BOFs →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re celebrating our 10th anniversary!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=13950</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/05/15/were-celebrating-our-10th-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T06:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From 5 people to almost 220 people. From working from our founders’ apartment to five offices in four countries. From an unknown challenger to being a reference in multiple fields in cyber security.

As a company, NVISO has come a long way since 2013 and we want to take a moment to celebrate what we have accomplished together so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Tischer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indirect Prompt Injection via YouTube Transcripts]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-plugin-youtube-indirect-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-plugin-youtube-indirect-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-14T07:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As discussed previously the problem of Indirect Prompt Injections is increasing.
They start showing up in many places.
A new unique one that I ran across is YouTube transcripts. ChatGPT (via Plugins) can access YouTube transcripts. Which is pretty neat. However, as expected (and predicted by many researches) all these quickly built tools and integrations introduce Indirect Prompt Injection vulnerabilities.
Proof of Concept Here is how it looks with ChatGPT end to end with a demo example.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Da Li’L World of DLL Exports and Entry Points, Part 6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8510</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/12/da-lil-world-of-dll-exports-and-entry-points-part-6/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love looking at clusters of files, because it’s the easiest way to find patterns. In the last part of this series I focused on Nullsoft installers (DLLs!) only, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA's New Cybersecurity Requirements: Are You Prepared as a Medical Device Manufacturer?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/fdas-new-cybersecurity-requirements-are-you-prepared-medical-device-manufacturer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/fdas-new-cybersecurity-requirements-are-you-prepared-medical-device-manufacturer"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Kayla Underkoffler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matlab persistent lolbin – 2 years too late, but always…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8501</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/12/matlab-persistent-lolbin-2-years-too-late-but-always/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T21:35:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just realized I have never published a post about lolbinish/persistencish Matlab feature that I referred to in this twit. The Tl;dr; is that Matlab can load a DLL of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fork off: Three ways to deal with forking processes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/fork-off-three-ways-to-deal-with-forking-processes</id>
        <link href="https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/fork-off-three-ways-to-deal-with-forking-processes"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever tested a Linux application that forks into multiple processes? Isn’t it a pain? Whether you’re debugging, trying to see a process crash, or trying to write an exploit, it can be super duper annoying! In a few days, I’m giving a talk at NorthSec in Montreal. I asked some co-workers to review my slides, and they commented that I have some neat techniques to deal with forking, so I thought I’d share a couple! Spoiler alert: The last one is the best, so you can just skip to that. :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkullSecurity Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AWS Lambda functions with Docker containers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571636</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/using-aws-lambda-functions-with-docker-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2020 at the AWS annual learning conference, re:Invent, one of the big announcements concerned AWS Lambda container image support for Docker and the Open Container Initiative (OCI). AWS Lambda, as a service, has always been popular, with its simple process of uploading code and not having to worry about provisioning servers. However, you might be a company that is invested in container technology, and it is not so easy to utilize Lambda. With the support for Lambda functions with container images, you can now enjoy this functionality.
Using AWS Lambda functions with Docker containers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Beer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enforce Zero Trust in Microsoft 365 – Part 2: Protect against external users and applications]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=12383</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/05/12/enforce-zero-trust-in-microsoft-365-part-2-protect-against-external-users-and-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first blog post of this series, we have seen how strong authentication, i.e., Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA), could be enforced for users using a free Azure Active Directory subscription within the Microsoft 365 environment. In this blog post, we will continue to harden the configuration of our Azure AD tenant to enforce Zero Trust … Continue reading Enforce Zero Trust in Microsoft 365 – Part 2: Protect against external users and applications →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillaume Bossiroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adversarial Prompting: Tutorial and Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/adversarial-prompting-tutorial-and-lab/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/adversarial-prompting-tutorial-and-lab/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T05:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To learn more about Prompt Engineering and Prompt Injections I put together this tutorial + lab for myself. It is as a Jupyter Notebook to experiement and play around with this novel attack technique, learn and experiment.
The examples reach from simple prompt engineering scenarios, such as changing the output message to a specific text, to more complex adversarial prompt challenges such as JSON object injection, HTML injection/XSS, overwriting mail recipients or orders of an OrderBot and also data exfiltration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog - The 2023 SANS Spring Cyber Solutions Fest Is Right Around the Corner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-2023-sans-spring-cyber-solutions-fest-is-right-around-the-corner</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-2023-sans-spring-cyber-solutions-fest-is-right-around-the-corner?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring into the season with SANS and our expert speakers at our Cyber Solutions Fest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Cybersecurity Analyst/Engineer (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-analyst-engineer-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-analyst-engineer-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[サイバーセキュリティアナリスト/エンジニアの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PE Section names – re-visited, again, in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8499</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/11/pe-section-names-re-visited-again-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T23:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous posts I have listed many PE sections present in different types of binaries. Today I am looking at win11 PE sections and am happy to report that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Elf walks into the bar…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8497</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/11/an-elf-walks-into-the-bar/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T22:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11’s advapi32.dll includes interesting export functions: ElfBackupEventLogFileA ElfBackupEventLogFileW ElfChangeNotify ElfClearEventLogFileA ElfClearEventLogFileW ElfCloseEventLog ElfDeregisterEventSource ElfFlushEventLog ElfNumberOfRecords ElfOldestRecord ElfOpenBackupEventLogA ElfOpenBackupEventLogW ElfOpenEventLogA ElfOpenEventLogW ElfReadEventLogA ElfReadEventLogW ElfRegisterEventSourceA ElfRegisterEventSourceW ElfReportEventA ElfReportEventAndSourceW ElfReportEventW And I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing and restricting NTLM authentication using Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571591</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/auditing-and-restricting-ntlm-authentication-using-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T10:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NTLM is an insecure authentication protocol that is still found in many environments. Using Group Policy and effective logging, admins can audit the environment and restrict the use of NTLM across the domain.
Auditing and restricting NTLM authentication using Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hypervisor Ransomware | Multiple Threat Actor Groups Hop on Leaked Babuk Code to Build ESXi Lockers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=80513</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/hypervisor-ransomware-multiple-threat-actor-groups-hop-on-leaked-babuk-code-to-build-esxi-lockers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T09:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Availability of leaked Babuk source code is fuelling a proliferation of file lockers targeting VMware ESXi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Small Business Cyber Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-small-business-cyber-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-small-business-cyber-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Small Business Cyber Summit 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real World Cryptography Conference 2023 – Part I]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=29957</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/10/real-world-cryptography-conference-2023-part-i/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual Real World Cryptography Conference organized by the IACR recently took place in Tokyo, Japan. On top of 3 days of excellent talks, RWC was preceded by the 2nd annual FHE.org Conference and the Real World Post-Quantum Cryptography Workshop and followed by the High Assurance Crypto Software Workshop. Nearly all of NCC Group’s Cryptography […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Henry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Time Valid Bugs Smashed in April 2023!]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/first-time-valid-bugs-smashed-april-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/first-time-valid-bugs-smashed-april-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ScriptRunner Portal Edition R5—New Query configuration and Action configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571576</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/scriptrunner-portal-edition-r5new-query-configuration-and-action-configuration/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ScriptRunner provides a centralized management interface for PowerShell scripts, allowing users, even with little or no scripting experience, to automate IT tasks. The most recent release, ScriptRunner Portal Edition R5, introduces many new refinements to the platform, including the introduction of Query and Action configuration into the portal.
ScriptRunner Portal Edition R5—New Query configuration and Action configuration first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C2 and the Docker Dance: Mythic 3.0’s Marvelous Microservice Moves]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f6e6e91356e2</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/c2-and-the-docker-dance-mythic-3-0s-marvelous-microservice-moves-f6e6e91356e2?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T14:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Mythic 3.0 — Title by ChatGPT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cody Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Prompt Injections - An Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/prompt-injection-an-introduction-video/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/prompt-injection-an-introduction-video/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many prompt engineering classes and currently pretty much all examples are vulnerable to Prompt Injections. Especially Indirect Prompt Injections are dangerous as we discussed before.
Indirect Prompt Injections allow untrusted data to take control of the LLM (large language model) and give an AI a new instructions, mission and objective.
Bypassing Input Validation Attack payloads are natural language. This means there are lots of creative ways an adversary can inject malicious data that bypass input filters and web application firewalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Cybercrime Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-dark-web-threat-hunting-blockchain-forensics</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/for589-dark-web-threat-hunting-blockchain-forensics?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR589: Dark Web Threat Hunting & Blockchain Forensics course teaches students how to hunt for threat intelligence within the cybercriminal underground using Human Intelligence (HUMINT) elicitation techniques and blockchain analytics tools to trace criminal cryptocurrency transactions. Following the completion of the course, each student will be prepared to social engineer cybercriminals, produce dark web intelligence, provide unique intelligence support to incident response cases, extract cryptocurrency artifacts from mobile and computer devices, negotiate with ransomware operators on behalf of a client, support Law Enforcement partners with attribution efforts, and investigate Anti-Money Laundering (AML) cases involving cryptocurrency transactions on and off the Blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog - Stronger Together: Recapping RSA Conference 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/stronger-together-recapping-rsa-conference-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/stronger-together-recapping-rsa-conference-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute cements its position as a thought leader in cybersecurity at one of the biggest infosec gatherings of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prove Your Worth: How to Measure Cybersecurity ROI and Impress Your Board]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ceo/prove-your-worth-how-measure-cybersecurity-roi-and-impress-your-board</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ceo/prove-your-worth-how-measure-cybersecurity-roi-and-impress-your-board"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Mårten Mickos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move a VM from XenServer to Hyper-V with StarWind V2V Converter]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571562</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/move-a-vm-from-xenserver-to-hyper-v-with-starwind-v2v-converter/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T18:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide drives you through the procedure of moving a VM from XenServer to a Hyper-V running on Windows Server 2022 with the free tool StarWind V2V Converter. For a guest OS, we use Windows Server 2019.
Move a VM from XenServer to Hyper-V with StarWind V2V Converter first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The May 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:645944452591b76f779cb5ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/5/8/the-may-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T17:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s patch Tuesday once again, and Adobe and Microsoft have released their monthly batch of security updates. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of the latest offerings from Microsoft and Adobe. If you’d rather watch the video recap, you can check out the Patch Report webcast on our YouTube channel.
Adobe Patches for May 2023
For May, Adobe released a single bulletin for Substance 3D Painter addressing 11 Critical-rated and 3 Important-rated vulnerabilities. All of these bugs were found and reported by ZDI vulnerability researcher Mat Powell. The most severe of these issues would allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system if they can convince a user to open a specially-crafted file.
None of the bugs fixed by Ado…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackBackBetter Sponsorship: Learn What Younger Coders Think About Hackers and Tips for Secure Code Review]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hackbackbetter-sponsorship-learn-what-younger-coders-think-about-hackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/hackerone-community-blog/hackbackbetter-sponsorship-learn-what-younger-coders-think-about-hackers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T22:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install and configure Traefik on Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571536</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-and-configure-traefik-on-docker/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T18:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post, I introduced Traefik as a cloud-native way to implement a reverse proxy and load balancer for your containers. In this post, you will get a bit more hands-on, learning the ins and outs of installing and configuring Traefik as a reverse proxy in your Docker environment.
Install and configure Traefik on Docker first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SecureAuth’s Arculix Wins Next-Gen Passwordless Authentication and Identity & Access Management in the Global InfoSec Awards 2023 at RSA Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=48297</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/secureauths-arculix-wins-next-gen-passwordless-authentication-and-identity-access-management-in-the-global-infosec-awards-2023-at-rsa-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we wrapped up a stellar RSA Conference 2023 with non-stop visitors at our “MFA is so 80s” themed booth in the South Hall where we had the opportunity to showcase  Arculix, meet with customers, partners and attendees, and receive two coveted industry awards. SecureAuth is honored to have Arculix named a winner in two […]
The post SecureAuth’s Arculix Wins Next-Gen Passwordless Authentication and Identity & Access Management in the Global InfoSec Awards 2023 at RSA Conference appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jendres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what-is-threat-detection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-threat-detection</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-threat-detection?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Threat Detection? is a blog by Shaun McCullough, cloud security course author for SANS Institute]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malware – some musings about the meaning of the word…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8490</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/05/malware-some-musings-about-the-meaning-of-the-word/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T23:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have read Ali‘s question with a great interest, because it’s the questions like this that make you pause and think. In my reply I suggested that the context is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Proxmox cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571525</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-a-proxmox-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T13:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Proxmox cluster provides a centralized interface for managing your data center's processing, storage, networking, and other resources. Furthermore, it provides easier VM/container migration across nodes and high availability to ensure ongoing service in the event of cluster node failure. Cluster management in Proxmox VE is handled by the Proxmox VE cluster manager (pvecm).
Create a Proxmox cluster first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Business Continuity on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=13894</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/05/05/implementing-business-continuity-on-azure/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a general misconception among cloud consumers that the availability of their resources in the cloud is always guaranteed. This is not true since all cloud providers, including Microsoft, offer specific SLAs for their products that almost never reach an availability target of 100%. For the consumers who have deployed critical resources and applications … Continue reading Implementing Business Continuity on Azure →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elpida Rouka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bullied by Bugcrowd over Kape CyberGhost disclosure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27009</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/bullied-by-bugcrowd-over-kape-cyberghost-disclosure/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T05:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The CyberGhost VPN client suffers from an elevation of privilege vulnerability and is filed under CVE-2023-30237.  A specially crafted JSON payload sent to the CyberGhost RPC service can lead […]
Bullied by Bugcrowd over Kape CyberGhost disclosure first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vulnerability Assessment Framework: Stop Inefficient Patching Now and Transform Your Vulnerability Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-vulnerability-assessment-framework</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-vulnerability-assessment-framework?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerabilities don’t matter! Patching is terrible! Prove me wrong!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Incident Response Team Member (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-incident-response-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-incident-response-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[インシデント・レスポンス・チームメンバーの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Hunting – architecture issues…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8488</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/05/04/threat-hunting-architecture-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T23:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my recent post I focused on localization issues, but there is (always!) more… Take a look at the Windows 11 ARM version – when you install it you will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Password Day 2023: Why Not Celebrate A Passwordless Continuous Authentication Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=48289</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/world-password-day-2023-why-not-celebrate-a-passwordless-continuous-authentication-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T16:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today around the world people are remembering password hygiene to protect their digital identities and it is time we make it World Passwordless Day. Recently, the State of Authentication Report 2023, based on results from 285 IT and security professionals on the latest MFA and passwordless authentication trends, provides compelling data for security professionals and […]
The post World Password Day 2023: Why Not Celebrate A Passwordless Continuous Authentication Day appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting no network or internet in VMware Workstation]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571502</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/troubleshooting-no-network-or-internet-in-vmware-workstation/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T14:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a virtual machine (VM) in a VMware workstation cannot establish a connection to other VMs or the internet, then you should check the settings in the guest operating system, in the virtual network, and in the adapter configuration of the host OS. Both NAT and bridged networks can be affected by such problems.
Troubleshooting no network or internet in VMware Workstation first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kimsuky Evolves Reconnaissance Capabilities in New Global Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=80355</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/kimsuky-evolves-reconnaissance-capabilities-in-new-global-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T13:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DPRK-linked threat actor deploys previously unseen reconnaissance tool 'ReconShark' in wave of ongoing attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSA 2023: Top Trends - Beyond AI, Tools, and Products]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/events/rsa-2023-top-trends-beyond-ai-tools-and-products</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/events/rsa-2023-top-trends-beyond-ai-tools-and-products"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Chukkapali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Passwords for Your Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-about-passwords-for-your-organization</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-about-passwords-for-your-organization?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expert advice for shoring up your password best practices today on this World Password Day]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware: Every internet-connected network is at risk. Be prepared!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ransomware-every-internet-connected-network-is-at-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ransomware-every-internet-connected-network-is-at-risk?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As ransomware attacks increase in number and severity, even the most advanced security systems can be compromised. However, there is one thing that can help you fight back: train your team!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud-Powered DFIR: Harnessing the cloud to improve investigator efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-powered-dfir-harnessing-the-cloud-to-improve-investigator-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cloud-powered-dfir-harnessing-the-cloud-to-improve-investigator-efficiency?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we covered eight different use cases for leveraging cloud resources and services to improve the efficiency of incident response workflows. If you want to hear a deeper discussion regarding this topic, check out the following webcast: Cloud-Powered DFIR: Harnessing the cloud to improve investigator efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMMM-self-assessment-tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/vmmm-self-assessment-tool</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/vmmm-self-assessment-tool?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new vulnerability management maturity model self-assessment tool uses a series of questions to determine an organization's maturity level across all 12 areas of the VMMM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – AWS Nitro System API & Security Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=29988</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/05/03/public-report-aws-nitro-system-api-security-claims/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T23:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last calendar quarter of 2022, Amazon Web Services (AWS) engaged NCC Group to conduct an architecture review of the AWS Nitro System design, with focus on specific claims AWS made for the security of the Nitro System APIs. The public report for this review may be downloaded below:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Zero Touch Production Platforms and Safe Proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/05/04/testing-ztp-platforms-a-primer.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/05/04/testing-ztp-platforms-a-primer.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more companies develop in-house services and tools to moderate access to production environments, the importance of understanding and testing these Zero Touch Production (ZTP) platforms grows 1 2. This blog post aims to provide an overview of ZTP tools and services, explore their security role in DevSecOps, and outline common pitfalls to watch out for when testing them.
SRE? ZTP?    
Safe Proxies In Production
The safety & security roles of Safe Proxies
What does ZTP look like today
What to look for when auditing ZTP tools/services    
A. Web Attack Surface
B. Hooks
C. Safe Centralization
D. Insecure Default Templates
E. Logging
F. Rate-limiting
G. ACL Ownership
H. Command Safeguards
I. Traceability and Scoping
J. Scoped Access
K. Different Interfaces, Different Requirements
L. Service …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade Windows Server 2012 RDS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571490</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/upgrade-windows-server-2012-rds/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T18:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Windows Server 2012 and 2012 R2 reaching their end of life at the end of 2023, organizations must consider migrating their Remote Desktop Services (RDS) deployments from Windows Server 2012 to 2022. When doing so, you have to follow a distinct order to upgrade the RDS roles. By migrating the connection broker, you keep the configuration of the deployment.
Upgrade Windows Server 2012 RDS first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Impersonation through the Named Pipe Filesystem Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/15f324dfbaf2</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/exploring-impersonation-through-the-named-pipe-filesystem-driver-15f324dfbaf2?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix MH370: The plane that wasn’t hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=26928</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/netflix-mh370-the-plane-that-wasnt-hacked/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T05:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a sucker for a good documentary, but the recent Netflix MH370 piece had me shouting at the screen. The first episode talks about the most widely accepted theory; a pilot-created […]
Netflix MH370: The plane that wasn’t hacked first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Banana Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-banana-incident</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-banana-incident?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m in the digital forensics (DF) of the DFIR, the Incident Response (IR) group approach to this action would be very different. How may our actions differ? The (IR) group may be more concerned about when is the next pallet of bananas going to arrive or how does the store quell the panic when only standard bananas are available because of the organics being sold out? In the meantime, I’m standing only focused on this pallet, or maybe only the bananas I’m holding. My lifetime of eating and cyber training tells me that I am correct, but not limited to many steps in my investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse engineering tricks: identifying opaque network protocols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/reverse-engineering-tricks-identifying-opaque-network-protocols</id>
        <link href="https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/reverse-engineering-tricks-identifying-opaque-network-protocols"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T22:37:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I’ve been reverse engineering a reasonably complex network protocol, and I ran into a mystery - while the protocol is generally an unencrypted binary protocol, one of the messages was large and random. In an otherwise unencrypted protocol, why is one of the messages unreadable? It took me a few hours to accomplish what should have been a couple minutes of effort, and I wanted to share the trick I ultimately used! I’m going to be intentionally vague on the software, and even modify a few things to make it harder to identify; I’ll probably publish a lot more on my work blog once I’m finished this project!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkullSecurity Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-28231: RCE in the Microsoft Windows DHCPv6 Service]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64502625e391c8439cbee9f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/5/1/cve-2023-28231-rce-in-the-microsoft-windows-dhcpv6-service"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T16:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Guy Lederfein and Lucas Miller of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in the Microsoft Windows DHCPv6 Service. This bug was originally discovered by YanZiShuang@BigCJTeam of cyberkl. The vulnerability results from the improper processing of DHCPv6 Relay-forward messages. A network-adjacent attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the DHCP service. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2023-28231, with a few minimal modifications.
A heap-based buffer overflow has been reported in Microsoft DHCPv6 Server. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of DHCPv6 Relay-forward messages. A remote atta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable BitLocker on Windows 11 without a TPM chip]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571476</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-bitlocker-on-windows-11-without-a-tpm-chip/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T15:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, Windows 11 requires a Trusted Platform Module (TPM) chip to be present on the computer. However, it is possible to enable BitLocker on Windows 11 without TPM if you jump through a few hoops.
Enable BitLocker on Windows 11 without a TPM chip first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmin Kahriman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring People, Process, and Technology Effectiveness with NIST CSF 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4638</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/nist-csf-2-0-ppt/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T13:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) recently released the latest draft of the Cybersecurity Framework (CSF) 2.0, incorporating numerous updates and improvements over its predecessor. Among these changes, the addition of the Governance function has generated significant buzz within the cybersecurity community. We also are particularly excited about the modification of subcategories in […]
The post Measuring People, Process, and Technology Effectiveness with NIST CSF 2.0 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enforce Zero Trust in Microsoft 365 – Part 1: Setting the basics]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=10366</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/05/02/enforce-zero-trust-in-microsoft-365-part-1-setting-the-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This first blog post is part of a series of blog posts related to the implementation of Zero Trust approach in Microsoft 365. This series will first cover the basics and then deep dive into the different features such as Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) Conditional Access policies, Microsoft Defender for Cloud Apps policies, Information … Continue reading Enforce Zero Trust in Microsoft 365 – Part 1: Setting the basics →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillaume Bossiroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.75]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10070</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/05/02/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-75/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This update brings an new plugin: plugin_vba_dir.py (there are no changes to oledump). This plugin parses the records found in the vba/dir stream to display project, references and modules information oledump_V0_0_75.zip (http)MD5: FB0F82B3B29883707A399B99C894EF08SHA256: D357E48D827822D15C9C22C0B5204924FBA9FC59104818C9824AD149FE6F6249]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in April]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10068</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/05/01/overview-of-content-published-in-april-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T22:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in April: Blog posts: Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.74 Update: re-search.py Version 0.0.22 Update: 1768.py Version 0.0.18 Update: dnsresolver.py Version 0.0.3 New Tool: myjson-transform.py Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.25 SANS ISC Diary entries: YARA v4.3.0 Release Update: oledump & MSI Files Chrome’s Download Tab: Dangerous Files Another Malicious HTA […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolve-DnsName: nslookup for PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1571457</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/resolve-dnsname-nslookup-for-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T17:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[nslookup has established itself as a popular tool for troubleshooting DNS problems. It exists on multiple platforms, including Windows. However, there is an alternative, the PowerShell Resolve-DnsName cmdlet, which can also check proprietary Microsoft protocols for name resolution, such as NetBIOS or LLMNR.
Resolve-DnsName: nslookup for PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS ICS Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ics-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ics-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS ICS Security Summit 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, No Case Studies—But . . .]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e7cf012af19807518fba2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/sorry-no-case-study"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend of the site recently suggested that we create a current-issue case 
study using our updated risk discovery approach. “It’s a great idea,” we 
replied and immediately started kicking around ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pointillism of Daily Events]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2c8f009baa12346d3711f</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/pointillism-daily-events"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Baker’s book Human Smoke brilliantly illustrates a unique approach 
to historical narrative. It also underscores the need to remember that 
every artist paints with intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Ready for What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62e2aa91391dcb70804f9850</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/getting-ready-whats-next"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new age of giant monsters, advanced awareness of classical 
surprise—that one big tipping moment—no longer suffices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Your ‘Free Cells’ Mindfully]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62deb6110fd7f314e5696ae6</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/manage-free-cells"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accommodate but don’t fight the limitations you can’t control, recognize 
those you can influence and leverage, and don't imagine you have more free 
cells than you actually do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popski’s Planning]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d81b5affdc983dd1f616f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/popskis-planning"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British officer Vladimir Peniakoff’s approach to planning might sound a bit 
unorthodox at first, but it aligns nicely with Patton’s view of 
intelligence and speaks to an enduring need to understand front-line 
conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a New Game Board]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62d5b6db0343fb487527fc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/time-for-a-new-game-board"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need a more flexible game board where players can explore hypergame 
strategies—in other words, a game board where the strategist can play the 
hero for a change. We’ve built it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survivors Exceeded the Minimum]]></title>
        <id>6220e7e8d42c312741f476b0:6220e80dd42c312741f47d6a:62cf11283f1bdb1191fcdf9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.redteamjournal.com/blog/survivors-exceeded-minimum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T18:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every surprise is a cunning thunderbolt. Some surprises creep up 
slowly, rusting away former resilience until a simple nudge reveals the 
rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Team Journal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>