<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-11T00:34:07.610Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying Cobalt Strike’s “make_token” Command]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33420</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/11/10/demystifying-cobalt-strikes-make_token-command/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T14:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction If you are a pentester and enjoy tinkering with Windows, you have probably come across the following post by Raphael Mudge: Windows Access Tokens and Alternate Credentials In this post, he explains how the Windows program runas works and how the netonly flag allows the creation of processes where the local identity differs from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simone Salucci and Daniel Lopez Jimenez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nested Docker containers: Run Docker in a Docker container]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577343</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/nested-docker-containers-run-docker-in-a-docker-container/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T09:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with nested Docker containers has several use cases. In this article, I will discuss three methods to create a container inside a Docker container: Docker socket (Dood), dind tag, and Sysbox. You will learn about the advantages and disadvantages of each solution, and I will outline the downsides of nested containers.
Nested Docker containers: Run Docker in a Docker container first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To: Modifying EV Chargers for Benchtop Experiments]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:654bfd0d7f205443a6f1f1fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/11/8/how-to-modifying-ev-chargers-for-benchtop-experiments"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T20:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, we looked at the ChargePoint Home Flex EV charger – one of the targets in the upcoming Pwn2Own Automotive contest. In this post, we look at how to safely modify an EV charger to perform research through benchtop experiments. This isn’t meant to be a comprehensive guide, but it should provide you with a solid base to start your own research into these devices.
In some of our previous blogs, we’ve looked at the attack surface of devices included in the Pwn2Own Automotive competition. In this post, we provide some information on hardware modifications that can be made to most electric vehicle (EV) chargers to assist in benchtop experimentation. But first, a safety reminder: 
 EV Chargers contain high voltages, use extreme caution when working with them.  Never touch interior compo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Budget Planning: Preparing For U.S. Mandates to Implement Vulnerability Disclosure Policies (VDPs)]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/budgeting-for-vdps</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/budgeting-for-vdps"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. policymakers are increasingly encouraging and mandating public and private sector organizations to enhance their cybersecurity programs by adopting VDPs. Have you planned for a VDP in next year’s budget?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilona Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abusing Slack for Offensive Operations: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/19fef38cc967</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/abusing-slack-for-offensive-operations-part-2-19fef38cc967?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started diving into offensive Slack access, one of the best public resources I found was a blog post by Cody Thomas from back…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Creel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Loki and visualize logs with Grafana]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577306</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-loki-and-visualize-logs-with-grafana/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T13:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loki is an open-source log aggregation system developed by Grafana Labs and tailored for cloud-native and containerized apps. Loki is often used in conjunction with Grafana for log visualization. In this guide, I will explain how to install Loki and outline how you can integrate the log aggregation solution with Grafana.
Install Loki and visualize logs with Grafana first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) to Manage Human Risk: Part 5 – Generating Images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-5-generating-images</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-5-generating-images?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about using Generative AI quickly and cost effectively create customized images for your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Difference Between Pentesting and Bug Bounty?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/what-difference-between-pentesting-and-bug-bounty</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/what-difference-between-pentesting-and-bug-bounty"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T16:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do pentesting and bug bounties serve the same purpose or complement each other? Let’s explore the four different approaches to pentests and the key differences between bug bounty and pentesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naz Bozdemir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote connect to VirtualBox VMs via RDP (VRDP)]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577195</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/remote-connect-to-virtualbox-vms-via-rdp-vrdp/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T14:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clients can connect to VMs on a remote host via the VirtualBox Remote Display Protocol (VRDP) without the need to enable Remote Desktop (RDP) in the guest OS. This allows VirtualBox to be used to host virtual desktops that users can access from various clients.
Remote connect to VirtualBox VMs via RDP (VRDP) first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Release: Magisk Module –  Conscrypt Trust User Certs]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33157</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/11/08/tool-release-magisk-module-conscrypt-trust-user-certs/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T14:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Android 14 introduced a new feature which allows to remotely install CA certificates. This change implies that instead of using the /system/etc/security/cacerts directory to check the trusted CA’s, this new feature uses the com.android.conscrypt APEX module, and reads the certificates from the directory /apex/com.android.conscrypt/cacerts. Inspired by this blog post by Tim Perry, I decided to create a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Xavier Cervilla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Security Podcast Featuring Seth Art: Network Pentest 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-security-podcast-network-pentest-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-security-podcast-network-pentest-2-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about cloud security and cloud penetration testing in Part 2 of Seth Art's interview with Cloud Security Podcast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Art</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Cybersecurity: Bridging the Gap Between Imagination and Reality]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=15439</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/11/08/ai-in-cybersecurity-bridging-the-gap-between-imagination-and-reality/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In today’s digital environment, we encounter a mix of evolving cyber systems and the complexities they introduce. One notable influence in this space is artificial intelligence (AI), alongside associated technologies such as machine learning, which offer promising avenues for reshaping cyber strategies. Traditionally, cybersecurity has operated with definitive parameters, set boundaries, and post-event counteractions. … Continue reading AI in Cybersecurity: Bridging the Gap Between Imagination and Reality →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maurice Striek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cloud Security Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cloud-security-curriculum?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog outlining the SANS Cloud Security Curriculum offerings and resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Emerging Playbook for AI Red Teaming With HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/thought-leadership/ai-safety-red-teaming</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/thought-leadership/ai-safety-red-teaming"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne builds upon the foundation of bug bounty in our approach to AI Red Teaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predator AI | ChatGPT-Powered Infostealer Takes Aim at Cloud Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=86059</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/predator-ai-chatgpt-powered-infostealer-takes-aim-at-cloud-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T15:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An emerging infostealer being sold on Telegram looks to harness generative AI to streamline cyber attacks on cloud services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lateral Movement without Lateral Movement (Brought to you by ConfigMgr)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9b79b04634c7</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/lateral-movement-without-lateral-movement-brought-to-you-by-configmgr-9b79b04634c7?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego lomellini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing With Dynamite]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7d33d8fac038</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/phishing-with-dynamite-7d33d8fac038?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Token stealing is getting harder. Instead, stealing whole logged-in browser instances may be an easier and more generic approach. One…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merge branches on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577262</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/merge-branches-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merging branches in Git is a way to incorporate changes from one branch into another branch. In the previous article in this series, we looked at the basics of branching in Git and GitHub, as a means of achieving isolated lines of development for parallel work and feature separation. Once the code on a branch has been judged production-ready, it can be merged into the production-ready line.
Merge branches on GitHub first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post-exploiting a compromised etcd – Full control over the cluster and its nodes]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33246</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/11/07/post-exploiting-a-compromised-etcd-full-control-over-the-cluster-and-its-nodes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is essentially a framework of various services that make up its typical architecture, which can be divided into two roles: the control-plane, which serves as a central control hub and hosts most of the components, and the nodes or workers, where containers and their respective workloads are executed. Within the control plane we typically […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Toro Puig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating IDA Type Information Libraries from Windows Type Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=16511</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/11/07/generating-ida-type-information-libraries-from-windows-type-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this quick-post, we'll explore how to convert Windows type libraries (TLB) into IDA type information libraries (TIL).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Thiebaut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D0nut encrypt me, I have a wife and no backups]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33384</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/11/06/d0nut-encrypt-me-i-have-a-wife-and-no-backups/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T18:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Dark Side: A Deep Dive into Active Ransomware Families Author: Ross Inman (@rdi_x64) Introduction Our technical experts have written a blog series focused on Tactics, Techniques and Procedures (TTP’s) deployed by four ransomware families recently observed during NCC Group’s incident response engagements.   In case you missed it, last time we analysed an Incident […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Global Threat Intelligence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Domain of Thrones: Part II]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/45080d5dbfc8</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/domain-of-thrones-part-ii-45080d5dbfc8?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T16:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Adversaries Play for Keeps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Prager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arid Viper | APT’s Nest of SpyC23 Malware Continues to Target Android Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=85995</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/arid-viper-apts-nest-of-spyc23-malware-continues-to-target-android-devices/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T16:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamas-aligned threat actor delivers spyware through weaponized apps posing as Telegram or Skipped messenger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflecting on a Year with Fortra and Next Steps for Outflank]]></title>
        <id>https://outflank.nl/?p=3332</id>
        <link href="https://outflank.nl/blog/2023/11/06/reflecting-on-a-year-with-fortra-and-next-steps-for-outflank/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T15:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we debuted OST back in 2021, we wrote a blog detailing both the product features and the rationale for investing time into this toolset. In 2022, we joined forces with Fortra and we can hardly believe it’s been over a year already. It was a big decision to go from being a small team of red teamers to becoming part of a large company, but we’re very pleased with the switch. In this reflection on the past 12 months, we want to provide an update on our mission, detail our continued dedication to OST, discuss the process of growing the Outflank community, and touch on where we’re headed next.  
A Product Oriented Focus
One of our biggest challenges when we joined Fortra was the decision to put most of our energy into Outflank Security Tooling (OST).
Tags: cobalt strike, Development, Fortra, OST, red teaming
Read full post
The post Reflecting on a Year with Fortra and Next Steps for Outflank appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Smeets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding build provenance to Homebrew]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105252</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/11/06/adding-build-provenance-to-homebrew/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William Woodruff This is a joint post with Alpha-Omega—read their announcement post as well! We’re starting a new project in collaboration with Alpha-Omega and OpenSSF to improve the transparency and security of Homebrew. This six-month project will bring cryptographically verifiable build provenance to homebrew-core, allowing end users and companies to prove that Homebrew’s packages […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install a container on Proxmox]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577173</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-a-container-on-proxmox/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T11:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the open-source platform Proxmox, you can not only operate virtual machines but also easily deploy containers. The native format for this is Linux Containers (LXC), for which numerous templates are available. The setup and management are done via a web console, which also offers backup capabilities.
Install a container on Proxmox first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Joos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persistence – Windows Telemetry]]></title>
        <id>http://pentestlab.blog/?p=31444</id>
        <link href="https://pentestlab.blog/2023/11/06/persistence-windows-telemetry/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T07:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has introduced the compatibility telemetry in order to collect usage and performance data about Windows systems. The telemetry tasks are collected via the binary… 
Continue reading → Persistence – Windows Telemetry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Administrator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Generation FOR572: Advanced Network Forensics: Threat Hunting, Analysis, and Incident Response]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/next-generation-for572-advanced-network-forensics-threat-hunting-analysis-and-incident-response</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/next-generation-for572-advanced-network-forensics-threat-hunting-analysis-and-incident-response?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS has released a major update to FOR572, Advanced Network Forensics and Analysis: Threat Hunting, Analysis, and Incident Response.  This course release includes a massive overhaul to the enterprise-scale incident response scenario and dataset.  Nearly every hands-on lab is all-new or has been re-written with the new data set, representing the latest in investigative tools, techniques, and procedures as well as adversarial tradecraft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzer Development: The Soul of a New Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://h0mbre.github.io/New_Fuzzer_Project/</id>
        <link href="https://h0mbre.github.io/New_Fuzzer_Project/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-04T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction &amp;&amp; Credit to Gamozolabs For a long time I’ve wanted to develop a fuzzer on the blog during my weekends and freetime, but for one reason or another, I could never really conceptualize a project that would be not only worthwhile as an educational tool, but also offer some utility to the fuzzing community in general. Recently, for Linux Kernel exploitation reasons, I’ve been very interested in Nyx. Nyx is a KVM-based hypervisor fuzzer that you can use to snapshot fuzz traditionally hard to fuzz targets. A lot of the time (most of the time?), we want to fuzz things that don’t naturally lend themselves well to traditional fuzzing approaches. When faced with target complexity in fuzzing (leaving input generation and nuance aside for now), there have generally been two approaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Human Machine Interface</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email domains AD 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8829</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/11/03/email-domains-ad-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T23:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in a day (90s/2000s), if you wanted an email, there were lots of (free) email providers available. With a minimum of effort one could sign up to as many free email services available at that time as possible. No … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking Google Bard - From Prompt Injection to Data Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-bard-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-bard-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently Google Bard got some powerful updates, including Extensions. Extensions allow Bard to access YouTube, search for flights and hotels, and also to access a user’s personal documents and emails.
So, Bard can now access and analyze your Drive, Docs and Gmail!
This means that it analyzes untrusted data and will be susceptible to Indirect Prompt Injection.
I was able to quickly validate that Prompt Injection works by pointing Bard to some older YouTube videos I had put up and ask it to summarize, and I also tested with Google Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First handset with MTE on the market]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/11/first-handset-with-mte-on-market.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/11/first-handset-with-mte-on-market.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=DFQxm4rd7fRHgM9OTejWVT5Vho6BE7M80rHXEVKqXWcinf93kRmgH2T4xWS0JMLd96xlbbE5D7Gw2o7jubnkMA);.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-0>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-0}ol.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-4{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_d02lf6xv7lip-8>li:before{content:"-  "}ol.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-3{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-6{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_d02lf6xv7lip-7>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_6winxzvxkxle-2>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_6winxzvxkxle-4>li:before{content:"-  "}ol.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-5{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-0{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-2.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-2 0}.lst-kix_d02lf6xv7lip-6>li:before{content:"-  "}.lst-kix_mpwcgajc4xj4-6>li{…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 23H2: The most important new features for professional users]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577162</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-11-23h2-the-most-important-new-features-for-professional-users/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T10:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft delivers new features for Windows 11 on a regular basis through monthly updates. The just released 2023 update unlocks these innovations on managed devices. They include the integration of LAPS, support for Passkeys, Multi-App Kiosks, and Dev Drive, among others.
Windows 11 23H2: The most important new features for professional users first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Office Documents Poisoning in SHVE]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/11/03/Office-Document-Poisoning.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/11/03/Office-Document-Poisoning.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, folks! We’re back with an exciting update on Session Hijacking Visual Exploitation (SHVE) that introduces an insidious twist to traditional exploitation techniques using Office documents. We all know how Office documents laced with macros have been a longstanding entry point for infiltrating systems. SHVE now takes a step further by leveraging XSS vulnerabilities and the inherent trust users have in websites they regularly visit.
Our newest feature integrates the concept of Office document poisoning. Here’s how it works: SHVE allows you to upload templates for .docm, .pptm, and .xslm formats. Whenever a victim of SHVE goes to download one of these document types, the tool will automatically intercept and inject the malicious macros into the file before it is downloaded. What makes t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpatched Powerful SSRF in Exchange OWA – Getting Response Through Attachments]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6542bb24762c666c130249d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/11/1/unpatched-powerful-ssrf-in-exchange-owa-getting-response-through-attachments"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T16:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF). This vulnerability class triggers a wide range of emotions and reactions, ranging from complete ignorance to panic. Though it is included in the OWASP Top 10 list of web application security risks, at times vendors tend to downplay it and not treat it seriously.
As usual, the truth lies somewhere in between. What appears to be SSRF may sometimes in fact be intended functionality. Even so, an attacker may be able to abuse that functionality to improperly disclose sensitive information, either from the application containing the SSRF or from unrelated internal systems.
You may have noticed battles between researchers and vendors where an SSRF vulnerability was at the center of the disagreement. The fun part starts when a single vendor responds to different…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abusing Entra ID Misconfigurations to Bypass MFA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=31386</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/cloud-penetration-testing/abusing-entra-id-misconfigurations-to-bypass-mfa/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While conducting an Entra Penetration Test, we discovered a simple misconfiguration in Entra ID that allowed us to bypass MFA.
The post Abusing Entra ID Misconfigurations to Bypass MFA appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Rozendaal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Rose Has Its Thorn SFTP Gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5362</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/every-rose-has-its-thorn-sftp-gateway/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T13:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations.  The recent vulnerabilities in GoAnywhere and MoveIT inspired us to take a look at Thorn SFTP Gateway, which is a solution that provides managed access […]
The post Every Rose Has Its Thorn SFTP Gateway appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRDP: Linux RDP server with Active Directory integration]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577148</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/xrdp-linux-rdp-server-with-active-directory-integration/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T11:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRDP is an open-source implementation of Microsoft's Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) that allows you to enable RDP functionality on your Linux server. In this article, I will walk you through the installation process of XRDP on Linux, sketch out the necessary firewall settings, and explain how you can integrate XRDP with Active Directory.
XRDP: Linux RDP server with Active Directory integration first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evi Vanoost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) to Manage Human Risk: Part 4 – Advanced Prompt Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-4-advanced-prompt-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-4-advanced-prompt-engineering?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about advanced prompt engineering for generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Detection: Tactical to Functional]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d214f64c580b</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-detection-tactical-to-functional-d214f64c580b?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T16:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 10: The Case of the Implicit Process Create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Security Podcast Featuring Seth Art: Cloud Pentest of AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-security-podcast-cloud-pentest-of-aws</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-security-podcast-cloud-pentest-of-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hear insights from Seth Art on how AWS cloud penetration testing improves cloud security and why cloud configuration reviews are not always enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Art</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popping Blisters for research: An overview of past payloads and exploring recent developments]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33061</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/11/01/popping-blisters-for-research-an-overview-of-past-payloads-and-exploring-recent-developments/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Blister is a piece of malware that loads a payload embedded inside it. We provide an overview of payloads dropped by the Blister loader based on 137 unpacked samples from the past one and a half years and take a look at recent activity of Blister. The overview shows that since its support for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mick Koomen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying stateful applications with Kubernetes StatefulSets]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577128</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/deploying-stateful-applications-with-kubernetes-statefulsets/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T11:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post in this Kubernetes guide, I introduced you to Kubernetes init containers. In today's post, I will walk you through deploying StatefulSets, which are used for deploying stateful applications in Kubernetes. Stateful applications require a persistent state across reboots and upgrades. They are typically characterized by their need for a consistent identity and reliable, durable data management. Typical examples are databases, caching systems, or analytics applications.
Deploying stateful applications with Kubernetes StatefulSets first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Cyber Threats Defenders Should Pay Attention To.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/recent-cyber-threats-that-defenders-should-pay-attention-to</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/recent-cyber-threats-that-defenders-should-pay-attention-to?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Threat Analysis Rundown (STAR) livestream host Katie Nickels was joined by Will Thomas (aka BushidoToken), Cyber Threat Intelligence Researcher at Equinix, co-founder of Curated Intelligence, and co-author of the upcoming SANS course, FOR589 Cybercrime Intelligence. Leveraging Will’s perspective monitoring adversary chats and dark web forums, they discussed recent cyber threats that defenders should pay attention to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory: Insufficient Proxyman HelperTool XPC Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33121</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/10/31/technical-advisory-insufficient-proxyman-helpertool-xpc-validation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary The com.proxyman.NSProxy.HelperTool application (version 1.4.0), a privileged helper tool distributed with the Proxyman application (up to an including versions 4.10.1) for macOS 13 Ventura and earlier allows a local attacker to use earlier versions of the Proxyman application to maliciously change the System Proxy settings and redirect traffic to an attacker-controlled computer, facilitating MITM […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scottleitch53e8989cc3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Dark Side: A Deep Dive into Active Ransomware Families]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33237</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/10/31/unveiling-the-dark-side-a-deep-dive-into-active-ransomware-families/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not so lucky: BlackCat is back!  Authors: Alex Jessop @ThisIsFineChief , Molly Dewis  While the main trend in the cyber threat landscape in recent months has been MoveIt and Cl0p, NCC Groups’ Cyber Incident Response Team have also been handling multiple different ransomware groups over the same period.   In the ever-evolving cybersecurity landscape, one consistent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RIFT: Research and Intelligence Fusion Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Common Mistakes When Running a Bug Bounty Program]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/common-bug-bounty-program-mistakes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/common-bug-bounty-program-mistakes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do organizations experience challenges when running bug bounty programs?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma Whitford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Ways to Tweak radare2 for Faster and Easier macOS Malware Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=85695</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/11-ways-to-tweak-radare2-for-faster-and-easier-macos-malware-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T15:08:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying radare2 for macOS malware research, these tips and tricks will help to improve workflow and supercharge productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Stokes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift vs. Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577103</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/openshift-vs-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T13:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes and OpenShift are two popular container orchestration platforms. In this article, I will compare these tools and outline which solution is best for your organization.
OpenShift vs. Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA medical IoT cyber device compliance. FD&C 524b]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28212</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/fda-medical-iot-cyber-device-compliance-fdc-524b/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T06:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR FD&C 524b is new FDA legislation for medical cyber device compliance Introduced on March 30th 2023 it is now a firm requirement as of October 1st 2023 It demands […]
FDA medical IoT cyber device compliance. FD&C 524b first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Leonard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FujiFilm printer credentials encryption issue fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=28239</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/fujifilm-printer-credentials-encryption-issue-fixed/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T06:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Many multi-function printers made by FujiFilm Business Innovation Corporation (Fujifilm) which includes Apeos, ApeosPro, PrimeLink and RevoriaPress brands as well as Xerox Corporation (Xerox) which includes VersaLink, PrimeLink, and […]
FujiFilm printer credentials encryption issue fixed first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Thakrar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce Teams Up With All-Star Hackers at H1-4420]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/lhe/salesforce-h1-4420</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/lhe/salesforce-h1-4420"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T19:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce and HackerOne joined 45 of the world’s best ethical hackers in London for a live hacking event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lateral Movement: Abuse the Power of DCOM Excel Application]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3c016d0d9922</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/lateral-movement-abuse-the-power-of-dcom-excel-application-3c016d0d9922?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T18:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we will talk about an interesting lateral movement technique called ActivateMicrosoftApp() method within the distributed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raj Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renew Windows root CA certificate]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577088</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/renew-windows-root-ca-certificate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T13:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A certification authority (CA) cannot issue certificates with a longer validity period than its own CA certificate. Therefore, it is crucial to renew the CA certificate in a timely manner. You can use this opportunity to set some parameters for the new certificate. You can perform this task using certsrv.msc and certutil.exe.
Renew Windows root CA certificate first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The issue with ATS in Apple’s macOS and iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105226</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/10/30/the-issue-with-ats-in-apples-macos-and-ios/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T12:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Will Brattain Trail of Bits is publicly disclosing a vulnerability (CVE-2023-38596) that affects iOS, iPadOS, and tvOS before version 17, macOS before version 14, and watchOS before version 10. The flaw resides in Apple’s App Transport Security (ATS) protocol handling. We discovered that Apple’s ATS fails to require the encryption of connections to IP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cyber Security? Protecting Our Digital Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cyber-security-protecting-our-digital-tomorrow</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-cyber-security-protecting-our-digital-tomorrow?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide explores the nuances of cyber security, shedding light on its importance without the tech jargon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond the good ol’ .bashrc entry… Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8809</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/10/28/beyond-the-good-ol-bashrc-entry-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T21:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update After I posted it, @netspooky pinged me with some additional info. Apparently, this technique is known since at least 2019 and was demoed by @zer0pwn first. This blog post from MCG describes various offensive techniques focused on .desktop and … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond the good ol’ .bashrc entry… Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8757</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/10/27/beyond-the-good-ol-bashrc-entry-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, okay, yup, it is a series now. Part two is here! Browsing available Ubuntu apps one can find a lot of interesting software. One of them is kchmviewer. Its purpose is to view CHM files – outdated, but still … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an Exploit for FortiGate Vulnerability CVE-2023-27997]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/building-exploit-fortigate-vulnerability-cve-2023-27997</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/building-exploit-fortigate-vulnerability-cve-2023-27997"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Bishop Fox built a POC exploit for the pre-authentication remote code injection vulnerability in the Fortinet SSL VPN published by Lexfo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Toronto 2023 - Day Four Results]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:653bbb6b3020ec49d9c1da62</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/10/27/pwn2own-toronto-2023-day-four-results"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T13:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The contest has wrapped, and we awarded $1,038,500 during the event for 58 unique 0-days. These bugs have been disclosed to the vendors, who now have 90 days to produce a patch. Congratulations to Team Viettel for winning Master of Pwn with $180,000 and 30 points. Our thanks goes out to the contestants and vendors for participating, and special thanks to Google and Synology for co-sponsoring the contest.
Welcome to the final day of Pwn2Own Toronto 2023! We’ll be updating this blog in real time as results become available. All times are Eastern (GMT -4:00).
FAILURE - Foundry Zero was unable to get their exploit of the Lexmark CX331adwe working within the time allotted.
BUG COLLISION - ANHTUD was able to execute a 2-bug chain of stack-based buffer overflows against the TP-Link Omada Gigabit Router and the Canon imageCLASS MF753Cdw for the SOHO Smashup. However, one of the bugs he used was previously known. He still earns $31,250 and 6.25 Master of Pwn points.
BUG COLLISION - Interrupt Labs was able to execute a 2-bug chain including a UAF and integer underflow against the Sonos Era 100. However, one of the bugs they used was previously known. They still earn $18,750 and 3.75 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Team Viettel was able to execute a heap-based buffer overflow and a stack-based buffer overflow against the TP-Link Omada Gigabit Router and the Canon imageCLASS MF753Cdw for the SOHO Smashup. They earn $50,000 and 10 Master of Pwn points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker networking: Connect a Docker container]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577039</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/docker-networking-connect-a-docker-container/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T11:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker, a cornerstone of the containerization world, offers powerful tools to connect Docker containers seamlessly across various environments. By diving into its rich set of network types—such as bridge, overlay, and macvlan—users can tailor their container communications to fit specific needs. This article will guide you through the foundational steps needed to create, manage, and remove Docker networks, ensuring that you have the knowledge to design optimal networking solutions for your containerized applications.
Docker networking: Connect a Docker container first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[whats-new-sec510]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/whats-new-sec510</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/whats-new-sec510?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC510 provides cloud security training on cloud agnostic security and defense in a public, multicloud environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-4632: Local Privilege Escalation in Lenovo System Updater]]></title>
        <id>http://enigma0x3.net/?p=939</id>
        <link href="https://enigma0x3.net/2023/10/26/cve-2023-4632-local-privilege-escalation-in-lenovo-system-updater/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T16:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version: Lenovo Updater Version <= 5.08.01.0009 Operating System Tested On: Windows 10 22H2 (x64) Vulnerability: Lenovo System Updater Local Privilege Escalation via Arbitrary File Write Advisory: https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/LEN-135367 Vulnerability Overview The Lenovo System Update application is designed to allow non-administrators to check for and apply updates to their workstation. During the process of checking for updates, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>enigma0x3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023–4632: Local Privilege Escalation in Lenovo System Updater]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2762e9667120</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/cve-2023-4632-local-privilege-escalation-in-lenovo-system-updater-2762e9667120?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T16:52:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version: Lenovo Updater Version <= 5.08.01.0009
Operating System Tested On: Windows 10 22H2 (x64)
Vulnerability: Lenovo System Updater…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Toronto 2023 - Day Three Results]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:653a669071444244e5843e7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/10/26/pwn2own-toronto-2023-day-three-results"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T13:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Day 3 of Pwn2Own Toronto 2023! We’ll be updating this blog in real time as results become available. We have a full schedule of attempts today, so stay tuned! All times are Eastern (GMT -4:00).
FAILURE - The DEVCORE Intern was unable to get their exploit of the Canon imageCLASS MF753Cdw working within the time allotted.
BUG COLLISION - Interrupt Labs was able to execute an RCE attack against the Synology BC500. However, the exploit they used was previously known. They still earn $3,750 and 0.75 Master of Pwn points.
FAILURE - Team Orca of Sea Security was unable to get their exploit of the Xiamoi 13 Pro working within the time allotted.
WITHDRAWAL - ToChim withdrew their attempt to target the Xiaomi 13 Pro.
BUG COLLISION - Claroty was able to execute a 4-bug chain against the TP…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install and enable IIS Manager for Remote Administration]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1577009</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-and-enable-iis-manager-for-remote-administration/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will help you get started with IIS remote management, so you no longer need to RDP into each server. If the target IIS server runs a GUI-less OS (e.g., Server Core), the IIS Manager for Remote Administration is the tool of choice.
Install and enable IIS Manager for Remote Administration first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CS2BR pt. III – Knees deep in Binary]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=14209</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/10/26/introducing-cs2br-pt-iii-knees-deep-in-binary/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Over the span of the previous two blog posts in the series, I showed why the majority of Cobalt Strike (CS) BOFs are incompatible with Brute Ratel C4 (BRC4) and what you can do about it. I also presented CS2BR itself: it’s a tool that makes patching BOFs to be compatible with BRC4 a … Continue reading Introducing CS2BR pt. III – Knees deep in Binary →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most common Active Directory misconfigurations and default settings that put your organization at risk]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=16151</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/10/26/most-common-active-directory-misconfigurations-and-default-settings-that-put-your-organization-at-risk/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In this blog post, we will go over the most recurring (and critical) findings that we discovered when auditing the Active Directory environment of different companies, explain why these configurations can be dangerous, how they can be abused by attackers and how they can be mitigated or remediated. First, let’s start with a small … Continue reading Most common Active Directory misconfigurations and default settings that put your organization at risk →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bastien Bossiroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory: F5 BIG-IP Unauthenticated RCE Vulnerability, CVE-2023-46747]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5319</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/advisory-f5-big-ip-rce/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T03:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Recently, we discovered a vulnerability which can lead to unauthenticated remote code execution on F5 BIG-IP instances with the Traffic Management User Interface exposed. This […]
The post Technical Advisory: F5 BIG-IP Unauthenticated RCE Vulnerability, CVE-2023-46747 appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) to Manage Human Risk: Part 3 – Issues and Limitations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-3-issues-and-limitations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-artificial-intelligence-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-3-issues-and-limitations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about leveraging AI safely by understanding its limitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunting for Windows API prototypes and descriptions…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8802</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/10/25/hunting-for-windows-api-prototypes-and-descriptions/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T23:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years I have made a lot of attempts to systematically extract Windows API information from various sources, but primarily, of course, from Microsoft help documentation available at different times, in different forms and file formats. If you need … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/thought-leadership/responsible-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/thought-leadership/responsible-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At HackerOne, we are combining human intelligence with artificial intelligence at scale to improve the efficiency of people and unlock entirely new capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jobert Abma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find weak, compromised, and reused passwords with Enzoic for Active Directory Lite]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576963</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/find-weak-compromised-and-reused-passwords-with-enzoic-for-active-directory-lite/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the #1 cause of a data breach for multiple years in a row now, weak or previously compromised passwords serve as a common entry point for hackers. Additional security gaps arise when multiple users use the same or even no password. Therefore, admins should regularly check Active Directory accounts for such weaknesses. We’ll dive into the tools Microsoft offers for password policies, understand their limitations, and uncover how Enzoic for Active Directory Lite's features make account protection both simpler and stronger.
Find weak, compromised, and reused passwords with Enzoic for Active Directory Lite first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Toronto 2023 - Day Two Results]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:65317cc1aa646b79baebb984</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/10/25/pwn2own-toronto-2023-day-two-results"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Day 2 of Pwn2Own Toronto 2023! We’ll be updating this blog in real time as results become available. We have a full schedule of attempts today, so stay tuned! All times are Eastern (GMT -4:00).
SUCCESS - Team Viettel was able to execute an OOB write against the Sonos Era 100. They earn $30,000 and 6 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Chris Anastasio was able to exploit a bug in the TP-Link Omada Gigabit Router and another in the Lexmark CX331adwe. He earns $100,000 and 10 Master of Pwn points.
BUG COLLISION - Bugscale was able to execute their stack-based buffer overflow attack against the Synology BC500. However, the exploit they used was previously known. They still earn $3,750 and 0.75 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - A DEVCORE Intern was able to execute a stack overflow attack a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Regulations and Risk Assessment Requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-regulations-risk-assessment-requirements</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-regulations-risk-assessment-requirements?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog from James Tarala is valuable for your cybersecurity toolkit to help you and your organization achieve the risk management requirements defined by many of the recent cybersecurity standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevate CVE Remediation with EPSS, Now Integrated in HackerOne Hacktivity]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/hacktivity-epss-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/hacktivity-epss-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne has integrated EPSS scoring into Hacktivity for more comprehensive CVE remediation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Domain of Thrones: Part I]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c183ee4bf379</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/domain-of-thrones-part-i-c183ee4bf379?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Adversaries Play for Keeps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nico Shyne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Toronto 2023 - Day One Results]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:65317ab7bb56fc5129b2d967</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/10/24/pwn2own-toronto-2023-day-one-results"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T13:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Pwn2Own Toronto 2023! We’ll be updating this blog in real time as results become available. We have a full schedule of attempts today, so stay tuned! All times are Eastern (GMT -4:00).
FAILURE - Peter Geissler was unable to get his exploit of the Canon imageCLASS MF753Cdw working within the time allotted.
SUCCESS - Binary Factory was able to execute their stack-based buffer overlow attack against the Synology BC500. They earn $30,000 and 3 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Pentest Limited was able to execute their 2-bug chain against the My Cloud Pro Series PR4100 using a DoS and SSRF. They earn $40,000 and 4 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Team Viettel was able to execute a single-bug attack against the Xiaomi 13 Pro. They earn $40,000 and 4 Master of Pwn points.
SUCCESS - Nguyen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos: Unleashing the Power of Perimeter Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cosmos-unleashing-power-perimeter-protection</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cosmos-unleashing-power-perimeter-protection"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, get a preview of the Cosmos: Protecting the Perimeter report and learn how continuous attack surface management protects digital perimeters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Israel-Hamas War | Cyber Domain State-Sponsored Activity of Interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=85538</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/the-israel-hamas-war-cyber-domain-state-sponsored-activity-of-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber warfare occurring amidst the Israel-Hamas war underscores the importance of keeping tabs on rising APTs and opportunistic hacktivists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyper-V VM does not boot from ISO]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576943</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/hyper-v-vm-does-not-boot-from-iso/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T09:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you want to boot a Hyper-V Gen2 virtual machine from an ISO file, it sometimes stubbornly tries to start from another drive, even if the virtual DVD drive is at the top of the boot order. Several reasons could be causing this issue.
Hyper-V VM does not boot from ISO first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cybersecurity-leadership-curriculum</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-cybersecurity-leadership-curriculum?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Leadership Curriculum provides chief information security officer training, as well as for other directors and leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own Toronto 2023 - The Full Schedule]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:65317a7a11e65b7d379ad514</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/10/23/pwn2own-toronto-2023-the-schedule"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T23:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Pwn2Own Toronto for 2023! Last year’s event was our largest ever, and this year’s contest looks to be just as exciting. Despite last-minute patches from many vendors, we have plenty of attempts across multiple categories - with plenty of attempts in the new Surveillance category as well. We have more than $1,000,000 in cash and prizes available for contestants. We came close last year to exceeding the million-dollar mark, and we are fans of setting records. As always, we began our contest with a random drawing to determine the order of attempts. If you missed it, you can watch the replay here. 
The complete schedule for the contest is below (all times Eastern [GMT -4:00]). 
Note: All times subject to change
Tuesday, October 24 – 0930
Peter Geissler targeting the Canon imageCLASS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Numbers turned weapons: DoS in Osmosis’ math library]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=105199</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/10/23/numbers-turned-weapons-dos-in-osmosis-math-library/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Sam Alws Trail of Bits is publicly disclosing a vulnerability in the Osmosis chain that allows an attacker to craft a transaction that takes up a disproportionate amount of compute time on Osmosis nodes compared to the amount of gas it consumes. Using the vulnerability, an attacker can halt the Osmosis chain by spamming […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git reset vs. git revert]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576932</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/git-reset-vs-git-revert/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T12:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git provides two critical undo commands—git reset and revert—which may initially seem confusing, but understanding their operation is essential to creating reliable project histories. In this blog, we aim to demystify git reset and revert with examples so that you can confidently implement Git in your workflows.
Git reset vs. git revert first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Zcash FROST Security Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=33055</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/10/23/public-report-zcash-frost-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T12:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Summer 2023, the Zcash Foundation engaged NCC Group to conduct a securityassessment of the Foundation’s FROST threshold signature implementation, based on thepaper FROST: Flexible Round-Optimized Schnorr Threshold Signatures. This projectimplements v12 of the draft FROST specification in Rust, with a variety of options availablefor underlying elliptic curve groups. The review was performed by three […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Bottinelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semgrep Rules for Android Application Security]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mindedsecurity.com/2023/10/semgrep-rules-for-android-application.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mindedsecurity.com/2023/10/semgrep-rules-for-android-application.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T07:32:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


  
The number of Android applications has been growing rapidly in recent years. In 2022, there were over 3.55 million Android apps available in the Google Play Store, and this number is expected to continue to grow in the years to come. The expansion of the Android app market is being driven by a number of factors, including the increasing popularity of smartphones, the growing demand for mobile apps, and the ease of developing and publishing Android apps. At the same time, the number of Android app
 downloads is also growing rapidly. In 2022, there were over 255 billion Android app downloads worldwide.

For this reason, introducing automatic security controls during Mobile Application Penetration Testing (MAPT) activity and the CI phase is necessary to ensure the security o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IMQ Minded Security Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Chrome extension IDs to their names, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8794</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/10/20/mapping-chrome-extension-ids-to-their-names-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 2 years ago I published the first part, so it’s time for a quick update. And this time I am publishing the file as well – note that it cannot be used for commercial purposes, but hope you will … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Detection: Tactical to Functional]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f37c9b0b8874</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/on-detection-tactical-to-functional-f37c9b0b8874?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T18:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 9: Perception vs. Conception]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloodhound Enterprise: securing Active Directory using graph theory]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1d0730e4c741</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/bloodhound-enterprise-securing-active-directory-using-graph-theory-1d0730e4c741?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T16:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prior to my employment at SpecterOps, I hadn’t worked in the information security industry- as a result, many security related terms and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Ajmal Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Git branch example]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576898</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/a-git-branch-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T14:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first post of this beginner's guide to Git and GitHub, you learned how to create a repository. Today, I will introduce you to Git branches. Git branches are independent lines of development within a repository, allowing for parallel work and feature separation. This beginner's guide will walk you through a Git branch example.
A Git branch example first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Recent Confluence Vulnerability (CVE-2023-22515) and Digging into Atlassian Bamboo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5294</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/recent-confluence-vulnerability-cve-2023-22515-and-atlassian-bamboo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T13:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Recently, Rapid7 disclosed a vulnerability within Confluence that allowed a remote unauthenticated attacker to create a new administrative user account by bypassing the XWork SafeParameterFilter functionality. Our vulnerability research team decided to take a look at another Atlassian product, Atlassian Bamboo, to determine if a similar vulnerability existed within that application. In this post, […]
The post Understanding the Recent Confluence Vulnerability (CVE-2023-22515) and Digging into Atlassian Bamboo appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes init containers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576866</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-init-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T02:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post in this Kubernetes guide, you learned how to use commands and arguments in a Kubernetes Pod. This post will teach you about Kubernetes init containers. A Kubernetes init container is a special type of container that runs before the main application container in a Pod. The init containers can be used to perform tasks such as setting up the environment, pulling code or a binary from a repository, downloading dependencies, or running scripts that are not part of the container image. You can use an init container to wait for other services, such as a database, to come up before the main app container starts. Essentially, init containers are used to get things ready for your app containers.
Kubernetes init containers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) to Manage Human Risk: Part 2 – Generative AI Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-2-generative-ai-basics</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/leveraging-ai-to-manage-human-risk-part-2-generative-ai-basics?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This second blog in the ongoing series gives and overview of Generative AI and prompt engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kicking Off the Final Round of the 2023 Ambassador World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/lhe/awc-final-round-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/lhe/awc-final-round-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T16:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final round of the 2023 Ambassador World Cup is here!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Listing remote named pipes]]></title>
        <id>https://outflank.nl/?p=3202</id>
        <link href="https://outflank.nl/blog/2023/10/19/listing-remote-named-pipes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T15:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Windows, named pipes are a form of interprocess communication (IPC) that allows processes to communicate with one another, both locally and across the network. Named pipes serve as a mechanism to transfer data between Windows components as well as third-party applications and services. Both locally as well as on a domain. From an offensive perspective, named pipes may leak some information that could be useful for reconnaissance purposes. Since named pipes can also be used (depending on configuration) to access services remotely – they could allow remote exploits (MS08-067).
In this post we will explore how named pipes can be listed remotely in offensive operations, for example via an implant running on a compromised Windows system.
Read more: Listing remote named pipes
Several tools already exist to list named pipes.

Read full post
The post Listing remote named pipes appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Van Bockhaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Multiple Vulnerabilities in Connectize G6 AC2100 Dual Band Gigabit WiFi Router (CVE-2023-24046, CVE-2023-24047, CVE-2023-24048, CVE-2023-24049, CVE-2023-24050, CVE-2023-24051, CVE-2023-24052)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31379</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/10/19/technical-advisory-multiple-vulnerabilities-in-connectize-g6-ac2100-dual-band-gigabit-wifi-router-cve-2023-24046-cve-2023-24047-cve-2023-24048-cve-2023-24049-cve-2023-24050-cve-2023-24051-cve/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T13:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connectize’s G6 WiFi router was found to have multiple vulnerabilities exposing its owners to potential intrusion in their local Wi-Fi network and browser. The Connectize G6 router is a general consumer Wi-Fi router with an integrated web admin interface for configuration, and is available for purchase by the general public. These vulnerabilities were discovered in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Houppermans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Vertex AI - Data Exfiltration Vulnerability Fixed in Generative AI Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-gcp-generative-ai-studio-data-exfiltration-fixed/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-gcp-generative-ai-studio-data-exfiltration-fixed/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T13:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Model (LLM) applications and chatbots are quite commonly vulnerable to data exfiltration. In particular data exfiltration via Image Markdown Injection is frequent.
This post describes how Google Cloud’s Vertex AI - Generative AI Studio had this vulnerability that I responsibly disclosed and Google fixed.
A big shout out to the Google Security team upfront, it took 22 minutes from report submission to receiving a confirmation from Google that this is a security issue that will be fixed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A First Look at Python in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=31266</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/red-team-operations/a-first-look-at-python-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you leverage Python in Excel for Red Team Operations? James Williams present a quick overview the new functionality and how it may be used.
The post A First Look at Python in Excel appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get and set IP address with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576838</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/get-and-set-ip-address-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T03:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting the IP address, subnet mask, default gateway, and DNS of your network card is one of the most basic tasks you're expected to do as an administrator. This guide will teach you how to use PowerShell to get and set the IP address.
Get and set IP address with PowerShell first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emanuel Halapciuc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Caliptra Security Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=32965</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/10/18/public-report-caliptra-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T18:26:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During August and September of 2023, Microsoft engaged NCC Group to conduct a security assessment of Caliptra v0.9. Caliptra is an open-source silicon IP block for datacenter-focused server-class ASICs. It serves as the internal root-of-trust for both measurement and identity of a system-on-chip. The main use cases for Caliptra are to assure integrity of mutable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Boone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-38600: Story of an innocent Apple Safari copyWithin gone (way) outside]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:652ef89b672df54ad5a5894b</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/10/17/cve-2023-38600-story-of-an-innocent-apple-safari-copywithin-gone-way-outside"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May 2023, we received a vulnerability report from an anonymous researcher regarding a vulnerability in Apple Safari. It turned out to be an interesting classic integer underflow vulnerability. Apple assigned CVE-2023-38600 to this issue and fixed it in the following security advisories:
— iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6 
— macOS Ventura 13.5 
— tvOS 16.6
— Safari 16.6 
— watchOS 9.6 
 Now that this vulnerability has been addressed by the vendor, we are ready to share additional details with the community.
Proof of Concept
Here is the minimal proof-of-concept code for this bug:
Let’s break it down quickly:  
     1 -    A new ArrayBuffer object of size 0x1000 is created. Note that it is resizable as it specifies maxByteLength.
     2 -    The ArrayBuffer object created at step 1 is used to crea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hossein Lotfi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncovering RPC Servers through Windows API Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5d23c0459db6</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/uncovering-rpc-servers-through-windows-api-analysis-5d23c0459db6?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Kai Huang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory: Vulnerabilities Identified within ListServ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=5259</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/vulnerabilities-within-listserv/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T13:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Our ultimate goal when performing our research is to identify unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerabilities which could be reliably exploited across a wide variety of […]
The post Technical Advisory: Vulnerabilities Identified within ListServ appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The single-packet attack: making remote race-conditions 'local']]></title>
        <id>the-single-packet-attack-making-remote-race-conditions-local</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/the-single-packet-attack-making-remote-race-conditions-local"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T12:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The single-packet attack is a new technique for triggering web race conditions. It works by completing multiple HTTP/2 requests with a single TCP packet, which effectively eliminates network jitter an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Champagne to drink?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8782</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/10/17/what-champagne-to-drink/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T22:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reading articles about criminals enjoying (I really hope they are not just flexing) drinking the emperor of all Champagnes aka Dom Pérignon, makes me feel that they are potentially missing out on so many opportunities! Not only Dom Pérignon is … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use commands and arguments in a Kubernetes Pod]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576815</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/use-commands-and-arguments-in-a-kubernetes-pod/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post in this Kubernetes guide, you learned about the HorizontalPodAutoscaler for automatic Pod scaling based on real-time usage. In this post, you will learn how to use commands and arguments in a Kubernetes Pod. Command and arguments help you specify the default command (or executable) and the parameters that are passed to it when a container runs in a Kubernetes Pod.
Use commands and arguments in a Kubernetes Pod first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use commands and arguments in a Kubernetes Pod]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576815</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/use-commands-and-arguments-in-a-kubernetes-pod/17/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post in this Kubernetes guide, you learned about the HorizontalPodAutoscaler for automatic Pod scaling based on real-time usage. In this post, you will learn how to use commands and arguments in a Kubernetes Pod. Command and arguments help you specify the default command (or executable) and the parameters that are passed to it when a container runs in a Kubernetes Pod.
Use commands and arguments in a Kubernetes Pod first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is phasing out NTLM, filling the gaps with new Kerberos features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576793</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-is-phasing-out-ntlm-filling-the-gaps-with-new-kerberos-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T13:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has unveiled its roadmap for authentication in Windows 11. According to this, NTLM will be disabled by default in the foreseeable future. However, NTLM currently serves as a fallback for several scenarios that Kerberos cannot cover yet. IAKerb and a local KDC are intended to fill this gap.
Microsoft is phasing out NTLM, filling the gaps with new Kerberos features first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is phasing out NTLM, filling the gaps with new Kerberos features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1576793</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-is-phasing-out-ntlm-filling-the-gaps-with-new-kerberos-features/16/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T13:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has unveiled its roadmap for authentication in Windows 11. According to this, NTLM will be disabled by default in the foreseeable future. However, NTLM currently serves as a fallback for several scenarios that Kerberos cannot cover yet. IAKerb and a local KDC are intended to fill this gap.
Microsoft is phasing out NTLM, filling the gaps with new Kerberos features first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS CloudSecNext Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-cloudsecnext-summit-2023?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS CloudSecNext Summit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dexray v2.33]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8779</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/10/13/dexray-v2-33/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T22:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even in 2023 Dexray seems to be delivering value to DFIR practitioners. I am always very humbled by unsolicited additions to Dexray code, because it means the tool is still alive, despite the fact it was written in archaic (by … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Grown Red Team: LNK Phishing In 2023 Revisited…Again]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2b8c885b9836</id>
        <link href="https://assume-breach.medium.com/home-grown-red-team-lnk-phishing-in-2023-revisited-again-2b8c885b9836?source=rss-fe83402397b0------2"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T20:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back. So, it’s been about a week since I published my post on LNK phishing. A few days after publishing, I was testing some other…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>assume-breach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of an in-the-wild iOS Safari WebContent to GPU Process exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/10/an-analysis-of-an-in-the-wild-ios-safari-sandbox-escape.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2023/10/an-analysis-of-an-in-the-wild-ios-safari-sandbox-escape.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T10:47:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw);.lst-kix_fcb9u51bqgft-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_fcb9u51bqgft-4}ol.lst-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-3.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-3 0}.lst-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-0>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-0}ul.lst-kix_wvnn2lytn2eh-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_wvnn2lytn2eh-2{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_wvnn2lytn2eh-5{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_wvnn2lytn2eh-4{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_wvnn2lytn2eh-1{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-6>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-6}ul.lst-kix_wvnn2lytn2eh-0{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-7.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_shbeio5ln3sf-7 0}ol.lst-kix_fcb9u51bqgft-2.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_fcb9u51…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet HackerOne’s Brand Ambassadors That Break the Hacker Stereotype]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ethical-hacker/young-hackers-for-good</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ethical-hacker/young-hackers-for-good"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T16:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The publicity around exploited young hackers perpetuates fear and stigma that young, skilled hackers have no ethical path to put their talent to work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariel Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enumerating Users on z/OS with LISTUSER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=31202</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/mainframe-penetration-testing/enumerating-users-on-z-os-with-listuser/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance mainframe security by learning about the risks of allowing all users the ability to run the LISTUSER command against any user.
The post Enumerating Users on z/OS with LISTUSER appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>