<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-09-22T00:49:51.864Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32 goes to hell…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9481</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/21/rundll32-goes-to-hell/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T22:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parsing command line invocations is fun, because it’s impossible to do it right (all the time). Imagine a test DLL that exports a function called foobar. We place this DLL in c:\test directory and name it like this: test.dll, #666 … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dexray v2.34]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9479</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/20/dexray-v2-34/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T21:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have updated the code to fix a few bugs that Роман Д. pointed out. Thank you Роман! Download the latest version here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spyware Injection Into Your ChatGPT's Long-Term Memory (SpAIware)]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-macos-app-persistent-data-exfiltration/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-macos-app-persistent-data-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explains an attack chain for the ChatGPT macOS application. Through prompt injection from untrusted data, attackers could insert long-term persistent spyware into ChatGPT’s memory. This led to continuous data exfiltration of any information the user typed or responses received by ChatGPT, including any future chat sessions.
 OpenAI released a fix for the macOS app last week. Ensure your app is updated to the latest version.
Let’s look at this spAIware in detail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Copilot responses with identical PDF and DOCX content: Causes and solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586793</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/different-copilot-responses-with-identical-pdf-and-docx-content-causes-and-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T15:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saving identical text as both a Word file and a PDF leads to different responses from Copilot because of the fragmented nature of PDF files. Here's why this occurs and how to modify your prompt for more consistent results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicki Borell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Accelerate Vulnerability Remediation with Hai]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/accelerate-vulnerability-remediation-with-hai</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/accelerate-vulnerability-remediation-with-hai"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T22:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hai, HackerOne's AI co-pilot, streamlines remediation efforts and accelerates the find-to-fix process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to change the SSH port on Ubuntu 24.04]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586630</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-to-change-the-ssh-port-on-ubuntu-2404/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changing the SSH port on Ubuntu 24.04 differs from that on Ubuntu 22.04 and older. Since Ubuntu 22.10, the SSH daemon (sshd) uses socket-based activation, which means that the traditional method of changing the port in /etc/ssh/sshd_config is no longer sufficient. In addition, you need to modify the socket configuration to specify the new port using the ListenStream directive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 3 – DLL Loading Chain for RCE]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66eb2241c9b27c27492158f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/18/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-3-dll-loading-chain-for-rce"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T18:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of 4 blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details. 
In this article, part 3 of the series, I describe a chain of 3 vulnerabilities that led to remote code execution:
·       CVE-2023-36744 – Arbitrary File Write vulnerability
·       CVE-2023-36777 – Arbitrary File Read vulnerability
·       CVE-2023-36745 – Local DLL Loading vulnerability
In the sections that follow, I’m going to describe each of these in detail and show how I chained them to eventually achieve RCE.
You can also watch the talk here: “Half Measures and Full Compromise: Exploiting Microsoft Exchange PowerShell Remoting”. This blog post covers the part from 21:00 to 26:25.
Introduction
I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Trail of Bits and Semgrep partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108295</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/19/announcing-the-trail-of-bits-and-semgrep-partnership/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T13:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Trail of Bits, we aim to share and develop tools and resources used in our security assessments with the broader security community. Many clients, we observed, don’t use Semgrep to its fullest potential or even at all. To bridge this gap and encourage broader adoption, our CEO, Dan Guido, initiated discussions with the Semgrep […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proroute H685 4G router vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29704</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/proroute-h685-4g-router-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Two vulnerabilities on the Proroute H685t-w 4G Router Authenticated command injection is possible through the admin interface Reflected Cross Site-Scripting is possible through the admin interface Patch any routers […]
Proroute H685 4G router vulnerabilities first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lovett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Security Engineering to Make Phishing Harder - A Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/09/19/phishing-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/09/19/phishing-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Recently Doyensec was hired by a client offering a “Communication Platform as a Service”. This platform allows their clients to craft a customer service experience and to communicate with their own customers via a plethora of channels: email, web chats, social media and more.
While undoubtedly valuable, such a service introduces a unique threat model. Our client’s users work with a vast amount of incoming correspondence from outside (often anonymous) users, on a daily basis. This makes them particularly vulnerable to phishing and other social engineering attacks.
While such threats cannot be fully eliminated, it is possible to minimize the possibilities for exploitation. Recognizing this, Doyensec was hired to performed a security review, specifically focused on social enginee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 Copilot: Wave 2]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586714</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-365-copilot-wave-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is maintaining a brisk pace with its AI strategy. Under the title "Microsoft Copilot Wave 2," Redmond unveiled a bundle of innovations and improvements surrounding the diverse Copilot portfolio. There are especially exciting updates in collaboration and Office integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Miedl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber threats to shipping explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29689</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/cyber-threats-to-shipping-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Modern vessels are becoming increasingly connected. While it is unlikely that hackers could fully control a container ship remotely, they may be able to disrupt systems such as the […]
Cyber threats to shipping explained first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Tierney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Biggest Update Ever to SEC510: Cloud Security Controls and Mitigations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/announcing-the-biggest-update-ever-to-sec510-cloud-security-controls-and-mitigations</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/announcing-the-biggest-update-ever-to-sec510-cloud-security-controls-and-mitigations?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the biggest update ever to SEC510: Cloud Security Controls and Mitigations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does OpenAI’s new model o1 solve the hallucination problem?]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586674</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/does-openais-new-model-o1-solve-the-hallucination-problem/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T17:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has officially launched its long-awaited "reasoning" AI model, formerly referred to as "Strawberry" and Q* (Q-star), now named OpenAI o1. Launched as o1-preview and o1-mini, this new family of models promises to tackle complex problems more effectively than its predecessors, including GPT-4o. However, while initial reports are promising, key questions remain about its capabilities. What matters most to me is whether OpenAI resolves the hallucination problem, an issue that all large language models (LLMs) face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside DEF CON: Michael Brown on how AI/ML is revolutionizing cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108279</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/17/inside-def-con-michael-brown-on-how-ai-ml-is-revolutionizing-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At DEF CON, Michael Brown, Principal Security Engineer at Trail of Bits, sat down with Michael Novinson from Information Security Media Group (ISMG) to discuss four critical areas where AI/ML is revolutionizing security. Here’s what they covered: AI/ML techniques surpass the limits of traditional software analysis As Moore’s law slows down after 20 years of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emergency Accounts: Last Call!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18604</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/17/emergency-accounts-last-call/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T10:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update your emergency accounts before October 15th. Even if you have been out of office for the last couple of months, you should be aware that starting October 15th you will need to provide Multi Factor Authentication (MFA) to logon to Azure portal, Entra admin center and Intune admin center. This will be enforced to … Continue reading Emergency Accounts: Last Call! →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Turegano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing HackerOne Automations]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/introducing-hackerone-automations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/introducing-hackerone-automations"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Alyona Vysotska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Microsoft 365 from Active Directory Users and Computers (ADUC) with Easy365Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586601</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/manage-microsoft-365-from-active-directory-users-and-computers-aduc-with-easy365manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T16:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many IT admins manage both on-premises Active Directory environments and hybrid setups like Microsoft 365. Constantly switching between on-premises management and Microsoft 365 can be challenging. Easy365Manager aims to simplify this process. Let's explore this tool and the features it offers for hybrid management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Mainframe Memory Made Easy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25510</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/mainframe-penetration-testing/mapping-mainframe-memory/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how NetSPI's own LPAR enhances pentesting efficiency through rapid tool prototyping and deployment.
The post Mapping Mainframe Memory Made Easy appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Windows on ARM64 / AArch64]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5258</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/09/16/windows_arm64/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T14:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Back in October 2018, I wanted to write ARM assembly on Windows. All I could acquire then was a Surface tablet running Windows RT that was released sometime in October 2012. Windows RT (now deprecated) was a version of … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating DORA Compliance: A Comprehensive Approach to Threat-Led Penetration Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/dora-compliance-penetration-testing</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/dora-compliance-penetration-testing"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how organizations can strategically prepare for and execute TLPT to meet DORA compliance while strengthening overall cybersecurity resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The delayed import-table phantomDLL opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9442</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/14/the-delayed-import-table-phantomdll-opportunities/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T21:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many native OS PE files still rely on delayed imports. When APIs imported this way are called for the first time, a so-called delay load helper function is executed first – it loads the actual delayed library, resolves the address … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expand the Copilot Language Model with external data sources using GraphRAG]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586541</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/expand-the-copilot-language-model-with-external-data-sources-using-graphrag/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the knowledge of a language model is insufficient to answer questions, integrating additional data sources comprehensively can be beneficial. Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) serves this purpose by connecting to data sources outside the trained language model. Microsoft 365 Copilot already works with RAG and is now expanding with GraphRAG to unlock even more extensive knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicki Borell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friends don’t let friends reuse nonces]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108229</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/13/friends-dont-let-friends-reuse-nonces/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Joe Doyle If you’ve encountered cryptography software, you’ve probably heard the advice to never use a nonce twice—in fact, that’s where the word nonce (number used once) comes from. Depending on the cryptography involved, a reused nonce can reveal encrypted messages, or even leak your secret key! But common knowledge may not cover every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA CUDA monopoly faces competition from AMD’s open-source alternative ROCm]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586521</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/nvidia-cuda-monopoly-faces-competition-from-amds-open-source-alternative-rocm/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA's quasi-monopoly in the AI GPU market is achieved through its CUDA platform's early development and widespread adoption. It serves as a moat by becoming the industry standard due to its superior performance and integration with key AI tools. While NVIDIA's dominance is bolstered by its proprietary advantages and developer lock-in, emerging competitors like AMD and innovations such as AMD's ROCm, OpenAI's Triton, and PyTorch 2.0 are beginning to challenge this stronghold by offering open-source alternatives and reducing reliance on CUDA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 2 - ApprovedApplicationCollection]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66e1d60259527a323d805e5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/11/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-2-approvedapplicationcollection"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of 4 blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details. You can read the first post in this series here.
In part 2, I describe the ApprovedApplicationCollection gadget, which was available for abuse because it did not appear on the deny list and could therefore be accessed via MultiValuedProperty. I am also presenting a path traversal in the Windows utility extrac32.exe, which allowed me to complete the chain for a full RCE in Exchange. For the moment, at least, Microsoft has made a decision not to fix this path traversal bug.
You can watch the full talk here: “Half Measures and Full Compromise: Exploiting Microsoft Exchange PowerShell Remoting”. This blog …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Burp Suite’s game-changing performance update ⚡🏎️]]></title>
        <id>introducing-burp-suites-game-changing-performance-update</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/introducing-burp-suites-game-changing-performance-update"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T11:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-on security testers need the best tools for the job. Tools you have faith in, and enjoy using all day long. Burp Suite has long been that tool, and now, it's faster than ever. We’ve listened to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Third-Party Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18459</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/12/introduction-to-third-party-risk-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s world, organizations are increasingly depending on their third-party vendors, suppliers, and partners to support their operations. This way of working, in addition to the digitalization era we’re in, can have great advantages such as being able to offer new services quickly while relying on other’s expertise or cutting costs on already existing processes. … Continue reading Introduction to Third-Party Risk Management →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fishel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living off the land, GPO style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29636</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/living-off-the-land-gpo-style/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T05:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The ability to edit  Group Policy Object (GPOs) from non-domain joined computers using the native Group Policy editor has been on my list for a long time.  This blog […]
Living off the land, GPO style first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32.exe bomb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9463</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/11/rundll32-exe-bomb/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T22:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a silly example of a basic mistake leading to a funny discovery… When I was experimenting with the imported phantom DLLs I accidentally placed a dummy 64-bit DLL in a place of a 32-bit phantom DLL called WDSUTIL.dll … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Bug Bounty Programs in S-1 Filings: A New Standard in Corporate Security]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-s-1-filings</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/bug-bounty-s-1-filings"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T21:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why more organizations are including their bug bounty programs in S-1 filings and other corporate disclosures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jobert Abma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Large Language Models: Local LLM CTF & Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/large-language-models-llm-ctf-lab</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/large-language-models-llm-ctf-lab"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore research on isolating functional expectations for LLMs using a controller to manage access between privileged and quarantined LLMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Rush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Built-in data security in Microsoft 365: What Microsoft provides and what the customer is responsible for]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586366</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/built-in-data-security-in-microsoft-365-what-microsoft-provides-and-what-the-customer-is-responsible-for/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T14:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How secure is the data in Microsoft 365, and what basic measures does Microsoft offer for data protection and reliability? The company has integrated some safeguarding mechanisms to protect customers from data mishaps. There is also a new framework that outlines the responsibilities of both the provider and the customer. Here's an overview of tools and regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Miedl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADCS Attack Paths in BloodHound — Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/33efb00856ac</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/adcs-attack-paths-in-bloodhound-part-3-33efb00856ac?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T13:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will explore the new ESC6/ESC9/ESC10 edges we have introduced with ADCS support in BloodHound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bülow Knudsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Improvements to table sorting and Repeater]]></title>
        <id>performance-improvements-to-table-sorting-and-repeater</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/performance-improvements-to-table-sorting-and-repeater"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T06:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance is a critical factor in the usability and efficiency of any software, and Burp Suite is no exception. We've recently focused on enhancing Burp Suite's performance across several key areas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite Performance Improvements]]></title>
        <id>burp-suite-performance-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/burp-suite-performance-improvements"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T06:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance is a critical factor in the usability and efficiency of any software, and Burp Suite is no exception. We've recently focused on enhancing Burp Suite's performance across several key areas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The September 2024 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66e07f45c60a2e7a02fabeb6</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/10/the-september-2024-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T17:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve reached September and the pumpkin spice floats in the air. While they aren’t pumpkin-spiced, Microsoft and Adobe have released their latest spicy security patches – including some zesty 0-days. Take a break from your regular activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts.If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for September 2024
For September, Adobe released eight bulletins covering 28 CVEs in Adobe Acrobat and Reader, ColdFusion, Photoshop, Media Encoder, Audition, After Effects, Premier Pro, and Illustrator. A total of seven of these bugs came through the ZDI program. If you’re prioritizing, I would look at the ColdFusion patch first. It corrects a single code execution bug rat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Hai Plays: Personalize Your Playbook for Spot-On Security Advice]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/hai-plays</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/hai-plays"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T17:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to introduce Hai Plays, a powerful new feature for Hai, HackerOne’s AI co-pilot. Hai Plays is designed to make your interactions with Hai more efficient and tailored to your specific security needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack My Career: Harley Kimball’s Journey to DEFCON]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-harley-kimballs-journey-defcon</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-harley-kimballs-journey-defcon"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>mbriones@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Workstation Pro 17.6: Free for personal use, enhanced OS support, and improved performance]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586460</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/vmware-workstation-pro-176-free-for-personal-use-enhanced-os-support-and-improved-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Workstation Pro 17.6 introduces a couple of valuable changes. Notably, it is now available for free for personal use. The update enhances OS support, adding compatibility with systems like Windows Server 2025 and Ubuntu 24.04 as both hosts and guests. Additionally, new tools like the vmcli command-line utility streamline virtual machine management, while crucial bug fixes and security updates enhance the platform's reliability and efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hijacking SQL Server Credentials using Agent Jobs for Domain Privilege Escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25333</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/network-pentesting/hijacking-sql-server-credentials-with-agent-jobs-for-domain-privilege-escalation/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how threat actors can exploit SQL Server credential objects to escalate domain privileges and how you can detect it.
The post Hijacking SQL Server Credentials using Agent Jobs for Domain Privilege Escalation  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Sutherland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sanitize your C++ containers: ASan annotations step-by-step]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108139</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/10/sanitize-your-c-containers-asan-annotations-step-by-step/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Dominik Klemba and Dominik Czarnota AddressSanitizer (ASan) is a compiler plugin that helps detect memory errors like buffer overflows or use-after-frees. In this post, we explain how to equip your C++ code with ASan annotations to find more bugs. We also show our work on ASan in GCC and LLVM. In LLVM, Trail of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudGoat Official Walkthrough Series: ‘glue_privesc’]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=25344</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/cloud-security/cloudgoat-walkthrough-glue_privesc/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CloudGoat Official Walkthrough Series: ‘glue_privesc’ appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John De Armas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart home security advice. Ring, SimpliSafe, Swann, and Yale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29600</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/smart-home-security-advice-ring-simplisafe-swann-and-yale/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T05:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This guide covers the security of smart home security products from Ring, Yale, Swann, and SimpliSafe. Whether you’re looking to monitor your property remotely, enhance your home’s security, or […]
Smart home security advice. Ring, SimpliSafe, Swann, and Yale first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Bromiley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance your Cyber Threat Intelligence with the Admiralty System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/enhance-your-cyber-threat-intelligence-with-the-admiralty-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/enhance-your-cyber-threat-intelligence-with-the-admiralty-system?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about using the Admiralty System for better cyber threat intelligence (CTI).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strengthen Your Supply Chain Security with Effective SBOM Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/strengthen-your-supply-chain-security-with-effective-sbom-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/strengthen-your-supply-chain-security-with-effective-sbom-management?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Master SBOM management to secure your software supply chain. Explore the SBOM lifecycle with our guide and enhance your compliance and security strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One Launches Public Bug Bounty Program with HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/capital-one-public-bug-bounty</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/capital-one-public-bug-bounty"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One has officially launched a public bug bounty program with HackerOne, partnering with ethical hackers to secure their assets and prevent security breaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block AI scrapers and other web parasites with Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586408</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/block-ai-scrapers-and-other-web-parasites-with-cloudflare/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T15:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post, I discussed three standard methods to block AI crawlers that have little prospect of being successful. Please also read it if you want to know why it is important to block AI scrapers. One way that works reliably for 4sysops is leveraging Cloudflare's Web Application Firewall (WAF). Cloudflare's free plan provides all the essential tools to safeguard your site against content theft by AI companies. However, I found that Cloudflare's new Block AI Scrapers and Crawlers feature is insufficient for the task. Fortunately, Cloudflare's WAF is sophisticated enough to reliably block all AI scrapers and other web parasites with a single, relatively simple rule. My proposed method serves as a way to enforce an opt-in approach, rather than relying on the non-binding opt-out recommendations in your robots.txt file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS AI Cybersecurity Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ai-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-ai-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS AI Cybersecurity Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why ICS Is the Business: Essential Cybersecurity Strategies for Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/why-ics-is-the-business-essential-cybersecurity-strategies-for-critical-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/why-ics-is-the-business-essential-cybersecurity-strategies-for-critical-infrastructure?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog detailing strategies to protect industrial control systems (ICS) and critical infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This post is totally Iconic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9457</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/07/this-post-is-totally-iconic/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T22:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 6 years ago I decided to pursue yet another silly idea: extract all the unique .ico files from PE resources from as many samples as I can. This exercise yielded ~450K unique .ico files. If I remember correctly, the … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of underDLLoading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9440</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/06/the-art-of-underdlloading/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T22:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post I created a posh artisan .exe file ornamented with a large number of intricate system32 DLL imports. The process of building that file was painful – before I even managed to run the final executable I … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Prospect to Partner: Jon Stone Shares HackerOne Career Story]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/prospect-partner-jon-stone-shares-hackerone-career-story</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/prospect-partner-jon-stone-shares-hackerone-career-story"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T20:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recover data from corrupted BitLocker drives with repair-bde and key packages]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586344</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/recover-data-from-corrupted-bitlocker-drives-with-repair-bde-and-key-packages/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activating BitLocker encryption on a drive automatically generates a 48-digit numeric recovery password. This password is crucial if other unlocking methods fail and Windows prompts you with the BitLocker recovery console during startup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Unstripping” binaries: Restoring debugging information in GDB with Pwndbg]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108110</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/06/unstripping-binaries-restoring-debugging-information-in-gdb-with-pwndbg/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jason An GDB loses significant functionality when debugging binaries that lack debugging symbols (also known as “stripped binaries”). Function and variable names become meaningless addresses; setting breakpoints requires tracking down relevant function addresses from an external source; and printing out structured values involves staring at a memory dump trying to manually discern field boundaries. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunting Chromium Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=17131</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/06/hunting-chromium-notifications/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browser notifications provide social-engineering opportunities. In this post we'll cover the associated forensic artifacts, threat hunting possibilities and hardening recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Thiebaut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of overDLLoading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9430</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/05/the-art-of-overdlloading/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T23:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some time ago I came up with a silly idea: i’d like to build an executable that statically links to most of the c:\windows\system2 libraries. It’s a non-sensical programming exercise, but it’s also an interesting challenge. Forcing a static import … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical debt of C:\Windows\System path]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9423</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/05/technical-debt-of-cwindowssystem-path/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T21:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to @sixtyvividtails who corrected a mistake I made in the earlier version of the post Updated post One of a less known paths that is being searched when the libraries are loaded is C:\Windows\System. Anytime the search for a … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Exchange PowerShell After ProxyNotShell: Part 1 - MultiValuedProperty]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66d8b6216c0b0917fc4e4ef7</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/9/4/exploiting-exchange-powershell-after-proxynotshell-part-1-multivaluedproperty"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, I recently presented my Exchange-related talk during OffensiveCon 2024. This series of four blog posts is meant to supplement the talk and provide additional technical details. For those who did not attend OffensiveCon, you can also watch the full talk here: “Half Measures and Full Compromise: Exploiting Microsoft Exchange PowerShell Remoting”. This blog post covers the part from 12:05 to 18:10.
In this article, part one of the series, I describe the MultiValuedProperty exploitation primitive, which became fundamental for my further exploitation of Exchange PowerShell. I also present a bypass for Microsoft’s first patch for this vulnerability, accomplished by chaining MultiValuedProperty with the Command class.  
Introduction
You might already be familiar with the Exchange…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Bazydło</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How not to block AI crawlers: robots.txt, authentication, CAPTCHA]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586317</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/how-not-to-block-ai-crawlers-robotstxt-authentication-captcha/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The content wars are on. AI crawlers ignore robots.txt, scraping greedily any web content they can reach to train their models. If search engine traffic from Google and Bing is helpful for your website, you must block all AI scrapers. This post covers three standard but ineffective methods for blocking AI crawlers on your site: robots.txt, authentication, and CAPTCHAs. In my next post, I'll introduce a solution that effectively blocks AI crawlers and other web parasites: Cloudflare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon23 Replay | They Spilled Oil in My Health-Boosting Smoothie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=104518</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon23-replay-they-spilled-oil-in-my-health-boosting-smoothie/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zuzana Hromcová explores how Iran-aligned APT OilRig targets healthcare and local governments with a stream of updated and newly developed tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What would you do with that old GPU?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108089</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/09/05/what-would-you-do-with-that-old-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T13:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg and Peter Goodman (Would you get up and throw it away?) [sing to the tune of The Beatles – With A Little Help From My Friends] Here’s a riddle: when new GPUs are constantly being produced, product cycles are ~18-24 months long, and each cycle doubles GPU power (per Huang’s Law), what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validate your Windows Audit Policy Configuration with KQL]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=14001</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/05/validate-your-windows-audit-policy-configuration-with-kql/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We provide a KQL query that will help you validate your defined Windows audit security policy configuration. Defining a Windows audit policy is an important step in establishing a robust security posture. Ensuring that the audit policy is applied consistently across your environment is just as important as defining that policy and quality controls should be in place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stamatis Chatzimangou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve Taken a SANS Course – Now What?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/youve-taken-a-sans-course-now-what</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/youve-taken-a-sans-course-now-what?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog detailing what to do once you have completed a SANS Live Training course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantifying the Value of Bug Bounty Programs: ROI, ROM, or Both?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/quantifying-value-bug-bounty-programs-roi-rom-or-both</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/quantifying-value-bug-bounty-programs-roi-rom-or-both"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T21:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is ROI the right method to measure bug bounty value? Check out the cost-benefit analysis of ROI vs. ROM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32 and Phantom DLL lolbins, 32-bit version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9419</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/04/rundll32-and-phantom-dll-lolbins-32-bit-version/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I have shown in the last post, there exists a class of DLLs on Windows OS that load other libraries via import table, and sometimes these needed imported libraries do not exist. This creates an opportunity that we can … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Determine effective password policy for AD users with PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586100</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/determine-effective-password-policy-for-ad-users-with-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T15:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the default domain password policy, administrators can assign different password rules to specific users or groups using fine-grained password policies. When multiple policies exist, it can become unclear which one is effective for a particular user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MEGAsync Forensics and Intrusion Attribution]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=17972</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/09/04/megasync-forensics-and-intrusion-attribution/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MEGAsync forensics can be leveraged to identify exfiltrated files, additional victims and, subsequently, perform attribution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Thiebaut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced forensic techniques for recovering hidden data in wearable devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29571</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/advanced-forensic-techniques-for-recovering-hidden-data-in-wearable-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T05:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR  A walk-through of forensic data recovery  Detailed example of how to retrieve potentially sensitive deleted data  Includes location, sleep and activity tracking  Understand the security and privacy implications of […]
Advanced forensic techniques for recovering hidden data in wearable devices first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Expect at SANS Live Training Events]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-to-expect-at-sans-live-training-events</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-to-expect-at-sans-live-training-events?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about what you can expect when you attend a SANS Live Training event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why SANS Live Training? What’s in It for You and Your Career?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/why-sans-live-training-whats-in-it-for-you-and-your-career</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/why-sans-live-training-whats-in-it-for-you-and-your-career?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the professional and personal benefits of attending a SANS Live Training event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rundll32 and Phantom DLL lolbins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9414</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/09/03/rundll32-and-phantom-dll-lolbins/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T21:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This may be a new, kinda ephemereal addition to the lolbin world (not sure if anyone covered it before). Windows 11 comes with a large number of DLLs – some of which are broken. DuCsps.dll on Windows 11 Pro 22H2 … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crushing FUD: Embracing Ethical Hackers to Strengthen Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/crushing-fud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/crushing-fud"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T18:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FUD can overshadow proactive collaboration with ethical hackers. Let's explore how to combat FUD and get organizational buy-in for bug bounty and VDP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine Williams-Baisy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abusing Arbitrary File Deletes to Escalate Privilege and Other Great Tricks (Archive)]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6571f96c06db0605e399951a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2022/3/16/abusing-arbitrary-file-deletes-to-escalate-privilege-and-other-great-tricks-archive"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T15:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This version of the blog is preserved for archival purposes only. An updated version of this blog, including links to new PoC code, can be found here.
What do you do when you’ve found an arbitrary file delete as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM? Probably just sigh and call it a DoS. Well, no more. In this article, we’ll show you some great techniques for getting much more out of your arbitrary file deletes, arbitrary folder deletes, and other seemingly low-impact filesystem-based exploit primitives.
The Trouble with Arbitrary File Deletes
When you consider how to leverage an arbitrary file delete on Windows, two great obstacles present themselves:
Most critical Windows OS files are locked down with DACLs that prevent modification even by SYSTEM. Instead, most OS files are owned by TrustedInstaller, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Zuckerbraun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the URL validation bypass cheat sheet]]></title>
        <id>introducing-the-url-validation-bypass-cheat-sheet</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/introducing-the-url-validation-bypass-cheat-sheet"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T14:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[URL validation bypasses are the root cause of numerous vulnerabilities including many instances of SSRF, CORS misconfiguration, and open redirection. These work by using ambiguous URLs to trigger URL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Lightsail vs. AWS EC2: Pricing and flexibility]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586222</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/amazon-lightsail-vs-aws-ec2-pricing-and-flexibility/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T13:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Web Services (AWS) offers two popular solutions for deploying virtual machines (instances): Lightsail and AWS EC2. While Amazon Lightsail is frequently recommended for smaller projects, is it really better than EC2 in terms of ease of use, flexibility, performance, and pricing?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 5 Items to Bring Along to a Live Training Event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/the-top-5-items-to-bring-along-to-a-live-training-event</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/the-top-5-items-to-bring-along-to-a-live-training-event?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the top five items you should bring to a SANS Live Training event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Goffloader: A Pure Go Implementation of an In-Memory COFFLoader and PE Loader]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3131</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/introducing-goffloader-a-pure-go-implementation-of-an-in-memory-coffloader-and-pe-loader/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T22:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the release of Goffloader, a pure Go implementation of an in-memory COFFLoader and PE loader. This tool is designed to facilitate the easy execution of Cobalt Strike BOFs and unmanaged PE files directly in memory without writing any files to disk. Goffloader aims to take functionality that is conventionally within […]
The post Introducing Goffloader: A Pure Go Implementation of an In-Memory COFFLoader and PE Loader appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sportsman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Windows Terminal: Restore buffers, code snippets, scratchpad and regex]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586238</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-windows-terminal-restore-buffers-code-snippets-scratchpad-and-regex/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T15:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Terminal unveiled a range of noteworthy features in versions 1.21 and 1.22 Preview, including the capacity to retrieve previous sessions' output buffer upon startup, store code snippets for reuse within the console, and utilize a scratchpad for crafting intricate commands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Your Upcoming SANS Live Training Event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-prepare-for-your-upcoming-sans-live-training-event</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-prepare-for-your-upcoming-sans-live-training-event?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about how to best prepare for a SANS Live Training event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: API Hashing with Block Ciphers (Maru4)]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5609</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/09/01/shellcode-api-hashing-with-block-ciphers-maru4/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T16:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Constructing your own hash algorithm is controversial because there will always be professionals in the field of cryptography and engineering that can expose vulnerabilities in the design. I’m not encouraging anyone to construct a cryptographic hash algorithm without extensive … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in August]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10541</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/09/01/overview-of-content-published-in-august-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T15:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in August: SANS ISC Diary entries: OOXML Spreadsheets Protected By Verifier Hashes Wireshark 4.4.0rc1’s Custom Columns Wireshark 4.4.0 is now available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: RSA (Data Masking 4)]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5595</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/08/31/masking4/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T15:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Malware like OceanLotus have used RSA-256 to hide strings. Darkhotel used RSA to hide code. For fun, some crackmes used RSA-32 or RSA-64 for simple keygen challenges. The RSA cryptosystem uses two exponents (or keys) and a modulus derived … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Pseudo-Random Involution (Data Masking 3)]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5569</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/08/30/shellcode-pris/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T18:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Not sure if the title is an accurate description, but when you apply a self-inverse permutation or involution twice, you get back the original data and that’s pretty much what the code shown in this post does. There’s a … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne’s Commitment to Learning and Development]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-commitment-learning-and-development</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hackerones-commitment-learning-and-development"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T16:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox 7.1: New features of the free  desktop virtualzation tool]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586171</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/virtualbox-71-new-features-of-the-free-desktop-virtualzation-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T15:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox, the popular open-source virtualization software from Oracle, has recently released its 7.1 Beta version, bringing exciting new features and improvements. The new update aims to improve the user experience and performance, ensuring that VirtualBox remains a viable option in the desktop virtualization market. This post focuses on the new features, thoroughly summarizing what users can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to enhance the security of your social media accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29545</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/how-to-enhance-the-security-of-your-social-media-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR  Strong passwords: Use a password manager. Multi-factor authentication (MFA): MFA requires multiple forms of identification, adding an extra layer of security. This makes it harder for unauthorised users to […]
How to enhance the security of your social media accounts first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentesting for iOS Mobile Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/ios-mobile-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/ios-mobile-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T21:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the different methodologies and best practices for pentesting for iOS applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul De Baldo V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SquaredUp Cloud: Comprehensive monitoring and dashboard solution for a wide range of on-prem and cloud services]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585869</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/squaredup-cloud-comprehensive-monitoring-and-dashboard-solution-for-a-wide-range-of-on-prem-and-cloud-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T18:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SquaredUp Cloud allows the creation of dashboards and visualizations of data as a SaaS solution with many sharing options, 70+ plugins, custom APIs, and on-prem integration for hybrid cloud monitoring. The dashboard solution is easy to set up and has many features and integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in July]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10539</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/08/29/overview-of-content-published-in-july-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in July: Blog posts: Update: hash.py Version 0.0.13 Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.77 Update: cut-bytes.py Version 0.0.17 SANS ISC Diary entries: 16-bit Hash Collisions in .xls Spreadsheets Wireshark 4.2.6 Released Protected OOXML Spreadsheets Create Your Own BSOD: NotMyFault Quickie: Password Cracking & Energy CrowdStrike Outage Themed Maldoc]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the VirusTotal Dataset | An Analyst’s Guide to Effective Threat Research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=104092</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/exploring-the-virustotal-dataset-an-analysts-guide-to-effective-threat-research/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T09:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We teamed up with VirusTotal to take a deep dive into the platform's extensive query capabilities through both the web and API interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Milenkoski &amp; Jose Luis Sánchez Martínez (VirusTotal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big TIBER Encyclopedia]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18027</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/08/29/the-big-tiber-encyclopedia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of current TIBER implementations ahead of DORA’s TLPT requirements Introduction TIBER (Threat Intelligence-Based Ethical Red Teaming) is a framework introduced by the European Central Bank (ECB) in 2018 as a response to the increasing number of cyber threats faced by financial institutions. The framework provides a standardized methodology and guidelines for conducting controlled … Continue reading The Big TIBER Encyclopedia →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Bauters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3CX Phone System Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=3094</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/3cx-phone-system-local-privilege-escalation-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T22:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In an effort to safeguard our customers, we perform proactive vulnerability research with the goal of identifying zero-day vulnerabilities that are likely to impact the security of leading organizations. Recently, we decided to take a look at the 3CX Phone Management System with the goal of identifying an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability within […]
The post 3CX Phone System Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenneth King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Hai Facilitates Clear and Effective Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/ai/hai-facilitates-effective-communication</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/ai/hai-facilitates-effective-communication"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T21:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HackerOne's AI co-pilot, Hai, bridges communication gaps and streamlines collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martijn Russchen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythic 3.3 — Out of Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9979e82660c3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/mythic-3-3-out-of-beta-9979e82660c3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T19:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythic 3.3 was released in a Beta six weeks ago, and since then there has been a bunch of feedback, not just about new Mythic 3.3 features…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cody Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Purview AI Hub – Monitor and block AI applications]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586139</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-purview-ai-hub-monitor-and-block-ai-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T16:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Purview is a data governance and compliance solution tailored for Microsoft's ecosystem, predominantly used in Microsoft 365. Microsoft Purview AI Hub is a feature within the platform that secures and proactively monitors AI applications, such as Microsoft Copilot for Microsoft 365 and third-party large language models (LLMs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-37079: VMware vCenter Server Integer Underflow Code Execution Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66ce3dcb39b07158e559220d</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/8/27/cve-2024-37079-vmware-vcenter-server-integer-underflow-code-execution-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Grigory Dorodnov and Guy Lederfein of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched code execution vulnerability in the VMware vCenter Server. This bug was originally discovered by Hao Zheng and Zibo Li from TianGong Team of Legendsec at Qi'anxin Group. Successfully exploiting this vulnerability could lead to a heap buffer overflow, which could result in the execution of arbitrary code in the context of the vulnerable service. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2024-37079, with a few minimal modifications.
An integer underflow vulnerability has been reported for VMware vCenter Server. The vulnerability is due to a lack of validation of the calculated response header size u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offensive Security Under the EU Digital Operational Resilience Act (DORA)]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/offensive-security-eu-dora</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/offensive-security-eu-dora"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the EU's new DORA regulation and how financial entities and their ICT vendors must promptly align their security frameworks with DORA's requirements to mitigate potential risks and ensure operational stability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harley Geiger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter ❤ Tool Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2dfbb952eb8a</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/ghostwriter-tool-integration-2dfbb952eb8a?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incorporating new components into existing systems is such a pain, this process has been labeled “Integration Hell”. To ease tool…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Sou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Provisioning cloud infrastructure the wrong way, but faster]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=108061</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/08/27/provisioning-cloud-infrastructure-the-wrong-way-but-faster/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Artem Dinaburg Today we’re going to provision some cloud infrastructure the Max Power way: by combining automation with unchecked AI output. Unfortunately, this method produces cloud infrastructure code that 1) works and 2) has terrible security properties. In a nutshell, AI-based tools like Claude and ChatGPT readily provide extremely bad cloud infrastructure provisioning code, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-37888 – CKEditor 4 Open Link plugin XSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25306</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/web-application-pentesting/cve-2024-37888-ckeditor-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NetSPI discovered CVE-2024-37888, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CKEditor 4 Open Link plugin. Read about the nature of the vulnerability and its implications.
The post CVE-2024-37888 – CKEditor 4 Open Link plugin XSS appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anurag Mondal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Maintenance Burden by Bending C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we look at how we were able to use new C features and GCC plugin additions to eliminate over a megabyte of changes from grsecurity patches without any change in functionality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Maintenance Burden by Bending C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.grsecurity.net/reducing_maintenance_burden_by_bending_c.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we look at how we were able to use new C features and GCC plugin additions to eliminate over a megabyte of changes from grsecurity patches without any change in functionality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grsecurity Blog RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Copilot: From Prompt Injection to Exfiltration of Personal Information]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/m365-copilot-prompt-injection-tool-invocation-and-data-exfil-using-ascii-smuggling/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/m365-copilot-prompt-injection-tool-invocation-and-data-exfil-using-ascii-smuggling/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post describes vulnerability in Microsoft 365 Copilot that allowed the theft of a user’s emails and other personal information. This vulnerability warrants a deep dive, because it combines a variety of novel attack techniques that are not even two years old.

I initially disclosed parts of this exploit to Microsoft in January, and then the full exploit chain in February 2024. A few days ago I got the okay from MSRC to disclose this report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory auditing with ManageEngine ADAudit Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1586073</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/active-directory-auditing-with-manageengine-adaudit-plus/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most organizations view Microsoft Active Directory as a "black box," lacking full visibility into its activities. ManageEngine ADAudit Plus aims to change that with its Active Directory auditing solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ring Around The Regex: Lessons learned from fuzzing regex libraries (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://secret.club/2024/08/23/ring-around-the-regex-2.html</id>
        <link href="https://secret.club/2024/08/23/ring-around-the-regex-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a little late (one whole month passed in a blink of an eye!). Let’s catch up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>secret club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Volume Email in Microsoft 365: Overcoming sending limits]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585881</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/high-volume-email-in-microsoft-365-overcoming-sending-limits/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T15:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sending a high number of emails in Microsoft 365 without hitting the throttling limits has always been an issue. Microsoft has introduced a new feature called High Volume Email to address this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New website address and RSS Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=34806</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2024/08/13/new-website-address-and-rss-feed/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T15:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that all of NCC Group’s latest research findings and articles are now hosted on our website at the following link: NCC Group Research Blog. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/) To stay up-to-date with our latest research, you can also subscribe to our RSS feed here: NCC Group Research Blog RSS Feed. (https://www.nccgroup.com/us/research-blog/feed/) Be sure to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>R.Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side-by-Side with HelloJackHunter: Unveiling the Mysteries of WinSxS]]></title>
        <id>65f5ceb78792421d3c2272e4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/hellojackhunter-exploring-winsxs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T09:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores Windows Side-by-Side (WinSxS) and DLL hijacking, deep-diving some tooling I've written and some of the fun along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>