<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-08-04T00:43:39.004Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The value-proposition of building and maintaining an internal Threat Hunting team…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9300</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/08/02/the-value-proposition-of-building-and-maintaining-an-internal-threat-hunting-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T23:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IT/cyber Buy vs. Build discussions often focus on, and present the issue at hand as a zerosum game. And in this game you MUST choose between either ‘Buy’ or ‘Build’. How limiting… TL;DR; This article suggests that you should … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reclaim WSUS storage space using deduplication]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585350</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/reclaim-wsus-storage-space-using-deduplication/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T17:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WSUS servers generally need substantial storage for updates. Although configuring WSUS can optimize storage use, additional steps may further reduce storage needs. WSUS servers appear especially well-suited for deduplication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Attack Paths, New Views and your favorite dog learns an old trick]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/335652a164df</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/hybrid-attack-paths-new-views-and-your-favorite-dog-learns-an-old-trick-335652a164df?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T17:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Hybrid Attack Paths]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Kohler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Evidence to Advantage: Leveraging Incident Response Artifacts for Red Team Engagements]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=17958</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/08/02/from-evidence-to-advantage-leveraging-incident-response-artifacts-for-red-team-engagements/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T09:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is this blog post about? This blog post is about why incident responder artifacts not only play a role on the defensive but also offensive side of cyber security. We are gonna look at some of the usually collected evidences and how they can be valuable to us as red team operators. We will … Continue reading From Evidence to Advantage: Leveraging Incident Response Artifacts for Red Team Engagements →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steffen Rogge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Steps To Implement A Zero Trust Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/10-steps-to-implement-a-zero-trust-architecture</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/10-steps-to-implement-a-zero-trust-architecture?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog highlighting an infographic about ten steps to implement a Zero Trust architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Page Updates: Boosting Consistency & Transparency for Security Researchers and Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-page-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-page-updates"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T23:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne has launched new updates to program security pages that standardize policy fields and drive hacker engagement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Fidelity detections are Low Fidelity detections, until proven otherwise, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9314</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/08/01/high-fidelity-detections-are-low-fidelity-detections-until-proven-otherwise-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T22:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post I looked at ‘good’ file names. Today I will look at them again. Sort of… Over the years I have written a number of yara rules that use a peculiar condition that hits on an internal … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relay Your Heart Away: An OPSEC-Conscious Approach to 445 Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1c9b4666c8ac</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/relay-your-heart-away-an-opsec-conscious-approach-to-445-takeover-1c9b4666c8ac?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T16:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even within organizations that have achieved a mature security posture, targeted NTLM relay attacks are still incredibly effective after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Powers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers and Assumptions: Techniques for Privilege Escalation on Windows: Part 3]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66aa8d813cfeb533ee74a5c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/31/breaking-barriers-and-assumptions-techniques-for-privilege-escalation-on-windows-part-3"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To wrap up this blog series we wanted to include one more technique that you can use when exploiting this class of vulnerabilities. This technique, introduced to us by Abdelhamid Naceri, becomes useful when you have an on-boot arbitrary delete primitive that you want to transform into an on-demand delete, so that you can escalate using the C:\Config.msi technique.  We will also share a tool that can make debugging protected processes on Windows easier and end by detailing some difficulties we faced during disclosures with several vendors. 
Technique ++
One way you can use an on-boot delete primitive is to abuse the Windows Task Scheduler included in default installations of Windows. The Task Scheduler uses the following two directories to perform tasks:  
C:\Windows\System32\Tasks - for st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael DePlante and Nicholas Zubrisky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breach Controls Readiness: A Step to Cybersecurity Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/breach-controls-readiness-a-step-to-cybersecurity-resilience</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/breach-controls-readiness-a-step-to-cybersecurity-resilience"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a look at Breach Controls Readiness Assessments, a testing that evaluates an organization's email, endpoint, and network security controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recover a PC if Windows is not booting]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585437</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/recover-a-pc-if-windows-is-not-booting/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CrowdStrike update won't be the last update that strikes down your Windows machines. If Windows is not booting due to a corrupted update, you have several recovery options using WinRE, Safe Mode, and Windows PE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootloaders explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29321</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/bootloaders-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T05:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Modern computers have a program that starts the operating system, known as a bootloader Bootloaders can be communicated with to access storage (and sometimes RAM) directly They are all […]
Bootloaders explained first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lovett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Microsoft Entra PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585387</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/microsoft-entra-powershell-to-replace-the-azure-ad-powershell-module/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Entra PowerShell module is the successor to the Azure AD PowerShell module. It's designed to streamline management and automation for the Microsoft Entra product family, which includes the services formerly known as Azure Active Directory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers and Assumptions: Techniques for Privilege Escalation on Windows: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66a943f9c6730443e0cd3f7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/30/breaking-barriers-and-assumptions-techniques-for-privilege-escalation-on-windows-part-2"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of vulnerabilities that we see through the program provides significant insight into the attack surfaces of each product that we purchase bugs in. These submissions sometimes reveal not only potential variants but also broader architectural flaws. Submitters frequently choose to provide a full exploit with their submission, which can further reveal interesting techniques. Some of these techniques are so versatile that they end up being useful in the exploitation of several products that all share common functionality. The technique discussed in this blog is one such example that we used to uncover and exploit several vulnerabilities. 
Due to paywalls and other obstacles, several vendors and products on the market remain untested and may be vulnerable to the weaknesses we are abo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael DePlante and Nicholas Zubrisky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Escalating Privileges in Google Cloud via Open Groups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25078</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/escalating-privileges-in-google-cloud-via-open-groups/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how attackers can abuse Open groups to potentially escalate privileges in Google Cloud and how to detect these attack paths.
The post Escalating Privileges in Google Cloud via Open Groups  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Elling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock enhanced API scanning with Burp Suite]]></title>
        <id>unlock-enhanced-api-scanning-with-burp-suite</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/unlock-enhanced-api-scanning-with-burp-suite"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T12:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More comprehensive scans. More vulnerabilities identified. More time saved. Enhance your API scanning with Burp Suite. As web portfolios have diversified, APIs have become an increasingly critical fun]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protected: KnowBe4 RCE and LPE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29260</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/knowbe4-rce-and-lpe/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no excerpt because this is a protected post.
Protected: KnowBe4 RCE and LPE first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ceri Coburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Visual Summary of SANS Security Awareness: Managing Human Risk Summit 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-human-risk-summit-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/a-visual-summary-of-sans-human-risk-summit-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Cybersecurity Blog pertaining to a summary of the SANS Security Awareness: Managing Human Risk Summit 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aviata Cloud Solo Flight Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/aviata-solo-flight-challenge-cloud-security-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/aviata-solo-flight-challenge-cloud-security-workshops/?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Master cloud security by tackling this free series of workshops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take Me to the Cyber Arcade! Level Up Your Cyber Skills with Core NetWars Version 10: A Cutting-Edge Retro Arcade and AI Adventure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/level-up-your-cyber-skills-with-core-netwars-version-10-a-retro-arcade-and-ai-adventure</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/level-up-your-cyber-skills-with-core-netwars-version-10-a-retro-arcade-and-ai-adventure?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about SANS Institute's new Core NetWars Version 10]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute: Leading the Way in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning Cybersecurity Training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-institute-leading-the-way-in-artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning-cybersecurity-training</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sans-institute-leading-the-way-in-artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning-cybersecurity-training?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about SANS Institute's artificial intelligence and machine learning cybersecurity training]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing HackerOne Gateway Internal Network Testing: Superior Security for Internal Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/gateway-internal-network-testing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/gateway-internal-network-testing"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Gateway Internal Network Testing (INT), powered by Cloudflare’s Zero Trust Network Access (ZTNA) technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Collins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect Your Copilots: Preventing Data Leaks in Copilot Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/copilot-studio-protect-your-copilots/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/copilot-studio-protect-your-copilots/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T17:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Copilot Studio is a powerful, easy-to-use, low-code platform that enables employees in an organization to create chatbots. Previously known as Power Virtual Agents, it has been updated (including GenAI features) and rebranded to Copilot Studio, likely to align with current AI trends.

This post discusses security risks to be aware of when using Copilot Studio, focusing on data leaks, unauthorized access, and how external adversaries can find and interact with misconfigured Copilots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using text embeddings in RAG]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585315</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/using-text-embeddings-in-rag/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T15:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My previous post introduced the basics of generating text embeddings using embedding models. Today, we'll expand on these concepts to explore how embeddings can enhance Large Language Models (LLMs) through Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers and Assumptions: Techniques for Privilege Escalation on Windows: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66a7c784acc06a697c34b0fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/29/breaking-barriers-and-assumptions-techniques-for-privilege-escalation-on-windows-part-1"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T14:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of link following vulnerabilities submitted to the Trend Micro ZDI program has been increasing rapidly over the past several years. These submissions have provided us with insight into how these vulnerabilities are being found and exploited.
In years prior we were seeing a lot of low-hanging fruit in this bug class where you simply just needed a privileged file operation in a directory with a permissive DACL. Now, as we will see with the vulnerabilities presented in this blog series, they often require programmatically exploiting a race condition. In a previous blog , we shared techniques that allow us to escalate our privileges using an arbitrary delete primitive, or to create a permanent DoS condition from an arbitrary file or folder creation primitive. In this blog series, we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael DePlante and Nicholas Zubrisky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Sea Phishing Pt. 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/29c48f1e214e</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/deep-sea-phishing-pt-2-29c48f1e214e?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making Your Malware Look Legit to Bypasses EDR]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our audit of Homebrew]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107865</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/07/30/our-audit-of-homebrew/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William Woodruff This is a joint post with the Homebrew maintainers; read their announcement here! Last summer, we performed an audit of Homebrew. Our audit’s scope included Homebrew/brew itself (home of the brew CLI), and three adjacent repositories responsible for various security-relevant aspects of Homebrew’s operation: Homebrew/actions: a repository of custom GitHub Actions used […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a GraphQL Bug Resulted in Authentication Bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/graphql-authentication-bypass</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/graphql-authentication-bypass"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experienced security researchers explain how a GraphQL bug resulted in authentication bypass — and how to avoid it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haoxi Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction to GCPwn – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=25045</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/cloud-pentesting/introduction-to-gcpwn-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T17:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GCPwn is a python-based framework for pentesting GCP environments. While individual exploit scripts exist today for GCP attack vectors, GCPwn seeks to consolidate all these scripts and manage multiple sets of credentials at once (for example, multiple service account keys) all within one framework. With the use of interactive prompts, GCPwn makes enumeration and exploitation […]
The post An Introduction to GCPwn – Part 1 appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New storage features in Windows Server 2025: NVMe-OF initiator, update for S2D, deduplication for ReFS]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585265</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-storage-features-in-windows-server-2025-nvme-of-initiator-update-for-s2d-deduplication-for-refs/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T16:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the most notable updates in Windows Server 2025 center on Active Directory, Hyper-V, and SMB, the upcoming OS release also introduces substantial improvements to the storage subsystem. These features include improved NVMe support, an updated Storage Spaces Direct (S2D), and enhanced deduplication for ReFS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drop the Mic (CVE-2019-1166)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2967</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/drop-the-mic-cve20191166/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T01:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview CVE-2019-1166 (“Drop the MIC”) is a tampering vulnerability in Microsoft Windows, specifically targeting the NTLM (NT LAN Manager) authentication protocol. The vulnerability allows a man-in-the-middle attacker to bypass the NTLM Message Integrity Check (MIC) protection. By doing so, the attacker can tamper with the NTLM authentication process without invalidating the signature, which can lead […]
The post Drop the Mic (CVE-2019-1166) appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Cloud Integration Capability with Chariot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2966</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/chariot-amazon-cloud-integration-capability/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T01:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On March 22nd, 2019, CapitalOne experienced a data breach that resulted in the loss of more than 100 million credit card applications. This vulnerability resulted from a misconfigured web application firewall, which caused a server-side request forgery vulnerability. This issue then allowed an attacker to gain access to an AWS IAM role with access to […]
The post Amazon Cloud Integration Capability with Chariot appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adjacent Discovery Capability with Chariot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2963</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/adjacent-discovery-capability/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T00:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaining a comprehensive understanding of the external assets in an environment is essential for accurately mapping the attack surface of our clients. If you don’t know something exists, you can’t attack or defend it. Identifying these adjacent assets with various capabilities is crucial for assisting IT departments looking to map their public external attack surface […]
The post Adjacent Discovery Capability with Chariot appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from HackerOne’s First Recharge Week]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/lessons-hackerones-first-recharge-week</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/lessons-hackerones-first-recharge-week"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T20:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>debbie@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Docker Desktop 4.32: Compose File Viewer, integrated terminal, cloud backup, move data, and MSI installer]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585222</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-docker-desktop-432-compose-file-viewer-integrated-terminal-cloud-backup-move-data-and-msi-installer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T15:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, I discussed Air-Gapped Containers, Docker Build Cloud, GitHub Actions support, and ARM support in Docker Desktop 4.31. Docker Desktop 4.32 introduces several new features, including the Compose File Viewer, integrated terminal, cloud backup for Docker volumes, data storage move on macOS and Windows, and an MSI installer for enterprise deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the SANS Cloud Security Exchange 2024!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/join-the-sans-cloud-security-exchange-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/join-the-sans-cloud-security-exchange-2024?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about SANS Institute's 2024 Cloud Security Exchange Event featuring AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Softaculous Webuzo Authentication Bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2280</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2024/07/25/softaculous-webuzo-authentication-bypass/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-ce40b086 Softaculous Webuzo contains an authentication bypass vulnerability through the password reset functionality. Remote, anonymous attackers can exploit this vulnerability to gain full server access as the root user. Vulnerability Identifier Exodus Intelligence: EIP-ce40b086 MITRE: CVE-2024-24621 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:C/I:C/A:C CVSSv2 Score: 10.0 Vendor References https://webuzo.com/blog/webuzo-4-2-9-launched/ Discovery Credit Exodus Intelligence Disclosure Timeline Disclosed to ... Read more Softaculous Webuzo Authentication Bypass
The post Softaculous Webuzo Authentication Bypass appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Advisories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Softaculous Webuzo FTP Management Command Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2282</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2024/07/25/softaculous-webuzo-ftp-management-command-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-4ab5e9b4 Softaculous Webuzo contains a command injection vulnerability in the FTP management functionality. A remote, authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to gain code execution on the system. Vulnerability Identifier Exodus Intelligence: EIP-4ab5e9b4 MITRE: CVE-2024-24623 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:N/AC:L/Au:S/C:C/I:C/A:C CVSSv2 Score: 9.0 Vendor References https://webuzo.com/blog/webuzo-4-2-9-launched/ Discovery Credit Exodus Intelligence Disclosure Timeline Disclosed to vendor: ... Read more Softaculous Webuzo FTP Management Command Injection
The post Softaculous Webuzo FTP Management Command Injection appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Advisories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Softaculous Webuzo Password Reset Command Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2281</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2024/07/25/softaculous-webuzo-password-reset-command-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-92dd8e27 Softaculous Webuzo contains a command injection in the password reset functionality. A remote, authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to gain code execution on the system. Vulnerability Identifier Exodus Intelligence: EIP-92dd8e27 MITRE: CVE-2024-24622 Vulnerability Metrics CVSSv2 Vector: AV:N/AC:L/Au:S/C:C/I:C/A:C CVSSv2 Score: 9.0 Vendor References https://webuzo.com/blog/webuzo-4-2-9-launched/ Discovery Credit Exodus Intelligence Disclosure Timeline Disclosed to vendor: July ... Read more Softaculous Webuzo Password Reset Command Injection
The post Softaculous Webuzo Password Reset Command Injection appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Advisories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Vulnerabilities in the Deep Sea Electronics DSE855]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:66a29d011b47f430c2e9d98a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/25/multiple-vulnerabilities-in-the-deep-sea-electronics-dse855"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T18:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, Trend Micro’s ZDI has published multiple advisories concerning Deep Sea Electronics DSE855, a communications device that allows monitoring of a single DSE controller with USB connectivity over a wired network connection. This blog post looks at these reports in further detail. All the findings were made against DSE855 software version 1.1.0 (the latest available at the moment of writing) and hardware version 4.00. None of these bugs were patched within the standard ZDI 120-day timeframe and were published as 0-day advisories in June.
The DSE855
The DSE855 device presents itself as an unassuming black plastic box with several connection options on the front. The device is supposed to be mounted on a DIN rail, oriented vertically.
On the front, we have an RJ45 port, a small hole fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Janushkevich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[E-MailRelay: Free SMTP server for Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584921</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/e-mailrelay-free-smtp-server-for-windows/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T16:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announced the deprecation of the SMTP feature for Windows Server long ago and is now removing it in Windows Server 2025. E-MailRelay is a lightweight, open-source, and free SMTP server for Windows, also available for Linux. A lightweight, open-source alternative is E-MailRelay, a free SMTP server for Windows, also available for Linux. It supports standard security features and is compatible with basic clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Ready for the New NIST Control Around Public Disclosure Programs?]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-vdp-control</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/nist-vdp-control"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new NIST control requires SaaS vendors to “establish a public reporting channel for receiving reports of vulnerabilities in organizational systems and system components.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blake Entrekin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our crypto experts answer 10 key questions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107830</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/07/25/our-crypto-experts-answer-10-key-questions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Justin Jacob Cryptography is a fundamental part of electronics and the internet that helps secure credit cards, cell phones, web browsing (fingers crossed you’re using TLS!), and even top-secret military data. Cryptography is just as essential in the blockchain space, with blockchains like Ethereum depending on hashes, Merkle trees, and ECDSA signatures, among other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Colab AI: Data Leakage Through Image Rendering Fixed. Some Risks Remain.]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-colab-image-render-exfil/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/google-colab-image-render-exfil/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T05:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Colab AI, now just called Gemini in Colab, was vulnerable to data leakage via image rendering.
This is an older bug report, dating back to November 29, 2023. However, recent events prompted me to write this up:
 Google did not reward this finding, and Colab now automatically puts Notebook content (untrusted data) into the prompt.  Let’s explore the specifics.
Google Colab AI - Revealing the System Prompt At the end of November last year, I noticed that there was a “Colab AI” feature, which integrated an LLM to chat with and write code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIPAA and Pentesting: What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/security-compliance/hipaa-pentesting</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/security-compliance/hipaa-pentesting"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T21:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to maintain compliance with HIPAA security standards through pentesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne Pentest Delivery Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in WSL 2.3: Linux kernel 6.6, GUI settings app, easily move distributions]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585144</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/new-in-wsl-23-linux-kernel-66-gui-settings-app-easily-move-distributions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T18:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest update to Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) 2.3 introduces several new features, including built-in support for the Linux kernel 6.6, enhancing performance and compatibility. A new graphical user interface (GUI) app simplifies managing WSL settings, making configuration more user-friendly. In addition, WSL users can now easily move their Linux distributions to different storage locations with a straightforward command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack My Career: Meet Naz Bozdemir]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-naz-bozdemir</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/hack-my-career-meet-naz-bozdemir"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T17:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Briones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leave the World Behind, or don’t]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29267</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/leave-the-world-behind-or-dont/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T05:26:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I watched Leave the World Behind on Netflix recently. I was intrigued as the trailers showed an oil tanker crashing on to a beach. It was implied that it had […]
Leave the World Behind, or don’t first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Broken Authentication Control In GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2951</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/exploiting-broken-authentication-control-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T02:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview The implementation of GraphQL in enterprise systems has grown rapidly. A recent report from Gartner predicted that at least 50% of enterprises will be implementing GraphQL in their production environments by the end of the calendar year. With its increasing adoption, correctly accounting for the security of GraphQL APIs becomes increasingly pertinent.  Although the […]
The post Exploiting Broken Authentication Control In GraphQL appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursive Amplification Attacks: Botnet-as-a-Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2948</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/recursive-amplification-attacks-botnet-as-a-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T00:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction On a recent client engagement, we tested a startup’s up-and-coming SaaS data platform and discovered an alarming attack path. The specific feature names and technologies have been generalized to anonymize the platform. Like many data platforms, various source types could be configured to ingest data, such as third-party CRM or marketing services. The platform […]
The post Recursive Amplification Attacks: Botnet-as-a-Service appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom Inbox Enhancements: Revolutionizing Vulnerability Management for Enterprises]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/custom-inbox-enhancements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/custom-inbox-enhancements"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T21:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HackerOne's Custom Inboxes Enhancements provide flexible report segmentation, reduce administrative overhead, and mitigate security risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Pearson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Sea Phishing Pt. 1]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/092a0637e2fd</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/deep-sea-phishing-pt-1-092a0637e2fd?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T18:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bypass EDR With Custom Payloads]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Receive critical Microsoft security alerts by email]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585062</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/receive-critical-microsoft-security-alerts-by-email/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T13:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Security Response Center (MSRC) publishes updates on vulnerabilities in Microsoft products and services. This information is critical for administrators to address and mitigate security risks quickly. Administrators can now use the MSRC REST API without registration or an API key to automatically receive critical Microsoft security alerts via email.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become an OSINT Investigator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-an-osint-investigator</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-an-osint-investigator?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about how to become an OSINT Investigator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Security Principle Every Attacker Needs to Follow]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/905cc94ddfc6</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/the-security-principle-every-attacker-needs-to-follow-905cc94ddfc6?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T14:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, I was tasked with developing a follow-on course for our renowned Adversary Tactics: Red Team Operations course. The new…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elad Shamir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text embeddings in machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585097</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/text-embeddings-in-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T14:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An increasing number of organizations are deploying Large Language Models (LLMs) enhanced with text embeddings as it is the most efficient method to augment a model via Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG). As an IT pro, you should have a basic understanding of how text embeddings are generated in machine learning to represent and capture semantic meanings. These insights help you select and format the content to augment your AI provider's model. I assume you have read my previous post and have a basic understanding of neural networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Instruction Hierarchy in OpenAI's gpt-4o-mini]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-gpt-4o-mini-instruction-hierarchie-bypasses/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-gpt-4o-mini-instruction-hierarchie-bypasses/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T13:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, OpenAI announced gpt-4o-mini and there are some interesting updates, including safety improvements regarding “Instruction Hierarchy”:

OpenAI puts this in the light of “safety”, the word security is not mentioned in the announcement.
Additionally, this The Verge article titled “OpenAI’s latest model will block the ‘ignore all previous instructions’ loophole” created interesting discussions on X, including a first demo bypass.
I spent some time this weekend to get a better intuition about gpt-4o-mini model and instruction hierarchy, and the conclusion is that system instructions are still not a security boundary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Zero Trust Framework: Key Strategies for 2024 and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/building-a-zero-trust-framework-key-strategies-for-2024-and-beyond</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/building-a-zero-trust-framework-key-strategies-for-2024-and-beyond?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog summarizing SANS Institute's 2024 Zero Trust strategy guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shellcode: Modular Exponentiation for Diffie-Hellman Key Exchange.]]></title>
        <id>http://modexp.wordpress.com/?p=5446</id>
        <link href="https://modexp.wordpress.com/2024/07/21/modexp_key_xchg/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T22:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents Introduction Symmetric vs Asymmetric Encryption with RSA Digital Signatures with RSA History Diffie-Hellman Key Exchange Crypto API Binary Exponentiation Methods Arbitrary-precision Arithmetic Addition Subtraction Multiplication Division Exponentiation Modular Multiplicative Inverse Modular Addition Modular Multiplication Modular Exponentiation Counting … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>odzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing OpenSSH vulnerabilities CVE-2024-6387 and CVE-2024-6409]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1585031</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/addressing-openssh-vulnerabilities-cve-2024-6387-and-cve-2024-6409/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T17:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two related vulnerabilities have been identified in the OpenSSH server daemon: CVE-2024-6387 and CVE-2024-6409. Although challenging to exploit, these vulnerabilities could enable remote code execution on servers. This article explores the vulnerabilities, their triggers, and available remediations. OpenSSH implements the Secure Shell (SSH) protocol, utilizing a client-server setup to create secure connections between machines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategies for Training and Hiring in the US Government: A Black Rainbow Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/strategies-for-training-and-hiring-in-the-us-government-a-black-rainbow-case-study</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/strategies-for-training-and-hiring-in-the-us-government-a-black-rainbow-case-study?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about strategies for training and hiring in the US government, a Black Rainbow case study]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Podman on Ubuntu, pull and run container images, and push to Docker Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584808</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-podman-on-ubuntu-pull-and-run-container-images-and-push-to-docker-hub/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T20:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Podman is a powerful container management tool that offers a flexible and daemonless alternative to Docker. This beginner's guide walks you through installing Podman on Ubuntu and provides examples of how to pull and push container images to Docker Hub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mercy Bassey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capturing Exposed AWS Keys During Dynamic Web Application Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2898</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/capturing-exposed-aws-keys-during-dynamic-web-application-tests/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T19:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview We have recently identified several vulnerable HTTP requests that allow attackers to capture access keys and session tokens for a web application’s AWS infrastructure. Attackers could use these keys and tokens to access back-end IOT endpoints and CloudWatch instances to execute commands. This blog was developed to raise awareness on common design flaws in […]
The post Capturing Exposed AWS Keys During Dynamic Web Application Tests appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Pwn2Own Ireland – Bringing Pwn2Own (and WhatsApp) to the Emerald Isle]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:6696d7e61753e66be8f6cd0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/16/announcing-pwn2own-ireland-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here. 
 
Over the last few years, our consumer-focused Pwn2Own event took place in the Trend Micro office in Toronto. However, that office closed, so we needed to find a new home. This isn’t unusual for this event, as it moved from Amsterdam to Tokyo to Austin to Toronto. We’re moving again. This year, we are heading to our offices in Cork, Ireland! We’re excited about our new location, and I personally have viewed several locations for after-hours and special events. Some of those will be secret until the competition, but I can tell you that our awards ceremony and end-of-contest party will be held at the historic Cork City Goal. It promises to be a fun and spooky event, and we’ll have more details about that in the future.
Beyond our …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunting for Remote Management Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18188</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/07/18/hunting-for-remote-management-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T11:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital landscape, Remote Management and Monitoring (RMM) tools have become indispensable for organizations seeking to streamline IT operations, enhance productivity, and ensure seamless remote support. However, within our threat hunting and incident response engagements we often see that these tools, while beneficial, can also pose significant security risks if not properly managed. This … Continue reading Hunting for Remote Management Tools →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michel Coene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Offensive Security for Effective Post-Attack Recovery]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/offensive-security-for-post-attack-recovery</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/offensive-security-for-post-attack-recovery"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bishop Fox's CISO Christie Terrill and former VP of Consulting Tom Eston discuss leveraging offensive security strategies for effective post-attack recovery, providing practical steps for remediation and building long-term cyber resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bishop Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Installer, Exploiting Custom Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/07/18/custom-actions.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/07/18/custom-actions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a year ago, I published my research around the Windows Installer Service. The article explained in detail how the MSI repair process executes in an elevated context, but the lack of impersonation could lead to Arbitrary File Delete and similar issues. The issue was acknowledged by Microsoft (as CVE-2023-21800), but it was never directly fixed. Instead, the introduction of a Redirection Guard mitigated all symlink attacks in the context of the msiexec process. Back then, I wasn’t particularly happy with the solution, but I couldn’t find any bypass.
The Redirection Guard turned out to work exactly as intended, so I spent some time attacking the Windows Installer Service from other angles. Some bugs were found (CVE-2023-32016), but I always felt that the way Microsoft handled the imperso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unconstrained Delegation in Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2884</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/unconstrained-delegation-active-directory/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T19:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Unconstrained delegation is a feature in Active Directory that allows a computer, service, or user to impersonate any other user and access resources on their behalf across the entire network, completely unrestricted. A typical example of a use case for unconstrained delegation is when certain services require access to another server or back-end database. […]
The post Unconstrained Delegation in Active Directory appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UniGetUI (formerly WingetUI): GUI for winget, Chocolatey, and PowerShell Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584876</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/unigetui-formerly-wingetui-gui-for-winget-chocolatey-and-powershell-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UniGetUI, previously known as WingetUI, is a free GUI tool that lets you easily install and update software packages from various sources, such as Winget, Chocolatey, and PowerShell Gallery. Let me show you UniGetUI's features and how it can help you quickly set up a new computer with all the essential software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leos Marek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HackerOne Organizes a Remote Hack Week]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/how-hackerone-organizes-remote-hack-week</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/how-hackerone-organizes-remote-hack-week"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Cotton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIN7 Reboot | Cybercrime Gang Enhances Ops with New EDR Bypasses and Automated Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=100781</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/fin7-reboot-cybercrime-gang-enhances-ops-with-new-edr-bypasses-and-automated-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This research explores how FIN7 has adopted automated attack methods and developed defense evasion techniques previously unseen in the wild.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Cocomazzi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Cloud Threat Detection with Cutting-Edge Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/master-cloud-threat-detection-with-cutting-edge-techniques</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/master-cloud-threat-detection-with-cutting-edge-techniques?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the newly update SANS SEC541: Cloud Security Threat Detection course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How SOAR Transforms Security Operations: A Real-World Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-soar-transforms-security-operations-a-real-world-case-study</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-soar-transforms-security-operations-a-real-world-case-study?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about using SOAR to transform an organization's cybersecurity culture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install AWS CloudShell in a VPC]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584911</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-aws-cloudshell-in-a-vpc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T15:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, AWS announced the general availability of CloudShell VPC support. This feature enables the creation of a CloudShell environment within a dedicated VPC, establishing secure connections to other resources in the same subnet. The CloudShell inherits the VPC network configuration without any additional modification. In this article, I will introduce CloudShell, explain the new VPC support, and outline how to install AWS CloudShell in a VPC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Essam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phish Out of Water]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/aaeb677a5af3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/phish-out-of-water-aaeb677a5af3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T14:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing Web Proxies so Your Phish Don’t Suffocate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting a Generative AI Chatbot – Prompt Injection to Remote Code Execution (RCE)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=24924</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical-blog/ai-ml-pentesting/how-to-exploit-a-generative-ai-chatbot-using-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how NetSPI exploits an externally exposed Generative AI Chatbot to compromise the hosting server.
The post Exploiting a Generative AI Chatbot – Prompt Injection to Remote Code Execution (RCE) appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Murrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NullBulge | Threat Actor Masquerades as Hacktivist Group Rebelling Against AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=100985</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/nullbulge-threat-actor-masquerades-as-hacktivist-group-rebelling-against-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actors are masquerading as hacktivists targeting AI-centric communities with commodity malware and customized LockBit payloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Punch Card Hacking – Exploring a Mainframe Attack Vector]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=18085</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2024/07/16/punch-card-hacking-exploring-a-mainframe-attack-vector/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mainframes are the unseen workhorses that carry the load for many services we use on a daily basis: Withdrawing money from an ATM, credit card payments, and airline reservations to name just a few of the high volume workloads that are primarily handled by mainframes. For those that like to see figures to support this … Continue reading Punch Card Hacking – Exploring a Mainframe Attack Vector →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons Learned on the Impact of Training on Hiring Success: A Mastercard Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/lessons-learned-on-the-impact-of-training-on-hiring-success-a-mastercard-use-case</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/lessons-learned-on-the-impact-of-training-on-hiring-success-a-mastercard-use-case?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog on the impact of training on Mastercard's hiring success]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing Successful Cybersecurity Maturity Models: A Microsoft Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/developing-successful-cybersecurity-maturity-models-a-microsoft-use-case</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/developing-successful-cybersecurity-maturity-models-a-microsoft-use-case?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about developing successful cybersecurity maturity models at Microsoft, a use case]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a SOC Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-a-soc-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/how-to-become-a-soc-analyst?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the role of a Security Operations Center (SOC) Analyst, including essential skills, daily activities, career growth, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authenticator backup: Microsoft, Google, Amazon, Authy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584861</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/authenticator-backup-microsoft-google-amazon-authy/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T18:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cloud providers such as Microsoft, Amazon, and Google, as well as popular services like Authy, offer multi-factor authentication (MFA), which provides superior protection against digital identity theft compared to using just a password. However, the enhanced security of an account can backfire if you lose access to your authenticator app. To prepare for this situation, take several precautions, like creating authenticator backups and syncing account tokens across your devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Years of the GitHub Security Bug Bounty Program]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/10-years-github-security-bug-bounty-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/10-years-github-security-bug-bounty-program"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T17:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 years of GitHub's bug bounty program! Learn insights into bug bounty growth from a top program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythic 3.3 Beta: Rise of the Events]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6aeb84aa6fed</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/mythic-3-3-beta-rise-of-the-events-6aeb84aa6fed?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T16:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A brief overview of Mythic 3.3’s new features]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cody Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncoordinated Vulnerability Disclosure: The Continuing Issues with CVD]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:669192f22870db53b1bcdabc</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/15/uncoordinated-vulnerability-disclosure-the-continuing-issues-with-cvd"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T14:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On patch Tuesday last week, Microsoft released an update for CVE-2024-38112, which they said was being exploited in the wild. We at the Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) agree with them because that’s what we told them back in May when we detected this exploit in the wild and reported it to Microsoft. However, you may notice that no one from Trend or ZDI was acknowledged by Microsoft. This case has become a microcosm of the problems with coordinated vulnerability disclosure (CVD) as vendors push for coordinated disclosure from researchers but rarely practice any coordination regarding the fix. This lack of transparency from vendors often leaves researchers who practice CVD with more questions than answers.
If you’re just interested in the technical details of the bugs we discovered in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending Against SCATTERED SPIDER and The Com with Cybercrime Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/defending-against-scattered-spider-and-the-com-with-cybercrime-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/defending-against-scattered-spider-and-the-com-with-cybercrime-intelligence?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about cybercrime intelligence and tracking threat groups like SCATTERED SPIDER and The Com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Fidelity detections are Low Fidelity detections, until proven otherwise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9279</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/07/14/high-fidelity-detections-are-low-fidelity-detections-until-proven-otherwise/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T00:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago Nas kicked off an interesting discussion on Xitter about detections’ quality. I liked it, so I offered my personal insight. I then added a stupid example to illustrate my point to which DylanInfosec replied: Would love … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: cut-bytes.py Version 0.0.17]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10533</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/07/13/update-cut-bytes-py-version-0-0-17/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T15:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[–prefix and –suffix can now also be filenames. cut-bytes_V0_0_17.zip (http)MD5: 86D0692C6303248639A740E7A2AC4525SHA256: D4FCFBD2305D7E5E97AB993741DF95B4565A882B0CD7DBA061D09578A1DDADA7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd v256: New features of the Linux service manager]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584819</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/systemd-v256-new-features-of-the-linux-service-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T15:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd is a system and service manager for Linux that initializes the system, manages services, and controls what programs run at startup. This article introduces Systemd v256, released last month, highlighting new features and improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Afenyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing AES-GEM (AES with Galois Extended Mode)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107802</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/07/12/announcing-aes-gem-aes-with-galois-extended-mode/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Scott Arciszewski Today, AES-GCM is one of two cipher modes used by TLS 1.3 (the other being ChaCha20-Poly1305) and the preferred method for encrypting data in FIPS-validated modules. But despite its overwhelming success, AES-GCM has been the root cause of some catastrophic failures: for example, Hanno Böck and Sean Devlin exploited nonce misuse to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Cybersecurity Hiring Challenges: Insights from Leidos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/addressing-cybersecurity-hiring-challenges-insights-from-leidos</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/addressing-cybersecurity-hiring-challenges-insights-from-leidos?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog summarizing how Leidos addressed cybersecurtiy hiring challenges]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: oledump.py Version 0.0.77]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10526</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/07/11/update-oledump-py-version-0-0-77/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T19:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an update for plugin plugin_biff.py. Protected xls files (workbook protection, sheet protection) are protected with a password, but are not encrypted. The password is hashed to a 16-bit hash called verifier, such a short hash gives ample opportunity for hash collisions. I calculated passwords for all possible hash values (32768, or 0x8000) mostly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feedback-Driven Interviewing at HackerOne]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/feedback-driven-interviewing-hackerone</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/culture-and-talent/feedback-driven-interviewing-hackerone"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how HackerOne hones its hiring process through structured interviewing, drawing invaluable lessons from candidate feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>debbie@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What HackerOne Customers Say About the Problems Hackers Solve]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/customer-stories/hackers-solve-problems</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/customer-stories/hackers-solve-problems"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T16:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why organizations work with ethical hackers, like preventing breaches, meeting regulatory compliance, and helping the security budget.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search and delete Copilot data in Microsoft 365]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584695</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/search-and-delete-copilot-data-in-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing and deleting unnecessary Copilot data from Microsoft 365 is essential for reducing security risks and ensuring compliance with data protection laws like GDPR and HIPAA. This blog post will guide you through the steps to search for and delete Copilot data using eDiscovery, Graph Explorer, and PowerShell. Following these steps can enhance data hygiene and safeguard your organization against potential data breaches and legal issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vignesh Mudliar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Race to the Bottom - Database Transactions Undermining Your AppSec]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/07/11/database-race-conditions.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com/2024/07/11/database-race-conditions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Databases are a crucial part of any modern application. Like any external dependency, they introduce additional complexity for the developers building an application. In the real world, however, they are usually considered and used as a black box which provides storage functionality.
This post aims shed light on a particular aspect of the complexity databases introduce which is often overlooked by developers, namely concurrency control. The best way to do that is to start off by looking at a fairly common code pattern we at Doyensec see in our day-to-day work:

func (db *Db) Transfer(source int, destination int, amount int) error {
  ctx := context.Background()

  conn, err := pgx.Connect(ctx, db.databaseUrl)
  defer conn.Close(ctx)

  // (1)
  tx, err := conn.BeginTx(ctx)

  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neural networks basics for IT pros]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584737</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/neural-networks-basics-for-it-pros/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T17:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT professionals need a fundamental understanding of neural networks to make informed decisions about deploying customized Large Language Models (LLMs). Understanding the basics of machine learning is essential for predicting the performance of a fine-tuned model and determining whether to work with Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) and embeddings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentesting for Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/web-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/web-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn testing methodologies, common vulnerabilities, and best practices for pentesting web applications with PTaaS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HackerOne Pentest Delivery Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unity Across Continents: Building Culture in a Remote Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2837</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/unity-across-continents-building-culture-remote-startup/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s dynamic world, where the boundaries of geography and time zones blur, fostering a cohesive company culture and unity becomes paramount. At Praetorian, we take immense pride in being a remote-first startup that spans across 11 countries, with the exciting addition of a 12th in just a few months. Our global footprint is not […]
The post Unity Across Continents: Building Culture in a Remote Startup appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutionalizing a Strong Security Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/institutionalizing-a-strong-security-culture</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/institutionalizing-a-strong-security-culture?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog about the new major update of the SANS LDR521 course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The July 2024 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:668d6a7d7c32144b1aede0ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2024/7/9/the-july-2024-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T17:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re just past the halfway point of 2024, and as expected, Microsoft and Adobe have released their regularly scheduled updates. Take a break from your regular activities and join us as we review the details of their latest security alerts. If you’d rather watch the full video recap covering the entire release, you can check it out here:
Adobe Patches for July 2024
For July, Adobe released three patches addressing seven CVEs in Adobe Premiere Pro, InDesign, and Adobe Bridge. The patch for InDesign is the largest, fixing four Critical-rated CVEs. All four could lead to arbitrary code execution. The fix for Premiere Pro fixes a single CVE that could lead to arbitrary code execution. Finally, the fix for Bridge fixes one Critical rated and one Important rated bug. The Critical-rated bug could…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delegated Managed Service Accounts in Windows Server 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584665</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/delegated-managed-service-accounts-in-windows-server-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server 2025 introduces the delegated Managed Service Account (dMSA) feature to address security concerns of regular service accounts. This blog post provides an overview of dMSA, explaining its functionality and offering guidance on its setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drink Like a Phish]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b9e91d0b5677</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/drink-like-a-phish-b9e91d0b5677?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T14:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Phishing Sites Blend In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Kasler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fickle PDFs: exploiting browser rendering discrepancies]]></title>
        <id>fickle-pdfs-exploiting-browser-rendering-discrepancies</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/fickle-pdfs-exploiting-browser-rendering-discrepancies"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine the CEO of a random company receives an email containing a PDF invoice file. In Safari and MacOS Preview, the total price displayed is £399. After approval, the invoice is sent to the accounti]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits named a leader in cybersecurity consulting services]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107783</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/07/09/trail-of-bits-named-a-leader-in-cybersecurity-consulting-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T11:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits has been recognized as a leader in cybersecurity consulting services according to The Forrester Wave™: Cybersecurity Consulting Services, Q2 2024. In this evaluation, we were compared against 14 other top vendors and emerged as a leader for our services. Read the report on our website. What is the Forrester Wave™? Forrester is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, ChatGPT Is Under Maintenance: Persistent Denial of Service through Prompt Injection and Memory Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-persistent-denial-of-service/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2024/chatgpt-persistent-denial-of-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T21:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you visit a website with ChatGPT, and suddenly, it stops working entirely!
In this post we show how an attacker can use prompt injection to cause a persistent denial of service that lasts across chat sessions for a user.
Hacking Memories Previously we discussed how ChatGPT is vulnerable to automatic tool invocation of the memory tool. This can be used by an attacker during prompt injection to ingest malicious or fake memories into your ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DORA: What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/penetration-testing/dora</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/penetration-testing/dora"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about DORA, the new EU regulation for digital operational resilience, and how to meet the requirements with pentesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayla Underkoffler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam Agent for Windows: backup job failed with VSS error 0x80042306]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584637</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/veeam-agent-for-windows-backup-job-failed-with-vss-error-0x80042306/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam Agent for Windows is a backup software for workstations and servers, and it is also available in a free edition. Like most backup programs, it creates snapshots using the Volume Shadow Copy Service (VSS), which it then backs up. However, this process can fail for various reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pen testing cruise ships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=29219</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/pen-testing-cruise-ships/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New build ships contracted for build from 1st July 2024 must comply with IACS UR E26 & 27. What does this mean for assessing the cyber security of a cruise […]
Pen testing cruise ships first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Tierney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Threat Exposure Management for Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2814</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/continuous-threat-exposure-management-for-google-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T19:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 9th, 2020, an independent security firm discovered a trove of personal health information belonging to Pfizer patients on the public internet. The breach exposed unencrypted conversations between patients and providers of four different Pfizer products, including full names, home addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, and medical status details. The entry point of this […]
The post Continuous Threat Exposure Management for Google Cloud appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a Frida-based VBS API monitor, Take two]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9292</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/07/07/writing-a-frida-based-vbs-api-monitor-take-two/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T18:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post I introduced a simple VBS API Monitor developed using Frida framework. Today I did some more code analysis of vbscript.dll and I realized that in my previous post I made a naive assumption that arguments are … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a Frida-based VBS API monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=9282</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2024/07/07/writing-a-frida-based-vbs-api-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T00:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love experimenting with Frida and I have presented a few different API Monitoring prototypes based on this framework a few times before… Today I will demonstrate how to write a quick & dirty VBS/VBScript (Visual Basic Script) API Monitor. … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: hash.py Version 0.0.13]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10521</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/07/07/update-hash-py-version-0-0-13/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a bugfix release for @files. hash_V0_0_13.zip (http)MD5: 43419BBB95FC1321EC6098AE369DEC26SHA256: 88BD3A7B71BB2C8579F49E76E8069E7A5A4B23DCF1DB1716E5E2C9F78BFF6D5B]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attack Surface Management: A Free Enablement Technology for Effective Continuous Threat Exposure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=2806</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/attack-surface-management-free-enablement-technology-continuous-threat-exposure-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T19:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As digital landscapes continue to evolve daily, organizations are increasingly aware and focused on their attack surfaces to identify and mitigate potential risks. However, a troubling trend has emerged: companies are often compelled to pay bug hunters for exploiting vulnerabilities based on surface-level discoveries. At Praetorian, we challenge this norm by offering a free version […]
The post Attack Surface Management: A Free Enablement Technology for Effective Continuous Threat Exposure Management appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in June]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10519</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2024/07/06/overview-of-content-published-in-june-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T08:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in June: Blog posts: Update: file-magic.py Version 0.0.8 Update: hash.py Version 0.0.12 Update: myjson-filter.py version 0.0.6 Update: strings.py Version 0.0.9 Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.30 Update: count.py Version 0.3.2 Update: simple_listener.py Version 0.1.5 Update: what-is-new.py Version 0.0.4 Update: FileScanner Version 0.0.0.9 Update: pdf-parser.py Version 0.7.9 Update: base64dump.py version […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List groups in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1584487</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/list-groups-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, I explained how to create and manage groups in Linux. Today, I will explore the various ways to list groups in Linux. The /etc/group and /etc/passwd files offer insights into user accounts and their primary groups. Commands like groups, id, compgen, and getent group are valuable tools for querying group information for specific users, listing all groups, and including network services in the group listings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Pietroforte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing the Ask Astro LLM Q&A app]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=107755</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/07/05/auditing-the-ask-astro-llm-qa-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we present the second of our open-source AI security audits: a look at security issues we found in an open-source retrieval augmented generation (RAG) application that could lead to chatbot output poisoning, inaccurate document ingestion, and potential denial of service. This audit follows up on our previous work that identified 11 security vulnerabilities in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side-by-Side with HelloJackHunter: Unveiling the Mysteries of WinSxS]]></title>
        <id>65f5ceb78792421d3c2272e4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.zsec.uk/hellojackhunter-exploring-winsxs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T09:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores Windows Side-by-Side (WinSxS) and DLL hijacking, deep-diving some tooling I've written and some of the fun along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Gill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>