<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-23T00:44:23.047Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stephenbradshaw.github.io/offsecfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 Cloud Log Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/microsoft-365-cloud-log-extraction</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/microsoft-365-cloud-log-extraction?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we discussed the various methods of accessing and exporting the Unified Audit Log (UAL). If you need a way to perform a quick and targeted search, you can leverage the Purview Compliance Portal. If you want to retrieve a small part of the UAL and export to JSON format, PowerShell has the Search-UnifiedAuditLog cmdlet. For larger organizations or those who need to continuously poll the UAL, there is the Microsoft 365 Management API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix ADC Gateway RCE: CVE-2023-3519 is Exploitable, and 53% of Servers Are Unpatched]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/citrix-adc-gateway-rce-cve-2023-3519</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/citrix-adc-gateway-rce-cve-2023-3519"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T17:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bishop Fox developed an exploit for CVE-2023-3519, a stack overflow in Citrix ADC Gateway that allows remote code execution. There are 61,000 affected appliances exposed on the internet, and roughly 53% of them are currently unpatched.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Team X</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Git Bash on Windows with git command examples]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572693</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-git-bash-on-windows-with-git-command-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T16:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system used by developers to collaborate and manage changes in their applications. It was created for Linux and macOS. But what about Windows? This is where Git Bash for Windows comes in. This tutorial will explain how to install Git Bash on Windows and introduce a few Git Bash commands to interact with the Git repository.
Install Git Bash on Windows with git command examples first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Jethva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Tic Tac Toe with 170mb of HTML - no JS or CSS]]></title>
        <id>tic-tac-toe-in-html</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/tic-tac-toe-in-html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it when Chrome releases a new feature, I especially like it when it is experimental. In this post I'm going to show you how I created Tic Tac Toe (Noughts and crosses) with HTML, using one of t]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzing on-chain contracts with Echidna]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104755</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/21/fuzzing-on-chain-contracts-with-echidna/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T11:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Guillermo Larregay and Elvis Skozdopolj With the release of version 2.1.0 of Echidna, our fuzzing tool for Ethereum smart contracts, we’ve introduced new features for direct retrieval of on-chain data, such as contract code and storage slot values. This data can be used to fuzz deployed contracts in their on-chain state or to test […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Media Exploitation Analyst (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-media-exploitation-analyst-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-media-exploitation-analyst-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[メディアエクスプロイテーションアナリストの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Ansible on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572625</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-ansible-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T19:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible is an open-source configuration management platform from Red Hat. So isn't Ansible a Linux-only solution? While it is indeed primarily for Linux configuration management, you can, in fact, install Ansible on Windows.
Install Ansible on Windows first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shifting boundaries: Exploiting an Integer Overflow in Apple Safari]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.exodusintel.com/?p=2144</id>
        <link href="https://blog.exodusintel.com/2023/07/20/shifting-boundaries-exploiting-an-integer-overflow-in-apple-safari/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vignesh Rao Overview In this blog post, we describe a method to exploit an integer overflow in Apple WebKit due to a vulnerability resulting from incorrect range computations when optimizing Javascript code. This research was conducted along with Martin Saar in 2020. We show how to convert this integer overflow into a stable out-of-bounds ... Read more Shifting boundaries: Exploiting an Integer Overflow in Apple Safari
The post Shifting boundaries: Exploiting an Integer Overflow in Apple Safari appeared first on Exodus Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exodus Intel VRT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-36934: Progress Software MOVEit Transfer SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64b84d887cb6720b78392146</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/7/19/cve-2023-36934-progress-software-moveit-transfer-sql-injection-remote-code-execution-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Guy Lederfein and Lucas Miller of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in Progress MOVEit Transfer. This bug was originally discovered by Trend Micro Vulnerability Researcher Guy Lederfein and is the same type of vulnerability being used by the Cl0p ransomware gang to exfiltrate data. A crafted request can trigger the execution of SQL queries composed from a user-supplied string. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the “moveitsvc” user. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2023-36934, with a few minimal modifications.
An SQL injection vulnerability has been reported for Progress MOVEit Tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trend Micro Research Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing jsluice: A Technial Deep-Dive for JavaScript Gold (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-technical-deep-dive</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-technical-deep-dive"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for a technical deep-dive of jsluice, an open-source mining tool for JavaScript code and files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing jsluice: The Why Behind JavaScript Gold Mining (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-gold-mining</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/jsluice-javascript-gold-mining"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use jsluice, an open-source, Go package and command-line tool used to extract information from JavaScript files and code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JumpCloud Intrusion | Attacker Infrastructure Links Compromise to North Korean APT Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=82769</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/jumpcloud-intrusion-attacker-infrastructure-links-compromise-to-north-korean-apt-activity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T10:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean state sponsored APT is behind a new supply chain attack on zero-trust directory platform JumpCloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Hegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SOC Toolbox: Analyzing AutoHotKey compiled executables]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=14236</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/07/20/the-soc-toolbox-analyzing-autohotkey-compiled-executables/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A quick post on how to extract AutoHotKey scripts from an AutoHotKey script compiled executable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Dhaeyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SecureAuth Identity Platform 23.07 Release Provides Streamlined Migration and Improved User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=48975</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/secureauth-identity-platform-23-07-release-provides-streamlined-migration-and-improved-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of the SecureAuth® Identity Platform version 23.07. The feature-rich release focuses on two major benefits: streamlined migration and improved user experience. Streamlined Migration / Upgrades  Since the creation of the Migration Tool, several customers have realized huge success in significantly reducing migration time and effort. Whether […]
The post SecureAuth Identity Platform 23.07 Release Provides Streamlined Migration and Improved User Experience appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect to Exchange Online with PowerShell and certificate-based authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572600</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/connect-to-exchange-online-with-powershell-and-certificate-based-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting to Exchange Online with PowerShell to automate tasks was made slightly more challenging when Microsoft discontinued basic authentication for Microsoft 365 tenants, making certificate-based authentication mandatory.
Connect to Exchange Online with PowerShell and certificate-based authentication first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pearman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cobalt Strike and Outflank Security Tooling: Friends in Evasive Places]]></title>
        <id>https://outflank.nl/?p=2948</id>
        <link href="https://outflank.nl/blog/2023/07/19/cobalt-strike-and-outflank-security-tooling-friends-in-evasive-places/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a joint blog written by the Cobalt Strike and Outflank teams. It is also available on the Cobalt Strike site.
Over the past few months there has been increasing collaboration and knowledge sharing internally between the Cobalt Strike and Outflank R&D teams. We are excited about the innovation opportunities made possible by this teamwork and have decided to align Cobalt Strike and Outflank Security Tooling (OST) closely going forward. Although we are actively collaborating, Cobalt Strike will continue to be the industry standard Command & Control (C2) framework, while OST will continue to offer a red team toolbox for all environments containing custom tradecraft that is OPSEC safe, evasive by design, and simple to use. Our vision is that Cobalt Strike and OST together will provide the best red team offering on the planet. 
Tags: announcements, c2, cobalt strike, developments, integrations, red team, yara
Read full post
The post Cobalt Strike and Outflank Security Tooling: Friends in Evasive Places appeared first on Outflank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pieter Ceelen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposed Gits: 10 Years on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27270</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/exposed-gits-10-years-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T05:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 10 years ago my colleague wrote a cracking post on exposed Git repositories. 10 years is a long time in cyber security, but you’d be surprised how many things […]
Exposed Gits: 10 Years on first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Parkes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trail of Bits’s Response to OSTP National Priorities for AI RFI]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104728</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/18/trail-of-bitss-response-to-ostp-national-priorities-for-ai-rfi/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Michael Brown and Heidy Khlaaf The Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP) has circulated a request for information (RFI) on how best to develop policies that support the responsible development of AI while minimizing risk to rights, safety, and national security. In our response, we highlight the following points: To ensure that AI […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Takeaways from Ohio Secretary of State's VDP Success Story]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-disclosure/five-takeaways-ohio-secretary-states-vdp-success-story</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-disclosure/five-takeaways-ohio-secretary-states-vdp-success-story"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Cybersecurity is on everyone’s radar, but not everyone knows all the specific details to ensure protection. We know bad actors are constantly looking for cracks in our defenses and applications. That's why it's so important for us to work with ethical hackers. They know what vulnerabilities the bad actors are looking for, and they know how to find them before the bad guys can."
- Jillian Burner, CISO, Ohio Secretary of State]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Raffa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Should Never Sleep: Adopting Continuous Testing for Evolving Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/adopting-continuous-testing-evolving-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/vulnerability-management/adopting-continuous-testing-evolving-threats"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compounding security debt from daily new releases creates serious challenges for security organizations — especially considering the scarcity of skilled personnel. Point-in-time security measures and an overreliance on automation and AI create a false sense of security that often leaves the door open for attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Coletta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Offensive Security: 2023 Insights From the Ponemon Institute]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-offensive-security-ponemon-institute</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-offensive-security-ponemon-institute"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we explore how offensive security solutions are implemented by mature organizations to proactively protect cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Offensive Security: 2023 Insights From the Ponemon Institute]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-offensive-security-2023-insights-from-the-ponemon-institute</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cloud-offensive-security-2023-insights-from-the-ponemon-institute"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we explore how offensive security solutions are implemented by mature organizations to proactively protect cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows file auditing and ransomware protection with PA File Sight]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572577</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/windows-file-auditing-and-ransomware-protection-with-pa-file-sight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T14:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An in-depth look at PA File Sight's Windows file auditing and ransomware protection features, their importance, and their role in enterprise security.
Windows file auditing and ransomware protection with PA File Sight first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlining Websocket Pentesting with wsrepl]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/07/18/streamlining-websocket-pentesting-with-wsrepl.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.doyensec.com//2023/07/18/streamlining-websocket-pentesting-with-wsrepl.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era defined by instant gratification, where life zips by quicker than a teenager’s TikTok scroll, WebSockets have evolved into the heartbeat of web applications. They’re the unsung heroes in data streaming and bilateral communication, serving up everything in real-time, because apparently, waiting is so last century.
However, when tasked with pentesting these WebSockets, it feels like you’re juggling flaming torches on a unicycle, atop a tightrope! Existing tools, while proficient in their specific realms, are much like mismatched puzzle pieces – they don’t quite fit together, leaving you to bridge the gaps. Consequently, you find yourself shifting from one tool to another, trying to manage them simultaneously and wishing for a more streamlined approach.
That’s where https://github.c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doyensec's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install winget on Windows Server and activate preview features]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572557</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/install-winget-on-windows-server-and-activate-preview-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's latest package manager is included in Windows 10 and 11. However, if you want to use winget on Windows Server or try a preview version, you will need to install it manually. In prerelease versions, you can enable experimental features.
Install winget on Windows Server and activate preview features first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CS2BR pt. II – One tool to port them all]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nviso.eu/?p=14094</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nviso.eu/2023/07/17/introducing-cs2br-pt-ii-one-tool-to-port-them-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In the previous post of this series we showed why Brute Ratel C4 (BRC4) isn’t able to execute most BOFs that use the de-facto BOF API standard by Cobalt Strike (CS): BRC4 implements their own BOF API which isn’t compatible with the CS BOF API. Then we also outlined an approach to solve this … Continue reading Introducing CS2BR pt. II – One tool to port them all →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burp Suite roadmap update: July 2023]]></title>
        <id>burp-suite-roadmap-update-july-2023</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/burp-suite-roadmap-update-july-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T14:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out our roadmap for Burp Suite and find out what exciting features are coming your way over the next 12 months. Burp Suite Professional Added to the roadmap Added BChecks - testing tool - When c]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.27]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10088</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/07/16/update-zipdump-py-version-0-0-27/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T08:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a bug fix release. zipdump_v0_0_27.zip (http)MD5: 91A26333FB6E2FF23A37462B5031A62FSHA256: 99E628622C5D3F3AD957C7A41264850A4FA267E46DE8F8E1AF61C684774C0850]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Content Published in June]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.didierstevens.com/?p=10086</id>
        <link href="https://blog.didierstevens.com/2023/07/16/overview-of-content-published-in-june-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T07:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an overview of content I published in June: Blog posts: Update: zipdump.py Version 0.0.26 SANS ISC Diary entries: Deobfuscating a VBS Script With Custom Encoding Brute-Force ZIP Password Cracking with zipdump.py]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Log Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/azure-log-extraction</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/azure-log-extraction?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we discussed the various methods for accessing and exporting Tenant and Subscription logs from Microsoft Azure. The quickest and simplest method, most useful for reviewing logs from within a recent time frame, is to access them via the Azure Portal directly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to start your own threat intel company?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8630</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/07/14/how-to-start-your-own-threat-intel-company/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered where all the threat intel feeds come from? How do these companies know that this, or that email account has been compromised? How do they identify […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade Proxmox VE 7 to 8]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572540</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/upgrade-proxmox-ve-7-to-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new version of Proxmox Virtualization Environment (VE) was released soon after the release of Debian 12 (Bookworm). Since this is a major upgrade, there are many improvements and new features. In this post, you will learn how to perform an in-place upgrade of Proxmox VE 7 to 8.
Upgrade Proxmox VE 7 to 8 first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image to Prompt Injection with Google Bard]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-bard-image-to-prompt-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-bard-image-to-prompt-injection/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prompt injection scenario that I, and others, have been wondering about in the past, is the potential risk associated with chatbots being able to analyze images.
Could this ability open up the way for Indirect Prompt Injection attacks?
Recently, Google added the ability to uploading and analyze images with Bard. And it turns out that it is indeed possible to add instructions to an image, and have the Bard follow those instructions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAMActionHunter: Query AWS IAM permission policies with ease]]></title>
        <id>https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/?p=24665</id>
        <link href="https://rhinosecuritylabs.com/aws/iamactionhunter-aws-iam-permissions/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post IAMActionHunter: Query AWS IAM permission policies with ease appeared first on Rhino Security Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yesland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluating blockchain security maturity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104716</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/14/evaluating-blockchain-security-maturity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T07:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Josselin Feist, Blockchain Engineering Director Holistic security reviews should reveal far more than simple bugs. Often, these bugs indicate deeper issues that can be challenging to understand and address. Given the time-boxed nature of reviews, security engineers may not have the opportunity to identify all bugs caused by these problems—and they may continue to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Guido</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: DevSecOps Engineer (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-devsecops-engineer-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-devsecops-engineer-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps エンジニアの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enter Sandbox 27: Account creation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/?p=8576</id>
        <link href="https://www.hexacorn.com/blog/2023/07/13/enter-sandbox-27-account-creation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T23:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been nearly 4 years since I published my last article in this series providing the community with a large corpora of sandbox reports (apilog_2019-07-14). One of the less known […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure password managers in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox using Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572526</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/configure-password-managers-in-chrome-edge-and-firefox-using-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T20:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All modern web browsers offer password managers that allow users to save website login credentials and automatically fill them in during subsequent logins. However, in professional environments, this can be undesirable for security reasons. Chrome, Edge, and Firefox provide Group Policy settings to mitigate or disable this feature.
Configure password managers in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox using Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SOHO Smashup Returns for Pwn2Own Toronto 2023]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64aee827e4a1b75c6a9bf846</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/7/12/the-soho-smashup-returns-for-pwn2own-toronto-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T15:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to read the rules, you can find them here. 
Our consumer-focus Pwn2Own event return to Toronto for 2023. The contest will be held at the Trend Micro office in Toronto on October 24-27. We had a great event last year, and we’re looking forward to another exciting contest. One of the things that made it so great was having so many of the competitors hanging out all day. We had so many fantastic discussions with talented researchers, and in-person attendance was key to that experience. While we are still allowing remote participation, we’ll be reimbursing up to $3,000 for travel expenses for former Pwn2Own winners that choose to come to Toronto to participate. We also will be able to host a limited audience for those who wish to attend and observe the contest, so look out for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Gorenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Scraping Part 2: Implementing Protections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=30563</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/adversary-simulation/anti-scraping-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing anti-scraping principles can deter scrapers by making it too difficult for them to bypass an application’s protections.
The post Anti-Scraping Part 2: Implementing Protections appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Dunn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudy With a Chance of Credentials | AWS-Targeting Cred Stealer Expands to Azure, GCP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=82546</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/cloudy-with-a-chance-of-credentials-aws-targeting-cred-stealer-expands-to-azure-gcp/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T12:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud credentials stealing campaign expands to target Azure and Google Cloud via unpatched web app vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Delamotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure, at the FREE SANS Cloud Security Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/join-aws-google-cloud-and-microsoft-azure-at-the-free-sans-cloud-security-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/join-aws-google-cloud-and-microsoft-azure-at-the-free-sans-cloud-security-exchange?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This FREE SANS Cloud Security Exchange is the can’t-miss Cloud security event of the year!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs AI Features: Vulnerabilities and Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-docs-ai-scam/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/google-docs-ai-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T21:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs is a popular word processing tool that is used by millions of people around the world. Recently Google added new AI features to Docs (and a couple of other products), such as the ability to generate summaries, and write different kinds of creative content.
Check out Google Labs for more info.
These features can be very helpful, but they also introduce new security risks.
At the moment there are not too many degress of freedom an adversary has, but operating your AI on untrusted data can have unwanted consequences:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kubeadm: Easily create a Kubernetes cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572510</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubeadm-easily-create-a-kubernetes-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Create Kubernetes clusters using kubeadm with this in-depth guide, exploring essential commands, the process of initializing the control plane, adding worker nodes, and performing lifecycle management.
kubeadm: Easily create a Kubernetes cluster first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI and Security: HackerOne's Predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/thought-leadership/generative-ai-security-predictions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/thought-leadership/generative-ai-security-predictions"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GAI capabilities will soon be table stakes for any software company as their customers will simply expect it. Those who do not take advantage of this technological evolution will decline into irrelevancy and be replaced by better and more productive alternatives. A world where Generative AI is ubiquitous will soon be here. What does that mean for security? We have two main predictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michiel Prins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Private Cache Can Lead to Mass Account Takeover – pentest case]]></title>
        <id>https://research.securitum.com/?p=2020</id>
        <link href="https://research.securitum.com/how-private-cache-can-lead-to-mass-account-takeover-pentest-case/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many situations, minor vulnerabilities might seem like small fish in the vast ocean of cybersecurity threats. They’re often marked as low severity and thus, overlooked by developers who assume that the conditions for their exploitation are too complicated to be met. However, in this article, we’re going to challenge that assumption and show you ...
The post How Private Cache Can Lead to Mass Account Takeover – pentest case appeared first on research.securitum.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miwn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we told the CFTC about blockchain threats]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104646</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/12/what-we-told-the-cftc-about-crypto-threats/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Guido, CEO In March, I joined the Commodity Futures Trading Commission’s Technology Advisory Committee (TAC), helping the regulatory agency navigate the complexities of cybersecurity risks, particularly in emerging technologies like AI and blockchain. During the committee’s first meeting, I discussed how the rapidly changing and public nature of blockchain technology makes it uniquely susceptible […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Windows LAPS with Azure AD]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572491</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/enable-windows-laps-with-azure-ad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T20:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Local Administrator Password Solution (Windows LAPS) is a built-in Windows feature that enables the management and rotation of local administrator passwords on Windows devices. On April 21, 2023, Microsoft released a public preview of Windows LAPS that supports Azure AD.
Enable Windows LAPS with Azure AD first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammed Kaif Joey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance, Diagnostics, and WMI]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/21f3e01790d3</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/performance-diagnostics-and-wmi-21f3e01790d3?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T18:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Steven F</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The July 2023 Security Update Review]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:64ac6669b2d6573db3ef1636</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/7/10/the-july-2023-security-update-review"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second Tuesday of the month, which means Adobe and Microsoft have released their latest security patches. Take a break from your regularly scheduled activities and join us as we review the details of their latest advisories. If you’d rather watch the video recap, you can check it out here.
Apple Patches for July 2023
Apple doesn’t conform to “Patch Tuesday,” but they started things off yesterday with an emergency patch for macOS, iOS, and iPadOS. The bug in Webkit is labeled as CVE-2023-34750. Apple notes the vulnerability has been reported to be under active attack. Apple terms these emergency patches as “Rapid Security Response (RSR)” and reserves them for the most critical components where exploitation has been detected in the wild. Apple also notes this update is causing probl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting XSS in hidden inputs and meta tags]]></title>
        <id>exploiting-xss-in-hidden-inputs-and-meta-tags</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/exploiting-xss-in-hidden-inputs-and-meta-tags"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we are going to show how you can (ab)use the new HTML popup functionality in Chrome to exploit XSS in meta tags and hidden inputs. It all started when I noticed the new popover behaviour]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skip welcome page in Chrome, Edge and Firefox using Group Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572431</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/skip-welcome-page-in-chrome-edge-and-firefox-using-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a user starts a web browser for the first time on a computer, he is presented with a welcome page. Depending on the manufacturer, this page prompts for various settings that are often configured centrally in managed environments. In Chrome, Edge, and Firefox, these pages can be blocked using group policies.
Skip welcome page in Chrome, Edge and Firefox using Group Policy first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-linux?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what Linux is, how Linux works, and why it is essential for cybersecurity professionals to learn Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes guide: Taints and tolerations in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572417</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-guide-taints-and-tolerations-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous posts, we discussed Kubernetes Pods and Deployments. In this post, you will learn about Kubernetes taints and tolerations. These are mechanisms for controlling the nodes on which specific Pods can be scheduled. Nodes are marked with taints, and then Pods that have matching tolerations can be scheduled on those nodes.
Kubernetes guide: Taints and tolerations in Kubernetes first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differential fuzz testing upgradeable smart contracts with Diffusc]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/?p=104543</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2023/07/07/differential-fuzz-testing-upgradeable-smart-contracts-with-diffusc/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By William E Bodell III (@WEBthe3rd) On March 28, 2023, SafeMoon, a self-styled “community-focused DeFi token” on Binance Smart Chain, lost the equivalent of $8.9 million in Binance Coin BNB to an exploit in a liquidity pool. The exploit leveraged a simple error introduced in an upgrade to SafeMoon’s SFM token contract, allowing the attacker […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trail of Bits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: ICS/OT Security Assessment Consultant (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-ics-ot-security-assessment-consultant-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-ics-ot-security-assessment-consultant-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICS/OT セキュリティ・アセスメント・コンサルタントの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cat &amp; Mouse - or Chess?]]></title>
        <id>https://s3cur3th1ssh1t.github.io/Cat_Mouse_or_Chess/</id>
        <link href="https://s3cur3th1ssh1t.github.io/Cat_Mouse_or_Chess/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I had the idea for a new approach to block EDR DLLs from loading into a newly spawned process. After several months this idea lead to a PoC, which was then published after presenting the topic at x33fcon and Troopers this year. This post will cover the background and description of the technique.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>S3cur3Th1sSh1t</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Removes the "Chat with Code" Plugin From Store]]></title>
        <id>https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-chat-with-code-plugin-take-down/</id>
        <link href="https://embracethered.com/blog/posts/2023/chatgpt-chat-with-code-plugin-take-down/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post we discussed the risks of OAuth enabled plugins being commonly vulnerable to Cross Plugin Request Forgery and how OpenAI is seemingly not enforcing new plugin store policies. As an example we explored how the “Chat with Code” plugin is vulnerable.
Recently, a post on Reddit titled “This is scary! Posting stuff by itself” shows how a conversation with ChatGPT, out of the blue (and what appears to be by accident) created a Github Issue!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embrace The Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[setspn: Manage service principal names in Active Directory from the command line]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572402</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/setspn-manage-service-principal-names-in-active-directory-from-the-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use the setspn command line tool to manage service principal names in Active Directory and properly configure your service accounts. The service principal name (SPN) is an often-misunderstood aspect of Active Directory Domain Services that can lead to authentication issues when improperly managed.
setspn: Manage service principal names in Active Directory from the command line first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is OPSEC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-opsec</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/what-is-opsec?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what OPSEC is, why it's important in the world of OSINT, and some best practices when conducting investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Takeaways from a Conversation Between Hackers and Program Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://hackerone.com/best-practices/a-conversation-between-hackers-and-program-managers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hackerone.com/best-practices/a-conversation-between-hackers-and-program-managers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, HackerOne has brought hackers and customers together more frequently. Bug bounty and pentests are where these two parts of the HackerOne community have historically met, but fostering open conversations outside of paid engagements has further reinforced the sense of community and collaboration that HackerOne embodies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ktansley@hackerone.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Docker containers]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572384</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/the-best-docker-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are Docker containers available for just about any application you can think of for self-hosting. In this article, I'll look at a list of the best Docker containers.
The best Docker containers first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passwordless: Can It deliver on Its promises?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.secureauth.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=48901</id>
        <link href="https://www.secureauth.com/blog/passwordless-can-it-deliver-on-its-promises/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite improvements in cybersecurity, digital security breaches are as prevalent as ever. In the last month alone, data breaches have been detected at American Airlines (8,000 affected in June 27th), Mondelez (50,000 affected in June 21st), and Reddit (a ransomware attack on June 19th with a demanded payout of $4.5 million). It’s clear that threat […]
The post Passwordless: Can It deliver on Its promises? appeared first on SecureAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Fronske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of Modern Memory Security Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31732</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/07/05/overview-of-modern-memory-security-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses the security concerns which must be taken into account whenever designing an embedded system. Failure to account for these security concerns in the system’s threat model can lead to a compromise of the most sensitive data within. Memory is a crucial part of any computer subsystem. The CPU executes instructions and operates […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/ransomware-in-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/ransomware-in-the-cloud?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we discussed the evolution of ransomware into cloud environments, the TTPs leveraged by the threat actors, and how we can defend against and prepare for such attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572370</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-guide-create-a-kubernetes-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T14:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Kubernetes Service enables network access to a set of Pods (basic Kubernetes objects) within a cluster. It provides a single stable IP address and DNS name that correspond to an evolving set of Pods, such as those resulting from a Deployment. In this post, I will explain the differences between the various types of Kubernetes Services: ClusterIP, NodePort, LoadBalancer, ExternalName, and Headless. After that, I will outline how to create a Kubernetes Service.
Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes Service first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find GraphQL API vulnerabilities, with Burp Suite Professional]]></title>
        <id>find-graphql-api-vulnerabilities-with-burp-suite-professional</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/find-graphql-api-vulnerabilities-with-burp-suite-professional"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a penetration tester, you need your tools to find the latest vulnerabilities. GraphQL APIs are widely used on today’s websites, and expose attack surface for a wide range of security issues. Burp S]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sec488-major-update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/sec488-cloud-security-course-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/sec488-cloud-security-course-updates?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the new updates to our flagship cloud security training course, SEC488, which supports our most popular cloud security certification, GCLD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demote a domain controller step by step]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572352</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/demote-a-domain-controller-step-by-step/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T17:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, you will learn how to demote a domain controller node in a Windows Server environment. I will guide you through the steps of preparation, demotion, and checks to make afterward.
Demote a domain controller step by step first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We want to check out your BChecks ...]]></title>
        <id>we-want-to-check-out-your-bchecks</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/we-want-to-check-out-your-bchecks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T14:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to create customized scans without the hassle of learning advanced programming? Burp Suite's got you covered. Scripted scan checks - or BChecks - are now a full reality with the 2023.6 release of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Advisory – Nullsoft Scriptable Installer System (NSIS) – Insecure Temporary Directory Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31823</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/07/03/technical-advisory-nullsoft-scriptable-installer-system-nsis-insecure-temporary-directory-usage/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description The NSIS uninstaller package did not enforce appropriate permissions on the temporary directory used during the uninstall process. Furthermore, it did not ensure that the temporary directory was removed before running executable content from it. This could potentially result in privilege escalation under certain scenarios. Impact A low-privileged, local attacker could exploit this vulnerability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rich Warren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Details of CVE-2023-30990 - Unauthenticated RCE in IBM i DDM Service]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/07/03/ibm-i-dde-vulnerability-cve-2023-30990/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.silentsignal.eu/2023/07/03/ibm-i-dde-vulnerability-cve-2023-30990/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T06:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preface]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silent Signal Techblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-27997 Is Exploitable, and 69% of FortiGate Firewalls Are Vulnerable]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-exploitable-fortigate-vulnerable</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-exploitable-fortigate-vulnerable"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out latest analysis for CVE-2023-27997, a heap overflow in FortiOS, the the operating system behind FortiGate firewalls, that allows remote code execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Gross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-27997 Is Exploitable, and 69% of FortiGate Firewalls Are Vulnerable]]></title>
        <id>https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-exploitable-and-fortigate-firewalls-vulnerable</id>
        <link href="https://bishopfox.com/blog/cve-2023-27997-exploitable-and-fortigate-firewalls-vulnerable"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out latest analysis for CVE-2023-27997, a heap overflow in FortiOS, the the operating system behind FortiGate firewalls, that allows remote code execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb Gross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check the BitLocker status of all PCs in the network]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572318</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/check-the-bitlocker-status-of-all-pcs-in-the-network/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T16:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The built-in tools for activating BitLocker do not provide a comprehensive report on the encryption status of the entire environment. Inactive BitLocker protection can be identified using the manage-bcd utility and PowerShell. The options for obtaining BitLocker status information through the GUI are severely limited.
Check the BitLocker status of all PCs in the network first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application optimisation with LLMs: Finding faster, equivalent, software libraries.]]></title>
        <id>http://sean.heelan.io/?p=2876</id>
        <link href="https://sean.heelan.io/2023/06/30/application-optimisation-with-llms-finding-faster-equivalent-software-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months back I wrote a blog post where I mentioned that the least-effort/highest reward approach to application optimisation is to deploy a whole-system profiler across your clusters, look at the most expensive libraries & processes, and then search Google for faster, equivalent replacements. At Optimyze/Elastic we have had customers of our whole-system profiler […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>seanhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Jobs: Application Pen Tester (Japanese)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-application-pen-tester-ja</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/cybersecurity-jobs-application-pen-tester-ja?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[アプリケーションペンテスターの主な業務や、スキルアップのためのSANSのおすすめのコースを紹介します！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-20864: Remote Code Execution in VMware Aria Operations for Logs]]></title>
        <id>5894c269e4fcb5e65a1ed623:58a5b38cb3db2bd67b608658:649da382cfd37f6cffd4d25c</id>
        <link href="https://www.thezdi.com/blog/2023/6/29/cve-2023-20864-remote-code-execution-in-vmware-aria-operations-for-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T15:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this excerpt of a Trend Micro Vulnerability Research Service vulnerability report, Jonathan Lein and Dusan Stevanovic of the Trend Micro Research Team detail a recently patched remote code execution vulnerability in VMware Aria Operations for Logs (formerly vRealize). This bug was originally submitted to the ZDI program by an anonymous researcher. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Similar bugs are reported as being exploited in the wild. The following is a portion of their write-up covering CVE-2023-24941, with a few minimal modifications.
An insecure deserialization vulnerability has been reported in VMware …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Childs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572298</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/kubernetes-guide-create-a-kubernetes-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T15:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post of this Kubernetes guide, I discussed how to create a Pod in Kubernetes using imperative and declarative configurations. In this post, you will learn how to create a Deployment in Kubernetes. In Kubernetes, a Deployment is a resource object that defines how your application is deployed and managed in a cluster. You just need to define the desired number of instances (a.k.a. replicas) of your application, the container image, resource requirements, and other options in a configuration file, and Kubernetes takes care of deploying and managing the application.
Kubernetes guide: Create a Kubernetes deployment first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Scraping Part 1: Core Principles to Deter Scraping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.netspi.com/?p=30458</id>
        <link href="https://www.netspi.com/blog/technical/adversary-simulation/anti-scraping-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part one of our anti-scraping series covers five core anti-scraping principles and how they stack up against a fake message board.
The post Anti-Scraping Part 1: Core Principles to Deter Scraping  appeared first on NetSPI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Dunn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Report – Zcash Zebra Security Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31786</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/29/public-report-zcash-zebra-security-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Spring 2023, the Zcash Foundation engaged NCC Group to conduct a security assessment of the Zebrad application. Zebrad is a network client that participates in the Zcash consensus mechanism by validating blocks, maintaining the blockchain state (best chain and viable non-finalized chains), and gossiping blocks, transactions, and peer addresses. Five consultants performed the review, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parnian Alimi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BChecks: Houston, we have a solution!]]></title>
        <id>bchecks-houston-we-have-a-solution</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/blog/bchecks-houston-we-have-a-solution"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T12:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scripted scan checks in Burp Suite Professional are now a thing ...  tl;dr Burp Suite Professional now has a powerful yet simple scripting language that allows you to quickly build on our world c]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PortSwigger Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid BitLocker recovery mode by customizing the TPM validation profile]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572279</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/avoid-bitlocker-recovery-mode-by-customizing-the-tpm-validation-profile/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T16:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On startup, BitLocker ensures that the configuration of a PC has not changed since encryption began. For this purpose, it stores several system parameters in the TPM's PCR. If the PC configuration cannot be validated, BitLocker will activate Recovery Mode. By adjusting the validation profile, you can avoid this behavior.
Avoid BitLocker recovery mode by customizing the TPM validation profile first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wolfgang Sommergut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sowing Chaos and Reaping Rewards in Confluence and Jira]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7a90ba33bf62</id>
        <link href="https://posts.specterops.io/sowing-chaos-and-reaping-rewards-in-confluence-and-jira-7a90ba33bf62?source=rss----f05f8696e3cc---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T14:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AtlasReaper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-26258 – Remote Code Execution in ArcServe UDP Backup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mdsec.co.uk/?p=3253</id>
        <link href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2023/06/cve-2023-26258-remote-code-execution-in-arcserve-udp-backup/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T13:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview During a recent adversary simulation, the MDSec ActiveBreach red team were performing a ransomware scenario, with a key objective set on compromising the organisation’s backup infrastructure. As part of...
The post CVE-2023-26258 – Remote Code Execution in ArcServe UDP Backup appeared first on MDSec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pentestpartners.com/?p=27235</id>
        <link href="https://www.pentestpartners.com/security-blog/black-basta-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T05:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Black Basta Ransomware? Black Basta is a threat group that provides ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS). The service is maintained by dedicated developers and is a highly efficient and professionally run […]
Black Basta Ransomware first appeared on Pen Test Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Harwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Workspace Log Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sans.org/blog/google-workspace-log-extraction</id>
        <link href="https://www.sans.org/blog/google-workspace-log-extraction?msc=rss"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we reviewed the methods through which we can extract logs from Google Workspace. One option is to query the logs in the Admin Console, although there are several limitations that result in this not being the most ideal method. The best option to obtain the most thorough and easily parsable data is to use the Reports API in the Admin SDK. We also mentioned the use of forwarding logs to Google Cloud for a subset of audit logs to be available via Google Cloud Logging. In the last two blog posts in this series, we’ll look at how to extract logs from Microsoft 365 and Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANS Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting per-user Conditional Access MFA status in Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=30746</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/27/getting-per-user-conditional-access-mfa-status-in-azure/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T20:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Long time has passed since Microsoft implemented the first Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) approach in Azure Active Directory with the Per-user MFA functionality [1]. However, this simple on/off mechanism has been replaced over time by the Conditional Access Policy (CAP) feature, which was released on July 2016. A conditional access policy is a set of conditions which, if matched, enforces its access […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Verza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How-to: Reversing and debugging ISAPI modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/how-to-reversing-and-debugging-isapi-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.skullsecurity.org/2023/how-to-reversing-and-debugging-isapi-modules"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I had the privilege to write a detailed analysis of CVE-2023-34362, which is series of several vulnerabilities in the MOVEit file transfer application that lead to remote code execution. One of the several vulnerabilities involved an ISAPI module - specifically, the MoveITISAPI.dll ISAPI extension. One of the many vulnerabilities that comprised the MOVEit RCE was a header-injection issue, where the ISAPI application parsed headers differently than the .net application. This point is going to dig into how to analyze and reverse engineer an ISAPI-based service! This wasn’t the first time in the recent past I’d had to work on something written as an ISAPI module, and each time I feel like I have to start over and remember how it’s supposed to work. This time, I thought I’d combine my hastily-scrawled notes with some Googling, and try to write something that I (and others) can use in the future. As such, this will be a quick intro to ISAPI applications from the angle that matters to me - how to reverse engineer and debug them! I want to preface this with: I’m not a Windows developer, and I’ve never run an IIS server on purpose. That means that I am approaching this with brute-force ignorance! I don’t have a lot of background context nor do I know the correct terminology for a lot of this stuff. Instead, I’m going to treat these are typical DLLs from typical applications, and approach them as such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkullSecurity Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetXMS: Open-source network monitoring and management]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572267</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/netxms-open-source-network-monitoring-and-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore NetXMS, an enterprise-grade, open-source network monitoring and management solution with advanced features such as customized data visualization, comprehensive monitoring, and automation capabilities.
NetXMS: Open-source network monitoring and management first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Gato Version 1.5!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.praetorian.com/?p=4736</id>
        <link href="https://www.praetorian.com/blog/gato-update-version-1-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T13:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 21, 2023 at ShmooCon 2023, Praetorian open-sourced Gato (Github Attack Toolkit), a first of its kind tool that focuses on abusing offensive TTPs targeting self-hosted GitHub Actions Runners. Since then, Praetorian and other offensive security practitioners across the information security community have leveraged Gato for so much more than just self-hosted runner attacks. […]
The post Announcing Gato Version 1.5! appeared first on Praetorian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmaline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Location-based printing for Active Directory sites]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572251</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/location-based-printing-for-active-directory-sites/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T21:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a modern hybrid workforce, admins must take a user's location into account when configuring printing solutions. Location-based printing can be controlled using Group Policy and the Print Management GUI.
Location-based printing for Active Directory sites first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABScon Replay | Quiver – Using Cutting Edge ML to Detect Interesting Command Lines for Hunters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/?post_type=labs&amp;p=81995</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/labscon-replay-quiver-using-cutting-edge-ml-to-detect-interesting-command-lines-for-hunters/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T13:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gal Braun and Dean Langsam explore how LLMs can be trained to parse command lines and perform tasks like attribution and detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LABScon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting Noisy Oracles with Bayesian Inference]]></title>
        <id>https://research.nccgroup.com/?p=31496</id>
        <link href="https://research.nccgroup.com/2023/06/23/exploiting-noisy-oracles-with-bayesian-inference/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T20:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In cryptographic attacks, we often rely on abstracted information sources which we call “oracles”. Classic examples include the RSA parity oracle attack, which depends on an oracle disclosing the least-significant bit of a ciphertext’s decryption; Bleichenbacher’s attack on PKCS#1v1.5 RSA padding, which depends on an oracle for whether a given ciphertext’s decryption is correctly padded; […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Sohl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Kubernetes Pod]]></title>
        <id>https://4sysops.com/?p=1572239</id>
        <link href="https://4sysops.com/archives/create-a-kubernetes-pod/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T15:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Kubernetes, a Pod is the smallest and most basic deployment unit that you create and manage in a cluster. The Pod contains one or more containers, storage resources, a unique network IP address, and other configuration options.
Create a Kubernetes Pod first appeared on 4sysops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surender Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16110</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/critical-infrastructure-national-cybersecurity-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “special relationship,” coined by Winston Churchill, describes the close, longstanding alliance between the United States and the United Kingdom. It has been applied to cooperation during war, to trade and commerce, and even to intelligence sharing. That special relationship has clearly influenced the two nations’ recent policy papers on national cybersecurity. The U.K. […]
The post Protecting Critical Infrastructure: A Tale of Two National Cybersecurity Strategies appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Luckett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16093</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/scoping-your-pentest-with-synack/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping Adventures is a series of blogs about some of the more interesting penetration tests that the Synack Customer Success teams have worked on over the last few months. Each blog outlines how we engage with the client to achieve the best results from a pentest. Pentesters love colors—red, blue, purple, black, white and grey […]
The post Scoping Adventures: How to Get the Most Out of Your Synack Pentesting appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huw Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16082</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/applying-strategic-thinking-in-your-pentesting-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Synack Platform & Five Pillars of Strategic Pentesting Why You Need to Think Strategically It’s no great revelation that tactics, techniques, and procedures utilized by nefarious hackers hacking activities are evolving on a daily basis. In 2022, 18,828 common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVEs) were published. At the same time, organization attack surfaces are expanding. […]
The post Applying Strategic Thinking in Your Pentesting Program appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Synack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.synack.com/?p=16074</id>
        <link href="https://www.synack.com/blog/new-cybersecurity-strategy-whats-next-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One week ago, the Biden administration unveiled its long-awaited U.S. National Cybersecurity Strategy, with an eye toward centralizing government cyber resources and holding IT vendors more accountable for their digital defenses. Now that the ink is dry on the 35-page document, top officials like Acting National Cyber Director Kemba Walden are busy putting it into […]
The post The U.S. has a new cybersecurity strategy. What’s next for CISOs? appeared first on Synack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Kuhr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>